Chapter 281: Bear Strength Phantom

When Fang Yuan stepped into the battle stage, all the random thoughts were cast out of his head.

He calmly sized up the opponent in front of him.

Tang Xiong.

He was eight feet tall, wide shoulders and a thick waist. Just his arms alone were as thick as Fang Yuan's thighs, as he stood on the stage without an upper garment or shoes.

His chest was filled with black chest hair, giving off a wild and formidable aura.

"Little scoundrel, you killed my little brother? Today, I shall send you to accompany him in the afterlife!" Tang Xiong looked at Fang Yuan with bloodshot eyes, the flames of hatred could be clearly seen.

The surrounding temperature was burning as if it was the torrid afternoon heat of July or August.

The ground was boiling hot; black and red mixed together to form the lava terrain.

This was a mid-scale battle stage. There were only few spectators about dozens, most of them came to watch how Tang Xiong took revenge.

As for Fang Yuan, he might have obtained two victories but it still wasn't enough for him to be famous.

"Tang brothers grew up relying on each other; now Tang Qing is dead and only Tang Xiong remains."

"Hehe, I am waiting to see how Tang Xiong tortures this kid to death."

"Eh, what is this kid's name?"

"I think he was called Gu Yue Fang Zheng, a no-name junior."

"This kid is too thoughtless, he actually dared to break the unsaid rules and kill his first two opponents."

"He should be a demonic Gu Master who had only recently entered the city..."

"Alas, the young do not know to conduct themselves. This day wouldn't have come if he had shown mercy."

The audience continued talking about the match, but no one was optimistic about Fang Yuan.

Wei Yang was in a disguise and was looking at the battle stage with a burning gaze. Tang Xiong also walked the strength path, he was a rank two peak stage expert but could unleash with the strength of three bears and even won his way through to fourth inner city. He was a strong opponent for the current Fang Yuan.

Ding!

A clear ring of the bell announced the start of the match.

Tang Xiong roared and charged straight at Fang Yuan like a wild bull.

The ground of this battle stage was made of dark red lava rocks. Fang Yuan could feel the scalding heat from the ground even though he was wearing boots. While Tang Xiong was barefooted, he did not pay any attention to the heat.

Tum tum tum.

Every time Tang Xiong's feet stepped on the ground, it produced a loud and deep sound. At the same time, his every step shattered the lava rocks and left a deep footprint in the ground.

Fang Yuan narrowed his eyes, his gaze as sharp as a blade's edge!

He was at ease despite Tang Xiong's aggressive momentum; the corner of his lips curled up into a cold smile as he outrageously charged at Tang Xiong head-on.

"Has he gone crazy?"

"He dares to face Tang Xiong head-on?"

"He could have had a chance to survive if he prolonged the match, this is simply charging towards his doom."

The audience shook their heads as they looked at this scene.

Fang Yuan was young, his body was not even half as muscular as Tang Xiong's. The scene of him charging at Tang Xiong was like a lamb colliding with a big ox.

Bam!

The two fiercely collided against each other, the enormous strength sent both of them flying.

Tang Xiong was thrown back six steps, as a clearly shocked expression showed on his face. 'How could this kid have such huge great strength?'

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan was thrown back three steps, as the white light armor protecting his body shook.

The result of the collision amazed the audience.

Some had their jaws wide open and some repeatedly blinked their eyes, not having expected Fang Yuan to possess such strength.

"My strength is actually less than his? No wonder little brother died at his hands!" Tang Xiong's expression changed, and looked at Fang Yuan properly for the first time.

Fang Yuan shook his numb arm, his expression was still indifferent; this result wasn't beyond his expectation.

He possessed the strength of two boars and a crocodile, there was also some increase to his strength due to using brown bear innate strength Gu these days. And Tang Xiong, he only possessed the strength of two bears.

Grand bear Gu!

Tang Xiong roared, the muscles on his body expanded visibly and his body size grew by a fold; he temporarily gained the strength of a bear.

Bear palm Gu!

A ball of yellow light covered his palms and soles. After the light dispersed, his hands and feet increased in size by over three times; turning into thick and enormous bear palms.

Whooshh!

He jumped with ferocious strength, next, he waved his right palm smashing at Fang Yuan.

The strong wind produced from his motion sent Fang Yuan's clothes fluttering before the bear palm even hit him.

Fang Yuan was still calm, he clenched his left palm into a fist and struck directly at the bear palm.

Fist and palm struck, producing a muffled sound. It was a draw.

However, following immediately, Tang Xiong's arm swept horizontally and another palm also came smashing over.

Fang Yuan used offence against offence; bang bang bang, fists and palms struck each other multiple times, the wind was screaming from their attacks.

The audience revealed astonished expressions when they saw Fang Yuan equally matched as he attacked Tang Xiong head-on.

'This youngster has some skills to be able to duke it out with Tang Xiong!"

"What was his name again?"

"This is a tough nut, Tang Xiong is in trouble. Grand bear Gu has a time limit, and once the effect disappears, he will be disadvantaged."

However, right at this moment!

A fierce bear's roar resounded throughout the battle stage.

A phantom image of a black bear appeared behind Tang Xiong; it opened its bloody mouth and roared towards the skies.

Beast Phantom!

Tang Xiong got lucky and was able to unleash the beast phantom.

The smack that should have been extremely normal, now had the strength of a bear!

Fang Yuan could not dodge in time and hurriedly put up his arms to stiffly block it.

Boom.

With a huge bang, he was sent flying, the white light armor on his body flickered rapidly before dimming.

His arms were numb and would not be usable for some time.

He did his best to maintain his balance in midair; he twisted his waist and landed on the ground on his feet.

The moment he landed, he activated the canopy Gu; the white light armor appeared once more, but this time it looked weak and transparent, its defense had decreased by a lot.

"That is a bear strength phantom, Tang Xiong has flared up!"

"Bear strength specializes in smacking, it is normal for the bear strength phantom to appear since Tang Xiong has already attacked so many times."

"The situation was still in deadlock, but with the bear strength phantom, that kid's momentum is destroyed. Tang Xiong holds the upper hand now."

"According to the previous statistics, Tang Xiong can use the bear strength phantom five times on average in every fight. If that kid has no way to deal with it, he will definitely be defeated."

Outside the battle stage, the audience kept on making a commotion with their comments.

The appearance of a bear strength phantom meant the true battle was starting, and it roused the audience's passion.

"I have the strength of two boars and a crocodile; boar strength is good at charging attacks and crocodile strength is good at bite attacks, but I have yet to acquire the bear strength. I can't bring out the beast phantom by using my fists or palms, moreover the canopy Gu is not good at defending against close combat attacks, and will likely be destroyed by one or two more attacks from the bear strength phantom."

Fang Yuan's thoughts flashed through and he decided to change his battle tactics.

Jumping grass.

He willed, and a spring like grass soon grew out from his soles then pierced through his boots.

Just as Tang Xiong was charging at him, Fang Yuan stamped on the ground and leapt far away like a frog.

At the same time, his left palm swiped at Tang Xiong's direction.

A scarlet colored moonblade immediately shot out of his palms and struck Tang Xiong; the defensive light on his body flickered for a while.

Blood moon Gu might not have high offensive power, but it was a rank three Gu after all.

Tang Xiong was distracted for a moment before he pounced upon Fang Yuan again.

Fang Yuan used the same trick again, throwing scarlet moonblades from afar; he had changed his battle tactics and didn't engage Tang Xiong in close combat.

Tang Xiong had no choice but to use his movement Gu and chase after Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan kept on attacking and retreating. It was not that Tang Xiong didn't have long range attacking methods, but they were many times weaker than his close combat power and simply could not threaten Fang Yuan.

Tang Xiong growled repeatedly in anger, and tried to provoke Fang Yuan by cursing at him; the audience also made booing noises since they wanted to see intense close combat.

However, how could Fang Yuan be so easily provoked?

He did not have a complete set of Gu worms and had yet to make close combat his forte. Even the long range attacks were forcefully improvised by him.

Time passed by, both their primeval essences continually fell.

Fang Yuan's advantage became clearer; he possessed light silver primeval essence of rank three initial stage, while Tang Xiong only had B grade aptitude and red steel primeval essence.

Despite the strength path Gu Masters' advantage in consuming very little primeval essence, they could not last forever.

By the time Fang Yuan's blood moon Gu made five to six wounds on Tang Xiong's body, the latter had no choice but to admit defeat since his healing Gu was not very good and blood kept on flowing out of the wounds.

"Just wait, one day, I will smack you into minced meat!" Tang Xiong covered his wounds and walked out of the stage.

He came with the aggressiveness of the devil but was leaving with a pale face, his steps light and weak.

"To think fourth inner city's Tang Xiong was defeated!"

"What is that Gu? It could form blood red moonblades and blood kept on flowing out of the wounds it inflicted, I have never seen such a Gu before."

"This kid is not one to trifle with, he will advance to fourth inner city's battle stage before long."

Winner takes it all; most of the audience focused on Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan received his third victory, and according to the rules, he took that grand bear Gu from Tang Xiong.

This was the most valuable Gu in Tang Xiong's possession. With this Gu gone, Tang Xion only possessed the strength of two bears, his battle strength decreased by thirty percent and there was no need to worry about him now.

However, Fang Yuan was not happy.

The legendary Gu was not in the stellar stone used as a leg support, then where was it?

Was there another piece of stone used as a leg support?

However, when Fang Yuan went back to the gambling den, the foot of that counter was already restored.

Maybe, it was not that gambling den?

Fang Yuan inwardly shook at the thought; stellar stone used to support counter in the rock gambling zone, only this gambling den fulfilled this condition.

"Without the legendary Gu, I won't have any advantage in walking on the strength path. Strength path had prevailed since ancient times, but now it is just a shadow of its previous glory. If I want to walk on the strength path without the legendary Gu, at the very least I will need an ancient strength path inheritance. Unfortunately, I only have memories of three ancient strength path inheritance, of which one is at Eastern Seas and another at Central Continent."

"The third one is at Southern Border, but has already been occupied and exploited by Wu Clan for several years now. Now that I recall it, even Empress Wu Ji of Wu Clan walked the strength path. And because of this ancient inheritance, the Wu Clan was able to sit on the throne of Southern Border's number one force."

Of course, this throne was only referring to the mortal realm. Rank six Gu immortals were at a level that crossed the ordinary and could not be calculated in this.

Fang Yuan continued to secretly investigate the next seven to eight days without any results.

"Sigh, only one clue remains now, I can only give up if that doesn't work." Fang Yuan thought, he was not someone who would waste time on an unsolvable problem.

This final clue was Li Ran — the protagonist who obtained the legendary Gu in Fang Yuan's previous life.

Chapter 282: A flash of inspiration Gu

Although Fang Yuan had the purple thorn token, he did not dare to investigate this openly.

But in his memory, Li Ran also participated in the battle stage. After obtaining the legendary Gu, he won his way up and swept the battle stage.

This made it easier.

Fang Yuan still had the once per month enforced challenge unused, thus, he came to the secret reception area using it.

There were three people who were named Li Ran among the ones who had signed up.

Two males and one female.

Eliminating the female since Li Ran was a male in the rumors.

The remaining two, one was an old man around sixty years old, slightly famous. With rank three cultivation, he had gone up to third inner city's battle stage a few years ago, but his body was getting worse as the years went, falling back to fourth inner city eventually. This was obviously not the Li Ran Fang Yuan wanted to find either, since Li Ran in his memories had a tough life.

The other is a middle aged man, over fifty years old. With rank two cultivation, he had arrived in Shang clan city for around ten years, but had remained at the fifth inner city battle stage. He loved gambling, and lived a difficult life. He had married and bore children in Shang clan city, but the couple did not get along and separated.

Fang Yuan secretly investigated, and found that this person was the one he saw at the gambling den.

Tailing him for several days, Fang Yuan found that this Li Ran lived from day to day, sometimes, after eating today, he could not afford food the next day.

But this did not mean he had no capabilities.

He relied on the primeval stones he earned in fifth inner city battle stage to survive.

Fang Yuan investigated his battle records, he won more than he lost.

According to logic, he should not be living such a life. But this person loved to eat, gamble and visit prostitutes, he spent his money without restraint. In order to gamble, he would even use all the primeval stones he has, such that for the next half a month, he would have to borrow money from people, and eat the cheapest food possible to survive.

Similarly, in order to have a feast, he would go to the highest grade restaurant, and spend most of the money he had. He even ate without paying, and still owed several restaurants money now.

"This person must be the owner of the legendary Gu in my previous life. But he could not control his desires, thus even with the legendary Gu, what could he do? No wonder he was like a shooting star, going missing soon after his fame." Fang Yuan shook his head secretly.

"He obtained the legendary Gu in my previous life, would he get it again now? It is not possible for me to continue tailing him for long. The day where he finds the legendary Gu is nearing. Am I truly not fated to receive this Gu?" Fang Yuan frowned.

These days, Fang Yuan spent a lot of time and effort in tailing Li Ran. If he spent this time on cultivating, he might achieve greater success.

Most importantly, Fang Yuan had no confidence of whether he would gain anything from doing this.

And if he continued, he might get found out. Thankfully, Wei Yang was a busy man, only coming over to watch when Fang Yuan had a battle, if not, Fang Yuan would not have the opportunity to tail Li Ran.

If Wei Yang found him doing this, how would Fang Yuan explain himself?

The greatest suspicion now was, why was the legendary Gu not inside the stellar stone, this did not match with the rumors!

Fang Yuan could not understand, this was too unimaginable! All the elements were present, but the Gu was nowhere to be found.

It could just be Fang Yuan's overwhelmingly suspicious nature, but he found this Li Ran very strange. He could not pinpoint what the strangeness was, but it was a feeling, an instinct. It was such a baseless feeling that even Fang Yuan could not be sure of it.

LIke this, after another twenty over days, Fang Yuan fell into deep perplexity. That strange feeling became stronger, but Fang Yuan did not know where it originated.

Li Ran's actions had nothing amiss.

He lived in Shang clan city for nearly ten years, if there was anything wrong with him, outsiders would've known already.

"I am too entrenched into this, and have thought about this too much. At this time, I need an outsider's opinion to inspire myself." Fang Yuan was clear of his situation.

But he only trusted himself, although he made a poison vow with Bai Ning Bing, Fang Yuan did not trust Bai Ning Bing one bit. He only used her to cultivate, since the bone flesh unity Gu was much better than the liquor worm.

Without anyone to help, Fang Yuan could only rely on himself. And he had gotten used to relying on himself, and liked it too.

Thus, he came to the shop: "Shopkeeper, do you have a flash of inspiration Gu?"

Fang Yuan had asked a few shops, they did not have it. Finally, a shop had it, but it was priced at twenty nine thousand primeval stones.

A flash of inspiration Gu, a rank three consumable Gu, gone after one use. Who would spend so much primeval stones to buy this?

But the truth is, many people did.

These people were recipe masters who specialized in creating Gu refinement recipes.

When they got into a bottleneck, and were a step from success, they would choose to use this Gu. Once this Gu was used, it would give them that spark of inspiration that would allow them to successfully create the new recipe.

A recipe's worth is far greater than twenty nine thousand primeval stones.

Thus, a flash of inspiration Gu was a Gu with a lot of demand, if Fang Yuan did not have the purple thorn token, the shop would never sell it to him.

A similar Gu to the a flash of inspiration Gu is the cactus pointer.

But the latter was a Tie clan specialty grass Gu, it was not sold in the market.

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, buying this a flash of inspiration Gu.

This Gu was like a blue jewel tadpole, small and agile, swimming about and waving its tail.

Fang Yuan activated his primeval essence, and this Gu entered his brain, turning into a white spiritual light, and like lightning, tore across the layers of mystery in Fang Yuan's head.

Fang Yuan's eyes shone with brilliance, finally realizing what the strange feeling was.

"That's right, although this Li Ran's life is a mess, without any control over himself, there exists a pattern among this mess. He goes to the restaurant once every three days, goes to the gambling den twice every seven days, and the brothel once every five days. And every ten days, he would go to a restaurant named 'Fu Tai Xiang He'.

From the messy report, under the influence of the a flash of inspiration Gu, the pattern within was revealed .

This was the strange part.

If a person was truly unrestrained and did not think of what to do, his life would be a complete mess, how could it have such a perfect rhythm?

Three days later, in Fu Tai Xiang He restaurant.

"Clerk, the bill." Li Ran looked away from the window, calling loudly.

"Coming, lord Li Ran, five and a half primeval stones please."

"This is six, no need for change." Li Ran tossed out six primeval stones.

"Thank you lord, take care!"

Dun dun dun...

Li Ran walked down the stairs, and as he walked out of the restaurant, he turned into an alley and gradually vanished under the shadow.

Downstairs, Fang Yuan observed silently, before calling the shop assistant, pointing at Li Ran's seat: "The view here is horrible, I want to sit there instead."

According to his understanding, every time Li Ran came here, he would sit at the window seat, that was indeed strange.

"No problem!" The shop assistant laughed: "It is a man's interest to peek at beauties."

"What?" Fang Yuan's eyebrows raised.

"Hmm, isn't esteemed customer trying to see Qin Yan brothel's number one star, Lady An Yu? Hehe, that seat can directly look into her room, if you're lucky, you can even see her body. That Li Ran earlier, he always sits here to look at her. He always makes me reserve the seat for half a primeval stones." The shop assistant said with a lecherous expression.

"Oh is that so?" Fang Yuan replied curtly, sitting at Li Ran's seat.

Through the window, he could indeed see into the brothel.

Qin Yan brothel had eight storeys, the number one lady An Yu was a rank two Gu Master, having a room at the top floor. She had a great body, and her Gu Master identity could invoke men's conquering desires, rumors say it takes almost ten thousand primeval stones to have her for a night.

With Li Ran's fortune, he could not afford this, but was he really here to peek at Lady An Yu?

Looking at the way he left the brothel, he was not such a man.

Fang Yuan looked outside, there were many restaurants around Qin Yan brothel, why did he choose this one?

If he had a Gu worm to improve his vision, then maybe, but Fang Yuan knew he did not have such a Gu.

At this distance, even if Lady An Yu was there, he would only see a blur image.

"Eh? This is..." Fang Yuan's gaze concentrated on a tofu shop opposite the street.

A pair of mother and son were packing up their stall, ready to go home.

Fang Yuan recognised them, they were Li Ran's wife and son!

"Don't tell me, his real motive was to look at them?" Fang Yuan could not help but think.

He closed his eyes, and the map of the street appeared in his head.

There were better places to peek at Lady An Yu, but to observe this mother and son pair, this was the only spot!

"If he really wanted to look at them, why does he have to do it sneakily? According to my findings, he abandoned them years ago, is he feeling guilty? Strange... if he was guilty, and wanted to show concern for them, he could appear in front of them personally, why does he have to be secretive."

"No, it could be that he was too ashamed to face them. But if he was, why would he not turn over a new leaf? This is really weird, he seems to be a mess, and cannot restrain himself, but his life is actually an orderly mess. This evidently shows he has good control over himself."

Fang Yuan's eyes were eerie as possibilities flashed across his mind.

He chewed on the food, but could not taste them at all.

He felt himself nearing the truth, like a blind man in a room getting close to the door.

All the clues and suspicions flew around in his head like a tornado.

Such a thinking speed, caused his eating action to be greatly slowed.

He slowly put down the chopsticks, raising his wine glass, the wine inside glimmering as it emitted a strong fragrance.

Suddenly, Fang Yuan's black pupils expanded!

The wine glass was raised halfway, and his arm stayed in midair, not moving like a statue.

In his mind, a bolt of lightning struck and exploded.

"So that's why... I finally understand!"

He screamed excitedly in his heart, as a great brilliance flashed across his eyes like lightning.

The mystery involving his last life and current life had finally been solved, all the suspicions were lifted and Fang Yuan found the answer he wanted!

At the same time, he 'found' the legendary Gu he lost!

Chapter 283: Got it

"Wu Ran, if we ask you to sacrifice your future for the clan, are you willing to do it?"

"I am willing!"

...

"Wu Ran, if we ask you to sacrifice your reputation for the clan, are you willing to do it?"

"I am willing!"

...

"Wu Ran, if we ask you to sacrifice your life for the clan, are you willing to do it?"

"I am willing!"

...

"I was right about you, Wu Ran. From your grandfather, father, and then you, you were all loyal Wu clan subjects! Now, the clan has a mission for you, this mission would need you to sacrifice your future, your reputation, and maybe even your life."

"Lord clan leader, I am willing to do it for the clan!"

...

In the darkness, Wu Ran opened his eyes.

"Huff..." He breathed out slowly, sitting up from his bed, muttering: "I dreamed again."

This dream was not fake, but originated from the deepest part of his memory.

'Li Ran' is his fake name, his real name is 'Wu Ran'.

The surname Wu, bore great significance in southern border. It represented the number one overlord in the southern border, Wu clan!

Eleven years ago, Wu clan leader Empress Wu Ji gave an audience to Wu Ran, and assigned him a secret mission —

Making his way into Shang clan's higher up level!

For this, he changed his name, and roamed the wilderness for three years before settling in Shang clan city.

He laid low for eight whole years.

"It has been eight years, an entire eight years. Wu clan's clansmen have mostly forgotten me by now huh? Wu Ran is dead, in this world, only Li Ran remains."

Li Ran sighed in his heart.

He had been lurking for too long. So long that he almost forgot his own name.

Here, he wore a mask, living for eight years, pretending to be a libertine, an ordinary Gu Master of the lowest social level. Even to his beloved wife, he did not say a thing.

During this period, he only left once every half a year to contact Wu clan. It had always been a one-sided contact, hiding all traces to the limit.

Until a year ago, the agent informed him that the clan was going to use him. His excitement then could not be expressed in words!

"After eight years, they have finally activated it, everything will be different now!" Li Ran exclaimed. He willed, and a Gu appeared from his storage.

This fossil was cube shaped, like a brick shining with star light on its surface.

This was a stellar stone.

If Fang Yuan was here, he would find that this rock was very similar to the rock used as a leg support in the gambling den.

Li Ran caressed this fossil gently, frowning slightly.

As a spy, he spent ten years lurking in the city, creating a perfect background for himself. It would definitely gain Shang clan's trust.

But trust is not enough, he needed ability that surpasses the ordinary man, so that he can dominate the battle stage. Only then would Shang clan recruit him, and make him into an external clan elder like Wei Yang, thus gaining authority in Shang clan.

This 'ability' had to appear naturally, and it cannot be too abrupt.

Thus, Wu clan leader Empress Wu Ji chose a Gu worm for him personally.

This was a Gu that possessed a legendary tale.

Obtained from an ancient strength path inheritance, it is an almost extinct Gu in the current world, it was extremely rare!

With this Gu, Li Ran can emerge from his slumber and dominate the battle stage.

As to the method of 'obtaining' this Gu, to avoid suspicion, Wu clan had made preparations.

That is, gambling rocks.

Luck is unpredictable, and an ancient Gu being sealed within a fossil was completely normal.

The demonic Gu Master Wei Shen Jing was a subordinate of Empress Wu Ji. Creating a fake scrap grade fossil was as easy as pie, no one would be able to discern it.

Li Ran spent some effort too.

To make sure people believed this was a fossil from the gambling den, and not his own, he chose a gambling rock that was used as leg support in the gambling den.

This rock was there for many years, people walked about and never noticed it.

Li Ran had communicated with Wu clan, asking Wei Shen Jing to create a similar stellar stone.

Later in his plan, he would swap this rock with the stellar stone in his hand without anyone noticing. He was a Gu Master, after observing for half a year, he knew when was the perfect time to swap the stones without anyone realizing.

When he finally opens the stellar stone, the entire gambling den would testify for him, that it was completely due to luck.

After he obtains this Gu, he would turn over a new leaf, and start the story of a prodigal son. He would rise up, find his wife and child, and become an external clan elder of Shang clan. He would complete his mission, and bring his wife and child back to Wu clan, where they belong.

Thinking of his wife and son, Li Ran felt extremely guilty.

He loved his wife deeply, she is so kind, so strong willed.

At the same time, as a father, he would love to give everything good in this world to his son.

He was only making use of her at the start, but as time went on, their relationship deepened, and he could not stop loving her. After their son was born, his love for them only grew. But eventually, because of his mission and secret identity, he had to temporarily leave them.

"You must hate me now, I've disappointed you too much. But it is alright, soon, soon. I have been deployed, I can bring you happiness!"

Li Ran gripped his fists, his eyes shining with determination.

Tomorrow, he would go to the battle stage, and engage in a battle. The day after, he would bring this stellar stone to the gambling den, and perform his life changing show.

"I had planned to use that stone as a cover, but life is hard to predict, someone actually chose it. Heh, that idiot, choosing a scrap grade stellar stone. But... tomorrow, I will have to be an idiot too."

Li Ran laughed, keeping the stellar stone back into his storage Gu.

Although there was some changes to his plans, it was still fine. He had planned for such a small accident anyway.

He laid down once more, and soon, fell into deep sleep.

This time, he did not have any dreams.

On the second day, he felt great, energetic and full of hope.

He felt that he was like a tourist walking in a dark cavern. After a long journey, he finally saw the light ahead, the exit of the cavern!

Eight years of enduring, everything would become so wonderful!

Everything would definitely become perfect!

With such a belief, he arrived at the battle stage.

He had gotten information of the opponent this time, a rank two peak stage Gu Master often seen in fifth inner city's battle stage, he was a familiar face.

Even the weakest Gu Master, if they can roam in the battle stage without giving up, they have the ability to hold their own.

Li Ran did not look down on his opponent, the Gu Li Ran currently had were quite weak and not considered high quality. He had to conceal himself as well, unable to fight fiercely, thus, this battle could go either way.

Indeed, as they fought, it was as Li Ran predicted.

From probing to fighting, the two were evenly matched, at a stalemate.

The battlefield was ravaged, and the few spectators gasped at the scene.

Suddenly, Li Ran's eyes shone brightly.

A chance!

He found a weak point of his opponent, and was about to attack.

Suddenly, his heart hurt, and his body stiffened; the counter attack from his opponent sent him flying.

Li Ran was heavily injured, groaning in pain. His body flew more than ten steps back, until he stopped himself.

A trace of blood fell from his mouth.

However, the severity of his injuries was on par with the shock and fear in his heart right now!

"My flowerbud Gu, my flowerbud Gu! How did it lose connection with me? The stellar stone is inside it!!"

At the same time, at Li Ran's residence.

The bed was flipped over, showing a secret compartment.

Fang Yuan stood beside it, holding a flowerbud Gu in his hand.

This Gu was rank two, used to store items. It was shaped like a flower, light blue in color but was crystal in material, shining clearly under sunlight.

Although it was Li Ran's Gu, with the Spring Autumn Cicada's aura, Fang Yuan instantly refined it.

Fang Yuan's mind went into the Gu, and saw many things inside. A large sack of rice, some daily necessities, a poor quality block of compressed tea, thirty to forty primeval stones and a few fossils.

"This is it!" Fang Yuan's heart trembled, as he activated his primeval essence, and a black light flew out of the flowerbud Gu.

The black light landed in Fang Yuan's palm, turning into a stellar stone.

It looked extremely ugly, squarish and resembled a brick, almost the same as the leg support rock.

The moment the stellar stone appeared, the entire world seemed to have went silent.

Fang Yuan's pupils expanded.

Thump thump... thump thump...

His heartbeat accelerated, he could clearly hear it.

Including this shabby house and the people walking outside, the surroundings faded away; only Fang Yuan and the stellar stone were left.

He held the heavy stellar stone, and he could feel the cold surface of the rock.

Fang Yuan stared at it passionately, at the same time, his lips curled up as he smiled.

His smile widened, until he opened his mouth and laughed silently!

The legendary Gu, is finally in my hands!!!

He screamed in his heart: "Just as I guessed, this Li Ran is a spy from another clan! When I was at Qing Mao mountain, I used the gambling rock to conceal my liquor worm, he is doing the same thing. No wonder the stellar stone was empty, my previous life's rumor was all part of his act."

"Today, he is going to the battle stage to fight. Whether he concealed his strength or not, according to his previous records, the opponent is around the same level as him, it would be a tough fight. The legendary Gu's stellar stone is so important, it will be tough to fight if he brings it around. With his vigilant nature, he would not hide the stellar stone in the storage Gu and bring it around."

Because if he lost the battle, his opponent would get to take one of his Gu worms.

He knew there was a legendary Gu within the stellar stone, if his opponent took his storage Gu, he would lose the stellar stone!

Chapter 284: One, Two, Five

"I admit defeat!" Li Ran suddenly half kneeled on the ground, shouting loudly.

His opponent stopped charging forward, holding back his attack as he did not want to drive Li Ran into a corner. There was no benefits in doing that for both parties.

Li Ran spit out a mouthful of blood, standing up shakingly.

In order to quickly leave the battlefield, he purposely took a few hits from his opponent.

The hosting Gu Master walked in front, announcing the results of the battle.

Li Ran was extremely anxious, after taking back the vine information Gu, he quickly left the battle stage after pretending to be dejected.

He half-heartedly bandaged his injuries before rushing back to his house.

"God damn it, how can this happen? What in the world happened, why did I lose connection with flowerbud Gu?"

Li Ran's heart was engulfed by a dark cloud.

The flowerbud Gu was a Gu he had refined, the moment Fang Yuan refined it, he could sense it.

"Only two possibilities exist for such a situation. One is that the flowerbud Gu was destroyed, the second is that someone else refined it! Was I discovered? No, maybe the situation isn't as bad as I imagine, a burglar could've entered my house. F*ck, I have lived in Shang clan city for eight years, I know almost all the thieves there are, why would someone want to steal from that house of mine!"

Li Ran walked quickly, the stellar stone was extremely important, even with his calm nature, he could not help but feel anxious.

He was regretting.

He should've hid the flowerbud Gu at a safer location, and not place it in the secret compartment under his bed.

But the truth is, that was not his fault.

He had gone undercover, to conceal himself, he did not have any friends, and for the last few years, he had not contacted his wife or child. He often went to brothels, gambling dens, restaurants, those areas were full of people and he could not hide anything there.

He could hide it at a pawn shop, but placing so much attention on a scrap grade fossil was too peculiar. When Shang clan investigates in the future,that would create huge suspicion.

In Shang clan city, all sorts of people existed, there were many thief Gu Masters. But to forcefully take over the flowerbud Gu, a rank three Gu is required. The problem is, why would any rank three Gu Master want to steal from a run down place like his?

Li Ran had lurked for eight years, so long that he almost forgot his past. When he hid the flowerbud Gu, he was very confident but now his confidence turned into regret and self blame.

"Hopefully, the situation can still be salvaged!"

He returned to his home feeling uncertainty, the door was closed.

He opened it, and saw the place was in a mess.

"It was a thief!" He suddenly had a thought.

Encountering a thief was not scary, as long as his identity was not exposed, all could be salvaged.

"That's right!" Li Ran consoled himself: "Every time I contacted Wu clan, it was a one-sided transmission. There are no evidence on me, and that legendary Gu is inside the stellar stone. If it is not opened, who would know the value of it? As long as I find the thief, with my eight years of experience in this city..."

As he thought about it, he calmed his emotions, and stopped panicking.

"Should I report the case? Using the guards' ability to arrest the thief? No, I should be polite before resorting to brute force, it is best if I can get back the stellar stone peacefully. The city guards can't be trusted too, they would not spend effort for a small fry like me. Maybe I should hire a Tie clan Gu Master?"

"Eh? This is..." At this point, he concentrated, and found a Gu after flipping over his bed.

Heart sound Gu!

This Gu was rank two, green and black in color, around the size of a baby's thumb. It was shaped like a conch shell, one end was large while the other end was tiny, and had a spiral appearance.

"Heart sound Gu comes in pairs, it can allow two Gu Masters to speak internally within a hundred steps. Don't tell me... the thief left this behind specially for me?!"

Li Ran's eyes shone with hesitation, but he gritted his teeth and placed the heart sound Gu into his ear, like a earplug.

"Who are you?" Li Ran injected primeval essence, and activated the heart sound Gu, concentrating his mind and asked.

"That question is not important. The important thing is, Li Ran is a fake name right? Hehehe." Soon after, Fang Yuan's voice appeared in Li Ran's head.

That instant, Li Ran's pupils shrunk as he looked like he was struck by lightning, stunned on the spot.

"Not good, he found out my identity!" Li Ran was horror stricken.

The situation had become the worst!

But he was after all, a spy for eight years, even with this turn of events, he calmed his mind and spoke to Fang Yuan: "Fake name? What fake name, what do you mean?"

He said as he carefully tiptoed, walking around in the shabby house.

He next leaned on the wall, looking at the street outside the window.

"The heart sound Gu has an effective range, only a hundred steps away at most, he must be near me." He rapidly thought of a solution.

To use the heart sound Gu, one has to concentrate in order to speak, ordinary thinking would not be transmitted.

But Fang Yuan was well aware of his mental state, lightly laughing: "Don't bother acting Li Ran. I am not your enemy, as long as you cooperate, to express my sincerity, we can meet up."

"Meet up?" Li Ran was shocked.

Next, Fang Yuan's voice rang in his head: "Now, walk out of your room and turn left around the door."

"Why should I listen to you?" Li Ran called out in his mind.

Fang Yuan laughed: "Don't try to test how much I know, it is beyond your imagination. I will count to five, consider well."

"One." Fang Yuan counted.

Li Ran rapidly thought about the situation.

Even though the flowerbud Gu was in the thief's hands, they had no evidence that he was a Wu clan spy.

He had lurked for eight years, how could there be evidence?

"Two." Fang Yuan spoke casually.

If at this time, he listened to Fang Yuan, and gets spotted by others, that would be concrete proof that he was a spy.

But if he did not listen, what happens to the stellar stone?

"Five." Fang Yuan continued to count.

Li Ran's mind was thrown into chaos, as he scolded: "God damn, can you even count properly?!"

"Hehehe, it seems you have come to a decision." Fang Yuan laughed.

Li Ran breathed deeply, his fists clenched tightly, as he gritted his teeth and left the house.

He walked out of the door, and arrived at a busy street. Next, he turned left.

About fifty steps later, Fang Yuan's voice rang out again: "Turn right, at the third cross junction, turn left."

"He can see my movements, he has to be beside me, but who?" Li Ran had sharp vision, like an eagle sweeping the crowd.

"I would advise you not to look around, that is not your usual behavior. Hehe, after eight years, you want it all to go down the drain?" Fang Yuan quickly said.

"Damn it..." Li Ran gritted his teeth till they squeaked, Fang Yuan's threat made him lower his head as he looked ahead.

Following Fang Yuan's instructions, he turned and walked around in circles, until Fang Yuan told him to stop.

"Turn around." Fang Yuan quickly followed: "In your vision, there should be a restaurant, go to the third storey, I will be waiting there."

Li Ran looked, and his heart jumped.

This restaurant, was the one he often came to, Fu Tai Xiang He restaurant.

"Don't tell me..." He had a bad feeling in his heart. The thief held so much information about him, it felt like he was stripped bare naked in the winter snow plains.

He entered the restaurant.

The familiar shop assistant looked at him, enthusiastically calling out: "Lord Li Ran, you are here, please come upstairs!"

Li Ran's grim face smiled slightly as he carried his utmost vigilance and ascended the ladder.

Halfway through, before the second floor.

"Wait." Fang Yuan suddenly said.

Li Ran stopped his movement, asking: "What?"

"Go downstairs, and out of the door." Fang Yuan instructed.

Li Ran snorted, having no choice but to leave.

The shop assistant looked at him, feeling confused, quickly asking: "What is the matter lord, are you not eating anymore?"

Li Ran waved his hand, asking him to leave, as he walked out of the restaurant.

"Opposite you, there is a shop selling baked pancakes, go buy a few." Fang Yuan continued.

Li Ran's eyes twitched, but he followed the instructions, buying a few pancakes.

"Okay, now return to the third floor of the restaurant." Fang Yuan said again.

Li Ran's forehead was popping with veins as he held the pancake and returned to the restaurant.

The shop assistant saw him entering again, looking at him weirdly: "Lord Li Ran, if you want to buy pancakes, just call me, I can buy it for you."

"Scram." Li Ran shouted, scaring the shop assistant as he shuddered and stopped talking.

He got to the third floor, and stopped after the ladder.

"Continue, take two to three steps and turn left, you will see me." Fang Yuan instructed.

Li Ran followed the instructions, as he walked around a pillar, and finally saw Fang Yuan, sitting at his usual spot.

Next, he saw Fang Yuan stretch out his hand, inviting him to the seat. At the same time, he heard in his mind: "Please take a seat."

Li Ran did not speak, quietly sitting before Fang Yuan, then staring at him without blinking.

The truth is, Fang Yuan's youthful appearance gave him a huge shock.

When they conversed, Fang Yuan held him tightly by the collar, he subconsciously pictured the image of Fang Yuan as an unscrupulous middle aged man, or an elderly wearing a hat, hiding his face in the darkness.

But the truth was completely the opposite.

The voice from the heart sound Gu would always be tuned, it cannot ascertain age, but could easily determine the gender.

If he did not see it with his own eyes, Li Ran would never have thought the mysterious man was so young!

Fifth inner city's street lights passed the windows and shone on Fang Yuan's face. Although he had a plain look, his eyes were as black as ink, like an abyss, deep and mysterious.

Li Ran memorised Fang Yuan's face deep in his heart.

Although this was the first time they met, he could swear, he would never forget Fang Yuan's appearance in this life.

Because it was due to this young man that all his plans were foiled, and in such a helpless way!

Chapter 285: All-out effort Gu

On the dinner table, dishes and wine produced amazing fragrance.

At the surrounding tables, some people were playing drinking games, some recited poems, others were playing around, it was a relaxed and fun atmosphere.

Fang Yuan and Li Ran sat opposite each other, they looked very peaceful, but they were secretly sizing each other up. It was the calm before the storm. Li Ran had deep killing intent in his heart, and although Fang Yuan looked relaxed, he was also wary of Li Ran.

"Who exactly are you?" Li Ran asked using the heart sound Gu.

"I said before, that is not important. Pass the pancake to me." The first half was spoken internally, while the second sentence was using his mouth.

Li Ran was stunned, before pushing the paper bag towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan opened the bag, taking out a pancake and biting, nodding: "Now this is the flavor I wanted, I'm so sorry for the trouble."

Next, he used the heart sound Gu: "Do you know, I tailed you for several days below this restaurant, I got hungry and bought a pancake, and found it really delicious, want to try?"

Li Ran had no mood to try the pancake.

He snorted in his heart, asking: "Aren't you afraid I'll poison it?"

But on the surface, he smiled and said: "It is no big deal, no trouble at all. Don't forget we have a great relationship."

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan laughed out loud, staring at Li Ran with deep meaning, transmitting in his mind: "You think I don't know what Gu you have?"

Li Ran smiled more brightly, but his heart sank.

"He is trying to remind me! That's right, the enemy is hiding in the shadows while I am out there, I did not even sense him tailing me these few days. He should've known all about me already. If I fight him now, there is a low chance of success, thus he used this pancake to warn me!"

Fang Yuan saw Li Ran keeping silent, his eyes shifting around, and knew the warning got through, thus he took out the stellar stone.

Li Ran's gaze was attracted, but the stone was quickly taken away.

The next moment, Fang Yuan's voice rang in his mind: "Stop pretending, I know the all-out effort Gu is inside this."

"WHAT?!" Li Ran's heart shook like he had been struck by lightning.

Even if he was a good actor, his expression changed showing fluster and fear.

He had been hoping the secret of the stellar stone would not be exposed. After all, it came form Wei Shen Jing, there were no flaws, but to think the matter had worsened to this extent, the other party knew the all-out effort Gu was sealed inside!

"Wait, the matter regarding the all-out effort Gu, only a few people know about it. Even I only knew about it soon after receiving it, how did he find out?"

"The matter is complex now... I am confident there are no loopholes on my end, thus this should've been exposed on the clan side! Wu clan can send a spy like me here, Shang clan can also send theirs over. The few large clans in the southern border, they infiltrate each other, and there are spies everywhere, they should be clear of each other's matters."

"If not, how could he know about the all-out effort Gu? That's right, I was so vigilant, how could I make a mistake and let him get a hold on me, or even suspect me? To think my home clan has been infiltrated to this extent, it is truly scary!"

"But maybe that isn't the case, in this world, there are too many special Gu worms..."

Fang Yuan left Li Ran ample time to think.

He was a smart person, the more he thought, the more suspicious he would get. Subconsciously, he would imagine Fang Yuan to be stronger, more mysterious, and scarier. That would make him feel inferior during the discussion.

Fang Yuan played with the stellar stone, after a while, when the time was almost ripe, he continued transmitting his voice: "I want the all-out effort Gu."

Li Ran was stunned, not understanding Fang Yuan's deeper meaning.

"But I know, if I take this Gu, I would face the wrath and revenge of your clan. Thus, I need your cooperation." Fang Yuan's gaze was eerie.

To be able to plot against Shang clan, they had to be an equally large clan. If Fang Yuan took the all-out effort Gu by force, he would be enemies with this clan.

This stellar stone was like bait on a hook. If Fang Yuan wanted to eat this bait, he needed to avoid getting stuck on the hook.

Li Ran revealed a mocking smile: "You want me to cooperate with you, what a joke, on what basis?"

"Based on the fact that I do not want to be enemies with you. Even if I have the purple thorn token, I do not want to be enemies with you, because like you, I have people I want to protect." Fang Yuan said in his mind to Li Ran, as he looked out of the window.

At the same time, he said with his mouth: "I heard that shop sells great tofu."

Li Ran squinted, his eyes showing a ferocious gaze, screaming in his mind: "Are you threatening me?!"

Fang Yuan shook his head, in his eyes, there were clouds drifting, as he showed a complex emotion on his face. Li Ran instantly caught his emotion, there were sadness, pain, helplessness, and fondness.

"Are you not clear of your situation?" Fang Yuan said in his mind: "People like us, squeezed between two strong forces, living on the edge everyday, hiding our emotions in the depths of our hearts, and could die anytime. Since we chose this path, we can only continue walking on it. It is all for the clan, we have no regrets. But some people, they are innocent, why should they be implicated into our business, and bear the risks for us?"

Li Ran's heart stirred, staring at Fang Yuan in disbelief: "You... are a spy too?"

Fang Yuan laughed helplessly, in a bitter tone: "What do you think?"

Li Ran saw this smile, and his eyes watered, as he stared tightly at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's expression did not have a tint of unnaturalness, as he turned to look outside the window.

Li Ran knew he was looking at his own wife and children.

Fang Yuan's gaze was so gentle, so dazed, as if he was recalling certain memories.

Li Ran did not think he was acting, because this youngster was too young, how could he fake such true emotions? Even at his age, Li Ran could not act to this level.

This was his true emotions!

Unknowingly, a sense of acceptance towards Fang Yuan grew in his heart.

As people in similar situations, they did not need a deep relationship to understand each other.

Fang Yuan blinked, looking back at Li Ran, and said: "Li Ran, you have lurked in Shang clan city for eight years. If your identity is exposed, your mission would fail. Your failure may cause you to lose your life, but more importantly, the clan would suffer a loss, and you would let down their expectations."

Li Ran clenched his fists.

Fang Yuan's words pulled the strings in his heart.

He was loyal to the clan, almost religiously. Otherwise, the clan would not have chosen him to be the spy.

Fang Yuan said again: "If you fail, your wife would lose her husband. Your son is only five now, he would lose his father. If your identity is exposed, there is a high chance of them dying because of you. You only have one step left to succeed, the position of clan elder is your goal, am I right? But do you think that is the end? No, you will continue lurking, as long as Shang clan existed, the clan would need your spying."

Li Ran gritted his teeth.

Fang Yuan's words hit the nail on the head.

All these things, did he not consider them? He only dared to think about them for a moment before stopping. The more he thought about it, the more pressure he felt, the future was really too long, it would cause him to lose the courage to continue!

"Thus, you need alliance mates, brother Li Ran." Fang Yuan continued speaking: "You will not betray your clan, I won't either. You have people you want to protect, so do I. We can cooperate, we need external force to ensure our family's safety. We have to live in order to make contributions to our clans. And the Shang clan is our mutual goal."

'Of course, this cooperation is only in private. If our clans want to wage war, you will be the first person I will eliminate." After pausing briefly, Fang Yuan added.

Li Ran snorted coldly, Fang Yuan's truthful declaration only made his words more trustworthy.

To him, loyalty to the clan is the top priority, next is his family, and then his own life.

Fang Yuan's suggestion catered to his three needs.

"But can this person be trusted? We are from different forces, cooperation between spies is wishful thinking! Maybe... it is because he is young, and coupled with his intellect and courage, he thought of this method? If I was this young, I'm afraid... I may do the same... or not."

The more Li Ran thought about it, the more he felt Fang Yuan's sincerity.

Most importantly, he had no other way out! He was completely exposed before Fang Yuan.

If Fang Yuan exposed him, his mission would fail, his ten years of hard work would go up in flames, how could he accept this?

Human nature is complex, they have this thing called fluke mentality.

Li Ran was like someone who was driven to a cliff, with his enemies approaching, he could only jump down. Even if he did not know what was below the cliff, he would still pray that there is a water body below, or maybe he would be saved by some tree branches while descending.

He fell into deep silence for a long time.

After a few minutes, he used the heart sound Gu: "How can I believe you?"

Fang Yuan smiled, taking out a poison vow Gu.

...

Three days later, Fang Yuan opened the all-out effort Gu in the gambling den, causing the entire district to go into chaos.

"Did you hear? Someone opened an all-out effort Gu in Lan Chao gambling den!"

"Is that really the all-out effort Gu? It is a near extinct ancient Gu, able to summon the beast phantom a hundred percent of the time!"

"You guys only knew now? Hehe, I know more than you. This extremely lucky person is called Gu Yue Fang Zheng. I don't know why, but he has a purple thorn token. The all-out effort Gu was not supposed to be his, but was chosen by a Gu Master called Li Ran, but he knocked into Gu Yue Fang Zheng who decided to find problems with him, taking away three fossils from him as compensation. That all-out effort Gu was within those fossils."

"Oh dear, he really is unlucky, the all-out effort Gu should've been his!"

"This is fate..."

"Lan Chao gambling den, no, I have to go take a look!"

At once, rumors spread all over Shang clan city.

Chapter 286: A Small Test Run

"This is the all-out effort Gu?"

In the secret room, Wei Yang held this Gu in his hand as he exclaimed, strange light shining in his eyes.

All-out effort Gu, it was shaped like a rhinoceros beetle.

Now, it was sitting quietly in Wei Yang's palm, its body was almost the size of Wei Yang's palm, and was quite heavy.

It was oval in shape, and had a strong armor exoskeleton. There was a strong horn on its head, looking heavy and powerful.

It had three pairs of legs, all strong and thick. Its body was dark brown, and glistened with a metallic surface. People only needed one glance to know it was not ordinary.

"That's right, this is the rank three all-out effort Gu. Once used, it would summon a beast phantom, able to move according to my will." Fang Yuan was sitting on a cushion opposite Wei Yang, as he explained.

Wei Yang breathed in deeply, handing the all-out effort Gu back to Fang Yuan.

"At this timing, is it fate? Brother Fang Zheng, are you truly bent on the strength path?" He gave his last attempt.

Fang Yuan nodded, not speaking, but his determined expression said everything.

Wei Yang sighed again.

If previously, he was confident of changing Fang Yuan's mind, at this moment, after obtaining the all-out effort Gu, he knew that Fang Yuan's decision was final, there was no hope in changing it.

"Fate is really mystical, obtaining the all-out effort Gu would greatly help you on the strength path. The all-out effort Gu is undoubtedly the core Gu worm in assembling your set. If you are so determined, I shall say no more. But I have one final thing to remind you, just treat it as my nagging."

Fang Yuan became serious: "Not at all, please give me your advice!"

"Although you have the all-out effort Gu, times are different now. If this all-out effort Gu is your core, you have to ensure its safety. It is only a rank three Gu now, if you want to refine it into rank four or rank five in the future, there is too much danger in refining it if it is not your vital Gu. If the all-out effort Gu is destroyed in the process of refinement, your entire set would collapse without the core. Thus, my first advice to you is to convert it into your vital Gu. Shang clan can help you to achieve this."

"To make a set, just one core is not enough, you need several important support Gu. Regarding this, you need to choose carefully, and think ahead. If your choice is wrong, it will not allow you to display the full value of all-out effort Gu. Sigh, actually, during ancient times, when strength path flourished, there were much more Gu worms that complemented the all-out effort Gu. Now, most of them are extinct, if you want to assemble a Gu set, you cannot use ancient methods, but can only explore this yourself."

"I have another extremely important matter that you have to take note of. Although you have the all-out effort Gu, you have no corresponding refinement recipe. But thankfully, most of the recipes from the Olden Antiquity Era were passed down. There should be some in certain recipe masters' hands, you have to collect them. If not..."

Saying so, Wei Yang hesitated.

"You can try your luck in exploring ancient strength path inheritances. Wu clan found such an inheritance several years ago, if you can find one, your future would be set. I really want to see the strength path flourish in your hands!"

After saying these things, Wei Yang took his leave.

Fang Yuan sent him off, and watched Wei Yang turn into light and fly away.

Fang Yuan stood at the door of the secret room, his gaze concentrating.

The advice Wei Yang gave, he had considered all of them long ago, and had plans already.

He already had a copy of the all-out effort Gu's recipe, obviously from Li Ran.

Wu clan provided Li Ran the all-out effort Gu, they naturally gave him the recipe.

But this recipe only allowed the rank three all-out effort Gu to reach rank four. Any higher, Fang Yuan needed to find out himself.

But in this aspect, Fang Yuan was only rank three initial stage now, in the short run, he had no worries about the rank five refinement recipe.

As for what Gu to choose, in order to complement the all-out effort Gu, and become support for the core, Fang Yuan had his plans.

He had always been the type to walk one step and plan ten ahead, he was extremely confident.

"The strength path Gu set, should use the all-out effort Gu as the core, self-reliance Gu and bitter strength Gu as the support. With a few other Gu worms accompanying, this set of Gu worms can be considered initial success. But to reach greater success, I have to rely on the three kings inheritance."

Spending two to three years in Shang clan city, assembling a set of Gu and reach initial success stage.

When the three kings inheritance activates, he will use the advantages of rebirth and add in useful Gu worms to cause his Gu set to reach greater success stage.

This was Fang Yuan's plans for the near future.

"This plan has to be executed perfectly. Because after the three kings inheritance, it would be the righteous demonic battle at Yi Tian mountain, if my battle strength is not high enough then, I would not be able to gather enough benefits for myself. Time, is really tight..."

As for the third, his vital Gu.

Fang Yuan's vital Gu is Spring Autumn Cicada, this cannot be changed.

Then the refinement of the all-out effort Gu would be much more difficult. Since there is a risk to the Gu, the refinement would need to be done extremely carefully.

If Fang Yuan was unlucky, and caused the all-out effort Gu to die during refinement, his set of Gu worms would lose their foundation, like a human without a soul.

If that happens, the outcome would be disastrous, almost equivalent to Fang Yuan's strength path cultivation being crippled.

But, there were ways to ensure the all-out effort Gu survives during refinement even if it was not his vital Gu.

Wei Yang did not know because he was a frog in a well.

Fang Yuan knew three methods.

First method was to head to the "Land of Bu Bai". This was the Bu Bai inheritance, far away in central continent, the sacred land for refinement masters.

Secondly, he could use the undefeated hundred battles Gu, when refining Gu, it could ensure a hundred percent success rate.

The third was also a Gu, called "green mountain remains". 'As long as the green mountain remains, one need not worry about firewood.' Only by keeping something vital is there a chance for a comeback. Using this Gu, it can protect the core Gu, even if refinement fails and the other Gu are destroyed, the all-out effort Gu will still remain.

The land of Bu Bai was too far away, it was impossible to get there. Undefeated hundred battles Gu, an extremely rare rank five Gu even during ancient times, right now it was extinct. "Green mountain remains" was in the hands of several refinement masters, this was a rank four Gu, it was difficult to obtain but there was at least some hope.

"There is one undefeated hundred battles Gu in the three kings inheritance. If I can get it, the all-out effort Gu's advancement to rank four would be ensured. Next, I can only think of other ways... now, it is time to replace everything."

Fang Yuan had a careful nature, before he obtained the all-out effort Gu, even though he had hundreds of thousands of primeval stones, he did not spend them.

Now that it is in his hands, he finally decided to act.

He did not need to leave Nan Qiu garden, instead going to the study room and taking out a large number of invitations.

Ever since he 'gambled' and won the all-out effort Gu, rumors flew about in Shang clan city, and everyone were acting like cats who saw fish, swarming at Fang Yuan's place.

Fang Yuan had the purple thorn token, and attended Shang Yan Fei's clan banquet before, he had a unique identity and no one dared to force him.

They had sent all sorts of invitations, but Fang Yuan stayed in his house for several days, not meeting a single guest.

Now, Fang Yuan took out the invitations, and saw that a portion were from recipe masters, hoping to meet Fang Yuan and become acquaintances, so that they can borrow the all-out effort Gu for research. A Gu from the Antiquity Era would be great help towards their recipe creation.

Another portion were established Gu Masters, holding all sorts of titles, they either wished to spar with Fang Yuan or wanted to exchange Gu worms with him.

But mostly, the invitations came from all the famous shops, and all the large clan's Gu Masters, hoping to purchase the all-out effort Gu.

Fang Yuan chose a small portion of them, and instructed his servants to send a message to them.

Not long after, a group of Gu Masters came running.

Fang Yuan met them at the reception hall: "I am not selling the all-out effort Gu, I am meeting everyone here today for other trading purposes."

This caused everyone to be disappointed, but some did not give up, only after Fang Yuan's firm attitude did they give up.

Three hours later, a few business were settled, and everyone left.

Two days later, the Gu worms arrived.

Fang Yuan's battle strength surged, but he paid a huge price.

Gu worms were seriously too expensive, he spent several hundred thousand primeval stones for them. The old man made of clouds in the primeval elder Gu was already hunching his back as he showed a painful and worried expression, in an extremely pitiful state.

Another day later, Fang Yuan stepped into the battle stage.

At once, everyone went wild.

Outside the battle stage, people were crowding to the point where there was no walking space.

His opponent was none other than Li Ran.

He stared at Fang Yuan, his expression twisted and his eyes burned with fire, as he screamed: "Gu Yue Fang Zheng, you stole my opportunity, that is extremely despicable! Today, I will take back what belongs to me."

"Hmph, who told you to knock into me? I asked for compensation but you refused to pay primeval stones. Those stones covered your debt, you were willing as well." Fang Yuan laughed coldly as he answered.

The viewers outside started to discuss among themselves as they became extremely noisy.

Fang Yuan and Li Ran's conversation testified the truth behind the rumors these days.

"Ahhh!" Li Ran grabbed his hair, screaming to the sky: "Fang Zheng, you tyrant, I was forced by you! I only knocked into you by accident, but you refused to let me go. Today, I will seek justice for myself!"

Saying so, Li Ran pounced at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, seeing him get close, he willed.

Vertical crash Gu.

Howl!

The winds blew as he took a step, and his body charged forward by fifty steps.

Li Ran felt his vision blur as Fang Yuan had already charged up to him.

All-out effort Gu.

Fang Yuan willed, and light burst forth, forming the phantom image of a wild boar charging in mid air behind him.

The wild boar was black and had sharp tusks, showing a fierce expression as the winds blew!

"Not good!" Li Ran screamed, dodging.

Fang Yuan charged right past him, although Li Ran was not hit head on, his arm was scratched.

Next, with a 'crack', his forearm bone broke, and the defensive light on Li Ran's body vanished, as he fell to the ground, unable to get up.

"Just one hit!"

"Was that the all-out effort Gu?"

"That Li Ran is too weak, he is definitely not Fang Zheng's match!"

Outside, the spectators exclaimed, expressing their shock.

Chapter 287: Reputation Gu

Fang Yuan charged for fifty steps before he stopped. He turned around, facing Li Ran, about to launch his second attack.

But Li Ran had already raised his hand, shouting loudly: "Wait, no more, I admit defeat!"

Once he said so, the surroundings went quiet, before exploding.

"What, no more?"

"We spent primeval stones to come here and see the all-out effort Gu."

"You coward, are you even a man, stand up and fight!"

Everyone shouted furiously.

Many people were angry and breathed roughly, feeling that their primeval stones were wasted, starting to grumble and scold. But a portion of the people understood Li Ran.

"There's no way to win, it is wise to concede."

"That hit earlier showed their difference. If they continue, Li Ran's life would be in danger.

"This Li Ran is a veteran in the battle stage. With his rich experience, I am not surprised he did that."

Clank.

A loud ring from the bell, and this match was over.

The spectators started to leave the stage, as Fang Yuan took his leave as well.

"Fang Zheng, wait first." Li Ran suddenly called, stopping him.

Fang Yuan frowned, turning around and looking at him: "What do you want?"

Everyone's footsteps halted.

"Fang Zheng, you are indebted to me, but now you hurt and injured me, this is repaying kindness with vengeance, you have to compensate me!" Li Ran shouted.

These words were shameless, he wanted to challenge Fang Zheng without knowing their difference, now that he got injured, how could he say his opponent was "repaying kindness with vengeance".

Many people heard this and snorted, feeling disdain towards Li Ran.

Challenging Fang Yuan forcefully, that was because he could not take it lying down, many people understood his emotions. But after losing, he still continued to pester Fang Yuan, that was going overboard.

Fang Yuan shook his head, turning to leave: "Your brain was damaged by my attack too?"

Many people jeered and laughed.

But Li Ran struggled to get up, shouting at Fang Yuan: "Fang Zheng, I know your personality! You distinguish kindness and hatred clearly, the acclaimed 'a droplet received in need will be repaid with a whole spring, a spark of hatred will result in the burning of an entire forest!' Shang Xin Ci showed you a little kindness and you risked your life to protect her, escorting her to Shang clan city. Shang clan leader wanted to reward you but you rejected all of them, saying that your kindness had been repaid. The Shang clan leader even had to force you to accept the purple thorn token!'

"Fang Zheng, to be honest, I have done you a favor. If I did not choose that stellar stone, would you be able to get that all-out effort Gu? No! Hehe, nevermind if it is another person, but I know you, I understand you. Although you are oppressive and tyrannical, you have to repay kindness or you will be unable to sleep. Isn't that so? Think about it, you owe me a favor, can you sleep tonight?"

"Heh, that is because you have never seen Fang Yuan's true colors!" Among the crowd, Bai Ning Bing heard Li Ran's words and snorted coldly.

Fang Yuan obtaining the all-out effort Gu had made her curious.

After all, Fang Yuan was her rival.

Suddenly, Fang Yuan stopped in his steps.

As everyone watched, he turned around and faced Li Ran, with a serious expression.

"If you put it like that, it seems I owe you a favor. But firstly, it was because you offended me, and second, I cannot give the all-out effort Gu away. What do you want me to do?"

Fang Yuan's words made everyone who was leaving stop their steps and observe their conversation again.

Bai Ning Bing gasped in her heart, feeling shocked.

"Although the all-out effort Gu is rank three, it originated from the Olden Antiquity Era, it is considered unique now, its true value cannot be estimated. Give me a hundred thousand primeval stones, and your favor will be considered repaid!" Li Ran thought about it and said.

"Is this Li Ran stupid?"

"He dares to ask for such a ridiculous sum, such stupidity, sigh..."

"Making such a request, he is so shameless!"

Everyone shook their heads, feeling disappointed at Li Ran's shamelessness.

Fang Yuan thought about it, shaking his head.

"A hundred thousand primeval stones is insufficient, I'll give you two hundred thousand, that would put me at ease." Saying so, he waved his hand and summoned the primeval elder Gu, pouring all the primeval stones out.

On the floor of the battle stage, a mountain of primeval stones appeared.

"This is eighty thousand, that's all I have now. I'll give you the rest when I have money!"

"What?!" Fang Yuan's words sent everyone into shock.

"He actually gave it? And... and even raised it to two hundred thousand!" Everyone was tongue-tied.

"Did I see wrongly?! Although this Li Ran did not obtain the all-out effort Gu, getting so much primeval stones as compensation is almost as good." Everyone blinked, seeing those primeval stones, they almost drooled.

"This Fang Zheng is really..." Many people saw Fang Yuan leave and felt weird in their hearts, not sure of what to say.

Although they did not manage to see the power of the all-out effort Gu, hearing Li Ran and Fang Yuan's conversation made the trip worth it.

News about this battle quickly circulated, and spread around Shang clan city.

The fact that Fang Yuan had a purple thorn token also circulated, resulting in people who had ill intentions to vanish without a trace.

Many people started to be envious of Li Ran, while others also felt doubt towards Fang Yuan's promise of two hundred thousand primeval stones.

But no matter what, Fang Yuan's 'distinguish kindness and hatred' reputation also became well-known.

Back at Nan Qiu garden.

"Do you really intend to give that Li Ran two hundred thousand primeval stones?" Bai Ning Bing asked suspiciously.

This was not Fang Yuan's style at all.

"Of course." Fang Yuan replied curtly. He was obviously not going to tell Bai Ning Bing that this was his secret agreement with Li Ran. Li Ran would act with Fang Yuan, and tell him the refinement recipe, while Fang Yuan compensates him two hundred thousand primeval stones.

Bai Ning Bing was solemn for a while, not believing him, then laughing coldly: "Two hundred thousand just for a reputation, is it worth it?"

Fang Yuan snickered: "Have you never heard the story of reputation Gu?"

Bai Ning Bing's gaze was hesitant: "What are you trying to say?"

"Reputation is a bridge, one that allows people to cross through the abyss. Reputation is a travel token, more important and precious than the purple thorn token, it allows one to move about with ease. Two hundred thousand cannot even buy the purple thorn token, yet i spent that amount to obtain this reputation. This is the best trade in the world. Hahaha." Fang Yuan laughed.

Bai Ning Bing snorted, but thinking that he had a precognitive Gu, she chose to believe him for now.

Regarding the reputation Gu's story, it originated from the legends of Ren Zu...

One time, Verdant Great Sun got very drunk, when he woke up, his head hurt and he forgot all that happened when he was drunk. He did not know why he was trapped on a lone hill, one which was surrounded by a bottomless abyss.

The abyss was filled with spiral winds, pale green color, this was the 'usual wind'. The winds blew dust into the air, those were the dark yellow color 'mortal dust'.

Verdant Great Sun's heart sank, because he recognised that this was the ordinary abyss. No living being had ever managed to fly past it. He was trapped on this lone hill, unable to get out; he would die of starvation eventually.

Thankfully, there was a forest on the lone hill. Verdant Great Sun was hungry, and came into this forest to find fruits to eat. But this forest was very strange, the black soil was like a swamp, smelling extremely pungent. The trees had no leaves, and the branches looked like strange claws. But when the wind blew, there was the sound of leaves moving in the wind.

Verdant Great Sun could not find food, and fell into despair, knowing he was going to die soon.

A few days later, he was so hungry he could not move, leaning on the tree trunk as he laid on the ground.

He eventually fell unconscious.

In his slumber, he could hear many voices talking.

"Hey look, this person finally passed out."

"Mm, as I expected, he's finished."

"Actually, it is possible to leave the ordinary abyss, you just need the reputation Gu."

"Reputation Gu is at the center of the forest, hidden under a rock. Too bad he doesn't know, hahaha..."

"Sshhh, speak softer, it will be bad if he hears us."

"It's okay, it's okay, he has fainted already, before long, the black soil will bury him, and turn him into nutrients for us trees."

Hearing this, Verdant Great Sun jolted awake.

It turns out this forest is Xi Yu forest, what he had thought was leaves brushing in the wind turned out to be the whispers of the trees.

After hearing the information, Verdant Great Sun walked to the center of the forest, lifted the rock, and obtained the reputation Gu.

Reputation Gu was like a chrysanthemum, its petals were golden yellow, emitting a fragrance.

Reputation Gu said to Verdant Great Sun: "Young man, thank you for lifting the rock, and saving me. To repay you, I have decided to help you get across this ordinary abyss."

Reputation Gu told Verdant Great Sun the method to use it.

Verdant Great Sun was overjoyed, arriving at ordinary abyss, and placed the reputation Gu in his mouth, shouting as loud as he could...

The strange thing was, no matter how loud he shouted, there was no sound, but the vibrations in the air caused the ordinary abyss to shake, as the commotion got bigger, it was like an earthquake. The air was even filled with a brilliant fragrance.

Verdant Great Sun did not feel anything weird, as he had known from the reputation Gu: Reputation itself has no voice, but it can spread wide and create tremors.

As he shouted, a golden bridge appeared in midair, but the bridge's length was limited, there was still a long distance to the other side.

Verdant Great Sun was too hungry, too tired, after trying several times, the effect continue to diminish, and his chance for salvation seemed dim.

Reputation Gu sighed: "Sigh, you have not eaten anything in a while, even though you have a breath left in your stomach, it is too little. From your diaphragm, it has to go through your stomach, chest, throat, and finally your mouth, the journey is too long, we have to reduce it, here, place me between your two buttcheeks.

Verdant Great Sun did as instructed.

Reputation Gu landed near his private part, and turned into a chrysanthemum cave.

"Okay, you can start shouting again." Reputation Gu said.

Verdant Great Sun forced that last breath of his, out of this hole, out of his body.

Prrrrrrrrt—

In his daze, Verdant Great Sun heard a loud sound. The air was filled with an unimaginable stench, but that golden bridge became majestic and large, stretching over a thousand miles, reaching the other side.

A shitty reputation compared to good reputation, is always easier to obtain and maintain.

Verdant Great Sun quickly crossed the bridge, leaving the ordinary abyss and reaching the other side, saving his own life.

Chapter 288: The Crux of Strength Path Cultivation

Eight days later.

Nan Qiu garden.

At the small square, the ground paved with starry stones shone under the starlight.

Fang Yuan stood in the square with his hands folded, legs slightly open and his eyes closed. His breathing was deep and long.

In front of him were a dozen stone pillars.

Every stone pillars were twenty feet thick, and were dark and rigid. The stone pillars were spaced apart so that it almost covered the small square.

Whish...

Fang Yuan let out a breath of turbid air and suddenly opened his eyes.

At that very moment, a ray of lightning seemed to flash through the void!

Dash!

He took large steps forward and in a few steps reached a stone pillar.

His steps stopped, he bent his waist before swinging his arms vigorously and punching at the pillar.

Bang.

With a dull thud, the stone pillar shook, stone fragments flew about and a spherical dent appeared on the pillar.

Again.

Fang Yuan held his breath then used his fists and palms to attack in turns. Not only that, he also used kicks, flying kicks, elbow strikes, knee strikes, shoulder bash... every part of his body became sharp, strong weapons.

Bang bang bang....

The dull sounds continued along with the stone pillar's continuous shaking and the stone fragments scattering in the air.

Fang Yuan attacked like a storm and gale in one breath, his attacks continuous and endless.

Within seconds, the stone pillar was reduced to half, like a small tree in a storm.

Crack.

Fang Yuan whipped his leg horizontally as a clear sound echoed; the stone pillar that was already hanging by a thread could not endure it anymore and broke into two, falling into the ground.

Fang Yuan relaxedly retracted his leg, his breath was only slightly affected and droplets of sweat seeped out of his forehead.

He looked at the ground.

The appearance of the two broken parts of the stone pillar were changed beyond recognition; their surfaces were filled with dents, results of Fang Yuan's punches and kicks.

"Indeed, it is difficult to bring out the beast strength phantom without using all-out effort Gu, and with just normal attacks."

Ha!

He shouted and in two large strides, he reached the nearest stone pillar.

His right palm smacked heavily towards the stone pillar.

Growl!

A brown bear phantom image suddenly appeared in mid air behind Fang Yuan. It was quite plump, and its mouth was filled with dense white sharp fangs. At the same time as Fang Yuan, it raised its right palm and smacked, the movement strikingly similar to Fang Yuan's.

In that instant, Fang Yuan felt a sudden surge of strength in his right palm!

BOOM.

A huge sound thundered at the impact of Fang Yuan's smack on the stone pillar.

The stone pillar, which needed two people to wrap around it, immediately broke by the smack, producing a loud sound as it collapsed and formed a small pit on the floor.

The countershock immediately struck Fang Yuan and shocked his right palm into numbness.

Fang Yuan had been using brown bear innate strength Gu since he bought it and now he mastered it, increasing his strength by the strength of a bear.

"I needed to hit the stone pillar dozens of times before I could break it. But after using the all-out effort Gu, I broke it in just one smack..."

Fang Yuan clearly perceived the difference.

All-out effort Gu was a support type Gu and not an attack type. But once used, it could produce a devastating blow!

Fang Yuan's battle strength before and after getting it was like the difference between night and day.

Using a support Gu as the core was quite rare. Most of the Gu Masters used support Gu in their Gu set, as an assistance to the core Gu.

For instance, Wei Yang used rainbow light Gu, a movement Gu, as the core; the offensive broadsword light Gu as one of the main support and light source Gu as another support. As a support, light source Gu could only decrease the primeval essence expenditure of light type Gu worms.

However, the all-out effort Gu was completely capable of filling the core position even as a support Gu. Just from this, one could tell how precious it was.

"But... canopy Gu might have impressive defense but it is too rigid. If I change it to golden shield Gu, there should be a clear difference in results." Fang Yuan pondered.

During the punching and kicking test just now, he used canopy Gu, otherwise his hands and legs would certainly be destroyed.

The effect of force is mutual.

Although Fang Yuan's bones were iron bones, his skin, flesh, tendons and blood were all normal. Without the use of canopy Gu, the smack attack just before would have mangled up his flesh and muscles, although his bones would be fine.

However, golden shield Gu was temporarily not available.

Fang Yuan also did not have money right now.

At the start, he had over nine hundred thousand primeval stones, but Bai Ning Bing took half of it. Then, he spent a lot strolling around the rock gambling dens for all-out effort Gu. The expenditure for basic needs along with feeding his Gu worms were rather high especially in Shang Clan's third inner city. Next, he used a lot of primeval stones to change his Gu line-up; eight days ago at battle stage, he gave eighty thousand primeval stones to Li Ran in front of everyone.

Now, Fang Yuan not only had no money, he was also in debt. Because, according to the poison vow contract, he still needed to give a hundred and twenty thousand primeval stones to Li Ran.

Fang Yuan knew this was a necessary investment.

Reputation was second, the important thing was to stabilize Li Ran by showing an attitude of sincere cooperation, despite him already using eating one's words Gu to disperse the poison vow Gu on him several days ago.

Li Ran was an unexpected gain for Fang Yuan. There would be traces left behind if he killed Li Ran which would attract Shang Clan's doubts and ruin his plans, so he did not do it.

To Fang Yuan, Li Ran was a chess piece which was not easy to use but had its own use. Someday in future, he might be able to obtain the rank five refinement recipe for all-out effort Gu from Wu Clan through Li Ran.

Right now, the most important thing was to stabilize Wu Clan through Li Ran.

Three days earlier, Li Ran used the emergency contact method to contact the emissary. He expressed that Fang Yuan could be used well. Like this, the chance of Wu Clan taking revenge was small.

Fang Yuan possessed purple thorn token which meant Shang Clan was paying attention to him. Fang Yuan was also a rank three Gu Master and his battle strength increased sharply with the all-out effort Gu. If Wu Clan really wanted to retaliate, they would have to send rank three or rank four Gu Masters. Mobilizing these elder level strengths would smash apart the tacit understanding of secret battles between high-tiered clans.

The benefit of saving Li Ran was evident here.

"Again." Fang Yuan swept away his unorganized thoughts and gave a low shout.

He lowered his body, held his arms and with a shift of his mind, five percent of his light silver primeval essence poured into vertical crash Gu.

Vertical crash!

The Gu's mystical ability immediately and uncontrollably sent his legs rushing forward.

Bang bang bang!

He dashed forward dozen of steps in a perfectly straight line, continuously knocking down three stone pillars. When he reached the fourth stone pillar, the pillar shook continuously but did not fall down in the end.

This was the result of Fang Yuan not using all-out effort Gu.

Vertical crash Gu was a movement Gu Fang Yuan bought, its ability was to break through by force.

If there were no obstacles, the straight charging momentum could last for fifty steps before it stopped. If there were obstacles, the momentum would last for less than fifty steps.

This Gu was more suitable for Fang Yuan compared to jumping grass.

Jumping grass's jumping ability came from the Gu worm's strength, while vertical crash Gu's strength came from Fang Yuan's body.

As Fang Yuan becomes stronger, the vertical crash Gu's forceful break through ability would also increase. In the battle with Li Ran, Fang Yuan had used vertical crash Gu in combination with boar phantom; the combination was perfect and inflicted heavy injuries to Li Ran!

Horizontal charge!

Fang Yuan activated a Gu, his whole body immediately charged horizontally like a tyrannical crab, smashing the stone pillars.

This was horizontal charge Gu and was similar to vertical crash Gu, except it charged horizontally.

Fang Yuan had sold jumping grass and bought horizontal charge Gu and vertical crash Gu as his movement Gu.

These two Gu allow the Gu Master to exert force while moving and were extremely suitable for strength path Gu Masters. The movement itself became a means of attack.

"When I reach rank four, I can then fuse these two Gu into charging crash Gu and continue using them."

This was a long term investment which also indirectly saved money.

Next, Fang Yuan alternatively used these two Gu and crashed here and there on the small square, like a wild bull.

This time, he multi-tasked.

Not only did he use horizontal charge Gu or vertical crash Gu alternatively, he also simultaneously used all-out effort Gu.

The stone pillars were sent flying before collapsing fiercely on the ground and producing dull thuds now and then.

"Using boar strength phantom can send five stone pillars flying and knock down eight. Using bear strength phantom can send seven pillars flying and knock down five. Using crocodile strength phantom can send three stone pillars flying and knock down four."

Fang Yuan carefully experienced these subtle differences.

It was clear that boar was suitable for charging and the longer the distance of the charge, better the result. Brown bear possessed formidable strength at first before becoming weaker later. As for the crocodile, it was clearly not suitable method for charging attack.

"Right now, all-out effort Gu can only activate the phantom of one Gu. I can't use boar strength phantom and bear strength phantom at the same time. That is to say, my strength of two boars is somewhat wasteful. If it was changed to some other beast strength, they could strengthen other aspects of attacking."

"Now I have strength of two boars, strength of a bear and strength of a crocodile; this has reached the limit of what my body can bear. It is time to use steel tendon Gu."

Fang Yuan had already bought steel tendon Gu.

Steel tendon and iron bones perfectly complemented each other.

But steel tendon Gu was different from iron bone Gu. The latter was an expendable type Gu while the former needed to be continuously used for a period of time before it could bring qualitative change to Fang Yuan's tendons, turning them into steel tendons.

Fang Yuan called for a servant to clean up the messed up square and returned to his secret room.

He did not want to waste even a second and began using steel tendon Gu to reform his body.

Three days later, fifth inner city's battle stage.

A blue shirt burly man stood in front of Fang Yuan, his breathing was rough and his heart still had lingering fear.

"I only crossed five to six moves with this kid and suffered heavy injuries. The all-out effort Gu really can't be stopped... every move can bring out a beast phantom. Truly terrifying!"

This blue shirt burly man stared tightly at Fang Yuan, barely raising his spirits.

"I can't lose! As long as I defeat him, I can get all-out effort Gu as per the battle stage's rules. With this Gu, I can also cultivate strength path!"

As the blue shirt burly man thought of this, he gave a fierce growl and pounced upon Fang Yuan.

Water prison Gu!

He opened his mouth wide and spit out a blue ball of water. The water ball rapidly expanded and trapped Fang Yuan inside it.

Fang Yuan coldly snorted and casually punched inside the water.

Boar strength phantom!

The water ball shook thrice before becoming deformed but did not collapse.

"It is no use. To deal with you, I purposely took a high interest loan and bought this rank three water prison Gu." The blue shirt burly man proudly laughed.

Fang Yuan's gaze turned cold and without any panic, punched again.

Bear strength phantom!

The water ball fiercely shook, deforming intensely and almost collapsed, but still returned to its original state in the end.

"Beast strength is hard, the flow of water is soft. Use softness to subdue hardness, you can't break it." The blue shirt burly man took a deep breath and relaxed his mind.

But right at this time.

Fang Yuan raised his leg and kicked to the side. Crocodile strength phantom!

Crocodile strength was different from boar and brown bear; it was an amphibious creature and was very adept at the water element.

Bang!

The water prison was smashed into pieces.

"What?!" The blue shirt burly man was pale with fright.

Vertical crash Gu!

Thump.

The blue shirt burly man was sent flying by Fang Yuan, blood spurted out of his mouth in large amounts and he only landed on the ground after flying for twenty full steps.

He struggled violently to get up, but he fell down again before he could stand even a little.

There were no movements anymore.

He was dead.

Chapter 289: Can’t stop me

"Even Wang Han lost and died in the battle stage."

"This lad is too ruthless, he does not know how to show mercy!"

"The all-out effort Gu is strong indeed..."

Outside the stage, spectators discussed.

Fang Yuan kicked and destroyed the water prison, charging over and killing the blue shirt man from the impact, causing the battle to end.

The blue shirt man's chest was completely caved in, as his white ribs were exposed, soon, blood dyed the battle stage's field red.

The hosting Gu Master walked onto the stage and declared Fang Yuan's victory.

The blue shirt man's corpse was left lying there, no one was dealing it with at the moment.

From the hosting Gu Master, Fang Yuan took back the vine information Gu, and looked into the Gu, he had seventeen victories now, with zero losses.

After all, this was the fifth inner city battle stage, it was mostly made up of rank two Gu Masters, Fang Yuan had the cultivation advantage plus the all-out effort Gu, after his first few matches, in the subsequent battles, he only took a few moves to win.

These victories earned him a large number of primeval stones.

Winning in the battle stage, you not only get your opponent's Gu worms, you can also receive primeval stones as a reward from the battle stage.

The more the spectators, the more primeval stones you earn.

"Li Ran, this is fifty thousand primeval stones, I'm passing this to you in public in case you try to defame me in the future." Under everyone's watchful gaze, Fang Yuan took out a bag of primeval stones.

Li Ran walked out from the crowd, receiving the primeval stones with a smiling face as numerous envious people watched.

"Fang Zheng, you truly kept your word. First, you passed me eighty thousand, and now fifty thousand, a total of a hundred and thirty thousand primeval stones already." He cupped his fists, saying that as he left.

The crowd went wild.

"This Fang Zheng, first he gave eighty thousand, next fifty thousand, where did he get all those stones?" Some did not understand.

"It is not strange, during these two weeks, he got consecutive victories in the battle stage, the fame of the all-out effort Gu attracted many spectators. Every match earns him thousands of primeval stones. After a few battles, he would have several tens of thousands." Someone replied in a sour tone.

"Not just that, this lad is ruthless, killing his opponent almost every match. Very few people can survive a match with him, thus he can get around two to three Gu worms per battle. After selling them, that is another sum of primeval stones." Someone snorted, revealing Fang Yuan's brutal acts.

"This Fang Zheng is too much, he is advancing by stepping on our corpses." Someone was furious.

Someone sighed: "We are all demonic Gu Masters, why is there a need to kill each other? Sigh..."

Someone exclaimed: "But to speak the truth, this Fang Zheng has his merits. Actually passing Li Ran two hundred thousand primeval stones as promised. To speak the truth, if I was in that position..."

Once he said so, the crowd became silent.

But someone quickly retorted: "He hasn't finished paying the two hundred thousand primeval stones. We can talk again after he pays the full sum."

Looking at fang Yuan leaving, someone laughed coldly among the crowd: "His good days are coming to an end. In five days' time, it would be the date where Li Hao forcefully challenges him."

"Li Hao? Didn't he ascend to fourth inner city already?"

"Just a little bit to go, hmph, I can't wait to watch this battle!"

"Hehe, this lad is too arrogant, let Li Hao teach him a lesson."

Swish swish swish...

In the aperture, primeval essence ebbed and flowed, waves appearing on surface of the light silver primeval sea.

Steel tendon Gu swam in the sea, absorbing primeval essence as it emitted a black light.

It was shaped like an earthworm, but had a black body and the surface was not as soft as an earthworm, instead, there was an oily and shiny exoskeleton.

It emitted an eerie light, penetrating the aperture and shining on every part of Fang Yuan's body.

Under the influence of the eerie light, Fang Yuan's muscles and tendons were covered in an oily dark color, causing them to become more firm and strong.

After half a day, Fang Yuan stopped using the steel tendon Gu.

He had sweated a lot, his breathing was rough, and his head felt slightly dizzy.

The feeling of using the steel tendon Gu was not comfortable, it gave a sort of numb, painful and itchy feeling, invading his nerves, it put the endurance of the Gu Master to test.

An ordinary Gu Master, when using the steel tendon Gu, it would take half a year to complete.

But in Fang Yuan's plans, he condensed the time to a month.

This means, the amount of time Fang Yuan uses on the steel tendon Gu a day is six times of an ordinary person, it was a strict test of his willpower and endurance.

"I have to treasure every minute and second, to cultivate! Increasing my strength as fast as possible!"

"I need primeval stones, the battle stage is the best way to earn. But if I lose a match, I would lose the all-out effort Gu. I might be able to use the purple thorn token to stop them, but I would have to pay a huge price in other aspects!"

"I cannot lose at all! I am like a battle horse charging rapidly now, as my battle strength rises. But if I lose one match, it would be game over. My rapid growth would experience a huge setback."

"Shang clan city is merely a starting point, how can I fall here? In this life, I have to become a Gu Immortal, I have to breakthrough to rank seven, eight, and nine. I want to ascend to the peak, and see the view that I did not manage to in my previous life. Legend says that beyond rank nine, it is the supreme realm of immortality! It is easy to have a long life, but to be an immortal, no one has ever managed to do it."

"The highest point for a lifeform is to reach immortality, their greatest desire is immortality. What is the point of wealth, it is merely a hoarding addiction. What men and women, it is just primal instincts. What reputation, it is just bullshit people spew about you, carrying the stench of depravity."

"Wealth, beauty, reputation, status, people who pursue all these are short-sighted. Back on Earth, there was no choice, as everyone was going to die eventually, thus they can only pursue these or life would be meaningless. But in this world, where primeval essence is rich, why would we not pursue immortality given the possibility?"

"For the sake of immortality, wealth, beauty, reputation, status, I can make use of all of them, and I can also discard them as easily! For immortality, fear cannot stop me, I will charge forward relentlessly! For immortality, laziness will not stop me, I will never slack even for a moment! For immortality, pain cannot stop me, gods and demons cannot stop me, even heaven and earth cannot stop me!"

As he affirmed his belief, Fang Yuan's black eerie eyes seemed to burn with a scarlet red demonic blaze.

After his rest was over, he activated the steel tendon Gu again without hesitation.

The dark eerie light shone on his body, even penetrating his skin.

In the silent secret room, his expression was extremely cold, like a statue made of steel, giving off the feeling of an everlasting toughness.

What numbness, pain or itching, they were merely tiny ripples in his heart.

Others might not be able to stand it, but that does not mean Fang Yuan cannot!

If stubbornness is demonic, then Fang Yuan is a demon among demons.

No matter how many times he dies, it would not influence his resolve! No matter what setbacks he faces, they would only be firewood that allows the demonic ambitions in his heart to burn even more brightly.

...

Bam!

The loud sound reverberated in the battle stage.

Rocks and soil flew, as a blast of air swept the battlefield, although his opponent escaped the fatal blow, he was still pushed away by the air current and retreated over ten steps.

The dust cloud dispersed, and the culprit behind this attack revealed its true form.

This was a giant toad!

It was larger than a mammoth, having two eyes as large as stone mills. Its body was grey and had a huge stomach and strong limbs. There was green moss on its skin, and even some tiny rocks on the surface.

What gathered the most attention, was its back.

Its back was extremely swollen, like it was carrying a small hill!

This hill was the real deal, completely made of mountain rocks, about ten and a half feet high. It had many layers and folds, like it was shaved by swords and axes. Grass and weed grew on the mountain rocks, and there were even two or three trees.

This was the rank three Gu, named mountain back toad. It was heavy and cumbersome, its signature move was to leap up, and crash down like a mountain.

Earlier, it had displayed this move, and caused an earthquake to strike the battle stage, many spectators lost their balance and many things toppled.

"This attack is too strong, really too strong!"

"What a grand sight, even a spectator would feel his heart thumping."

"The mountain back toad is like a castle, attack and defense all in one. The only weakness is a lack of speed, but its owner perfectly covered up this weakness!"

Everyone discussed as they looked at this mountain back toad, but quickly shifted their gaze to a Gu Master.

This Gu Master wore a flowery robe, was thin, and had a delicate appearance.

Although he was a man, he had makeup and powder on his face, as he stood at one end of the battle stage, playing with his long fingernails.

His name is Li Hao, rank three cultivation with a rich combat experience. He was especially proficient in dealing with strength path Gu Masters.

"Just you alone, you want to compete with me? Hehe, admit defeat, don't waste my time." Li Hao stared at his fingernails, not even giving his opponent a glance.

"Scoundrel, looking down on me! Take this!" His opponent was also someone commonly seen in the battle stage, being humiliated in public like this, his face contorted with anger as he gritted his teeth and pounced on Li Hao.

Li Hao looked at him silently. As the opponent rapidly approached, Li Hao laughed coldly: "You have not learnt your lesson, was it not enough? Then, I'll let you experience it again."

Position swap Gu!

Li Hao's gaze gave off a strange light as he looked at his mountain back toad.

In a breath's time, he vanished on the spot, appearing at the mountain back toad's location.

At the same time, the mountain back toad appeared at his former location.

Using the position swap Gu, he swapped places with the mountain back Gu.

His opponent was rushing towards Li Hao, but in a split second, the mountain back toad appeared before him.

Bam!

Mountain back toad jumped, and like a flying mountain, it sent the opponent flying.

The battle ended just as expected!

"Mountain back toad with position swap Gu, such a battle strategy is unbeatable."

"That's right, the position swap Gu can not only change the mountain back toad's location, it can also swap with the opponent. This completely eliminates the mountain back toad's weakness of low movement speed."

"After this battle, Li Hao has twenty-nine net victories. Just one more, and he can rise to fourth inner city."

"Hurry and leave, no one can stop him here anymore."

"Who is his final opponent? Eh, it is that super lucky guy who got the legendary Gu."

Chapter 290: Fang Yuan vs Li Hao (1)

In the blink of an eye, five days passed.

Fang Yuan had another battle scheduled.

"Your opponent today has quite the background." Wei Yang walked towards Fang Yuan, instructing him to be careful.

Fang Yuan nodded.

He had never fought without adequate preparations, after being in an alliance with Li Ran, he obtained a lot of valuable information about the battle stage participants.

Li Ran was a spy, undercover for eight years, his job was to gather information anyway. His understanding of the battle stage surpasses even Wei Yang.

"Li Hao was also once a strength cultivator, rising to fourth inner city. He once had a glorious past, but encountered a bottleneck. In terms of strength cultivators, they were strong at the start, but start to show weakness in the middle stage, stuck there with no way to progress further. Li Hao was greatly traumatised, giving up on the strength path and changing to a support style."

"Well, it was due to him finally getting lucky, choosing a good rock in the gambling den and obtaining the rare position swap Gu. With his rich experience, he immediately sold all the Gu he had and purchased a mountain back toad in the auction house."

"Next, he relied on the cooperation between these two Gu and won all the matches he participated in. Relying on the Gu and primeval stones he won, he slowly accumulated his assets and gathered a new set of Gu worms. He is forcefully challenging you because he wants that all-out effort Gu, you have to be careful."

Wei Yang said, as he patted Fang Yuan's shoulders and blended into the crowd.

Fang Yuan looked deeply at Wei Yang, as he walked onto the arena.

Whenever there was an important battle, Wei Yang would come and watch. Fang Yuan understood he was mere to act as mental support for Fang Yuan. One reason was because Shang clan wanted to recruit him, but more likely...

It was because he treated Fang Yuan as a real brother!

Relationships between people is this weird.

Some people interact for tens of years without getting closer. Some people just talk once and become close friends.

Fang Yuan understood Wei Yang's emotions. He could see his former shadow in Fang Yuan. This strong sense of acknowledgement, as well as Fang Yuan's candid nature, made him treat Fang Yuan as a close friend.

"Wei Yang..." Fang Yuan thought, as he walked to the center of the arena.

The terrain of this arena is a large sized swamp. Black rotten mud, giving off a putrid smell, and there were even puddles everywhere.

Li Hao had not arrived yet.

Outside the battle stage, large number of spectators were gathered.

This was the most people Fang Yuan had seen at any of his battles. Standing on the arena, he looked around to see people all around him.

Everyone conversed at the same time, causing the entire battle stage to be full of noise and chattering.

"This Fang Zheng is in trouble today!"

"He had been so arrogant these days, he should be taught a lesson."

"Youngsters think too highly of themselves, he really thinks one all-out effort Gu makes him invincible!"

"Li Hao is here." Someone shouted.

The crowd went silent, before going wild again, their voices bursting through the roof.

At the entrance, Li Hao appeared.

"Lord Li Hao, we're all counting on you!"

"May you win your thirtieth match and advance to fourth inner city."

Among the crowd, many people shouted, some screamed.

Compared to Fang Yuan, they thought more highly of Li Hao. When Fang Yuan first came, he was extremely arrogant, killing many opponents, ruthless and cruel. He had the purple thorn token, causing everyone to be jealous of his good luck.

In contrast, Li Hao was a veteran in the battle stage. He had first walked on the strength path, then fell from fourth inner city. He had risen from the lowest part of his life, signifying the spirit of 'never give up' in the battle stage, it would ignite everyone's passion.

Li Hao carried a light smile as he walked onto the stage.

He was thin, wearing a flowery robe and makeup, as he walked casually towards Fang Yuan.

But around sixty steps away, he stopped, not advancing further.

Fang Yuan, in his previous few fights, used the vertical crash Gu to assault his opponents, sending them flying, easily winning in one strike. Li Hao was a veteran in the battle stage, he obviously made preparations for that.

The vertical crash Gu's effective range was fifty steps, he was safe at the sixtieth border.

"Strength cultivator, hehe..." He gave Fang Yuan a sweeping glance, filled with disdain: "Young man, unfortunately, your consecutive victory ends here. Do you know, looking at you now, it is just like me in the past. There is no future in the strength path, so what if you have the all-out effort Gu? Thank me, after I defeat you today, you will know it is for your own good, letting you understand the insufficiency of the strength path."

He started lecturing Fang Yuan with his status as a senior.

"You sure talk a lot, can you shut up?" Fang Yuan folded his arms, with a plain expression.

"You..." Li Hao's face flushed with fury, as his laughter was filled with animosity: "Hehehe, young man, you do not respect your elders, you are bound to suffer."

At this time, with the sound of the bell, the hosting Gu Master announced the start of the battle.

Vertical crash Gu!

Fang Yuan took a big stride, charging forward.

Pew!

The soil under his feet danced like waves, splashing high up on his left and right.

"Wow, what a grand sight." Li Hao laughed lightly.

He knew very clearly the vertical crash Gu could only charge fifty steps ahead. Every time it is used, there is a cooldown period of five breaths.

He was sixty steps away, it might seem dangerous, but he was completely safe.

This terrain was advantage to him. A muddy terrain was unlike a rough and flat surface, it was not suited for charging type attacks.

As expected, Fang Yuan charged forty-five steps and stopped.

But soon after, Fang Yuan turned his body to one side, facing Li Hao with his side view.

Horizontal charge Gu!

The soil and mud were split apart as the phantom image of a wild boar appeared, with a charging action, its speed raised sharply, wild and tough. In the blink of an eye, Fang Yuan reached Li Hao.

If he was hit, he would definitely vomit blood and break a few bones.

Li Hao went pale, at the crucial moment, he activated his vital Gu.

Position swap!

In an instant, he swapped with Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was facing Li Hao as he charged, but now, Li Hao was behind him as he charged ahead, getting further away from Li Hao.

"I was careless!" In just this moment, Li Hao's forehead was pouring with sweat.

He did not think that Fang Yuan would be much of a threat to him. After knowing Fang Yuan had the vertical crash Gu and horizontal charge Gu, he did not think much about it, but that almost caused him to be severely injured.

At the crucial moment, his years of experience saved him.

Compared to defending, why not dodge.

One position swap, and Fang Yuan missed.

No matter how great your strength, as long as you hit air, you cannot cause damage, it is pointless.

"This lad has the all-out effort Gu, every move of his strikes hard. I sold my strength Gu and got rid of the beast strength in my body, I cannot compete with him head on."

Li Hao calmed his nerves, and retreated.

He used his movement Gu, his body turning light as the wind, floating backwards, rapidly pulling distance from Fang Yuan.

At the same time, he raised his finger and pointed at the sky, as a green light shot out from his aperture, towards the sky.

It was a jade green light, stopping in mid air, then exploded.

Under the glaring light, the body of the mountain back toad showed itself, descending.

There was a black shadow on the ground, engulfing Fang Yuan, and got larger over time.

Five breaths had long passed, Fang Yuan looked at Li Hao, and activated the vertical crash Gu, charging over.

He raised his speed rapidly, quickly getting out of the shadow's range.

THe moment he got out, the mountain back toad landed.

Bam!

A loud bang, and the entire battle stage trembled, as black mud and soil flew into the air like tidal waves.

The waves splashed to the edge of the arena, causing the spectators to dodge instinctively, but a huge dark red shield protected them.

The battle stage obviously had defensive Gu to protect the audiences.

"It appeared, Lord Li Hao's mountain back toad!" Seeing this, someone screamed in excitement.

"Even if Fang Zheng charges at Li Hao, it is pointless. Li hao only needs to use the position swap Gu, and easily change position with the mountain back toad... hehehe."

But Fang Yuan did not charge at Li Hao.

He stopped in his tracks.

The black mud splashed on him like a wave, but were repelled by the canopy Gu's white armor.

Horizontal charge Gu.

After the waves subsided, he tilted his body away from the mountain back toad, and charged horizontally towards it.

Howl!

The roar of a bear was heard, as a brown bear phantom appeared, howling at the sky, giving off its wild aura.

Bam!

Fang Yuan slammed on the mountain back toad's body, causing the toad to sway.

But that was it.

The mountain back toad's unique hill was made of mountain rocks that have great density. It was one of the heaviest rank three Gu.

Once its four legs stood on the ground, it was like an unmovable mountain, causing everyone to gasp at its firmness.

But Fang Yuan did not care, he raised both arms and smashed on it like a hammer.

Howl!

Above his head, the phantoms of boar, brown bear, and crocodile appeared one after another.

His punches tore through the winds as he attacked without restraint. Hitting on the mountain back toad, thunderous sounds went off like firecrackers.

Such a fierce attack sent the spectators into deep fear, as cold sweat ran down their back.

"If I was the target, I would not have a complete corpse by now!"

"The all-out effort Gu is too strong, really too strong."

"But Fang Zheng's brain is fried, not attacking Li Hao but instead, punching that mountain."

...

The defense of the mountain back toad was impressive, even with Fang Yuan's ferocious attacks, it did not move, causing people to feel helpless against it.

But Fang Yuan had a cold expression, the more he attacked, the fiercer it got, like this toad had a great feud with him.

Li Hao's expression changed.

No matter how tough the mountain back toad was, it had its limits, it could not endure this rain of punches anymore.

Gua gua gua...

The mountain back toad started shouting, as the pain was exceeding its limits.

"This cannot go on!" Li Hao's heart jumped, as he willed and rode on the mountain back toad.

Mountain back toad started to counter attack, stepping on the mud and charging at Fang Yuan.

With its weight, if Fang Yuan took this head on, he would definitely be sent flying.

Horizontal charge Gu.

His eyes shone brightly, moving away at the last moment, dodging the mountain back toad's attack.

Getting around the toad's body, and hitting again!

Chapter 291: Fang Yuan vs Li Hao (2)

Roar!

The beast phantom appeared with a flash and gave a loud roar; the mountain back toad croaked in pain and suddenly slammed towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan snorted and dodged.

Mountain back toad carried a small hill on its back; it was very heavy and had a slow speed, so Fang Yuan could easily dodge it.

Horizontal charge Gu and vertical crash Gu were used in succession; mountain back toad repeatedly tried to attack Fang Yuan but could not even touch his clothes.

The audience was watching the match with stupefied expressions.

The mountain back toad was a lofty and immovable image in everyone's minds, but right now, it was crying out from Fang Yuan's attacks.

"This kid is actually so violent!" Li Hao was starting to get worried. He gritted his teeth and prompted the mountain back toad to jump.

"You brat, I am going to smash you into minced meat!" Li Hao cracked a sneer; his mind full of killing intent.

However, mountain back toad's shadow was not over Fang Yuan.

Instead, it was over Li Hao.

Mountain back toad's enormous body began to fall down and smash heavily on Li Hao.

Most of the audience were so stupefied that they could not react in time. Only Wei Yang and a few others' eyes shone as they realized Li Hao's battle tactic.

Just using mountain back toad to smash Fang Yuan was likely to fail easily.

Fang Yuan possessed horizontal charge Gu and vertical crash Gu; he could completely dodge the attack.

However, the mountain back toad was landing on Li Hao and Li Hao could use position swap Gu to change his position with Fang Yuan. As long as he grasped the proper timing, he could prevent Fang Yuan from reacting in time and be crushed by the mountain back toad.

With a weight like that of mountain back toad, even if Fang Yuan was not squashed to death, he would absolutely suffer heavy injuries.

However, the moment mountain back toad jumped in the air, Fang Yuan immediately charged towards Li Hao!

By using horizontal charge Gu and vertical crash Gu, he soon reached Li Hao.

"Accursed brat, he actually saw through my plan!" Li Hao was very annoyed right now.

There was still some distance between Fang Yuan and him now, but if he used position swap Gu now, Fang Yuan would have enough time to dodge mountain back toad's attack.

But if he did not use it now and Fang Yuan stuck close to him, even if he used position swap Gu to change positions, it would be too late to escape and he would be crushed to death along with Fang Yuan by the mountain back toad.

Helplessly, Li Hao activated position swap Gu and changed position with Fang Yuan.

Bam!

The mountain back toad landed on the ground, Fang Yuan, as expected, used horizontal charge to dodge.

He was always paying attention to the cooldown period of horizontal charge Gu and vertical crash Gu. There were three breaths of time interval between them. Taking into account the time taken to charge fifty steps, he would always have a movement Gu to use.

These small details often determined success or failure.

Fang Yuan accumulated a rich combat experience in his previous life, allowing him to have no flaws.

He again charged towards mountain back toad, punching and kicking with an all-out offensive. Beast phantoms also appeared one after another, making his attacks extremely fierce.

Stones flew about, mountain back toad got into a dangerous situation again and began croaking.

The audiences who were hooting before fell silent.

Many watched this scene, startled and their jaws opened wide.

All-out effort Gu became so powerful and tyrannical in Fang Yuan's hands, even mountain back toad could only turn into a punching bag and fall into a vulnerable position!

One side was like wildfire, extremely intense; but at Li Hao's side, it was quiet and still.

Li Hao had never expected Fang Yuan to persevere in attacking the mountain back toad so relentlessly.

His previous opponents had all ignored mountain back toad and tried attacking Li Hao. If Li Hao was defeated, there was no need to worry about mountain back toad.

This was the strategy that smart people used!

But Fang Yuan apparently chose the most stupid target to attack.

He concentrated all his strength on mountain back toad and paid no heed to Li Hao.

Li Hao was given the cold-shoulder, he felt like he had become a spectator who was not related to the situation; the situation was truly embarrassing!

Beast phantoms continually flashed and converged in the air. Fang Yuan moved around mountain back toad and attacked fiercely.

Mountain back toad's enormous and mighty physique now looked so clumsy.

"Not good, mountain back toad is coughing out blood!" Li Hao who was watching the scene from afar felt his body go cold.

Position swap Gu!

Strange lights flashed in his eyes as he captured Fang Yuan's image.

The next instant, Fang Yuan's field of view had changed greatly, he was moved far away by Li Hao in a split second.

In contrast, Li Hao took Fang Yuan's position and was standing beside mountain back toad.

He placed his palms on mountain back toad and started healing it.

He was inwardly startled by the injuries on mountain back toad.

He had fought so many matches on the battle stage, but had never seen such serious injuries.

"Am I going to lose this match? Losing to such a young junior? No, impossible!" The intense premonition of defeat rose for the first time in Li Hao's heart.

Fang Yuan sneered and charged again.

How could he allow Li Hao to heal mountain back toad so openly in front of his eyes?

Seeing Fang Yuan charging over, Li Hao gritted his teeth, but he could only give up on healing and retreated back.

He waited till Fang Yuan had charged in front of mountain back toad before using position swap Gu.

Like this, he was again standing beside mountain back toad and Fang Yuan was far away.

But Fang Yuan was not worried and still charged over.

Li Hao's healing was repeatedly disrupted while Fang Yuan's attacks also had no effect.

Despite this, Fang Yuan still kept on charging over without giving up.

Several repeated attempts later, it was Li Hao instead who stopped healing; his complexion mixed.

The audience could not make any sense of this.

But there were still some smart people.

"Fang Zheng's repeated attacks appear to be useless but actually Li Hao's primeval essence was greatly consumed."

"That's right. Although position swap Gu is mystical, it has its flaws and huge primeval essence consumption is one."

"The further the distance and stronger the target, the more primeval essence Li Hao needs to expend to activate position swap Gu."

"Fang Zheng possesses the strength of two boars, a crocodile and a bear; the primeval essence consumption of Li Hao to use position swap Gu is definitely a lot. Moreover, he still wanted to heal mountain back toad, even a rank three's primeval essence can't support such intense usage."

Li Hao also realized this and thus stopped his healing attempt.

He did not have much primeval essence left now.

If it were his previous opponents, he could still continue with his rank three white silver primeval essence. But his opponent now, Fang Yuan was also a rank three Gu master and had already established superiority in terms of primeval essence.

Looking at Fang Yuan charging over again, Li Hao hesitated but had no choice but to go ahead.

Fang Yuan clenched his fists and immediately abandoned the mountain back toad, attacking towards Li Hao.

Bang bang bang.

His fists broke the air, the momentum and fierceness they contained were incomparable, like tides striking the cliff.

Several moves later, Li Hao could not endure it anymore!

Although he had other Gu, his true core was the mountain back toad and position swap Gu.

In order to decrease the primeval essence consumption of position swap Gu, he had completely removed the beast phantoms hidden in his body.

Fang Yuan's offensive was extremely fierce like the howling storm, making Li Hao have difficulty breathing.

Li Hao relied on his previous foundation of a strength cultivator to forcefully withstand few moves before he had no choice but use position swap Gu to change places with mountain back toad.

Fang Yuan did not pursue Li Hao but began attacking mountain back toad.

Phantoms of boar, brown bear and crocodile flashed one after another.

Rocks flew about and mountain back toad spurted out large mouthful of blood, counterattacking in a frenzy.

But Fang Yuan used horizontal charge and vertical crash Gu alternatively; as such, mountain back toad's counterattacks looked really clumsy.

"How could it be like this...."

"Even Lord Li Hao had to fight personally and share the burden with mountain back toad."

"Fang Zheng's attacks are terrifyingly fierce, suppressing both Li Hao and mountain back toad."

The match's progress was beyond most of the audience's expectation. Every since Li Hao abandoned strength path and changed into support path, they had never seen him fall into such a predicament.

Li Hao's battle tactics were pretty good. The combination of position swap Gu and mountain back toad was brilliant.

Even Fang Yuan could not crack this battle tactic.

However...

He did not need to crack it!

He had never thought of cracking it, just swinging his arms, and continuing his all-out strategy. No matter who appears in front of me, I will beat them!

This seems like a foolish move, but actually concealed great wisdom in it.

Savagery and tyrannical momentum was unleashed like this.

"This is a good method." Some people's eyes brightened, "If I were to fight Li Hao in the future, I need to be like Fang Zheng; disregarding everything else and attacking mountain back toad."

As soon as these words came out, the person's words was denied and mocked by others beside him.

"Nonsense! You want to imitate him, is your brain okay? Fang Zheng can do this because he is a strength cultivator and his primeval essence expenditure is low. You are a fire path cultivator, you attacking mountain back toad is exactly what Li Hao would want to see."

Without primeval essence, a Gu Master's battle strength was sure to fall sharply and would be almost equal to a mortal.

In a battle, the side with higher primeval essence was often dominant. And as the gap between primeval essence quantity increased, this dominance increased further.

The Gu Master who thought of imitating Fang Yuan heard this and immediately choked with no way to retort.

Someone patted his head and said as if he had comprehended something: "I suddenly see that strength cultivators have their advantages."

"That's right." Someone sitting nearby immediately replied, "Strength cultivators' attacks draws the strength of their bodies, thus strength Gu Masters have a common advantage in that they have little primeval essence consumption."

"Every cultivation path has its own advantage and disadvantage. Strength path being renowned back in the Antiquity Era was not without reasons."

Everyone looked at the stage again.

Li Hao and mountain back toad were retreating step by step under Fang Yuan's fierce attacks.

All-out effort Gu's primeval essence consumption was very small.

And Fang Yuan's true attacking power came from his several beast phantoms.

But these beast phantoms by themselves did not expend any primeval essence!

This was the most absurd part!

If it were other Gu Masters in Fang Yuan's place, they would have been tired after dozens of rounds, but Fang Yuan's attacks became fiercer the longer he continued.

His momentum continually rose, his fists carried with it the sound of the wind and were extremely tyrannical; the sound they produced were like the roars of ferocious tigers or the growls of giant bears!

From Fang Yuan's performance, the crowd could see the grand and proud demeanour of strength path cultivators from the ancient times!

His heartbeat pulsed rapidly and his blood raced; Fang Yuan felt more pleasant the more he fought.

Since rebirth, he had been extremely cautious in his actions which accumulated suppressed feelings in his heart, and now as he punched and kicked fanatically, those feelings were all let out.

The gloominess in his heart was swept clean.

No doubt, obtaining all-out effort Gu was a turning point in Fang Yuan's life.

Before this, he had to rush about busily, always in danger, not even able to fill his stomach properly. Encountering even a slightly larger problem would require him to think and ponder extensively.

But after obtaining all-out effort Gu, he finally had the qualification to be proud and could use his fists to resolve many things.

Like now, he did not need to crack Li Hao's brilliant battle tactic and could just use his fists to sweep across.

Demons was cunning but they were even more tyrannical!

Sweeping the heaven and earth, engulfing the mountains and rivers, blood splashing the world, absolute strength prevails over all schemes!

You are fierce; I am fiercer than you. You are unreasonable; I am more unreasonable than you!

Demon! Demon! Demon!

Kill! Kill! Kill!

Fang Yuan fought to his heart's content, his emotions surging intensely inside him; finally, he could bear it no longer and the emotions poured out like a torrent.

"Because hardships strengthen resolve, the strong-minded will not be lured by worldly affairs. Today I step on grass; later I shall step on mountains and rivers!"

From today, I will walk on the path of supremacy!

Sweep the earth and laugh at the world.

Tread the green mountains; step on the blue seas; bind the blue dragon; assault the sky!

Bath in difficulties and sharpen the demonic soul; lift the flag and sing in triumph; defy heaven, defy fate, defy the universe!

Bam!

A punch ruthlessly struck the mountain back toad, the small hill on its back collapsed, blood flowed out of its body as it was beaten to death by Fang Yuan!

Horizontal charge, vertical crash!

Li Hao was sent flying for dozen of steps before he fell down on the ground.

Plop, he fell on the mud, no longer moving.

The black mud mixed with dark red blood contaminated his flowery robe.

He paid with his life for his contempt.

The battle ended abruptly. Fang Yuan proudly stood on the spot; his masculine, ferocious aura pervaded the scene.

His declaration still echoed in the battle stage.

Other than that, it was a scene of silence, no one spoke!

Chapter 292: Law Fragment, Traces of Great Dao

In the secret room, Fang Yuan sat on the cushion, his eyes shut tightly.

Light silver primeval essence continued to pour into the self-reliance Gu.

Self-reliance Gu was diving in the primeval sea in Fang Yuan's aperture.

It was shaped like a cockroach, a dark-brown colored flat body. There were feelers on its head, and wings on its back.

This was the rank three healing Gu that Fang Yuan purchased for a huge amount of primeval stones.

Self-reliance Gu could be said to be the best Gu for strength cultivating Gu Masters.

The greater the physical strength of the Gu Master, the better the effect of the self-reliance Gu's healing. In contrast, the weaker the Gu Master, the weaker the healing effect.

Self-reliance, relying on oneself, it meant obtaining the ability to regenerate and heal using one's own strength.

Fang Yuan had the strength of two boars, one bear and a crocodile, now that he used the self-reliance Gu, the healing effect was on par with the flesh-bone Gu. This was not its limit yet, when Fang Yuan gains new strength from more Gu, its effect would surpass the flesh-bone Gu, continually improving.

But the self-reliance Gu has its weaknesses.

It could not heal others, only the Gu Master himself.

This greatly limited its use.

Moreover, it was expensive, as a rare Gu, it costs forty-five thousand primeval stones! Even more expensive than the sword shadow Gu. Thus, although there were many strength path Gu Masters, few could afford it.

Different from ancient times, strength path Gu Masters now were of the lowest social class, holding jobs that involve physical work. There were many low rank ones, few high rank ones, and even less outstanding ones. Barely any stood at the peak, in the entire southern border, only Empress Wu Ji was a successful story. But even she relied on the ancient strength path inheritance to do so.

This was an era where strength path declined.

Now, Fang Yuan was using the self-reliance Gu to recover his injuries.

In the battle with Li Hao, he had gotten injured.

The biggest culprit was not Li Hao, not the mountain back toad, but Fang Yuan himself.

As he attacked with such a ferocious force, and for such a long time, it caused his muscles and tendons to be overworked, and some of them tore, even the canopy Gu was in bad shape, needing time to recover.

Thankfully, he had used the iron bones Gu before, thus there was no problems with his bones. If not, even his bones would have broke.

Normally, when people exerted too much strength, they would pull a muscle. If a cannon is fired too many times, it would be easy to jam up.

Any kind of strength needed a foundation to contain it. On this aspect, strength path Gu Masters follow the same rule.

Fang Yuan had the canopy Gu and iron bones, but his strength was too great, unleashing such a flurry of attacks, even his muscles could not take it, there was great stress on his organs, blood etc.

After this battle, there were lots of hidden injuries in his body.

Even his sweat had blood traces.

"Since I started using the self-reliance Gu to heal, this is the tenth hour already. Mostly because of the steel tendon Gu, it is making my healing difficult." Fang Yuan had an understanding of his situation.

Before this, he had been using the steel tendon Gu to transform and train his body. It caused the tendons in his muscles to gain a layer of black color, shining with a metallic glow, becoming tougher.

Right now, his tendons were either pulled or torn, to reconnect and heal them, it would be much harder than an ordinary person's muscles and tendons.

Why is that so?

Ordinary people might not know why, only treating this as a natural phenomenon. But Fang Yuan knew clearly, he had been a Gu Immortal after all, he knew these involved the natural laws of heaven and earth.

Man is the spirit of all beings, Gu is the essence of heaven and earth.

Whether the Gu worm's body is large or small, it would contain a law fragment of the Great Dao.

Steel tendon Gu's effect is to reinforce the tendons in the Gu Master's body until they are tough as steel. This caused Fang Yuan's tendons to contain the corresponding power of the natural law, the traces of Great Dao.

For the self-reliance Gu to heal, it not only has to recover the body's tendons, but also has to overcome and overwrite this layer of natural law.

But thankfully, this law did not clash with the healing law. Otherwise, not only would Fang Yuan not be healed, he would be damaged instead.

Similarly, the brown bear innate strength Gu, black and white boar Gu, and crocodile strength Gu were the same.

They contained the Great Dao law fragments regarding "physical strength", when their strength lurk in Fang Yuan's body, they form into beast phantoms and conceal themselves. Only after he unleashes their true power could they be seen by the naked eye.

The so called beast phantom, its essence was the Dao mark of "physical strength"— a trace of Great Dao in heaven and earth.

Take the poison vow Gu as another example.

It contained the law of restriction, it stays in a Gu Master's body to restrict them.

This Dao mark is normally not seen, but under the effect of the eating one's words Gu, it will be forced to appear, and then exterminated.

The law contained in the eating one's words Gu were opposite of the poison vow Gu. But the former was slightly stronger, thus it could overwrite the other.

Or taking it further, why did the rainbow light Gu, position swap Gu, require Gu Masters to be free of strength modifications?

It was the same reason.

The law of strength would interfere with the law of light and the law of space. If the Dao mark of strength is too strong, it would cause the two Gu to fail when utilized.

"Gu Masters use Gu, but the truth is that they use the Great Dao law fragments within the Gu. Gu is the carrier of the fragment, a tool of heaven and earth. When Gu Masters refine Gu, they are fusing laws, and forming laws. Nurturing Gu, using Gu and refining Gu... Gu cultivation is not a small Dao, but a true Great Dao. In cultivating, Gu Masters learn about nature, and learn about heaven and earth. This is why the hope for immortality, and becoming an everlasting existence still remain."

Fang Yuan was clear in his heart.

...

"Because hardships strengthen resolve, the strong-minded will not be lured by worldly affairs. Today I step on grass; later I shall step on mountains and rivers!"

In the study room, Shang Yan Fei muttered, thinking about the poem Fang Yuan recited, showing interest on his face.

"Because of difficulties, one gain aspirations and resolve. The allure of the mortal world cannot restrict one's heart. What grand aspirations! Especially that last line, are you treating my Shang clan as grass?"

"Lord clan leader, the way I see it, Fang Zheng was referring to his opponent Li Hao, being too weak for him." Wei Yang cupped his fists and said.

Shang Yan Fei shook his head: "It is fine, I am not so narrow minded. But it is a pity I missed a good show. Although I did not see it personally, I can imagine the scene of Fang Zheng unleashing his ability, striking with a grand aura."

Shang Yan Fei stood at a high point, he had a broad vision, and naturally was broad minded. Towards Fang Yuan's aspirations, he could understand, and appreciate it.

Reminded by Shang Yan Fei, Wei Yang recalled the scene of the battle, and exclaimed: "That is indeed so. The battlefield back then, Fang Zheng was extremely ferocious, stunning the spectators, everyone was dominated by his aura and no one said a word!"

Shang Yan Fei got up from his seat, strolling slowly to the window: "Armies are easily built, but generals are hard to come by. A pity this general is too arrogant, not even placing Shang clan in his eyes. But, he had gone through tough times, managed to survive, and gained much from it, as his cultivation rose rapidly. This caused his nature to develop in that direction."

"Lord clan leader's analysis is spot on. Young men would definitely have such ambitions, being lawless and fearless." Wei Yang lowered his head, adding on.

Shang Yan Fei looked outside the window, squinting.

Fang Yuan equated Shang clan city to grass, this was an overwhelming aspiration, he was definitely someone with great ambition. But Shang Yan Fei himself did not mind that.

He was a man standing at the peak, on the top of the whole southern border, he could definitely accept people with ambitions. Furthermore, Shang clan city would not truly become grass just because someone said so.

What he minded was the first sentence.

Because hardships strengthen resolve, the strong-minded will not be lured by worldly affairs...

In this world, there were lots of people with great ambitions but no ability, while people with aspirations and talent were few, one in a million. Those who not only had talent and aspirations, but also a firm will, were almost non-existent!

Aspiration and talent were not scary, but if they had an indomitable will and determination, that would cause worry.

Such a person, in history, he would either be called a hero, a villain, or a conqueror.

Such people, can change history, and create history!

Such a person, how would he submit to others? How would he allow himself to be used by Shang clan? If he could not be used, and this person walks the demonic path, he would definitely leave his mark in this world, causing storms and disasters in his life. This was not something the righteous path wants to see...

Thinking so, Shang Yan Fei suddenly said: "I heard, Fang Zheng snatched Li Ran's opportunity, thus he compensated him two hundred thousand primeval stones to repay the favor. How much does he still owe?"

Wei Yang replied: "He already paid a hundred and thirty thousand, only seventy thousand remain. But it should be repaid soon."

Hearing this, Shang Yan Fei's worry eased.

He nodded: "That's true. Someone with ambition would not mind the small details, so what if it is two hundred thousand primeval stones. Hehehe."

Thinking of how Fang Yuan saved Shang Xin Ci, Shang Yan Fei laughed.

He was really interesting, doing things with his own principles, repaying kindness and taking revenge for hatred. But he does not have righteous morals nor any restraints, such a nature was dangerous, but there was still hope of recruiting and controlling him.

Right now he was at the peak of his fame, there was little hope of recruiting him, they had to wait.

After he faces hardship from reality, they will use kindness to move him, and recruit him under Shang Xin Ci's wing. With such a helper, Shang Yan Fei would feel assured about her safety.

"Nevermind, Fang Zheng, let me see how far you can go..." Shang Yan Fei thought in his heart.

He had a sharp foresight, entirely clear of the situation.

After Fang Yuan killed Li Hao, the entire battle zone went into a commotion.

The power of the all-out effort Gu was seen by everyone.

Many started to realize Fang Yuan was a tough opponent. But on the other hand, it made many experts start to notice and desire the all-out effort Gu.

Fang Yuan would have a peaceful time for a while, but soon, those days will end.

According to his nature, he would definitely suffer extensively. At that time, he would know how weak he truly was.

Using the battle stage, he would be suppressed and polished.

As Shang Yan Fei predicted, Fang Yuan's days got easier, as he won without a fight in his subsequent matches.

Who was Li Hao?

He was the number one strongest in fifth inner city battle stage, someone about to rise to fourth inner city.

Even he died by Fang Yuan's iron fist, who could stop him?

But a forceful challenge cannot be cancelled, those demonic Gu Masters thinking of taking advantage of the situation were forced to enter the arena.

At the start, some minded their reputation and tried to spar with Fang Yuan.

But Fang Yuan heavily injured several people, and after he killed one person, they did not dare to think highly of themselves anymore, once the battle started, they surrendered.

Nineteen, twenty, twenty-one victories...

Fang Yuan went onto the stage no longer to battle, but just to collect primeval stones.

It could be said to be the easiest time of his life.

And during this period, a group of pursuing Bai clan Gu Masters arrived at the foot of Shang clan city.

Chapter 293: Heaven is blind

"We've finally reached Shang clan city." Staring at the mountain of buildings, Bai Feng sighed.

He was a Bai clan elder, when he was young, he roamed the southern border, and had once came to Shang clan city. But this time round, he was already old, the buildings were all unfamiliar to him, and even his goal was to arrest the two demonic Gu Masters.

"Do you guys think those two demonic scoundrels really chose this direction?" Bai Lian sounded worried.

"It should be this direction. We split into a few groups at the place where the footless bird landed, but the other directions were all dead ends. Only this path left behind traces." Tie Dao Ku said.

He was uncertain in his heart.

Although Tie clan was the number one investigator in the southern border, he was an attacking type Gu Master. Moreover, the southern border had many forests and mountains, complex terrain that made it easy to hide oneself and difficult to trace them.

"Maybe the two of them died long ago along the way, becoming food for wild beasts." Someone said optimistically.

There was a huge possibility in this, they had found many traces of skeletons along the way, and all the remains of the caravan assaulted by beast hordes.

"I do hope they are alive!" Bai Zhan Lie gritted his teeth, his grandfather was killed by Fang and Bai, he wanted to kill them with his own hands, taking revenge for that intense hatred in his heart.

"Alright, let's enter the city first. If there are no discoveries, we shall spend some primeval stones to send a letter to clan leader, and see what orders she has for us." Bai Feng took the first step.

The few of them arrived at the city gate looking like travellers on a long journey.

Coincidentally, this gate was the one Fang and Bai had once gone through.

"To enter the city, each person has to pay ten primeval stones." The city guard stopped them from entering.

Bai Feng took out a yellow pear token, waving it.

The guard looked at it, and after inspecting it, said: "Yellow pear token can exempt three people from the fees."

Bai Feng's group of six handed in thirty primeval stones.

"This brother, did you see the two of them entering the city?" Bai Zhan Lie pointed at an arrest warrant on the wall, asking.

This was the arrest warrant for Fang and Bai.

But the surface of this arrest warrant had been covered by another new arrest warrant, almost half of the surface was covered.

This was common.

Once in a while, new arrest warrants would appear.

The city guard's expression changed, howling at Bai Zhan Lie: "What are you saying? A city gate with me guarding, how can there be a demonic Gu Master entering? Do you think I am blind? This is slander, you are slandering a righteous young man from Shang clan!"

Bai Zhan Lie's expression froze.

Clan elder Bai Feng quickly apologised, in Shang clan city, even if he was a Bai clan elder, he had to lower his head.

The city guard saw Bai Feng's rank three cultivation, and did not dare to pursue the matter, only muttering under his breath.

Only until Tie Dao Ku showed an unhappy expression, and displayed his identity: "Enough, shut up. Do you think my Tie clan is unclear of what your Shang clan is like?"

The city guard stopped speaking.

After facing this initial display of authority, Bai clan entered the outer city grimly.

"Let's get some food, we are all tired after these few days of travelling. We need to rest, it will not affect our mission. I know a good restaurant in fifth inner city, it is at the battle zone, I had participated in it back in the day, and reached fourth inner city." Bai Feng recommended.

This suggestion was well received.

The gang arrived at fifth inner city, at the battle zone. Bai Zhan Lie, Bai Lian and the other juniors were instantly awed by the atmosphere of the battle zone.

As they walked, they could hear the people's excited conversations.

"Tan Jing finally took revenge, and defeated Shi Nan Sheng. Shi Nan Sheng vowed to take revenge, their grudge is growing."

"Sang Kong controls the virus cloud moth, his battle strength has risen again, he can almost dominate the fifth inner city."

"Dominate? Hehe, he will have to wait until Gu Yue Fang Zheng ascends to fourth inner city."

...

"Gu Yue Fang Zheng!!!"

Bai clan's gang stared with wide opened eyes, like they were struck by lightning. They quickly stopped, and stared at the talking passerby.

They scared the shit out of him.

After three minutes.

On the battle stage, Fang Yuan walked up to the stage. His opponent was a middle aged man, tall and burly, thick waist and shoulder, with a long moustache on his face, looking extremely fierce and aggressive.

Ding!

The bell rang and the battle officially started.

"I admit defeat!" The middle aged man shouted at the first second. He was swift and direct, causing the audience to feel unsatisfied.

"Again?"

"Aren't you embarrassed, admitting defeat before fighting."

"Embarrassment is better than dying, in the entire fifth inner city now, who dares to fight against Fang Zheng? The all-out effort Gu is too powerful!"

The crowd was noisy as usual.

The battle ended as soon as it started.

The hosting Gu Master took both their vine information Gu and edited the information inside before returning it to them.

The middle aged man turned to leave, admitting defeat was a humiliation, but circumstances forced him to, after all Fang Yuan was cruel and ruthless, he never spares his opponents. He did not dare to fight just to save his reputation.

Fang Yuan did not leave immediately, but took out forty thousand primeval stones and handed them to Li Ran.

This caused everyone to go into discussions again.

"Another forty thousand, he really gave it!"

"Although this Gu Yue Fang Zheng is ruthless, he keeps his word. Two hundred thousand, he has repaid most of it already. Only thirty thousand remain."

"Li Ran used these primeval stones to purchase Gu worms, he is starting to display his strength in the battle zone. I am so envious."

"Repaying kindness and taking revenge for hatred. From this aspect, I truly respect Gu Yue Fang Zheng."

"With this win, he is at twenty-nine net wins. Just one last match, and he would be in fourth inner city."

"The faster the better, how dares to challenge him? Even Li Hao died by his hands..."

...

"Gu Yue Fang Zheng, after all these hardships, we've finally found you!" Among the crowd, Bai Zhan Lie gritted his teeth, as his face contorted with anger.

His companions also showed an ugly expression.

They had chased after him for so long, suffering along the journey. In the end, they found that the person they wanted to arrest had been living luxuriously in Shang clan city, making a name for himself.

Before this, they had continuously guessed if he had died under the beast hordes, digested into faeces and defecated.

The scene now, was a huge contrast to their expectations.

Not only did Fang Yuan not have problems, he was living well, even changing his Gu worms and raising his battle strength and cultivation.

What were they supposed to feel!

"Oh heaven is blind, how can such a vile scoundrel live so well?" Bai Feng raised his head and cried out.

"His luck is too good, saving the illegitimate daughter of Shang clan leader and receiving the purple thorn token! In Shang clan city, we can do nothing to him, he is protected by Shang clan!" Bai Lian gritted her teeth, she had learnt much from the passerby.

The enemy who killed the two young masters were right before them, but there was nothing they could do to him.

"Not only him, even that Bai Ning Bing received the purple thorn token. Now, she has also joined the battle stage, and has good battle records." A companion beside her sighed.

"What world is this, evil people live well while good people die. Sigh!"

"Actually, it is not like we have no way to deal with them. They could join the battle stage, so can we." Tie Dao Ku spoke with a low voice, his gaze sharp as daggers.

He had heard from Bai clan leader that Fang Yuan had the charred thunder potato mother Gu.

Right now, he could confirmed that Fang and Bai were the ones who killed his young master!

But arresting them was impossible now, so why not just kill them! That way, young master's revenge can be taken, and Tie Dao Ku can return to Tie clan.

"That's right! This is a good idea." Bai Feng's eyes shone, as his spirits were lifted.

Using the rules of the battle stage, even if Fang Yuan had the purple thorn token, he could not be protected. Even if they could not kill him, taking away his all-out effort Gu would halt his growth.

The truth is, his growth speed was too scary, it struck fear in them. He cannot be allowed to grow anymore!

"Wait, where is Bai Zhan Lie?" Bai Lian suddenly asked.

...

Fang Yuan walked out of the battle stage, as numerous people gave way to him.

Numerous gazes landed on him, there were fear and respect, indifference and animosity.

"Although I killed many Gu Masters, my reputation is not bad. Every time I give Li Ran primeval stones, it is a performance that improves my reputation. Out of the two hundred thousand, only thirty thousand remain."

Fang Yuan walked as he considered his options.

After battling Li Hao, he earned three Gu worms, but did not gain the mountain back toad or the position swap Gu.

He beat the mountain back toad to death, and the position swap Gu is Li Hao's vital Gu, it perished after Li Hao died.

But that battle had many spectators, Fang Yuan earned over six thousand primeval stones.

This month, his consecutive victories earned him enough to return forty thousand to Li Ran and still save a small sum of primeval stones for himself.

Because of his actions, and Li Ran's response, Wu clan did not do anything to Fang Yuan for now.

This earned him precious time for development.

"I have twenty-nine victories now, just one more and I'd be in fourth inner city. The pressure there is much higher, with experts everywhere, but wins also give me much more reward. After using the steel tendon Gu, I can increase the number of my beast phantoms already, but..."

To increase the number of beast phantoms, it is a long process, there will only be effect after two to three months.

After getting to fourth inner city, Fang Yuan's pressure would be greater, he needed more strength to deal with the situation.

"A large size auction will be held soon, and there is an instant success Gu up for bidding. If I can get it, I would be able to obtain new beast phantoms overnight, but my primeval stones are too few, I don't even have the qualification to participate in the auction..."

Money is always insufficient when one needs to use it!

Just as Fang Yuan was considering who to borrow from, a young man appeared and blocked his path.

"Gu Yue Fang Zheng, do you recognise me?!" Bai Zhan Lie screamed.

"Zhan Lie!"

"Zhan Lie, don't be rash."

Bai clan and gang arrived, forming a semi circle around Fang Yuan.

A stand-off!

Chapter 294: Crimes have to be punished!

Fang Yuan slightly furrowed his eyebrows and lightly glanced at the group.

He had some impression of Bai Zhan Lie; the number one genius from Bai clan's younger generation, they had even drank together at one time.

Bai Lian was even more familiar, she had accompanied him for some time, using honey trap on him. Unfortunately, how could beauty shake Fang Yuan's heart? The result was that Fang Yuan played her at her own game.

Others such as Bai Feng, Tie Dao Ku and so on, Fang Yuan did not recognize them.

Even so, Fang Yuan knew this group of people's origins and motives.

This was the victim's family coming to visit.

"Justice has long arms, Gu Yue Fang Zheng, you slaughtered my Bai clan's two young clan leaders, you will not escape justice even if you escape to Shang clan city!" Bai Feng shouted.

"Fang Zheng, the trap you buried killed my Tie clan's young master and clansmen. This hatred is absolutely irreconcilable, I, Tie Dao Ku, will take your head!" Tie Dao Ku's expression was flared up as he pointed at Fang Yuan's nose and roared.

The disturbance here immediately attracted the attention of nearby passerbys. To go where the crowds were, it was human nature; more people began to pay attention.

"Oh, you are a Tie clansman? Strange! How could I have no idea what you are talking about if I killed your clansmen?" Fang Yuan sneered.

"Stop denying it! You have the charred thunder potato mother Gu, you dug the pitfalls with extremely sinister intentions. My Tie clan group stepped into your pitfall, the explosions blew up even their corpses. We have been chasing your all the way, who could it be besides you?" Tie Dao Ku's eyes seemed to be almost shooting out flames, wishing he could immediately cut Fang Yuan into pieces.

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan was dazed for a moment before he started laughing, "So it was like that, it seems I did the right thing by digging those pitfalls. Thank you for telling me this good news and making me happy."

"You!" Tie Dao Ku opened his eyes wide, he was seething with anger, "You admitted it! You actually admitted it! Good, very good, Fang Zheng, you are dead meat. You dared to kill my Tie clan's young master, you have made an enemy out of Tie clan!"

"So what?" Fang Yuan shrugged his shoulders and sarcastically said, "Laughable, I dug those pitfalls to deal with the grass skirt monkeys. But you guys stepped on them, this can only be blamed on your Tie clansmen for not having eyes. Moreover, what crimes did I commit for you guys to tail after me? Courting your own death, hehehe, it is good that they died, it is fabulous that they died..."

The surrounding people were dumbstruck.

"He provoked a Tie clansman so directly?"

"Has Fang Zheng gone crazy? Tie clan is also one of the lords of southern border and isn't any weaker than Shang clan."

"Tie clan has captured demonic Gu Masters from everywhere and its famous demon suppression tower is the nemesis of the demonic path. Fang Zheng actually killed a young master of this clan!"

"He has the purple thorn token and knows he is safe! As long as he stays in Shang clan city, he would be a distinguished guest of Shang clan. Even if Tie clan leader came, Lord Shang Yan Fei would need to protect him. If he didn't protect Fang Zheng and the news spread out, it would signify that Shang clan is afraid of Tie clan. Hehe..."

The discussion of the surrounding people calmed down Tie Dao Ku who was burning in anger.

Fang Yuan possessed a purple thorn token and his cultivation was now rank three; dealing with him was not as easy as before.

"Hmph, Fang Zheng, don't think you are safe by hiding here. You want to rely on the battle stage to become Shang clan's external elder? In your dreams! I will tell you, as long as I Bai Feng am here, you will never be able to dominate the battle stage!" Elder Bai Feng said in a gloomy tone.

Tie Dao Ku followed immediately: "Fang Zheng, I will deal with you in the battle stage. There is no escape for you, the huge crime you have commited must receive severe punishment!"

"Oh, you guys want to stop me in the battle stage?" Fang Yuan's eyes flashed with a trace of cold light.

He was not afraid of these people, even though Bai Feng, Tie Dao Ku, Bai Zhan Lie and Bai Lian were all rank three Gu Masters.

If they were going to deal with him through the battle stage, they could not display their superiority in numbers.

"It is just that my current situation...."

Fang Yuan mumbled inwardly then suddenly chuckled and said to Bai Feng: "Your Bai clan obtained Bai Gu inheritance but are still not satisfied and want to deal with me? Without me, how could you have obtained the inheritance? Hmph, it seems you don't want to know the whereabouts of your two young clan leaders."

The Bai clansmen immediately revealed astonished expressions.

From Fang Yuan's tone, it seemed the two young clan leaders were not dead...

"Fang Zheng, what do you mean?" Bai Feng immediately asked in bewilderment.

"Fang Zheng, don't try to deceive us with lies. We have searched almost everywhere in Bai Gu inheritance ground but haven't found even a trace of the two young clan leaders." Bai Lian coldly shouted.

"It was me who found the Bai Gu inheritance, does Bai clan think it has more understanding of the place than me? Ridiculous!"

Fang Yuan disdainfully scoffed and continued: "Why would I retreat while carrying those two burdens? Can't you think with your brains? Deceive you? Hmph, I am not even afraid of Tie clan, why would I fear your puny Bai clan?"

"Fang Zheng, if the two young clan leaders are still alive then this will just be a misunderstanding, our Bai clan... is not an unreasonable clan." Bai Feng picked his words carefully to coax Fang Yuan into revealing the whereabouts of the two young clan leaders.

"You want to know? Hehe, fine. It just so happens that I am starving, how about you treat me to a meal? Let's go to third inner city's most famous Shi Zi restaurant." Fang Yuan indifferently said.

Bai clansmen looked at each other.

The whereabouts of the two young clan leaders was extremely important since it affected the future of Bai clan.

Despite Bai clan having extreme hatred towards Fang Yuan, elder Bai Feng gritted his teeth and nodded: "Alright, let's go there!"

Shi Zi restaurant was not just a simple restaurant, but was a luxurious brothel.

This restaurant introduced women from foreign lands like Northern Plains, Eastern Seas and Western Desert; the women were all enchanting, with plump butt and large breasts. Another speciality of this restaurant was their lion meatball and was served on a human.

Lion's meat, tiger's meat and all kinds of precious ingredients were made into meatballs and displayed on top of a beautiful woman in between her breasts.

The name lion meatball held deep meanings. It was not only to eat the food, but also to 'eat human'.

The reason why Fang Yuan wanted to visit this place was not because he was interested in lion meatball, but because this restaurant had a strong background and contained many secret private rooms. Many Shang clansmen would often choose a private room for their private affairs, concealing their names and had no worries about news leaking.

Fang Yuan chose a secret room and sat along with everyone.

A feast was laid before them, the aroma of the dishes assailed their nostrils. However, they did not order the signature dish, lion meatball.

"Say it, where are our two young clan leaders?" Bai Feng impatiently asked the moment he sat down.

"Before I tell you, I would like to ask this Tie clan Gu Master to stay outside for a moment." Fang Yuan gazed at Tie Dao Ku.

"Why?" Tie Dao Ku's gaze was sharp as knife, as he ruthlessly cut off Fang Yuan. A bad feeling emerged in his mind.

"Because this is a private affair between me and Bai clan!" Fang Yuan's tone was unyielding, "Besides me, everyone else should be Bai clansmen, otherwise I guarantee I won't say a word!"

Bai Feng hesitated, the matter concerned the two young clan leaders, he had to be careful about it, thus he looked at Tie Dao Ku.

Tie Dao Ku snorted and annoyedly left the secret room, closing the door shut.

The sound produced in the secret room was isolated from the outside.

"Say it, where are the two young clan leaders, don't even think of deceiving us! This is Shang clan city, there are many Gu worms that can verify your words." Bai Feng sternly asked.

Fang Yuan lifted a wine cup and sipped at it: "Whereabouts? Of course, they are both dead, you guys are really naive! Since I made an enemy out of your Bai clan, I will naturally eliminate all threats!"

"What!"

"You dared to toy with us?

"Fang Zheng, you are courting death!!"

The Bai clansmen stood up furiously, their flaming anger pressed on towards Fang Yuan.

They were full fury but could not take any actions.

This was not Bai clan's territory, Fang Yuan possessed a purple thorn token and also had impressive strength. They would definitely have to pay a catastrophic price to kill Fang Yuan. Most importantly, if they killed him like this, it was making an enemy out of Shang clan!

Your Bai clan killed my Shang clan's esteemed guest in Shang clan city, hehe.

Bai clan was now facing the crisis of their spirit spring drying up, they were in a precarious situation. Now, after obtaining the Bai Gu inheritance, many forces were eyeing it covetously, if they provoked a titan like Shang clan on top of that, the consequences would be too dire to imagine!

Fang Yuan calmly sat on his seat, he raised his eyes and looked at everyone, then indifferently said:

"I actually admire you guys. Your Bai clan's spirit spring is drying up and are in deep trouble, yet you guys still have the mood for leisure and came chasing after me. Hehe, you are really amazing."

These words were like a bolt of lightning which fiercely struck their hearts, causing tides to surge in elder Bai Feng's heart.

He was horrified as he blurted out: "This... how do you know this?!"

This information was sealed off by Bai clan's higher ups, even Bai Zhan Lie and Bai Lian did not know it. But Fang Yuan laid bare the secret with one sentence, how could it not frighten Bai Feng?

"Of course it was from your noble clan's two young clan leaders. Before I killed them, they knelt and begged for forgiveness, trying to use this information to obtain my trust and exchange for their lives." Fang Yuan talked nonsense, anyway, dead men tell no tales.

"Impossible! This information is only confined to clan leader and few elders. The two young clan leaders are young and ignorant, how could we let them know this?!" Bai Feng immediately retorted.

Fang Yuan curled his lips: "Maybe they heard it when they were playing around? After all, their mother is your clan leader. These are just minor details."

"Lord clan elder, is what he said about the spirit spring drying up true?"

"How could this be, if the clan's spirit spring dries up..."

Bai Lian, Bai Zhan Lie and others questioned one after another, their expressions worried and frightened.

Spirit spring was the foundation of a clan, there was no need to mention its importance. If the clan lost the spirit spring, no matter how strong it was, it would only be rootless weed.

Bai Feng immediately came back to his senses by their questions and inwardly knew he had messed up.

Maybe Fang Yuan was only guessing, the two young clan leaders were young, their credibility were not high.

Bai Feng felt immense regret and wished he could give himself a tight slap. He was impatient and could not hide secrets. Otherwise, when he was young, he would not have been driven out of the clan by his father to force him to mold his character.

These years, he had cultivated some shrewdness but in the end, a leopard cannot change its spots.

But honestly, he could not be blamed. Spirit spring was too important, Bai Feng was carrying this burden in his heart. The pressure was accumulating like a volcano and burst out due to Fang Yuan's one sentence.

Chapter 295: Actually, I was a victim too

Bai Feng's expression was gloomy and his gaze kept on flashing. He was thinking of denying this but Fang Yuan saw through his plan.

"Don't even try to cover it, it's no use. As the spirit spring continues to dry up, the primeval stones produced will also decrease sharply. Bai clan has been concealing it well, you have either used your remaining stock in the storage or traded to fill up this gap. But this will definitely leave traces, as long as someone carefully investigates it, they will find out." Fang Yuan was calm and comfortable.

Bai Feng tightly clenched his fists, glaring at Fang Yuan like he wanted to swallow him alive.

Looking at the appearance of this elder, even a stupid person would realize the truth.

"Our clan's spirit spring is drying?" Bai Lian was dazed, leaning on her chair listlessly.

Bai Zhan Lie bit his lips, going silent.

The others also did not speak, they were astonished and terrified. The atmosphere in the secret room turned extremely oppressive.

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan chuckled, "Your Bai clan is really in danger. Even a stronger clan will collapse if their spirit spring dries up and they don't find a new spirit spring. Now, you have obtained Bai Gu inheritance, the forces around you are all coveting it; tell me, what will happen if I spread this secret information?"

"No!" Bai Lian lost color in her face and immediately interjected.

The others also thought of the seriousness of the matter and their expressions turned grave.

Now, Bai clan had obtained Bai Gu inheritance, their strength rose due to the benefits gained from Fang Yuan's discovery. The few neighbouring large clans were staring at them covetously, but also held their guard.

If the news of the spirit spring drying up was exposed, Bai clan would lose their deterrence and become a paper tiger; the surrounding forces were sure to make their move!

Those forces would never want to see Bai clan survive this ordeal and because of the Bai Gu inheritance, rise in power and suppress them.

Hence, this information had to be guarded!

Bai clan's gang were startled awake by Fang Yuan, gaining some understanding of the situation. Bai Zhan Lie and others fixed their gazes at Fang Yuan, their eyes shining even more fiercely and emitted killing intent.

"Want to kill me?" Fang Yuan sneered and shook his finger, "Since I am meeting with you alone, I have naturally made thorough preparations. In truth, if you hadn't come to find me, I would have gone to find you."

These were not senseless words. The Bai clansmen had no choice but to restrain their killing intent and retract the ominous glint in their eyes.

"Alright, let's get down to business now." The corner of Fang Yuan's lips slightly curled up as he adjusted his sitting posture.

He pointed his hands down and said: "Take a seat and let's discuss it."

"Discuss what, what's there to talk about with you? Hmph!" Bai Feng's expression was gloomy, but despite saying so, he still sat down.

The remaining clansmen hesitated for a while before sitting down.

The tense situation immediately eased a little.

"Of course we are going to discuss the fees to keep me silent. Was it easy for me to lead you here? Wasting my time and energy, you should compensate me! Primeval stones, I want primeval stones. Give me three million primeval stones and I can promise you I won't reveal this information."

The Bai clansmen immediately stood up again when they heard Fang Yuan.

"You dare to threaten us!"

"You killed our two young clan leaders, and dare to demand primeval stones?!"

"Fang Zheng, don't go too far. At worst, I will stake my old life and take you down with me!!"

The group roared and growled in anger.

"Hahaha." Fang Yuan threw his head back and laughed. He then stood up and a cold light blossomed in his dark eyes as he looked at the group.

"That's right, I am threatening you! You don't agree? Then I will simply leak this information. What did you say, you want to die together with me? Hmph, even if I die, this information will be leaked to the world. At that time, you will become the sinners of the clan; because you didn't agree to my request, your clan will be besieged by the surrounding forces!"

"You, you, you..." Elder Bai Feng was angered to his limit as he speechlessly pointed at Fang Yuan.

The other clansmen also glared at Fang Yuan with furious eyes while gritting their teeth, but no one moved.

"You what?" Fang Yuan sneered at Bai Feng, his tone full of disdain, "What can you do to me? Kill me? I have a purple thorn token, do you dare to try it? I know you are all courageous, not afraid of death. But your clan is the most important. If your family and friends die, it will be all because of you!"

The Bai clansmen clenched their fists, standing stunned on the spot.

"Ahh—!" Bai Zhan Lie suddenly raised his head and shouted, he then lifted his fist and smashed it down.

Due to his furious punch, the whole banquet table was smashed and the dishes crashed to the ground.

He felt deep hatred!

His grandfather Bai Zhan Wen had died because of Fang and Bai. This hatred was irreconcilable!

Because of this, he joined the pursuit group, constantly running about, now that he finally found the killer...

The enemy was clearly in front of him, but he could not do anything! Fang Yuan was clearly within his reach, but he could not exact revenge!

Not only could he not exact revenge, he still had to endure Fang Yuan's threat.

His chest burned with anger, an anger that threatened to burn the sky and was already burning his heart. But he could not move, he did not dare to imagine the consequences if he moved. His life was a minor thing, but the whole clan might face a calamity because of him!!

"No need to get angry. Actually, in this whole event, I was also a victim." Fang Yuan's tone relaxed and said with a sigh.

"Just think of it, Bai Gu inheritance was originally mine, but your Bai clan stole it from me. Your Bai clan chased after me and Bai Ning Bing, we were forced to kill Bai Hua and Bai Sheng to make it easier to escape. Later, I suffered serious injuries and landed on Zi You mountain, having close encounter with death all along the way. Do you think it was easy for me?"

"Your Bai clan's power is huge and I can't afford to offend it. I could only curl up in Shang clan city, but you still won't let me go. Tell me, what should I do? I am not someone who is unreasonable, three million primeval stones, that is the lowest I will go. I am very sincere, I have told this secret to only a few people and haven't spread it outside. I also intentionally sent the Tie clansman outside in consideration for your Bai clan."

Fang Yuan's expression was very sincere.

"Three million primeval stones, you are demanding an exorbitant price!"

"Fang Zheng, let's be fair, how did our Bai clan treat you! We treated you nicely with food and accomodation, but what came out of it? You repaid our kindness with enmity!"

"Our clan's two young clan leaders died in your hands, elder Bai Zhan Wen also died because of you. Many of our expert clansmen also died or got seriously handicapped while protecting you on your travels around Bai Gu mountain!"

The Bai clan's group all had different expressions; some were extremely angry, some were sneering and some were crying, but they all had a similarity — their deep hatred towards Fang Yuan!

Fang Yuan's expression changed, he gave a cold smile: "It seems you are still not aware of the situation, I tried to give you face, but you don't want it? Very well."

Fang Yuan stood up and turned to leave.

Bai clansmen immediately fell into panic.

"Wait, wait a moment." Bai Feng was desperate as he sidestepped and blocked Fang Yuan.

"I will tell you honestly, I am going to go sell this information now. I believe Shang clan's Feng Yu Manor will give a good price for it. Can you guess how much they are going to pay me?" Fang Yuan smiled sinisterly.

"Fang Zheng, don't go too far!" Bai Zhan Lie roared and quickly walked towards Fang Yuan and stared at him dead on.

Fang Yuan nonchalantly said: "You want to attack me? You want to put your clan in danger?"

Bai Zhan Lie's inner fire was stumped, as he stood stunned.

Slap!

Fang Yuan took this chance and slapped. He was very strong and with just a little strength, he sent the energetic Bai Zhan Lie retreating five to six steps.

"What do you think you are doing?!" Bai clansmen immediately flared up and surrounded Fang Yuan.

"Do you all want to become the sinners of your clan?" Fang Yuan snorted, his words were like ice, dousing the Bai clansmen's surging anger.

"You unappreciative scum." Fang Yuan pointed at Bai Zhan Lie, "If I don't teach you a lesson, do you really think you are the Heavenly Emperor?"

Fang Yuan showed no restraint in berating Bai Zhan Lie in front of the Bai clansmen.

He next looked at everyone: "You are all idiots! If I wanted Bai clan to face a calamity, it just takes one sentence from me! A wise man succumbs to circumstances, you still can't see the situation clearly? Make a move if you want. Come, even if I die, having your Bai clan accompany me in death won't be so bad."

Fang Yuan was completely surrounded, but his attitude was still unbridled.

Instead it was Bai clansmen, who were bigger in numbers, that had to give in while gritting their teeth and clenching their fists.

Bai Zhan Lie held his swollen face, his eyes bloodshot. This humiliation almost caused the anger in his his heart to burst up to the nine heavens. The veins in his forehead bulged out as he tried his best to maintain the final sliver of reason left in his mind.

The clan was their weak spot; Fang Yuan targeted this and also showed an attitude that was unafraid of death, causing Bai clan fall into a hopeless situation where they could only tolerate Fang Yuan.

"I will give you thirty breaths of time to consider." Fang Yuan continued.

The group of Bai clansmen immediately fell into a struggle.

They did not want to lower their heads to Fang Yuan, this murderer. However, if they did not lower their heads, their clan would be in danger.

They were at a loss and all of them looked towards elder Bai Feng.

Bai Feng's clenched fists slowly loosened before he again clenched them and unclenched after a while.

This continued again and again, showing the struggle in his heart.

Thirty breaths of time passed by, but Fang Yuan looked like he had forgotten it.

Bai Feng was impatient, but he only opened his mouth after five minutes, breaking the silence.

"Three million... is too much. We can't agree to this. Moreover, we don't have that much money on us!" His voice was hoarse like a guy who was about to die of thirst in desert.

He listlessly loosened his hands, having no more strength to clench them again.

For the clan, he had no choice but to give priority to the overall situation. Despite wishing he could cut Fang Yuan into pieces, he chose to lower his head for the moment.

The other Bai clansmen also felt their hearts relieved after hearing his words. Their killing intent towards Fang Yuan sank into the shadows, becoming thicker and deeper.

Fang Yuan laughed: "The three million does not need to be paid in full, just take it slowly, for now hand over five hundred thousand."

"Five hundred thousand? Why would we carry so many primeval stones with us?!" Bai Feng refuted.

Fang Yuan's brows raised: "You can borrow from loan sharks, pawn your belongings or even sell Gu worms... no matter what you do, I need five hundred thousand primeval stones within a day. Moreover, I do not want to see any of Bai clan's people staying in Shang clan city!"

Chapter 296: Auction

"What are they doing inside, it has already been over an hour..." Outside the secret room, Tie Dao Ku was standing with his arms crossed, the doubt in his heart increasing with time.

The secret room isolated sound but it was not firm. In the case where a fight broke out, he would be able to immediately sense it.

The problem, however, was that it had been calm and quiet since the start, making Tie Dao Ku unable to figure it out.

Creak.

Just as he was thinking this, the door opened from the inside.

"Brother Dao Ku, please come inside, we have finished our talk." A Gu Master of Bai clan informed.

Tie Dao Ku entered the secret room, the first thing he saw was the table smashed by Bai Zhan Lie and all kinds of dishes scattered on the ground.

Tie Dao Ku could not help but raise his brows.

Clearly, this feast could not be enjoyed anymore. Even if it could, the Bai clansmen present there did not have any appetite.

Their faces were ashen and their expressions sluggish as if they had suffered heavy injuries.

Only Fang Yuan's complexion was normal and even looked healthier than normal.

Just now, he had reached an agreement with the Bai clansmen and everything was settled by using poison vow Gu on the spot.

"What happened?" Tie Dao Ku was bewildered.

"I will leave first, take care." Fang Yuan left these words and walked out of the secret room.

"Fang Zheng, just wait for me at the battle stage!" Tie Dao Ku growled.

Fang Yuan ignored him and walked away, disappearing from everyone's sights.

"What exactly happened here?" Tie Dao Ku was very puzzled. How could talking for a while make all these Bai clansmen's expression change, he could not feel any flames of hatred in them.

"Sigh...." Bai Feng heaved a deep sigh.

He raised his head and looked at Tie Dao Ku, his gaze complex: "Brother Tie, something happened and it is not convenient for me to speak of it. We are withdrawing, we cannot go against Fang and Bai anymore."

"What?" Tie Dao Ku cried out involuntarily, revealing an incredulous expression.

"Our Bai clan has little assets, we cannot afford to take risks. Take care!" Bai Feng stood up and walked straight out of the secret room.

"You don't have to be worried, he is relying on Shang clan, but isn't my Tie clan also one of the lords of the southern border?" Tie Dao Ku hurriedly tried to persuade them. To deal against Fang and Bai, it was better with more people. If Bai clan left, he would be all alone!

However, how could he know the situation behind this?

His persuasion was of no use, Bai clan was bent on leaving and he was not able to stop them anymore.

Looking at the image of the Bai clansmen leaving, Tie Dao Ku's expression turned extremely cold and mumbled to himself: "The supreme art of war is to subdue the enemy without fighting; Fang Zheng, you made a good move! But don't think I, Tie Dao Ku, will give up just like this. Hmph!"

His will was firm, others might have given up, but he still chose to persist.

He decided to register his name at the battle zone right away. He would hunt Fang Yuan in the battle stage!

"Sir, please stop." A waiter ran over and politely stopped Tie Dao Ku with a smile on his face: "You haven't paid the bill."

"...what?"

...

"Five hundred thousand primeval stones, how can we prepare such a large sum of money within a day?" Walking on the spacious street, Bai Lian voiced out her worries.

"With my identity as an elder of Bai clan, I can go to the loan sharks to borrow three hundred thousand. As for the remaining two hundred thousand... I will have to pawn small tornado." Bai Feng understood the situation.

The other Bai clansmen were moved.

Bai Zhan Lie cried out: "Lord Elder, small tornado Gu is your core Gu, are you really going to pawn it?"

Bai Feng let out a bitter smile.

"Even with elder pawning small tornado Gu, it won't be enough to get two hundred thousand. Add in my lotus cloth Gu." Bai Lian pursed her lips.

With this, the remaining Bai clansmen also understood.

"Pawn my fountain thoughts Gu as well."

"My little wind drill Gu as well."

"I will contribute my three forked bone spear..."

Bai Feng slowly nodded: "You all have the spirit of sacrificing for the clan, there is no worry that Bai clan won't flourish. Today's disgrace will be paid a thousand times over in future. But now, we still need to think of the clan. I decided on this, so I will take all the responsibility for this matter once we return to the clan."

"Lord Elder!" The group was stunned.

They could not take their revenge and had to instead sign a disgraceful and unfair treaty. Although it was the best choice, there would definitely be heavy pressure and criticism when they returned to the clan.

Political struggles existed everywhere.

However, Bai Feng was going to bear the responsibility for the whole affair, no doubt he was protecting the political prospects of Bai Lian, Bai Zhan Lie and the others.

Bai Feng revealed an affectionate smile and sighed: "No need to say anything, I am already old, the clan's future lies on your shoulder. How could we gain anything without giving and sacrificing? It is because of countless people sacrificing and enduring humiliation, that the clan is able to thrive, and preserve the smile of our family members."

"Yes!" Bai Lian, Bai Zhan Lie and others nodded, realization dawned on their minds.

Their ashen expressions gradually disappeared and were replaced with a gaze that was glowing brighter and brighter.

...

Three days later, in a large scale auction.

"Ladies and gentlemen, you are looking at a frost breath Gu. Rank three Gu worm, able to breathe out cold air which has the effect of inflicting frostbites and slowing your opponents. Frost breath Gu's biggest advantage is that every activation only consumes five percent of light snow primeval essence. The starting bid is twenty-three thousand primeval stones!" On a round platform, the hosting Gu Master was speaking through sound amplify Gu.

"Twenty-five thousand."

"Twenty-eight thousand."

"Thirty thousand!"

After a round of intense bidding, the frost breath Gu was sold for thirty eight thousand primeval stones.

Fang Yuan calmly looked down at the circular stage from his seat.

He was sitting in a private room at the auction; others could not see him. This was the benefit of having a purple thorn token.

In small scale auctions, he could use the purple thorn token to buy auctioned goods in advance. He was not able to do that for the large scale auctions.

"Please take a look, this is a flame heart Gu. Its shape is like a miniature volcano. After refining it, it resides in the heart of the Gu Master. As everyone knows, its ability is to strengthen fire type Gu worm's attacks. Rank three flame heart Gu, starting bid of thirty thousand primeval stones!" The hosting Gu Master shouted loudly from the platform.

He had just finished speaking, when someone immediately made a bid: "Thirty-five thousand!"

The first bid immediately raised the bid by five thousand primeval stones, showing a clear assertiveness.

But this could not stop interested parties.

"Thirty-six thousand!"

"Thirty-eight thousand."

"Forty thousand..."

The price finally stopped at forty-two thousand.

"Looks like these people are quite rational. This is a reasonable price..." Fang Yuan watched this from the private room, evaluating the situation.

Shang clan city frequently traded, this type of large scale auctions were held at fixed intervals. The Gu Masters living in Shang clan city were all used to it and were smart when bidding in auctions.

No one was foolish.

Of course, there were occasional extravagant participants.

Fang Yuan had observed for a long while, today's auction did not seem to have such a person.

This was his luck and also others' luck.

If there had been such a person, Fang Yuan would have to start bidding and empty out these people's capital early. This type of battle of wits and contest of force was child's play to Fang Yuan.

All the Gu showed in the large scale auctions were rare and precious. All of them were rank three or above, there was almost none below rank three.

Besides the Gu worms, there were also rare Gu food, rare Gu refinement materials, Gu refinement recipe, information about some inheritances, perfect looking gambling rocks; there were also female slaves, male slaves, captured beast kings and so on.

Frost breath Gu and flame heart Gu were sold for about thirty to forty thousand; this price could only be considered to be low compared to other auction goods.

Soon, Fang Yuan saw a rank four grass tree army Gu being sold for two hundred and fifty thousand primeval stones.

Grass tree army Gu could turn every plant and tree within a certain range of the Gu Master into an offensive method. In the terrains of Southern Border, it was an absolute killing weapon.

Ordinary rank four Gu could cost up to a hundred thousand primeval stones. Grass tree army Gu's price already reached the price of an ordinary rank five Gu.

Fang Yuan carried five hundred thousand on him right now, but at this auction, it really was not much and could only buy two grass tree army Gu.

Instant success Gu was a rank four rare Gu.

After a bidding competition, Fang Yuan successfully bought it with over one hundred and eighty thousand primeval stones.

Next, he spent a total of eighty-three thousand primeval stones to buy a white silver relic Gu and a golden shield Gu.

He did not make any bids after that.

Primeval stones could not be spent recklessly and should be spent in useful areas. Currently, all-out effort Gu was his core, he also had self-reliance Gu. He lacked a bitter strength Gu; this Gu was not cheap, moreover it was extremely rare, rarely seen even at Shang clan city.

Why?

Because the fusion success rate was extremely low, so there were only a small number of people who used it.

Gu worm's transactions also depended on the supply and demand of the market. With low demand and high production costs, the supply would naturally be low.

"If I can't buy bitter strength Gu, then I can only try refining it myself. It is just that its success rate really causes a headache."

"I got the white silver relic Gu, but there is no hurry to use it. If I was cultivating alone, it would be better if I used it earlier, but now that I have Bai Ning Bing to rely on. I will leave the white silver relic Gu to use for later."

"I have used over two hundred and seventy thousand primeval stones today, now just over two hundred and twenty thousand remains. I will accumulate them for the super sized auction held every two years in Shang clan city."

"Li Ran told me that Bai clan's group has indeed left Shang clan city. Although I extorted three million out of them, I can't underestimate this clan. Suffering in silence with the mentality of sacrificing, no wonder they rose to power abruptly in my previous life. Right now, they are using the excuse of exploring Bai Gu inheritance to recklessly search for the spirit spring in Bai Gu mountain. The progress is a lot faster than in my previous life, I have no choice but to be vigilant against them."

"Bai clan has already chased me to here, would Tie clan be far off? Tie clan, demon suppression tower... as for that Tie Dao Ku, he is of no worry for the moment."

Just as Fang Yuan was making future plans, at the entrance of Shi Zi restaurant.

Eighteen foreign girls stood in two rows, laughing and chatting with each other.

They wore revealing clothes and the fragrance of their makeup filled the air. They had plump breasts and looked sultry.

They had no need to solicit customers, just standing there was the best signboard, attracting countless male Gu Masters to loiter around and enter.

With a grim face, Tie Dao Ku was standing at the side with several other Gu Masters, guarding the entrance.

Humiliating!

The shame in his heart had reached its limits.

To think that Shi Zi restaurant's banquet was so expensive, without any money to pay for it, he could only work to write off his debt.

"Look at what a grand Tie clan's Gu Master has fallen to, I am actually forced to do this type of thing! The restaurant has background and doesn't care that I am a Tie clansman. Sigh! I hope no one sees me, absolutely no acquaintances..." Tie Dao Ku prayed desperately.

"Eh! Isn't this brother Tie Dao Ku? What are you doing here?" A voice arrived.

Tie Dao Ku was immediately stunned.

A familiar person...

Familiar...

Person...

"Aaaah! Fang Zheng, just wait!" Veins bulged out of Tie Dao Ku's forehead as he roared furiously in his heart.

Chapter 297: Instant Success Gu

"Yin cloud Gu."

In the secret room, Fang Yuan sat on the cushion, muttering as he pointed his finger forward.

Suddenly, a Gu came out of his aperture like a flash of light.

The moment it appeared, it lightly exploded, turning into a dark black cloud.

This cloud sank quickly, as it circulated within itself, in the blink of an eye, it landed on the ground, and placed Fang Yuan above the cloud layer.

Fang Yuan sat on the black cloud, it was softer than the cushion, but slightly colder.

He was not surprised, stretching out his index finger and pointing to the air.

"Yang cloud Gu."

A white light tore through the air as it exploded into pure white mist.

Once the white cloud appeared, it wanted to rise, but sensed the black cloud below Fang Yuan.

The two cloud layers had a formless attraction to each other, as the black and white clouds continued to roll internally, looking after one another.

One was below Fang Yuan, while the other was above his head.

The gloomy cloud was like ink, while the bright cloud was like foam, as the two converged, lightning appeared.

Traces of blue lightning quickly flashed between these two clouds.

Initially, there was one or two traces, but they soon multiplied, growing in numbers, in a few breath's time, they formed into a field of lightning.

Fang Yuan had already activated the canopy Gu, his body covered in a white armor.

At the same time, he activated the all-out effort Gu as he casually stretched out his arm, and a wild boar phantom appeared behind him, becoming a giant boar image in the air.

Crack crack.

Once the boar phantom appeared, the lightning bolts acted like sharks attracted to blood, shooting towards it.

In an instant, the boar phantom was forcefully suppressed, shrinking to the size of a stone mill. Lightning circulated in its body, like deep blue chains that trapped it.

The rest of the lightning hit Fang Yuan's body, but was blocked by the white armor.

Fang Yuan recalled the all-out effort Gu, but this boar phantom did not vanish, like a caged bird, trapped firmly.

Under the constant attack of the lightning cage, the boar phantom started to show signs of disappearing.

Lightning, combining destruction and purification into one. After a thunderstorm, new life grows. The power of lightning specialized in destruction, and contained the destruction law fragment.

At this point, Fang Yuan was using the Yin Yang dual cloud Gu to gather lightning and remove one of his wild boar strength.

It had been three days since that auction.

Although the Yin Yang dual cloud Gu was rank three, it was an ordinary Gu bought in the shop. Other than this, he also bought some material, and after failing once, he refined the eating one's words Gu and removed the poison vow Gu on him.

Fang Yuan had once used the black and white boar Gu on Qing Mao mountain, to gain the strength of two boars.

The rank three all-out effort Gu can only summon one beast phantom at a time. After it reaches rank four, there are stronger beast phantoms available. Thus, the strength of two boars would be redundant and repetitive.

Now that Fang Yuan had excess money, he decided to optimize his body.

To get rid of this boar phantom, it would take some time, at least nineteen days. The cooperation of the Yin Yang dual cloud Gu to summon lightning was the most common and cheap method.

Beast phantoms are the law fragments lurking in a person's body. To get rid of them, it would take some effort.

Fang Yuan carefully used the Yin cloud Gu and Yang cloud Gu, as both clouds moved rapidly, like two thick carpets filling the entire secret room.

One white cloud covered the ceiling. One black cloud covered the floor.

In the middle, lightning struck, bolts of blue lightning connected the two clouds and trapped the boar phantom as it slowly disintegrated.

A soft 'crack crack' sound, different from loud thunder, could be heard continuously.

To get rid of this boar phantom, it would take a while, but now Fang Yuan called out another Gu.

This Gu was like a dragonfly, three pairs of wings, palm size. It had four colors that shone brilliantly: jade green, sapphire blue, gold and bright red.

This was the instant success Gu, its body containing the Dao mark of time. As the name suggests, it can speed up the flow of time, it was a rank four consumable Gu.

Fang Yuan split his mind into three, controlling the Yin Yang dual cloud Gu, activating his primeval essence, and injecting them into the instant success Gu.

His primeval sea level fell drastically, eighty, seventy, sixty percent...

Instant success Gu was a rank four Gu, with his rank three initial stage cultivation, it was tough for Fang Yuan to activate it.

When his light silver primeval essence fell to thirty percent, Fang Yuan halted his primeval essence usage, and the heavenly essence treasure lotus slowly opened up, as natural essence gushed out from it, instantly infected by Fang Yuan's aura and becoming his light silver primeval essence.

His primeval sea level started to rise, forty, fifty, sixty percent...

Rinse and repeat, after his primeval sea level fell and rose several times, the instant success Gu was finally full, and once activated, it gave off a dazzling light show.

This colorful display of lights shone on the Yin Yang dual cloud Gu and the beast phantom, dying the secret room with a rainbow color.

The boar phantom's disintegration accelerated.

Originally, the speed of disintegration was almost unnoticeable by the naked eye. But now, like a snowball rolling down a mountain, the speed increased drastically.

After more than ten breaths' time, the wild boar phantom was completely destroyed.

After confirming it, Fang Yuan quickly stopped using the instant success Gu, and kept his Yin Yang dual cloud Gu.

He could return the Yin Yang dual cloud Gu back to the shop, with the purple thorn token, as long as it is within three days, Fang Yuan can return the Gu and get back the same amount he paid. It was safer than borrowing a Gu from people, and he would not make any loss.

If he borrowed a Gu, the initiative is in their hands, with just a thought, they can take back the Gu in an instant, there would be nothing Fang Yuan could do.

As for the instant success Gu.

After the lights were dimmed as much as possible, its three pair of wings only had two left, and its entire body was slowly vanishing.

Once this Gu was used, it could not be stopped, the lights will continue to shine and accelerate time accordingly. Fang Yuan reducing the light intensity would only prolong its remaining time.

"Again."

Fang Yuan made use of his remaining time, next, he activated the galloping horse strength Gu.

This Gu was rank three, able to modify a Gu Master's body and form a horse strength phantom for him.

Under the influence of the galloping horse strength Gu, Fang Yuan's body felt numb as the fragment of the strength law started to reside in his body.

This process would last two to three months normally, it was time consuming.

But now, Fang Yuan still had the instant success Gu.

He breathed in deeply, releasing the restraints on the instant success Gu, and a dazzling light shone on him immediately.

The numb feeling intensified at once, the two to three months of torture assaulted him, turning into a painful numb feeling.

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, after five minutes, his body was drenched in sweat.

But the horse strength phantom had successfully taken root in his body. After removing the strength of a boar, he added the strength of a horse!

The instant success Gu's light dimmed again, it had lost another wing in this process, it only had one pair of wings plus another half a piece.

But Fang Yuan paid a much greater price.

Instant success Gu had a great drawback, that is, in this short period, he lost three months of lifespan!

"Again!"

Fang Yuan wiped away his sweat, ignoring the intense pain in his body and used the Gu again.

He had to make the best of his time, while the instant success Gu was still around, he had to make the best out of it.

Green bull labor Gu!

The dazzling light shone on his body again.

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, his eyebrows squeezing tightly, as his pain was even greater than earlier, like giant waves crashing on the shore.

It was five minutes again, but this time, it was much harder to endure.

Finally, through Fang Yuan's determination, he endured through this period. His body gained the strength of a bull!

The instant success Gu now, had two wings left, both tattered and torn. Its entire dragonfly body was turning translucent, like a hologram floating in the air.

Fang Yuan felt an intense headache, his ears were buzzing and his heart was beating quickly.

"Barely any time left..."

He breathed in deeply, forcing himself to focus, as he activated the stone turtle strength Gu.

But this time, the process only lasted half the time before the lights dimmed, and vanished, as the instant success Gu's time was used up.

The secret room fell into complete darkness after the lights vanished.

The primeval sea was left with less than thirty percent of primeval essence, but under the help of the heavenly essence treasure lotus, it started to rise slowly.

Heavenly essence treasure lotus was a rank three Gu, it was a very strong assistance to the recovering of Fang Yuan's primeval essence.

Fang Yuan breathed out deeply, feeling fatigue assault him, almost draining his entire body.

Although he was seated on the cushion, his body was swaying, and he had difficulties sitting.

Activating this instant success took half a year's lifespan from him. It was a heavy price, but he managed to remove the boar phantom, and gain the strength of a bull, horse, and half a turtle!

Thankfully, he was still young, he had enough lifespan to spare.

Fang Yuan's battle strength rose sharply!

A day later, on the battle stage, Fang Yuan had his thirtieth match.

Ding.

The bell announced the start of the battle.

"I admit defeat!"

His opponent shouted, ending the battle.

Thus, Fang Yuan obtained his thirtieth victory. In fifth inner city, he had thirty consecutive battles, thirty net wins, and rose to fourth inner city!

No one was surprised by this result.

The Gu Masters in fifth inner city battle stage saw him leave and sighed in relief.

...

"I will return this sum of money to you!" Tie Dao Ku said with a serious expression, his attitude extremely firm.

"Just a small matter, don't mind it. Brother Tie, what plans do you have now?" His friend smiled.

Tie Dao Ku showed a determined expression: "Gu Yue Fang Zheng is my target, I will not stop until I arrest him. I am going to participate in the Shang clan battle stage!"

After saying bye to his friend, Tie Dao Ku came to the battle zone alone, but heard a nightmare.

"What, Fang Zheng went to fourth inner city? Damn it!"

Tie Dao Ku clenched his fist, indignant: "Fang Zheng, do you think you can escape? Hmph, if you went to fourth inner city, so will I. Not mentioning third inner city, but do you think fifth inner city can stop me? I have to hurry, I shall have my first match today!"

"I refined the ice crystal Gu as my vital Gu. Coupled with the vitality Gu to prevent the backlash from the energy of the ice crystal, this way, my core is completed. For close range, I have ice edge Gu, and for long range, should I use snowball Gu or icicle Gu?" Bai Ning Bing thought along the way as she walked to the battle stage.

"Eh? It's you!" Tie Dao Ku saw Bai Ning Bing walk onto the stage, and was stunned before cheering: "Great! Heaven has eyes, for me to encounter you on the first match!"

Bai Ning Bing heard this, and raised her beautiful jewel-like blue eyes, and spoke in her usual cold tone: "Who are you?"

Chapter 298: Bai Ning Bing vs Tie Dao Ku

Honestly speaking, Bai Ning Bing did not know who Tie Dao Ku was.

When Fang and Bai left Qing Mao mountain, Tie Dao Ku and gang were constantly lagging behind them. Even during Bai Gu mountain inheritance, the eventual battle did not involve Tie Dao Ku, nor did Fang and Bai meet him.

Only until a while ago, when Tie Dao Ku and Bai clan came to Shang clan city, did he see Fang Yuan in person for the first time.

But after that, Fang Yuan lured them to Shi Zi restaurant, and after a conversation, Bai clan took out all they had and ran away after giving him five hundred thousand, leaving Tie Dao Ku behind, arrested by Shi Zi restaurant and forced to be a guard outside the door.

Bai Ning Bing did not know of his existence.

But Tie Dao Ku recognised Bai Ning Bing.

From the Bai clan arrest warrant, he had already engraved their appearances deep into his heart.

Now that he saw Bai Ning Bing, he was exhilarated.

Heaven is kind to me, heaven has eyes, giving me a chance to take revenge so quickly!

But after his exhilaration, came intense rage.

Bai Ning Bing's 'who are you' triggered the rage, hatred, humiliation, grievance in Tie Dao Ku, pouring out of a volcano like molten lava!

You murderer, killing my young master, causing me to nearly die, and caused me to be forced into being a guard for a brothel, causing me to be seen by a friend, and losing my reputation.

These were all caused by you, you culprit, And you, you don't know who I am!

"Ahhhh!" Tie Dao Ku screamed in fury, his neck turning red from shouting, as intense killing intent burst out of his body.

Ding!

The battle started, and Tie Dao Ku did not hesitate, charging towards Bai Ning Bing.

Feeling her enemy's intense killing intent, Bai Ning Bing squinted as she snorted coldly, rushing towards him as well.

The two got closer rapidly, almost instantly appearing before each other.

Iron hand Gu! Hand blade Gu!

At once, Tie Dao Ku's hands became iron, and the edges of his palms became sharp blades.

Ice edge Gu!

Bai Ning Bing placed her palms together, and split them apart, instantly forming a blade of pure ice.

Clang!

A crisp sound, and the iron hand blade collided with the frosty iceblade.

The two crossed swords, and as they travelled five to six steps, Bai Ning Bing twisted her waist and flicked her wrist; three icicles flew towards Tie Dao Ku's back.

Tie Dao Ku growled, forcefully turning around his body and swinging his palms around, smashing the icicles into bits, then ferociously charging towards Bai Ning Bing again.

Bai Ning Bing's gaze became serious.

After that short exchange, she had understood that this was a fierce opponent.

"Very good, I can use him to assess the quality of my Gu set." Bai Ning Bing's battle intent rose.

She was not a monster like Fang Yuan, without such a massive pool of experience, she could only trial and error on her own. Entering the battle stage, one was to earn primeval stones, and two was to develop her own unique set of Gu worms.

Swift shadow Gu!

At this time, Tie Dao Ku's speed increased, leaving a trace of shadows behind him like a tail.

His acceleration allowed him to reach Bai Ning Bing in a moment.

"So fast!" Bai Ning Bing's pupils shrunk.

Tie Dao Ku had already stretched out both arms, raising them high above his head, then splitting down, like an axe, chopping towards Bai Ning Bing.

Even before he hit his target, the wind already blew Bai Ning Bing's silver hair into the air, as her face felt a chill.

The arms were like two sharp blades expanding in Bai Ning Bing's vision.

Tie Dao Ku first used iron hand Gu, then used the hand blade Gu to cause the edges of his palm to become sharp as a blade.

Not only this, the two sides of his forearm also became dull blades.

Tie Dao Ku's attack was strong and heavy, with unparalleled sharpness, even a huge rock could be broken, not to mention a fragile human body.

Even with her ice muscles jade bones, Bai Ning Bing did not dare to take it head on, forced to dodge.

Bai Ning Bing retreated as she guarded with her iceblade.

Tie Dao Ku rotated his arms, like a moving windmill, sending his hand blades slashing towards her.

Clang clang clang...

Iceblade and hand blade collided and continuously gave off a loud noise.

Bai Ning Bing created another iceblade, dual wielding, as she retreated and blocked Tie Dao Ku's furious assault.

Ice edge Gu was the advancement of the rank two iceblade Gu, it had a tougher body and sharper edge.

But Tie Dao Ku also used rank three Gu, using the combination of iron hand Gu and hand blade Gu, with the hand blade Gu was the core of his entire Gu set.

At once, ice shards flew into the air, as the iceblade was filled with cracks.

Tie Dao Ku whipped up a steel blade tornado, he was older and more experienced than Bai Ning Bing, with his anger unleashed, he attacked without rest, forcing Bai Ning Bing to retreat over a hundred steps.

Tie Dao Ku was picked by the Tie clan young master and acted as his right hand man, he had to have some outstanding ability.

If that Tie clan young master became the clan leader in the future, Tie Dao Ku would be like Wei Yang, promoted to an elder in the clan!

Bai Ning Bing was fiercely suppressed, she was bound to lose if this continued. There were numerous cuts on her body as blood poured out.

"This cannot go on... frost breath Gu!" Bai Ning Bing activated her primeval essence, injecting them into her tongue.

There was a six sided ice flower symbol on her tongue, it was the insignia of the frost breath Gu.

Her cheeks puffed up as she exhaled a breath of icy wind.

The light blue icy wind engulfed Tie Dao Ku, causing his arms and half his chest to have a layer of frost.

Coldness assaulted him, as Tie Dao Ku shivered, like he was doused with a bucket of icy water in the hot summer weather, causing his attacks to slow down.

Bai Ning Bing quickly jumped back, pulling distance from Tie Dao Ku.

Tie Dao Ku still wanted to get closer to her, but why would Bai Ning Bing give him the opportunity?

Icicle Gu!

Snowball Gu!

Many icicles and snowballs formed, shooting towards Tie Dao Ku, attacking him like a torrent, as Tie Dao Ku's assault was forcefully terminated.

Bai Ning Bing breathed out in relief, Tie Dao Ku's momentum was broken, as she finally caught her breath.

"This person is obviously bad at long range and specializes in close range. But how could I lose in sword technique? Ice crystal Gu!"

Bai Ning Bing was arrogant and proud, her silver hair fluttered as a fierce light shot out of her jewel-like blue eyes.

The cuts earlier had already stopped bleeding, this was the effect of the ice muscles to stop bleeding.

Ice crystal Gu was Bai Ning Bing's vital Gu, once activated, the sound of water freezing could be heard all over Bai Ning Bing's body.

Her flesh and blood vanished, converted into a diamond-like crystal form.

At a glance, she was like an ice sculpture, her expression disappeared, her cold appearance became even more emotionless. Her eyes stopped blinking and on the surface of her eyes, there was a thick layer of transparent frost.

Her body grew slightly, her height increasing by two to three inches, and her entire aura had a dominating coldness.

Tie Dao Ku's ferocious attacks earlier gave her no time to activate the ice crystal Gu, but now she finally could.

When Gu Masters use Gu, they would have to multitask.

Be it battles or refinement, this was so. Even the strong Fang Yuan could only do three things at once with no error, he could not split his mind into four for a long time, otherwise mistakes would occur.

Earlier, Bai Ning Bing had placed all her attention on Tie Dao Ku's attacks, she concentrated extensively and could not think of anything else. If she activated her ice crystal Gu during that period, she would definitely be distracted and expose a weakness. If Tie Dao Ku made use of it, the consequences would be severe.

Making any changes would require attention, in contrast, doing the same thing only needed one thought.

"It is my turn now."

She lightly shouted, taking huge steps and carried a cool killing intent, charging at Tie Dao Ku.

Clang clang clang...

The two collided and unleashed their attacks.

Fighting offense with offense!

Bai Ning Bing held her iceblades and waved them around, as Tie Dao Ku used his arms as blades, more agile and flexible.

In a few breath's time, they had unleashed over a hundred attacks, the white iceblade and the black steel hand blade, struck lightning fast, almost turning into a blur black and white silhouette.

The surrounding spectators were not many, seeing this, they breathed in deeply and were shocked.

Evenly matched!

Bai Ning Bing had turned into ice crystal, her body was made of hard ice, when Tie Dao Ku hit her, he could only make a small scar on the ice.

In contrast, Tie Dao Ku had a very outstanding defensive Gu, causing him to turn into a black iron man, when the iceblades hit him, they create slashing marks.

But gradually, Tie Dao Ku felt increasing pressure.

Bai Ning Bing had stop defending, and concentrated on attacking, thus, her attacks became increasingly sharper.

"This person is improving so much amidst battle. She had such outstanding battle talent, she is using me as a practice dummy to refine her sword technique!" Tie Dao Ku was stunned in his heart, he could feel Bai Ning Bing's attacks, becoming more refined and precise under pressure, as their force increased.

His inner thoughts caused his movements to slow, and finally, Bai Ning Bing found her chance to strike.

"A chance!" Bai Ning Bing's eyes shone brilliantly, as her right hand slashed towards Tie Dao Ku's brain.

Tie Dao Ku could not dodge in time, thus had to defend against it. He was very confident of his defense, every close range Gu Master would not have weak defenses, as long as his eyes stayed intact, there was no issue.

But at this time, Bai Ning Bing activated a Gu in her aperture.

Ice explosion Gu!

Bam!

The iceblade in Bai Ning Bing's right hand exploded intensely.

This change caught Tie Dao Ku off guard, as the force of the explosion tore through his defenses.

He subconsciously closed his eyes, as an intense pain assaulted him.

"Oh no, it's a trap!" Tie Dao Ku's heart sank, he had a rich battle experience, meticulous and courageous, encountering this, he did not fluster but quickly used the swift shadow Gu to move backwards.

Bai Ning Bing did not let go of such an opportunity, also activating her movement Gu and chased after him, hacking and slashing.

Tie Dao Ku could hear her movements, with his experience and keen senses, he blocked most of Bai Ning Bing's attacks.

But Bai Ning Bing held the upper hand, at this moment, there was little hope of Tie Dao Ku turning this around.

As he retreated, he barely opened his eyes, finding his left eye blind and his right heavily injured, as his vision was dyed red.

"I admit defeat!" He screamed his throat out.

"The battle has been decided, both sides stop now!" The hosting Gu Master quickly announced.

Bai Ning Bing laughed coldly, attacking more urgently.

But suddenly, a huge invisible force pulled her and Tie Dao Ku apart. In Shang clan city battle stage, there were obviously defensive measures.

As long as the hosting Gu Master reacted in time and acts, there will hardly be any killings on purpose.

"Hmph!" Bai Ning Bing showed displeasure, she felt this force holding onto her, not allowing her to move.

She had to stop.

Tie Dao Ku breathed roughly, removing his defense and quickly healing himself.

He also had a healing Gu, but it could not heal his left eye, he could only stabilize his right eye's condition and try to preserve it.

"This scoundrel is truly shameless, I got tricked by her and almost died. Damn it! Too hateful!" Tie Dao Ku still had some afterfear mixed with rage and hatred.

Chapter 299: Shut up, you fat pig!

"This match is over. I have consumed seventy percent of my primeval essence, only twenty percent is left..." After obtaining victory, Bai Ning Bing left the battle stage.

She summarized her battle learnings while walking.

She would summarize every match she fought. The battle with Tie Dao Ku today, although she felt a pity that she was not able to kill him, her gains were quite great.

"The battle just now was intense but it lasted only a brief period. However, it expended a lot of my primeval essence, come to think about it I have A grade aptitude primeval essence recovery speed. During an intense battle, my set of Gu worms clearly has high primeval essence consumption issues."

Many Gu Masters faced difficulties in this aspect when they organized their Gu worms.

Who did not like powerful Gu worms? But often, those Gu worms with higher efficacy had higher consumption rates of primeval essence.

Of course there were Gu worms who were powerful and consumed less primeval essence. But they were all rare Gu worms and were very expensive.

Bai Ning Bing had extra money on hand, but it was not a lot. She was smart and after quickly realizing her situation, she started saving money.

Before, she would spend money like water and had no clear concept of the value of primeval stones. That was because the clan spent all their efforts in cultivating her.

Now, she was in charge of her own money during in this period of time, her awareness had a significant transformation.

While Fang Yuan was growing, Bai Ning Bing too was improving rapidly in all aspects.

"It would be good if I had Fang Yuan's heavenly essence treasure lotus. At least in rank three stage, there would be no need to worry about primeval essence expenditure." Bai Ning Bing thought of this, inevitably having a feeling of jealousy.

Fang Yuan walked the strength path. Strength path Gu consumed the least primeval essence and with his ninety percent A grade aptitude, he had an abundant source of primeval essence. Heavenly essence treasure lotus could not display its true value in his hands, it was simply casting pearls before a swine!

"What if I buy heavenly essence treasure lotus from Fang Yuan?"

Bai Ning Bing shook her head, quickly throwing away this impractical thought from her mind.

She understood too well what kind of person Fang Yuan was.

She had never seen him suffer a loss, if someday she was able to take heavenly essence treasure lotus from his hands, then it would definitely be after she pays a heavy price.

"Without the help of the heavenly essence treasure lotus, I can only reduce the Gu worms on me."

After carefully thinking it, Bai Ning Bing decided to give up on snowball Gu.

Snowball Gu was a high tier Gu in rank three and she had planned to use it as a long range attacking method.

However, this Gu expended quite a bit of primeval essence.

It was still okay if she only used it one time. But how could she only send out one snowball in the midst of intense battle?

Five to six snowballs after, her primeval essence consumption would amount to a lot.

"I will give up snowball Gu and keep icicle Gu. Icicle Gu might only be rank two, but it can also restrict the opponent. It would be a threat if I use it with ice explosion Gu."

Ice explosion Gu was a rank three Gu which could detonate ice and form an instantaneous destructive power.

The larger, older, and colder the ice, the greater the power of the explosion.

She was able to establish her dominance in the battle against Tie Dao Ku because of this ice explosion Gu.

Of course, if the ice explosion spread towards Bai Ning Bing, she would also receive injuries. But if she turned her body into ice crystal, the severeness of injuries would fall to a low level.

Thinking of the splendid battle just before, Bai Ning Bing licked her lips in excitement.

A normal ice path Gu Master pursued defensive or trapping abilities. Only those like fire path Gu Masters or thunder path Gu Masters focused on explosive strength.

However, Bai Ning Bing did the very opposite. The inspiration for it was the ice explosion Gu and she had not expected the results to be so good, beyond her original estimation.

"Ice explosion Gu is brilliant and very effective in battle, I will continue to make full use of it later." Bai Ning Bing inwardly planned.

She used to advocate a direct and straightforward fighting style; fierce and swift, slashing everything with her ice wind. However, she was influenced after being in contact with Fang Yuan all the time, and now was interested in making treacherous moves.

She was interested in everything splendid in this world.

"Ice crystal Gu, Ice edge Gu, Icicle Gu, Ice explosion Gu...can this set defeat Fang Yuan?"

Bai Ning Bing considered this, considering Fang Yuan as her number one imaginary enemy.

"Fang Yuan walks the strength path, he has all-out effort Gu and is much more domineering in close combat than that guy just before. With my current methods, it won't be easy to win against him. Unless I can regain my killer move."

Bai Ning Bing's killer move was her self created ice blade storm. She had created this using revolving Gu paired with whirlwind Gu and ice blade Gu, forming the icy tornado.

But now Bai Ning Bing's vision had widened, this move was already old fashioned. Ice blade storm could bully rank two, but would be substandard in rank three realm.

These days, she had been thinking of ways to improve and polish her killer move, but was not able to get any ideas.

She suddenly thought of something and her pace quickened: "Oh right, today is Fang Yuan's first battle after advancing to fourth inner city. It shouldn't be too late if I go see now!"

...

"Kill, kill him!"

"Zhu Ba, finish this kid quick!"

"The way I see it, Zhu Ba doesn't even need to make a move and this Fang Zheng kid won't be able to bear it."

"Hehe, this kid is in trouble. He ran into Zhu Ba who happens to subdue his strength path on his first match!"

The battle stage was lively and full of people.

"Fang Yuan's match has attracted many spectators. Well, the battle zone doesn't have any restriction regarding the spectator's cultivation. As long as the Gu Master has money, he can come watch." Bai Ning Bing arrived to the battle stage and looked around her before concentrating towards the stage.

This was a mid-scale battle stage and the terrain was ordinary stone tiled floor.

Fang Yuan and a heavily built Gu Master were fighting fiercely. According to the spectators' comments, Fang Yuan's opponent should be that Zhu Ba.

Zhu Ba was huge, almost three meters tall. His whole body was full of fats, making his head and limbs look smaller. He was like a enlarged version of the Earth's sumo wrestlers.

In this world, whether it was a Gu Master or a mortal, their height normally did not cross two meters. Zhu Ba's height was clearly the result of using some Gu worm.

This was quite normal in fact.

Many flying type Gu Masters would make their bones hollow to reduce the weight. Some earth burrowing Gu Masters would use bone shrinking Gu to turn into a dwarf; like this, their energy consumption would be much lower when drilling a tunnel.

Bai Ning Bing did not have much knowledge about Zhu Ba, but from the continuous comments of the spectators around her, he understood Zhu Ba's methods.

Zhu Ba was a defensive Gu Master.

The fats in his body provided him with a strong defense.

Fang Yuan moved around Zhu Ba, punching and kicking him. When Zhu Ba received the strikes, the fat on his body shook like water ripples and dispersed the force of the attacks onto all parts of his body. Then with the use of a Gu, this force was gathered together and through a counter-shock method, it was returned back to Fang Yuan.

According to sources, Zhu Ba received his Gu from a demonic inheritance. It was uncertain because he had never exposed the amount of Gu he had and their names.

However, his method of fighting made people helpless, particularly effective against strength path Gu Masters.

"Fang Zheng, take a rest, it is no use. I can send eighty percent of the force of your attacks back at you through counter-shock. Punches and kicks do nothing to me, instead you will be injured. Have you still not realized it?" Zhu Ba spoke in a low muffled voice.

He directly sat on the battle stage, letting Fang Yuan attack him, giving an immovable presence.

Boar phantom, brown bear phantom and crocodile phantom constantly flashed above Fang Yuan. It was the reappearance of the scene when he viciously beat the mountain back toad, but Zhu Ba was indifferent.

No matter how much strength you used, the other did not even glance at you, who would not be discouraged by such a situation?

However, Fang Yuan persevered and continued to move and attack Zhu Ba without saying a word.

It had been like this since the match started and by now, fifteen minutes had passed.

"Puff!" Fang Yuan let out a breath of turbid air and suddenly took back a step, stopping his attacks.

Blood seeped out from the corners of his lips; the counter-shock force from Zhu Ba jolted his organs, inflicting internal injuries on him.

He had iron bones, steel tendons, canopy Gu and there was also golden shield Gu, but this shock passed through all his defense and attacked his internal organs.

His internal organs were not strengthened at all, even though he was healing them with self-reliance Gu, the injuries were getting heavier.

Fang Yuan stopped his offensive, the counter shock force also dissipated. Several breaths later, his internal organs were completely healed.

The offensive resumed!

He took a strong step and began his attacks; his fists smashed like a meteor, bringing with it the sound of the wind. The fats in Zhu Ba shook once again, creating ripples and sending it back.

"Fang Zheng, you have a healing Gu, but so do I. You are suffering eighty percent of the attack, while I only receive twenty percent of the damage. Your consumption is more than mine, it is better to just admit defeat." Zhu Ba continued to persuade.

Fang Yuan only attacked, without replying.

When blood started seeping out again, he stopped the offensive and used self-reliance Gu to recover.

Although he eliminated the strength of a boar, he added in bull strength, horse strength and half a turtle strength; self-reliance Gu's effect had surpassed flesh-bone.

This state continued to persist and the spectators were starting to get bored, some even yawned.

"Too boring..."

"I really wonder why Fang Zheng is putting in so much effort."

"Today, Zhu Ba also looks somewhat abnormal, why hasn't he attacked?"

"Hasn't this been his style all along? First defend and waste his opponent's primeval essence and fighting spirit, then make his move, beating down his opponent."

"The problem lies here, Fang Zheng has too much energy, he has been attacking for so long with no results but he doesn't look the least bit discouraged. He is a strength cultivator, so his primeval essence consumption is also small. When will this stalemate end?"

"You guys can't see what is going on? Zhu Ba is playing with the newbie."

These words immediately caused the surrounding people to laugh.

To these Gu Masters who hung out in the battle zone all year round, Fang Yuan was indeed a very inexperienced newbie.

"Fang Zheng, there is no meaning in continuing this. I have no interest in your all-out effort Gu, I don't want to bully a newbie as a senior. It will be better for you to retreat, I promise I won't choose your Gu worms." Zhu Ba chuckled.

He had received Fang Yuan's attacks which contained the boar's collision force, the crocodile's biting force and the brown bear's smacking force, but he was still able to laugh.

"What kind of strength is this!"

"Indeed worthy of being rank eight in fourth inner city."

"His strength is the real deal."

The audiences were truly moved.

"Shut up, you fat pig!" Fang Yuan suddenly shouted.

The battle stage went silent.

Chapter 300: Fang Yuan vs Zhu Ba (1)

"He... he actually dared to scold senior Zhu Ba?"

"This newbie is too arrogant."

"Lord Zhu Ba, teach him a lesson, let him know the depths of heaven and earth!"

After the short silence, the audience flared up.

"Young man, you should learn humility. I tried to persuade you with good intentions; nevermind if you don't listen to it, but you still cursed me. How can a person behave like this? In the end, you will run into walls everywhere and no one will help you." Zhu Ba sighed.

Fang Yuan laughed loudly: "Are you concerned about me, or are you just afraid to attack? More likely, you can only passively defend my attacks. Your ability to send counter-shock force to injure me while defending is really amazing but how many Gu are you controlling to maintain such a defense? At least three? Can't concentrate enough to attack while defending? I have already seen through your tricks, do you think I am like those idiot spectators?!"

As he spoke, the spectators got furious and started shouting.

"What nonsense is this!"

"He dares to call us idiots, my insight is much wiser than yours."

"This kid is overflowing with arrogance. Senior Zhu Ba, he is treating your kindness as dirt, please quickly teach him a lesson."

Zhu Ba's expression changed and said in a grave tone: "Young man, since you are so ignorant, I will teach you a lesson to teach you reality. This is a good thing for you."

He then moved.

This movement was not a small action!

His whole body curled into an enormous meatball and rolled towards Fang Yuan.

At the same time a pale black blade aura wrapped around the enormous ball.

As the enormous ball rolled, stone slabs split open and stone fragments flew. The crushing attack fused with the sharp blade aura, further increased in might making people feel the urge to dodge.

"It appeared, Lord Zhu Ba's killing move — rolling blade meat!" The Gu Master spectators shouted with excitement.

Bai Ning Bing's gaze concentrated: "A movement type rolling meat Gu with blade aura Gu? A normal person would not be able to unleash such power but Zhu Ba's enormous body can amplify his attacking strength!"

"Couldn't endure it anymore?" Facing Zhu Bai's violent offense, Fang Yuan was not afraid but pleased instead, his lips outlining a trace of madness.

Vertical crash Gu!

Boar phantom!

Abruptly, he charged straight towards the giant ball!

"Has this kid gone mad?"

"Facing this attack head-on, does he not want his life?!"

"Someone is going to die!"

The audience were stunned.

The two sides collided; meat ball's charge immediately slowed down while Fang Yuan was sent flying before falling heavily on the ground.

"Look, this is what happens when you overestimate yourself."

"Eh? This kid didn't die!"

Fang Yuan wiped off the bloodstains on the corner of his lips and jumped up.

The giant ball charged towards Fang Yuan again. Fang Yuan gave a loud laugh before charging again.

Thump.

A dull thud and Fang Yuan was sent flying again.

Thud!

Sent flying once more.

Thud!!

Sent flying yet again!!

"This match is already set. Fang Zheng might have all-out effort Gu, but he unfortunately met an opponent who counters him." Someone commented, gloating in Fang Yuan's misfortune.

"It is difficult to overcome Zhu Ba's killer move. As his rolling speed increased, his striking force also became stronger. Actually, Fang Zheng's method was correct, to stop Zhu Ba's momentum immediately. But the way he chose to do it was too forceful." Another spectator sighed and shook their head.

"I have never seen such a stupid guy. Choosing to ram into Zhu Ba like this, most of the strength is returned back to him as counter-shock." Another spectator scoffed.

"This kid shouldn't be able to get up anymore. Eh? He actually got up!"

Fang Yuan was sent flying again and again, but also stood up each time.

His injuries were not light, but self-reliance Gu gave him potent sustainability.

"Still so stubborn, then die!" Zhu Ba let out an angry roar and fiercely rammed at Fang Yuan.

Vertical crash Gu!

Fang Yuan did not change his battle tactic. Boar phantom flashed above his head.

The two sides collided like meteors.

However, this time, Fang Yuan was not sent flying, instead his fist wedged deeply into the meatball. Rather it was the meatball that shook violently, as blade aura moved rampantly and slashed Fang Yuan like a dark waterfall.

Fang Yuan was ruthlessly sent flying, as the blade aura was completely expended.

Canopy Gu suffered heavy damage, the white light armor flickered weakly before dissipating completely.

Fang Yuan's whole body was bathed in blood, deep and long injuries on all parts of his body as if he had been hacked by countless sharp knives. He was not like Bai Ning Bing with the defense of her ice muscles, but still the tendons in his body were mostly intact and there was also no damage to his bones.

Self-reliance Gu!

Fang Yuan activated it and his blood loss immediately came to a stop, new flesh grew and the wounds began healing. However, the recovery of his tendons were slightly slower.

Bai Ning Bing's eyes flashed as she analyzed inwardly: "Without the canopy Gu, it would be difficult for Fang Yuan to win this battle by just relying on self-reliance Gu's recovery... eh?"

Right at this time, golden rays of light flashed around Fang Yuan.

The light condensed and formed into a light armor: Golden Shield Gu!

"This kid has quite a few defensive Gu!"

"First it was canopy Gu and now it is golden shield Gu; both are great defensive rank three Gu. This kid is rich!"

Golden shield Gu could not be used at the same time as canopy Gu; it was always stored inside Fang Yuan and now it showed itself for the first time.

Bai Ning Bing was slightly dazed before coming back to her senses. She had gotten many new Gu worms, Fang Yuan certainly would also do the same. To Fang Yuan, golden shield Gu was slightly better than canopy Gu since it was more suitable for his strength path methods.

"Even if you have golden shield Gu, the result remains the same." Zhu Ba's deep voice came from within the meatball.

The meatball charged towards Fang Yuan, sending him flying again.

"How many times do I have to say it till you understand? You can't defeat me, you will only bring disgrace upon yourself if you continue." Zhu Ba sighed.

"Enough, how long are you going to keep acting?" Fang Yuan stood up and wiped the bloodstains on his lips. Others felt no hope for him, but he saw victory waving at him!

It was time.

Fang Yuan lowered his eyes, covering his pupils which were flashing with a sharp light.

Charge!

He again charged head-on.

"Ungrateful kid, then I shall show it to you the true difference between us." Zhu Ba rolled towards him.

Horizontal charge Gu.

Fang Yuan suddenly charged horizontally and evaded.

Vertical crash Gu.

After charging fifty steps, he quickly turned his direction and charged.

Howl!

In the moments before collision, he activated all-out effort Gu; a brown bear phantom flashed.

Under this attack, the meatball's skin and flesh folded over and over like the waves in river and sent the counter-shock back towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was sent back several steps before he charged forward again.

He unleashed violent attacks while constantly moving around the meatball, all his punches and kicks were targeted at different areas. This greatly raised the difficulty for Zhu Ba to defend.

Right now, Fang Yuan's attacks were fiercer than ever before!

Zhu Ba controlled his Gu worms frantically till he was no longer able to cope with it. The meatball trembled crazily but this time, it was not able to return even a bit of the force as counter-shock.

Howl!

Zhu Ba was extremely furious, he cancelled his meatball form and turned back to his human form. Blade aura formed again and flew towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was overjoyed at this; the more Gu Zhu Ba used, more difficult it would be for him to control all of them.

Zhu Ba's mind was already in a mess!

The opponents he faced before would admit defeat after being struck several times. Even those persevering ones lost their fighting spirit after experiencing Zhu Ba's rolling attack.

But unfortunately, he met Fang Yuan.

There were many types of men in this world. Some loved their family and some had high ambitions.

Among them, there was a type of man: After he has a clear goal and ambition, he cannot be stopped even if the whole world turned against him!

Fang Yuan was such a man!

No one could stop him, not to mention just merely this Zhu Ba.

Horse phantom!

Vertical crash Gu!

His speed increased suddenly, rapidly charging fifty steps. Horse strength increased his speed by thirty percent more than boar strength.

Horse hooves hit the floor and sped forward!

Zhu Ba did not expect Fang Yuan to still have this trump card and due to being caught unprepared, his blade aura hit the air behind Fang Yuan.

As for Fang Yuan, he was already right before Zhu Ba.

There were no words. Just...

One punch!

This punch was incomparably powerful, exploding even the air around it, the heavy recoil from the punch destroyed the stone tiles under Fang Yuan's feet into countless shards and even shook the whole stage.

Zhu Ba's fats trembled violently to disperse the force of the punch around his body before attempting to return eighty percent of the force back to Fang Yuan.

However, Fang Yuan immediately followed with another punch.

Zhu Ba's physique was huge and was poor at agility. The punch ruthless hit his body.

"I... I... counter-shock!" Zhu Ba opened his eyes wide as he did his best to manipulate several Gu in his body.

However, he had just used all his concentration to manipulate blade aura Gu, and now he was activating other Gu at the same time; it might be okay if he was at peak condition, but right now his mind was in disarray and his mental state had already weakened due to manipulating all the Gu for such a long time.

A flaw appeared.

The fats on Zhu Ba's body that was shaking like water ripples stopped.

His defense crumbled!

He was still dispersing the force of Fang Yuan's previous force and so had to stiffly endure this punch.

An intense pain assaulted him, causing his head to spin. The dispersing process of the force of Fang Yuan's punch was broken. Eighty percent of the force exploded in all parts of his body.

Backlash!

In that instant, Zhu Ba's heart suddenly stopped due to the intense pain!

Fang Yuan's fierce gaze flashed, he had been waiting for this moment for so long and he finally created it forcefully.

Grabbing the opportunity, and strike!

Punches were thrown out like the wind. Bear phantom, boar phantom, crocodile phantom and horse phantom flashed in turns in mid-air.

Wind whistled, beast phantoms roared, golden armor covered Fang Yuan's whole body as his punches exploded out with unrivalled fierceness.

Under everyone's astonished gazes, the 'giant' Zhu Ba was beaten into retreating and howling in pain by the 'dwarf' Fang Yuan.

However, Zhu Ba's extremely obese body forced him to become a punching bag.

Fang Yuan's vigor rose continually, his unyielding ferocity birthed a feeling in all the spectators that this person could not be stopped.

The intense pain surged like a tsunami and struck Zhu Ba head-on, almost drowning his consciousness.

His thoughts were in a mess and he found it even more difficult to activate his Gu to increase his defense.

Fang Yuan firmly held the upper hand and Zhu Ba was already starting to show the white part of his eyes.

"How can this be? Just now, it was clearly..."

"Was Fang Zheng right about him?"

The audience were in an uproar, the shocking swap of their predicament stupefied them.

Chapter 301: Fang Yuan vs Zhu Ba (2)

Looking at the number eight expert in fourth inner city senior Zhu Ba, beaten till he vomited blood by a newcomer, this scene overturned many people's expectations!

But Zhu Ba was still an experienced veteran, he suddenly shouted, stretching out both arms and tightly hugged Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan felt that he was wrapped by cotton, the fat meat squeezed at him from all directions, causing him to be unable to move.

He punched and kicked, hitting flesh with every hit. Zhu Ba's bones were broken, and his flesh was beaten to pulp, mashed under his skin.

But Zhu Ba gritted his teeth, forcefully trapping Fang Yuan. He was almost beaten senseless by Fang Yuan, but the only clear thought on his mind reminded him, if he let this monster out, he would be in deep trouble.

As the space around him was squeezed, Fang Yuan snorted, showing no fear as he activated the all-out effort Gu.

A green bull phantom appeared in mid air.

"A new beast phantom!" Bai Ning Bing saw this and her pupils shrunk.

"Secretly, Fang Yuan had already grown this powerful. If I go against him, with just my Gu worms, I'm afraid..." Bai Ning Bing's heart sank.

The bull strength was strong and lasting, Fang Yuan stretched out his arms and pulled Zhu Ba's fat arms that were tightly coiled around him.

Comparing strength, how could Zhu Ba be his match.

Zhu Ba tried his best, his arms were shivering, and sweat poured down like rain, but he could not stop Fang Yuan.

"Damn, damn it, if he gets loose, I am done for!" Zhu Ba felt an intense feeling of unease, the intense premonition of death was causing him to feel extremely scared.

"I... I admit defeat!" He screamed.

Compared to his life, what was fame?

The hosting Gu Master immediately used the battle stage to forcefully separate the two.

"The battle has been decided, Fang Zheng wins, Zhu Ba loses!" The hosting Gu Master announced.

The crowd gasped.

"He actually won!"

"Zhu Ba is just a paper tiger, pretending to be strong on the outside, I was almost fooled by him."

"Zhu Ba can't even beat a newcomer, how can he be the number eight expert, this is truly shameful for our fourth inner city battle stage..."

Zhu Ba's pathetic state now, destroyed the image he had painstakingly built up over the years.

Bai Ning Bing heard the chattering, and shook her head internally: "Zhu Ba has been an expert for many years, he is definitely strong, unfortunately he met Fang Yuan. Zhu Ba's fighting style was countering his opponent's attacks. First using defense to waste his opponents' primeval essence and stamina, then counterattacking to win. But he fought against Fang Yuan, this monster, as a strength cultivator, coupled with the heavenly essence treasure lotus, he has endless primeval essence. Stamina is also his forte as a strength cultivator... the two countered each other in different aspects, but the tougher one won!"

Speaking of which, it was rather ironic.

Bai Ning Bing changed her style, becoming more scheming and devious. Fang Yuan was also changing, from his former scheming style, he started fighting with raw power, a forthright style that goes all in.

The two seemed to have swapped styles.

Zhu Ba fell and admitted defeat, losing to Fang Yuan, his reputation was completely tarnished.

"Good job." Below the stage, Wei Yang laughed as he said to Fang Yuan.

This was Fang Yuan's first battle in fourth inner city, thus Wei Yang came to watch.

Fang Yuan's performance was out of Wei Yang's expectations.

Wei Yang was very concerned about Fang Yuan, one because of the clan leader's orders and mission, but also because of their friendship.

"Maybe you were born for the strength path." At the banquet, Wei Yang exclaimed.

He patted Fang Yuan's shoulders: "I walked on the strength path in the past, but failed. Now, I see hope in you, do you know, many eyes are watching you now. Continue walking on this path without doubt!"

Fang Yuan nodded.

He knew his circumstance.

He had just risen to fourth inner city, and met Zhu Ba, defeating him. Getting famous overnight, many were taken aback.

This battle had just ended, but he had received many people's forceful challenge.

These people were mostly strength path Gu Masters, coming after his all-out effort Gu.

The better he performs, the greater the value of the all-out effort Gu, and the more greed it attracts. Right now, those that were coming for him were all experts in fourth inner city.

Henceforth, his predicament would only get tougher.

But the tougher it got, the more his battle intent surged, as Fang Yuan felt his blood burning.

Just this level of risk and difficulty, what are they? How can they stop me, Fang Yuan's advancement!

"In this world, nobody is capable of ending my ambitions!"

Eight days later, he fought Jin Bian Yuan, after fighting evenly for a while, he unleashed his beast phantoms, destroying Jin Bian Yuan's core defensive Gu worm, killing him on the spot.

Ten days later, Liao Hua Dong who is famed for aggressive attacks, fought against Fang Yuan. Fang Yuan fought attack with more attacks, taking him down head-on. If not for the hosting Gu Master, Liao Hua Dong would have been dead.

Seventeen days later, Zhong De who has the strength of five tigers fought an exciting match against Fang Yuan, but was beaten like a dead dog, lying on the ground, motionlessly.

...

Time continued to pass by, as Fang Yuan won again and again.

There were many experts in fourth inner city, but Fang Yuan's growth was insane.

Be it cultivation, addition of new Gu worms, or other these aspects.

The more he won, the more primeval stones he received.

He fought his way through, advancing bravely, every match was a treat to watch for the spectators.

But on the other hand, he was very vigilant. He had never looked down on any opponent, getting all the information he needed beforehand. With Wei Yang and Li Ran, one having authority while the other one has an underground network, Fang Yuan could gather all the information necessary before a battle.

He was not a brainless brute, he only accepted four matches a month. Although forceful challenge was a rule, to prevent intentional targeting, the challenged Gu Master can have eight days of rest time after every match.

Fang Yuan used this time to prepare himself adequately, ignoring the taunting from others. He focused on cultivating, the battle stage's purpose was to assess and train himself, as well as a source of revenue.

He had become famous.

His victories caused his name to spread wide.

The strongest newcomer in history!

The star of hope in reviving strength path!

The ferocious and ruthless beast!

...

Many titles were bestowed onto him, depicting his traits: Newcomer but has an amazing win record, owns the all-out effort Gu, ruthless and cruel, never letting go of an enemy he can kill, and others.

Three months passed like this.

This day, in the secret room.

Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing sat opposite each other.

Bai Ning Bing placed both palms on Fang Yuan's back, injecting her snow silver primeval essence into him.

The primeval essence were converted over by the flesh bone unity Gu, after some losses, they were injected into Fang Yuan's aperture.

In the aperture, primeval essence ebbed and flowed, as waves crashed and assaulted the aperture walls.

Swish swish swish...

The tides rose and fell, never ending.

The white light walls were assaulted and started to change.

A moment later, the light walls were replaced by water walls, as the white light flowed like water, causing the aperture walls to become thicker and stronger.

From rank three initial stage, he advanced to middle stage!

Fang Yuan only used a few months.

This was all due to the flesh bone unity Gu and Bai Ning Bing. The higher the Gu Master's rank, the larger the difference between their cultivation across small realms. Bai Ning Bing was rank three peak stage, it was very helpful to Fang Yuan.

This speed, if exposed, would cause a great commotion. Even Fang Yuan who was knowledgeable felt secretly shocked.

But Bai Ning Bing, who was a former ten extreme physique and had a monsterous cultivation speed, did not feel any shock towards Fang Yuan's advancement.

If Bai Ning Bing was rank four, using the light gold primeval essence, Fang Yuan's cultivation speed would be increased further.

Feeling the change in Fang Yuan's aura, Bai Ning Bing knew he had succeeded and retracted her palm.

"So how, in a few days, you will reach fourth inner city battle stage. Are you interested in raising your cultivation to rank four?" Fang Yuan turned around and asked.

The higher Bai Ning Bing's cultivation was, the faster he could cultivate himself.

"No need, if you can stand firm with rank three cultivation and fight your way through, so can I." Bai Ning Bing snorted coldly, not showing any nice expressions Fang Yuan.

But at the end, she added: "My aptitude rose again, reaching ninety-two percent. At this rate, when are you going to give me the Yang Gu?"

"Oh. That's fast..." Fang Yuan was shocked, he knew a lot about the ten extreme aptitude, but the details were not in-depth.

Even though poison vow was removed, Bai Ning Bing still served a huge purpose.

"You don't have to worry, with me around, I can protect your life. We used the poison vow Gu before, even if you don't trust me, surely you trust the Gu's power?"

"Hmph." Bai Ning Bing did not rebuke him, these last few months she spent with Fang Yuan were the most peaceful period of her life. As the two worked hard together, and with the poison vow Gu allowing them to form an alliance. But it seems..."

"This guy, he's growing faster and gaining more rewards." Regarding this, Bai Ning Bing had a clear understanding of their differences.

Her improvement was large, but his was larger.

These few months, Fang Yuan not only gained the strength of a turtle, but also used the rank three bronze skin Gu, giving his skin another layer of defense.

Rank two bronze skin Gu can only give the Gu Master's skin increased defense for a limited period of time.

The rank three bronze skin Gu, used one's own body and grants this defense to their body permanently.

Now, Fang Yuan's skin is bronze color, like he had undergone a sun tan.

Iron bones, steel tendon, bronze skin, with golden shield Gu, Fang Yuan's defense was at initial success stage, even among third inner city battle stage, it is sufficient to deal with any strong foe.

As for the canopy Gu, Fang Yuan had already sold it. It overlapped with the golden shield Gu, and did not suit Fang Yuan's fighting style.

Just as Fang Yuan advanced to middle stage, a group of people arrived outside Shang clan city.

"Shang clan city... Gu Yue Fang Zheng is inside huh." Tie Ruo Nan thought as she walked ahead of everyone.

"Tie Dao Ku greets young master." Tie Dao Ku rapidly paid his respects.

Chapter 302: Tie Ruo Nan

"Tie Dao Ku, what happened to your eyes?" Tie Ruo Nan saw Tie Dao Ku wearing a black eyepatch and asked in surprise.

Tie Dao Ku showed an embarrassed expression, speaking the truth: "My eyes were injured by Bai Ning Bing."

A few months ago, he had a battle with Bai Ning Bing, and suffered a great setback.

Losing his left eye, his battle strength fell drastically, and with the hand blade Gu mercilessly taken by Bai Ning Bing, he was no longer her match.

But Tie Dao Ku did not give up.

He had a determined heart, gritting his teeth and relied on the battle stage, along with taking some jobs of escorting and investigating, to survive in Shang clan city.

He was like a lone wolf licking his wounds, as he observed Fang and Bai secretly, slowly gaining back his strength as well as reporting to the clan.

Precisely because of his letter, Tie Ruo Nan brought a team here personally.

"Bai Ning Bing... actually injured you. Tie Dao Ku, your intel had some errors, why did you not mention this in your letter?" Tie Ruo Nan frowned, slightly unhappy.

How could I have the face to say it...

Tie Dao Ku laughed bitterly, he was a rank three Gu Master, he had his pride and dignity.

But towards Tie Ruo Nan's accusation, he lowered his head, answering: "It was my mistake."

He was a proud man, but he was very respectful to Tie Ruo Nan.

It has been two years.

Two years ago, Tie Xue Leng's death was reported to the clan, causing them to fall into deep sorrow.

A rank five Gu Master was a great strength, standing at the peak of the mortal realm, even a huge clan like Tie clan would feel pain in losing one.

Moreover, this was the divine investigator Tie Xue Leng.

His name spread throughout the southern border, he was a symbol and a flag for Tie clan.

Tie Xue Leng's death was a loss to Tie clan, but also a loss to the entire righteous faction.

Just as the clan grieved, Tie Ruo Nan, as Tie Xue Leng's daughter, stood up.

She had been following her father, roaming the southern border. After returning to the clan, she challenged the Tie clan thirteen halls, defeating her foes in the arena battles and becoming one of the eight young masters in Tie clan. After taking over Tie clan's internal affairs, she cracked many cases, corruption and greed could not hide from her, as she brought the criminals to justice.

TIe Xue Leng fell, but Tie Ruo Nan rose, taking over her father's duty, and became the new rising star for the last two years in Tie clan.

Tie Ruo Nan's name started to travel wide, and even Tie Dao Ku, someone who was far away in Shang clan city, heard about her stories.

Tie clan and Shang clan had different policies, even if Tie Ruo Nan fails to attain the position of Tie clan leader, she will still be an important member, a great general protecting the mountain.

She was young, but already rank three upper stage. Her title of genius was true to its name.

Be it Tie Ruo Nan's current or future achievements, it was worth Tie Dao Ku's respect.

"Tie Mu, go see to his injuries." Tie Ruo Nan waved her hand, saying.

Tie Mu had a delicate face, he was the healing Gu Master in the team. He quickly went forward and checked Tie Dao Ku's eyes in front of everyone.

In just a few breath's, Tie Mu reported: "His eye is crippled, there is nothing I can do. To heal it, a rank five Gu Master is needed."

He was being humble, merely twenty-eight years old but already rank three peak stage, he was a clan elite from Tie clan's side branch.

Many people tried to recruit him, but he decided to serve Tie Ruo Nan instead.

These few years, Tie Ruo Nan had taken the role of young master, and her forces expanded, recruiting many talented elites into her faction, TIe Mu was only one of them.

"In Shang clan city, there is a rank five expert named Doctor Su Shou. Tie Dao Ku, take this money and go heal your eyes." Tie Ruo Nan took out a primeval elder Gu, and threw it to Tie Dao Ku.

"Thank you young master." Tie Dao Ku took the Gu and showed a grateful expression.

Doctor Su Shou's treatment fee was extremely expensive, he had scrimped and saved these few years, to save up enough money to heal his eyes.

But a hundred thousand primeval stones was not a small sum. Commodity prices in Shang clan city is high, and Tie Dao Ku had to buy a hand blade Gu, he had no opportunity to save enough money.

He straightened his back: "I have already reserved a garden estate for young master to stay in, please follow me."

But Tie Ruo Nan waved her hand: "No rush, bring me to Nan Qiu garden, in your report, you mentioned that Fang and Bai stayed at Nan Qiu garden right?"

"Erm... yes, that is so." Tie Dao Ku was stunned, not expecting Tie Ruo Nan to be so direct.

"Lead the way." Tie Ruo Nan instructed.

"Yes."

Tie Ruo Nan had a swift and decisive nature, but a moment later, she was denied entry.

"Sorry, my two masters are cultivating in their secret rooms." Nan Qiu garden's doorboy respectfully said.

"What, scared? Trying to hide inside!" Tie Dao Ku snorted in disdain.

The doorboy had been specially trained by Shang clan, he had great qualities, after giving Tie Dao Ku a look, he remaining guarding the door firmly, not letting them through.

Tie Ruo Nan was one of the young masters of the great Tie clan, she would not make a fuss towards a child.

She smiled, taking out an invitation, passing it to the doorboy: "No worry, pass them my invitation letter. I have some relationship with your masters, we will come again at night."

"I will definitely convey Lord's message, but they are in closed cultivation, I cannot guarantee when they will come out. They might not come out by dinner time." The doorboy reminded before they left.

Until dinner time, when Tie clan came again, they were rejected once more.

"I think this Fang and Bai are afraid of young master's grandeur, hiding inside afraid to show up."

"Maybe they are trying to display their authority, specially targeting us."

Tie clan gang guessed, speaking in indignance.

They had visited twice, but were treated like this. Did they really think so highly of themselves? Even Shang clan young master would need to leave his work and come to attend to the group.

"Do not be anxious, we will come again tomorrow morning." Tie Ruo Nan calmed the gang, handing out another invitation as she showed an expression deep in thought.

On the second morning, Nan Qiu garden closed shut again.

Tie clan gang's emotions were surging, almost breaking through by force, but were halted by Tie Ruo Nan, who handed out another invitation.

The group had just left, and Fang Yuan came out of his secret room.

"Tie Ruo Nan?" Hearing the servant's report, Fang Yuan gave a weird look.

He knew that this woman was Tie Xue Leng's daughter, didn't she die on Qing Mao mountain?

Tie Xue Leng flew out of the bronze mask of the mountain giant puppet Gu, using the steel hand Gu to save Tie Ruo Nan. Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing were engaging in a fierce fight at that moment, his vision obstructed by the white form immortal snake, thus he did not see it.

After the fog dispersed, he was attacked by the crane group, the scene was a mess and he did not have a second to rest. Even until Bai Ning Bing self-detonated, Fang Yuan did not see Tie Ruo Nan.

Thus, in Fang Yuan's impression, he had always thought that the Tie clan father and daughter had died on Qing Mao mountain.

"To think this Tie Ruo Nan is still alive, not only that, she even became Tie clan young master." Fang Yuan held the three invitations, taking a look and frowning deeply.

Seeing this name, he felt a strong killing intent oozing out of his heart.

This person is too much of an eyesore!

A survivor of Qing Mao mountain, had interacted with himself and Gu Yue Fang Zheng, a huge threat to himself.

If his true identity was exposed, it would affect his current peaceful lifestyle, and the haven he had painstakingly crafted in Shang clan city would be lost.

But this Tie Ruo Nan, Fang Yuan could not do anything to her.

Tie clan young master, in Shang clan city, he was not permitted to kill her.

"I am still too weak, if I was rank six like back then, I could kill this small-fry with one finger." Fang Yuan sighed in his heart.

Although his battle strength surged, and his growth was astounding, killing Tie Ruo Nan had consequences the current him could not bear.

In fact, he could not even use his own name at this point.

There is always a mountain higher than a mountain, an expert stronger than another expert. Rank five was only the mortal realm peak, yet he was merely rank three.

Fang Yuan quickly sorted his thoughts, eliminating her was the most direct method, but it could not be used, thus he had to think of a way to deal with this unwanted guest.

"The matter on Qing Mao mountain was not exposed, seeing Tie Ruo Nan's action, she must not know anything. Otherwise, she would not come with just this group to arrest me."

"She sent out three invitations and purposely displayed her determination of wanting to meet me. It seems she wants to learn what happened back then from me. After all, her father died on Qing Mao mountain."

"Then the matter now is, I am using Gu Yue Fang Zheng's name now, will she suspect my true identity?"

"If she has suspicions, how do I get rid of her doubts?"

"Or even worse, if my identity is exposed, how do I salvage it? From Shang Yan Fei's findings, I have an ordinary aptitude, only my brother is A grade aptitude, how do I explain the change in my talent..."

Fang Yuan's brain rapidly worked.

He was a sly schemer, having a vigilant nature, he always considered the worst outcome, and this huge crisis was no different.

He quickly thought of a countermeasure.

"If I really get to that stage, I will sell the blood skull Gu to Shang Yan Fei. He had been collecting the blood sea true inheritance, if I sell the blood skull Gu to him, he would be able to raise Shang Xin Ci's aptitude. He dotes on her so much, using the man triumphing heaven Gu for her to change her fate. He will not reject this deal."

Handing over the blood skull Gu, would allow Fang Yuan to explain the reason why he concealed his identity.

But unless the matter had progressed to the worst stage, Fang Yuan would definitely not sell the blood skull Gu.

"The blood skull Gu is a divine Gu to raise geniuses for a clan. If I sell it to Shang clan, Shang clan's forces would expand rapidly. Although the blood skull Gu has no value to me anymore, it is another story for others."

Fang Yuan did not know Fang Zheng was still alive now, and was experiencing a rapid growth in strength.

Chapter 303: I really want to kill her

Fang Yuan could not help but think again: "According to Tie clan's reaction, Tie Ruo Nan probably has no idea the blood skull Gu is in my hands. Maybe my A grade aptitude now is the greatest facade I have."

Regarding this, Fang Yuan was spot on.

The truth is, Tie Ruo Nan had never suspected Fang Yuan's identity.

The reason was obviously aptitude.

Tie Ruo Nan had always assumed that Fang Yuan was the Desolate Ancient Moon physique. Regarding the weakness of the ten extreme physique, she had learned much about it in Tie clan. After such a long time had passed, if it was really Fang Yuan, he would've died long ago.

Furthermore, from Tie Dao Ku's reports, Fang Yuan's fighting style of being brave and forthright, was also a testament to his identity.

In Tie Ruo Nan's mind, Fang Zheng was the one with such a style, as for that devious Fang Yuan, how could he fight with such ferocity?

On Tie Ruo Nan's fourth visit, she finally met Fang Yuan.

In the living room, only Fang Yuan and Tie Ruo Nan were present, the rest were sent away.

"To think that you and I would meet under such circumstances." Tie Ruo Nan exclaimed.

Fang Yuan and Fang Zheng were twins, they looked almost identical.

She exclaimed, but Fang Yuan was even more emotional, sighing deeply: "The past is the past. Let it stay that way, I do not want to mention it again."

Tie Ruo Nan's eyes shone sharply: "No, some things cannot be forgotten. My visit this time is for the matter back then. You must know how my father died, please tell me the truth!"

Fang Yuan looked at Tie Ruo Nan deeply, she showed no fear, staring right back at him. Her gaze showed a strong determined spirit.

Her eyes and eyebrows were sharper than before, as she did not roam around these few years, her slightly dark skin had turned pale, and together with her aquiline nose and red lips, it displayed the image of a heroic female general.

No doubt, she was a beauty. Although no match for Bai Ning Bing and Shang Xin Ci, her body had great shape, especially the long legs. Coupled with her unique disposition, it caused her to shine among people, and lure the conquering desire of men.

But Fang Yuan was not concerned with her appearance, from her gaze, Fang Yuan sensed that she had no doubt about his identity.

This was good.

Then next, the problem was how to explain the matter back then.

Fang Yuan knew, if he did not give a proper explanation, Tie Ruo Nan would not let go.

Regarding this, Fang Yuan had his measures.

Thus, he sighed: "Every time I think about Qing Mao maintain, my heart aches. You may have lost a father, but I lost a clan, every single one of my family, and was forced to roam in the wilds. Although Shang clan city is good, it is after all a foreign land, there is no feeling of home."

Saying so, his eyes turned red.

Seeing Fang Yuan act like this, Tie Ruo Nan's tough as steel gaze softened.

As people in similar circumstances, both of them were victims. But compared to her, Fang Zheng who had lost all his clansmen was no doubt more pitiful.

"Do you know? You killed a young master from my clan, if I had not stopped them, you would have been trialed by my clan already." Tie Ruo Nan changed the topic.

Fang Yuan's expression changed, rapidly explaining: "I know about the matter regarding Tie Dao Ku, it was not intentional! I dug the traps to deal with the grass skirt monkeys. Who asked your Tie clan to tail after me and fall into my trap? They were asking for death, how can you blame me!"

"A life for a life, it is perfectly justified, no?" Tie Ruo Nan's expression turned solemn.

Fang Yuan laughed coldly in his heart: "If that is the case, how many lives would I need to repay them?"

His face showed a cold smile too: "Tie Ruo Nan, after so many things had happened, we are no longer naive kids. Your Tie clan has no justification in this matter, the reason you did not act is because of the purple thorn token in my hand, is that not the case?"

Tie Ruo Nan replied honestly: "The purple thorn token is the main reason. But it can only protect your safety in Shang clan city, once you leave, we will not let you go. If you can tell me the truth behind the matter back then, I can assure you, as long as I live, Tie clan will not pursue you for this matter."

Fang Yuan's heart was slightly shocked.

This Tie Ruo Nan seemed to have developed well these few years. Even as a Tie clan young master, not many had this level of authority.

"If you do not believe me, we can use the poison vow Gu." Tie Ruo Nan continued.

Poison vow Gu again?

To speak the truth, Fang Yuan was already getting sick of refining the eating one's words Gu.

"The truth is nothing much, now that you are Tie clan's young master, can you not guess it?" Fang Yuan lowered his head, secretly observing Tie Ruo Nan.

He used this to probe her, but Tie Ruo Nan did not seem to notice it.

The young girl smiled: "Actually, even if you do not say it, I have an idea already."

Fang Yuan's tone changed: "You know?"

Tie Ruo Nan sighed slowly: "The ten extreme physique is not a secret to the high-tier clans in the Gu Master world. Causing that scene and sealing the entire Qing Mao mountain in ice, even a rank five Gu Master cannot do it. But what I did not expect is, your brother was not the Desolate Ancient Moon physique, but the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique."

"What?" Fang Yuan called out in his mind, but his expression remained the same, only squinting appropriately.

"Why did she think I am the Desolate Ancient Moon physique?" Fang Yuan felt weird at the absurdity of her claim.

"Wait... no wonder back then, the Gu Yue clan leader protected me for no reason. Don't tell me, they thought my cultivation speed was due to the ten extreme physique?" As he considered this, many things started to make sense.

"If she thinks so, then the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique is my greatest cover. This means she had never doubted my real identity. As long as I do not show a flaw in my pretense later..."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan's face showed a complicated and painful expression.

He did not speak, only sighing.

The more he speaks, the more loopholes he creates, words lead to mistakes!

Tie Ruo Nan looked at his expression and affirmed her guess, as her tone became softer: "Fang Zheng, I know the pain in your heart is very complicated. The only who ruined your home, causing you to roam outside, and murdered your entire clan, was your own brother Fang Yuan..."

Fang Yuan stopped her words, his eyes turning red: "Stop speaking, since you know so clearly, why must you ask me now."

"But I need a clear answer, all these were my assumptions!" Tie Ruo Nan gave a forceful gaze.

Fang Yuan nodded, as tears fell silently.

Tie Ruo Nan seeing this, could not force him further, only saying dejectedly: "Do you know, I had rushed back to Qing Mao mountain, seeing the snow that engulfed the mountain, my heart was a mess. I know my father was killed by Fang Yuan, if he was still around, the hatred of killing my father is greater than the heavens, I will definitely kill him for revenge. But he is already dead..."

"So what if I am not content with the outcome? I want to be filial to my parents but it is too late, I want to kill the murderer but he is already dead. It is the greatest regret in life!" Tie Ruo Nan sighed, not knowing that her mortal enemy was right in front of her.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, showing displeasure: "Fang Yuan is after all my brother, he is already dead, what more do you want?"

Tie Ruo Nan's eyes shone: "I want to know some things. Back then, my father had received a mysterious letter, I know what is written in it. It says that the Gu Yue village contained a blood sea inheritance, thus my father disregarded his injuries and rushed to Qing Mao mountain immediately. Do you and Bai Ning Bing know about it?"

Fang Yuan shook his head: "If I obtained it, I would've used it already. Why would I suffer so much on this journey?"

Tie Ruo Nan stared at Fang Yuan with deep meaning: "The blood sea inheritance brings endless disasters. Back then, the demonic path Gu Master blood sea ancestor left this vile inheritance behind. Getting to the root of the problem, my father's death was also due to this inheritance. Fang Zheng, if you really received this inheritance, I hope you can hand it over to me, and let me compensate for some of my regrets."

Fang Yuan shook his head: "No means no."

Tie Ruo Nan was solemn, before speaking: "According to my reports, you have a Gu in your possession that gives off a strong blood aura, you used to use it as a long range attack. But after you converted to a strength path cultivation, you no longer use it. Why is that?"

Fang Yuan was stunned, before realizing.

"You are suspecting me of taking the blood sea inheritance, but wanted to conceal it? Hmph, you mean this Gu?"

Fang Yuan willed, and took out the blood moon Gu from his aperture, tossing it to Tie Ruo Nan.

"This is the blood moon Gu from my clan, did you not see my brother use it before? Back when the explosion occurred, my clan leader and Bai clan leader worked together and protected me and Bai Ning Bing at the expense of their lives. The clan leader handed me his remaining Gu, and during the journey with Bai Ning Bing, many Gu died of hunger, but only this blood moon Gu remained became it was easy to feed."

Fang Yuan's words not only answered Tie Ruo Nan's enquiry, but even explained why he and Bai Ning Bing were able to escape from the icy hell.

Tie Ruo Nan inspected the blood moon Gu, her expression turning relaxed: "So that's it. Your clan leader was courageous, in order to protect the bloodline, he sacrificed himself, he is truly noble!"

Fang Yuan snorted: "That is why I have to live better, and rebuild Gu Yue village. Whoever dares to stop me, I will end his life!"

This explains why he was so cruel and ruthless in the battle stage.

"Although we did not spend much time together, I can evidently feel that you have changed." Tie Ruo Nan looked at Fang Yuan, she was only reminiscing and did not suspect him.

After encountering such a trauma, most people would change, that was normal.

Fang Yuan looked at her plainly: "People change, didn't you change as well?"

Tie Ruo Nan shook her head: "I have just been walking on my own road."

After that, both of them went silent.

Long after, Tie Ruo Nan spoke: "I will bring Tie Dao Ku back. I promise you, Tie clan will no longer pursue this matter. Relying on Shang clan and rebuilding your clan is a good method, many people succeeded, and I wish you success as well."

After saying that, the young girl stood up and left decisively.

Fang Yuan looked at her leave, his eyes squinting.

He had an obscure premonition, this Tie Ruo Nan was not simple, she might bring him great problems in the future.

"I really want to kill her in advance..." Fang Yuan was filled with helpless regret.

Chapter 304: Bitter Strength Gu

Tie Ruo Nan really left. And like she said, she took Tie Dao Ku with her.

Fang Yuan understood very well what kind of person Tie Dao Ku was.

Being able to fight intensely with Bai Ning Bing for such a long time, he clearly was an expert and could not be looked down upon. Now, he had been recruited by Tie Ruo Nan.

"This Tie Ruo Nan must be eliminated, leaving her alive will be an enormous threat." Fang Yuan had an intense premonition in his heart, because Tie Ruo Nan, him and Bai Ning Bing had a common point —

They were people who found the road they want to walk on in life.

Such people had great willpower and courage, as long as they didn't die prematurely, they were sure to have huge accomplishments.

Tie Ruo Nan also had A grade aptitude along with the support of Tie Clan.

She was one of the eight young masters of Tie Clan, just this alone, Fang and Bai could not compare with her even with the purple thorn tokens.

"If our growth continues like this, she will gradually throw me and Bai Ning Bing far away. Only through the three kings inheritance, can I decrease the gap between us." Fang Yuan made a plan.

With a normal development, Fang and Bai were not Tie Ruo Nan's match. The latter was one of the young masters of Tie Clan, the resources she received were so much that Fang and Bai could not even begin to compare.

Only by walking on an uncommon route, by taking risks and shortcuts, could they decrease this gap.

The three kings inheritance and the great demonic righteous battle of Yi Tian mountain were such 'shortcuts'.

Spring came and left; autumn left and returned.

The river of time continued to flow ceaselessly and over a year passed.

Nan Qiu garden, secret room.

Fang Yuan was sitting cross-legged on a cushion, beads of sweat seeped out of his forehead, as he gritted his teeth and endured.

He was refining Gu and it was the crucial moment.

A red, orange and green sphere floated in mid-air; the size of a basket. Its lights tinged Fang Yuan's face with a variety of colors.

Doing four tasks at once!

"Stone turtle strength Gu, go."

Following Fang Yuan's will, a darkish light flew out of his aperture and pierced into the three colored light sphere.

The addition of stone turtle strength Gu immediately created an intense reaction in the three colored light sphere.

The light sphere which had red, orange and three colors, now had a dark light mixed into it.

The four colors contended against each other but no one could overwhelm the other, and the battle became chaotic.

For a moment, the four colors moved fiercely, just like boiling water which was being stirred by a large hand.

Boom.

Suddenly, there was a small explosion.

The light sphere burst apart and formed a four colored rain. The light rain came fast and left just as quickly; in a blink of an eye, the secret room was submerged in darkness.

Everything disappeared.

"Failed again..." In the eerie darkness, Fang Yuan sighed softly.

Blood slowly seeped out from his nose and due to the failure in refining Gu, his soul also received a backlash, causing him to have a burst of dizziness.

This was already the fourth failure.

"A year and a half has gone, I have advanced to third inner city from the fourth. However, I haven't been able to buy bitter strength Gu."

Fang Yuan knew the reason.

One was because bitter strength Gu was extremely rare and also very expensive; it rarely appeared even in Shang clan city.

Second was because Shang Ya Zi was the one who managed the shops and was obstructing Fang Yuan from the dark.

Shang Ya Zi was one of the young masters of Shang clan and was in control of the stores in Shang clan city. Fang Yuan wanted to buy bitter strength Gu, and Shang Ya Zi possessed all kinds of ways to obstruct Fang Yuan.

Two years ago, Fang Yuan arrived at Shang clan city and had extorted Shang Ya Zi. And after this was done, Shang Ya Zi relied on Bai Gu inheritance to pass the clan's examination and maintain his young master position. Although he was hindered by poison vow Gu - not being able to make fatal moves against Fang Yuan - this way of taking revenge was still allowed.

Shang Ya Zi was after all Shang Yan Fei's son, each loss he suffered made him wiser. After the setbacks he suffered, he roused his spirit, wiped away his decadence, became cautious in indulging in wine and women, and became more shrewd.

He relied on the clan's system to deal with Fang Yuan, using more hidden means that even the purple thorn token Fang Yuan possessed was of no use.

Purple thorn token holders were considered Shang clan's esteemed guests. But in the end, they were outsiders and could not compare to Shang Ya Zi who was Shang clan's young master.

Since he could not buy bitter strength Gu, Fang Yuan could only attempt to refine it himself.

However, the success rate in refining bitter strength Gu was really very low.

Counting in today's attempt, Fang Yuan had already tried the fusion four times and in the process lost brown bear strength Gu, galloping horse strength Gu, green bull labor Gu and stone turtle strength Gu.

Apart from these, he had also lost precious supplementary materials and large amounts of primeval stones.

Fortunately, Fang Yuan was able to keep on winning at the battle stage and earn resources, allowing him to bear the cost of Gu refinement failure.

"Sigh, this time is also a failure... I can only wait for my injuries to recover before I try again." Fang Yuan sighed.

Gu refinement required prudence.

Failure to refine a Gu could inflict backlash on the Gu Master's body and soul. Injuries on the body were easier to resolve; but because of multitasking, the soul suffered damage which was extremely troublesome to deal.

The higher the rank and rarer the Gu was, the more severe the consequences of failure.

Thus, refinement Gu Masters would often be seriously injured or become bedridden because of Gu refinement failures, and sometimes the backlash even led to deaths.

It was not that Gu which could heal the soul did not exist, but they were all extremely rare and were usually kept secretly by the large clans.

The injuries to his soul this time would inflict light dizziness to Fang Yuan for over a month.

This dizziness would affect Fang Yuan's battle strength and such a minor gap could be fatal in a battle between experts.

Thus Fang Yuan usually attempted this after an interval of a month to let his soul have enough time to recuperate.

Gu refinement failed but today's cultivation was not over.

Fang Yuan waited in meditation; a short while later, he heard a knock from outside. He opened the door and welcomed Bai Ning Bing.

Over this course of a year and a half, Bai Ning Bing made rapid progress and also reached the third inner city, having assembled a set of Gu worms. She was on par with Fang Yuan and rarely suffered losses. They were called the two new stars of this generation in the battle stage and received attention from many people.

The two did not speak and only nodded to each other.

Bai Ning Bing sat cross-legged on the opposite cushion and placed her palms against Fang Yuan's back, pouring her snow silver primeval essence.

Bai Ning Bing was intentionally suppressing her cultivation and thus, was still at rank three peak stage.

In contrast, Fang Yuan's cultivation was advancing rapidly and was now only half a step away from rank three upper stage.

Four hours later, Bai Ning Bing stopped injecting the primeval essence and withdrew her palms.

Fang Yuan slowly opened his eyes.

His aura was even more abundant and there was a vague feeling of fullness. This was the sign of cultivation close to breaking through.

"My cultivation is getting close to rank three upper stage, I will breakthrough within a few days." Fang Yuan calmly analyzed in his mind.

"After I breakthrough to upper stage, I will use the white silver relic Gu and directly push my cultivation to rank three peak stage. Like this, I can catch up to Bai Ning Bing, and also ease Spring Autumn Cicada's pressure on the aperture."

Spring Autumn Cicada was Fang Yuan's vital Gu and was also a rank six Gu.

Over this course of a year and a half, it had been continually absorbing the water of the river of time and its aura was growing stronger as it recovered, creating a pressure on Fang Yuan's aperture again.

But the situation this time was many times better than the one on Qing Mao mountain.

Fang Yuan's cultivation was advancing rapidly, and with a rank three aperture, it was not as pressing as back then on Qing Mao mountain.

All this should be attributed to bone flesh unity Gu and Bai Ning Bing.

Cultivation ended; Bai Ning Bing stood up and left the secret room immediately.

During the whole process, she did not say a word and her expression was cold as ice.

Fang Yuan was also not someone who spoke a lot. Over this year and a half, the two were already used to interacting like this.

Fang Yuan inwardly pondered: "When I reach rank three peak stage, Bai Ning Bing's primeval essence won't be of much help to me. But from this long period of interaction with her and from the minute changes in her aura, I can vaguely feel that she isn't far from rank four realm."

Even if Bai Ning Bing was trying her best to delay her cultivation, the curse of the ten extreme physique had not disappeared and started showing its effect.

According to what Bai Ning Bing said, her aptitude had raised by two percent again and was now at ninety-three percent.

Another seven percent increase would reach hundred percent and she would regain her northern dark ice soul physique.

"If she reaches rank four, her yellow gold primeval essence would be of great help to me in breaking through to rank four realm."

"In some aspects, she and I are in similar circumstances. I have Spring Autumn Cicada and she has northern dark ice soul physique..."

Seven days later, Fang Yuan received good news from Wei Yang.

An auction!

"A rarely seen disaster appeared at Ju Feng mountain and destroyed Ju clan. The remnants of Ju clan had submitted to Shang clan city and are auctioning large amounts of their clan's collections to maintain their livelihood. Thus, there will be an auction held soon."

After saying this, Wei Yang intentionally said to Fang Yuan: "Brother Fang, your luck has come. I have investigated and found there is a bitter strength Gu being auctioned this time."

Wei Yang was clear of Fang Yuan's demand for bitter strength Gu. Fang Yuan had even requested him to make inquiries before.

"The main thing is everyone in Shang clan city are viewing this auction with importance, it will be difficult for young master Shang Ya Zi to play tricks." Wei Yang added.

The conflict between Shang Ya Zi and Fang Yuan was no secret to Shang clan's higher ups.

"Bitter strength Gu!"

"Ju clan!"

Fang Yuan's gaze brightened.

Ju clan had centuries of foundation, there was sure to be many useful things up for bidding now that they were selling their properties. Bitter strength Gu which Fang Yuan had not obtained despite searching all over for it, was one of them.

"I have accumulated close to a million primeval stones in the course of this year and a half. I have a huge chance of successfully buying the bitter strength Gu."

"Cases like Ju clan's destruction aren't rare. In this world, besides human disaster, there are also natural disasters. Strong wind blows throughout the year in Ju Feng mountain, although it is a spiritual mountain possessing spirit springs, the environment is really bad. There could be many treasures in Ju Clan's storage."

"I need to participate in the auction!" Fang Yuan immediately decided.

...

"What, Ju Clan has a bitter strength Gu?" In a study, Shang Ya Zi slowly furrowed his brows.

He was holding a document on one hand; the document contained most of the details of the auction.

And his other hand was on the table, his index finger knocking on the surface.

"To think Fang Zheng's luck is so good, I did everything to obstruct him and it seems he is still going to obtain the bitter strength Gu. Even father is paying attention to the auction this time, it won't be easy for me to interfere."

"But, Fang Zheng... I won't let you get the bitter strength Gu so easily. I will also participate in the auction and make sure you suffer a huge loss!"

Shang Ya Zi could not help but let out a cold snort at the thought.

He had always kept a grudge due to Fang Yuan's extortion.

He was a narrow-minded and petty person, refusing to see Fang and Bai gain fame and status. He could only ease the hatred in his heart by seeing Fang and Bai's pain and suffering.

Chapter 305: Auction (1)

Strong winds blow continuously throughout the year on Ju Feng mountain, since its creation, Ju clan village had been facing the threat of hurricanes.

Ju clan village is situated at the top of Ju Feng mountain, having hundreds of years of history. Contesting the natural disaster as mere humans, the clan often faced the threat of extermination, but they pulled through every time. But this time, they faced a giant hurricane that is rarely seen in a hundred years.

Ju clan village could not longer defend themselves, and was destroyed by the disaster.

The terrifying hurricane destroyed the spirit spring, and many people in Ju clan died. After losing their village, they could only leave and come to Shang clan city, seeking refuge in hopes of rebuilding their home in the future.

Commodity prices are high in Shang clan city, to live, they had to sell their assets.

To Ju clan, this was a disaster, but to others, this was a rare opportunity.

Although Ju clan was a small size clan, they had their secrets for being able to live on Ju Feng mountain and fighting the natural disaster for hundreds of years without falling.

Ju clan selling off their assets made this auction very attractive to people.

Once news got out, it attracted most people's attention in Shang clan city.

Seven days later, the auction was held.

At the auction, it was overcrowding with people and there were zero empty seats in the large hall. The private rooms on higher floors were all sold out as well.

Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing, using their purple thorn tokens, snatched a private room for themselves.

Fang Yuan opened a slit in the curtain of the room, standing at one side feeling the rowdy atmosphere of the hall.

At this time, the auction had not started yet, and nearly a thousand people in the hall were talking among themselves, making a great commotion.

"Sigh, what a pity for Ju clan. After hundreds of years, they finally lost to the hurricane. Man really cannot contest the strength of the natural elements." Someone exclaimed.

"This is nothing much, new clans rise up and old clans get eliminated. Just like a few years ago, the three clans on Qing Mao mountain were wiped out together. Ju clan's demise was nothing extraordinary." Someone felt indifferent.

"Ju clan's tragedy is our happiness. I hear there are lots of good stuff in this auction." Someone was gloating at the clan's disaster.

"So many Ju clansmen entered Shang clan city, this will cause great disturbance to Shang clan city's economy." Someone predicted the future.

At this moment, there was a huge commotion.

"Look, that is Shang clan young master Qiu Niu."

Fang Yuan followed the voice and looked, seeing Shang Qiu Niu walk in from the entrance, taking large strides in.

He had a muscular build and his steps were stable. He was thirty years old now, as Shang Yan Fei's eldest son.

"Greetings to eldest young master Qiu Niu!"

"My respects to eldest young master."

"It is our honor to be able to see eldest young master in person."

At once, many people rushed up and paid respects to Qiu Niu.

"Hello everyone." Qiu Niu did not speak much, smiling lightly as he calmly faced the situation.

Finally, he walked into a private room under everyone's gaze.

The auction house became quiet again.

But soon after, a commotion rose again.

"Young master Chao Feng and Fu Xi are here too!"

"They had a great relationship since young, as expected, they came here today together."

The fourth son Shang Chao Feng, still had a messy hair and a wild aura. The thirteenth son Shang Fu Xi was refined and delicate, looking like a scholar.

The two talked as they entered the private room together. Their servants opened a path for them along the way, and they did not care about the surrounding people.

Fang Yuan looked with a cold expression, squinting.

In his memory, Shang Chao Feng almost managed to get the Shang clan leader position, he was Shang Xin Ci's greatest competitor. He was wicked and devious, and had decisive courage, this was somewhat like Shang Yan Fei.

Shang Fu Xi was his greatest supporter, willingly going under him and had wits, being good at planning. In the future, when the righteous demonic battle at Yi Tian mountain occurred, he schemed and employed strategies that caused great damage to the demonic Gu Masters, gaining fame instantly.

The two, one was capable and the other was good at scheming, complementing each other. The former controlled the Gu battle zone while the latter controlled the auction zone. They were both important domains in Shang clan city, being fully developed. Right now, these two were the third largest faction among the ten contesting young masters.

Before Shang Chao Feng and Shang Fu Xi entered their room, another group of people came.

Shang Pu Lao, Shang Suan Ni, and Shang Bi Xi walked in full of smiles as they spoke.

These three were the eighth, ninth, and tenth children of Shang Yan Fei. Because of benefits, they formed into a small alliance. They were the second largest faction among the contesting young masters as they had a strong collective force and were temporarily suppressing Shang Chao Feng and Shang Fu Xi.

Shang Pu Lao controlled the brothels in Shang clan city, he was a casanova and womaniser. Shang Suan Ni was in charge of restaurants and silk stores, having a large mouth and wide nose, two traces of yellow smoke came out of his nose when he breathed. Shang Bi Xi was short and fat, but was also a strength path Gu Master. His core Gu was the turtle tire Gu, having the strength of ten turtles.

Shang Suan Ni and Shang Bi Xi were strong experts in cultivation, while Shang Pu Lao had literary talent and fate with women. With the three as the head, two fighters and one scholar, they had great coordination.

The three young masters did not choose a room, but sat in the hall.

Shang Pu Lao had great interpersonal communication skills, everywhere he went, people followed. He spoke casually among the people, blending in perfectly, causing the scene to be even more liven.

On his left and right, Shang Suan Ni and Shang Bi Xi stood like two guardians.

"Shang Yan Fei's children are all dragons and phoenixes among men!" Fang Yuan sighed internally.

He had a clear understanding of Shang clan's ten young master situation now.

Right now, there were three factions among the young masters.

The first, was Shang Qiu Niu. He was Shang Yan Fei's eldest son, with just this identity, he had many Shang clan elders and clansmen supporting him.

The second, was Shang Pu Lao, Shang Suan Ni, and Shang Bi Xi, the three gathered into a strong force and were currently the center of attention.

The third was Shang Chao Feng and Shang Fu Xi, hiding their strength and awaiting a chance to rise up.

As for the others, Shang Ya Zi was a loner, having little influence. Shang Chi Wen was bubbly and vibrant, but had no ambition. Shang Pi Xiu had great talent, but was too scheming...

"I want to help Shang Xin Ci ascend to the throne, we cannot compete with the three factions. Although Shang Xin Ci can cultivate, a forcefully awakened aperture only has C grade aptitude, this is not a weak foundation, but zero foundation."

Shang Xin Ci was Shang Yan Fei's illegitimate daughter, and her mother was from Zhang clan. Zhang clan and Wu clan were very close, having much grudges with Shang clan. This was Shang Xin Ci's political weakness.

"Every year, during the young master assessment, there is a great opportunity for Shang Yan Fei's other children to rise up. In my memory, Shang Xin Ci only became Shang clan young master after six years. But this is too long, if I want to make use of her, I have to get her up there as soon as possible. This year's assessment is a chance." Fang Yuan evaluated in his heart.

To get Shang Xin Ci into power, he had to deal with Shang Yan Fei's other children. Since he could not deal with the three large factions, he will have to deal with the others.

On this aspect, Fang Yuan had a plan every since he entered Shang clan city.

Just as he thought about Shang Xin Ci, she arrived.

Numerous eyeballs were attracted to the entrance of the auction house.

"Shang clan's two beauties!"

"Really pretty..."

"Young master Shang Chi Wen looks cute and innocent, but coming with Lady Shang Xin Ci, she loses out in terms of appearance."

The people discussed.

Shang Xin Ci and Shang Chi Wen held hands and spoke as they entered the auction house.

Shang Chi Wen wore a colorful dress, her face was like peach, soft and tender. Shang Xin Ci wore a green skirt, her black hair silky and her eyes shining like the moon. Her skin was white as snow and her lips were pink and tender. She looked elegant and graceful, gentle like water, when she smiled, it was pure and flawless, a perfect beauty. It caused people's gaze to become dazed.

Beside the two of them, there were four servants.

Two of them were Tian Lan and Xiao Die, Shang Xin Ci's personal servants.

The servants blocked the excited young men in the hall, as Shang Xin Ci and Shang Chi Wen walked towards Fang Yuan's private room.

"Brother Hei Tu, Sister Bai Yun." Shang Xin Ci greeted, unable to hide the joy and excitement in her voice.

Shang Yan Fei used the man triumphing heaven Gu to forcefully awaken her aperture. These two years, he used a lot of precious Gu worms to raise her aptitude. From the lowest twenty percent D grade aptitude, it slowly rose to C grade fifty-nine percent, a step away from B grade.

Shang Yan Fei paid such a huge price to nurture her, and taught her personally, Shang Xin Ci felt his fatherly love, and her hatred vanished into thin air, enjoying the love and bliss.

Shang Yan Fei chose many Gu Masters to teach her. Shang Xin Ci stayed home for most of the time, studying more about Gu Master cultivation of her own accord. She was smart and mature, having faced some difficulties, she desired strength but was not arrogant, had strict goals for herself and improved by leaps and bounds, causing Shang Yan Fei to be extremely pleased.

This auction was a rare chance to relax, she had accepted Fang Yuan's invitation and wanted to come alone, but met Shang Chi Wen along the way.

"Fang Zheng, I came uninvited, are you going to chase me out?" Shang Chi Wen laughed as she followed Shang Xin Ci into the room.

"How would I dare to, please take a seat." Fang Yuan invited her with a smile.

Bai Ning Bing sat at one side, hearing this, she did not turn around, but remained expressionless.

Shang Chi Wen gave this ice beauty a curious look, thinking: "Outsiders say Bai Ning Bing is cold and arrogant, it seems they were right."

Next, she looked at Fang Yuan.

"Actually, this Fang Zheng is also extremely arrogant. After reaching third inner city, and winning all his battles, never having a single loss, many forces started recruiting him. Shang Chao Feng, Shang Qiu Niu, Shang Pu Lao and others, they even held a banquet and invited him personally, but were rejected. These two being together... truly birds of a feather flock together."

Shang Chi Wen controlled Shang clan city's battle stage, she was extremely clear of Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing's situation.

Fang and Bai had never lost a battle since they joined the battle stage, they had overwhelming talent and were the most famous people in the battle zone. Their fame even rivalled the two great rank four Gu Masters, Ju Kai Bei and Yan Tu.

Anyone could tell that their future was promising, if any of the Shang clan young masters get their assistance, it would be a huge boost to their force.

But she, Shang Chi Wen, had no ambition, thus she did not send any invitations to them.

"Brother Hei Tu, it has been a while, are you doing fine? I heard you fought with a Gu Master called Teng Jiu Long..." Shang Xin Ci sat beside Fang Yuan, her gaze fixed on him as she asked in concern.

Fang Yuan laughed lightly: "It has only been ten days since we met, why is it 'been a while'? As for Teng Jiu Long, he could not even stop my advancement before losing. In this battle stage, only Ju Kai Bei and Yan Tu are a threat, the rest are nothing to be worried about."

Fang Yuan's calm words displayed his extraordinary pride and self-confidence, as Shang Chi Wen listened with shining eyes, and Shang Xin Ci's heart was moved once again.

Chapter 306: Auction (2)

As time passed, more and more people entered the auction house.

"Look, that is one of the five generals of Shang clan, White Light Swordsman!" Someone shouted.

Wei Yang's title was the White Light Swordsman, he came as well.

"I have already checked, the bitter strength Gu you want is the thirteenth item. But, Shang Ya Zi is already in the fifth private room. I heard he purposely withdrew all of his assets, you have to be careful brother Fang Zheng." Wei Yang walked into the private room, giving Fang Yuan important information.

According to logic, the sequence of the auction items should not be revealed, and the identities of the guests should be kept secret as well. But as one of the five great generals of Shang clan, Wei Yang controlled the intelligence agency Feng Yu Manor, thus it was easy for him to get all the information he wanted.

Wei Yang patted Fang Yuan's shoulders, still feeling worried: "Shang Ya Zi is not here for fun, he has at least one million and two hundred thousand primeval stones on hand. The bitter strength Gu is a treasure for strength path Gu Masters, other than Shang Ya Zi, there are two more people who are your greatest competitors, one is Shang Bi Xi, the other is Ju Kai Bei, you have to watch out."

Tenth son Shang Bi Xi had the turtle tire Gu, having the strength of ten turtles, he was a strength path Gu Master not inferior to Fang Yuan. He controlled the Shang clan city's substitute refinement zone, although there was not much profits there, his eighth brother Shang Pu Lao controlled the brothels and ninth brother Shang Suan Ni controlled the restaurants and silk stores, they earn buckets of primeval stones everyday. If Shang Bi Xi wants the bitter strength Gu, as an alliance mate, the two of them would surely help.

Other than them, there was still Ju Kai Bei.

He had rank four cultivation, dominating third inner city battle stage.

What did rank four cultivation mean?

In an ordinary clan, he would be a clan leader!

Ju Kai Bei was a rank four Gu Master, but remaining in the battle stage and rejected all of the invitations sent to him by all sorts of forces.

"I will not leave the battle stage unless I defeat Yan Tu!" He declared.

Yan Tu was also a rank four Gu Master, and was the same as Ju Kai Bei as 'half the sky of battle stage'. Both of them vowed to defeat each other, and only after they became a true number one would they leave the battle stage gloriously.

Yan Tu is a fire path Gu Master, he would not have any desire for the bitter strength Gu. But Ju Kai Bei was a genuine strength path Gu Master, he had won numerous battles, only losing occasionally to Yan Tu, he had to have a lot of primeval stones on him!

Thus, be it Shang Bi Xi or Ju Kai Bei, they were Fang Yuan's competitors.

"I have some spare money here, use them for now." Next, Wei Yang passed Fang Yuan a primeval elder Gu.

Shang Chi Wen gasped, slightly surprised.

She knew Wei Yang and Fang Yuan were close, but did not think their relationship was so deep!

She had investigated earlier, this auction had a light type Gu that would be useful to Wei Yang. To think he would hand his primeval stones over to Fang Yuan just for his sake.

Looking at the elderly's cheerful expression, this primeval elder Gu had nearly a million primeval stones!

This means that Wei Yang gave up on his own Gu.

"Brother Wei, this..." Fang Yuan showed hesitance, as he also revealed a look of gratitude.

"Say no more, accept them. I am only lending them to you, not giving them. From now on, I am your creditor." Wei Yang laughed loudly, not giving Fang Yuan a chance to reject, forcing the primeval elder Gu onto him.

Shang Xin Ci at the other side also took out a primeval elder Gu.

"Brother Hei Tu, this is mine."

In her primeval elder Gu, the cloud elder was frowning and upset, from that, one can deduce that there was around a hundred to three hundred thousand primeval stones in it.

This was the pocket money Shang Yan Fei gave to her every month. She scrimped and saved, accumulating them and handed them all to Fang Yuan now.

"If I speak anymore, it will be hypocritical. I accept it all, I will definitely repay you later!" Fang Yuan laughed heartily, cupping his fists and keeping the primeval stones.

Shang Xin Ci smiled lightly, not thinking about Fang Yuan's repayment. Even if she had to give these to him, she would not feel upset. But she knew, with his temper, he will not accept such a 'gift', thus she could only 'lend' him.

"That's the way." Wei Yang nodded.

He had high hopes for Fang Yuan, and liked his clear definition of kindness and grudges.

At one side, Shang Chi Wen hesitated, but eventually did not take out her primeval elder Gu.

Her gaze was flickering with light, as she changed the topic: "Look, Ju Kai Bei is here."

At the entrance of the auction house, a strong and muscular man appeared.

He was at the prime of his life, eight feet tall. His skin was tightly wrapped around his muscles, layers after layers. When he walked, every step was the exact same distance, showing his strict and disciplined nature.

He was like a tower, tall and straight, giving off a sense of pressure to his surroundings. It caused people to move away from him, but also look at him with respect and reverence.

He was Ju Kai Bei.

Rank four Gu Master, the peak of experts in third inner city battle stage!

"Senior Ju, my clan's young master Shang Ya Zi invites you to the fifth private room."

"Lord Ju, my clan's young master Pu Lao is already in fourth private room, and has prepared a banquet."

"Sir Ju Kai Bei, this is the invitation from my clan's young master Chao Feng, please accept it."

...

At once, many servants crowded over, representing their young masters and sent out invitations to Ju Kai Bei.

But Ju Kai Bei snorted coldly, not looking at them, walking to the first row of the hall and sitting down.

The servants looked at each other before helplessly leaving.

Time passed, and after Ju Kai Bei, another important person arrived.

This person was neither fat nor thin, not tall or short, had a common face but his features were strange.

The left of his face was bright red, and the right was pale blue. The two colors split his face into two portions, from the center of his nose, two colors split on both sides.

"He is Shang Bu Li, to think he came." Wei Yang told Fang Yuan immediately.

"It is him indeed. "Fang Yuan nodded slightly, having a clear picture in his mind.

Shang Bu Li, titled 'Two faced man', was the number one general under Shang Yan Fei. He had rank four cultivation, controlling Gu worms of fire and ice.

He was Shang clan's most important subject, and was a clan elder in Shang clan, in charge of the trading of servants in Shang clan, his authority was higher than that of Wei Yang.

When Shang Bu Li appeared, it attracted many greetings and bootlicking. He had a proud expression, squinting as he walked slowly between the people, enjoying the feeling of being praised to the heaven.

His authority was greater than the ten young masters.

The young masters can only control some of Shang clan's businesses, but as the number one subject of Shang clan, Shang Bu Li controlled the entire slave trade market in Shang clan.

"Shang Bu Li, can you walk faster, dragging your steps like this, are you a man?" At this time, an unhappy tone complained.

With Shang Bu Li's position, in Shang clan city, he was second only to the clan leader, who dared to be so rude to him?

Shang Bu Li heard this, and his heart shuddered, shrinking his head as he turned around, bowing to the person speaking: "Lord Doctor Su Shou, Bu Li pays respect to you."

The person who came was Doctor Su Shou.

She was one of the four great doctors of southern border, and had rank five cultivation, she had once treated Fang Yuan's injuries.

She still wore a white shirt, and her face was covered in a white veil, preventing others from seeing her appearance, but her body curves could not be hidden.

Shang Bu Li did not dare to look at her body, shifting his gaze to the floor beside her feet.

Doctor Su Shou and clan leader Shang Yan Fei had a complicated relationship, she had a high position in Shang clan. As Shang Yan Fei's 'rumored lover', even if Shang Bu Li had a million guts, he would not dare to disrespect her.

"Just don't block my path." Doctor Su Shou snorted coldly, bringing her eight white shirt servants and walking past Shang Bu Li, entering a private room and vanishing from everyone's sight.

Shang Bu Li rubbed his nose, laughing bitterly, there was nothing he could do in front of Doctor Su Shou.

Not long after, many people appeared again.

Yan Tu who shared the same fame as Ju Kai Bei, Shang Yan Fei's fifth general Yi Huo, Yi Bu Hui elder from Yi clan, Fei Luan Feng elder from Fei clan, and others.

"This auction is a gathering of experts. There are established Gu Masters, new generation rising stars, lone warriors, and leaders of large clans. Among them, I wonder how many will become my obstacle?" Fang Yuan thought.

"Sorry for the long wait everyone, the auction officially starts now!" The hosting female Gu master had a young beautiful appearance as she stood on the stage using the sound amplify Gu.

She knew everyone was impatient, thus she spoke quickly, and started introducing the first item.

Frost arrow Gu.

Rank four Gu, shaped like a drain fly, its body was blue like ice, and its mouth was long and needle-like.

This kind of ice type Gu was a treasure in Ju clan village. It was like Gu Yue clan who collected many types of moon type Gu.

"Once the frost arrow Gu is activated, frost energy gathers and it shoots out an arrow of ice to quickly assault the enemy. As everyone knows, its greatest advantage is low primeval essence consumption, even a rank three Gu Master can use it. The base price is seventy thousand primeval stones!" The female Gu Master quickly introduced.

"Seventy-five thousand."

"Eighty thousand!"

"Eighty-five thousand!"

...

The bids continued to rise, until ninety thousand, and the speed decreased drastically. Gu Masters' bids increased by three thousand, compared to five thousand at the start.

After the hundred thousand benchmark, the three thousand increment shrunk to one thousand.

"A hundred and ten thousand. " Bai Ning Bing said.

"The esteemed guest from ninth private room bid a hundred and ten thousand!" The hosting Gu Master raised her pitch, this was the first time a guest from a private room had bid.

"A hundred and twenty thousand." Shang Ya Zi's voice came out of fifth private room.

Bai Ning Bing squinted, calling: "A hundred and thirty thousand."

Shang Ya Zi quickly followed: "A hundred and forty thousand."

Bai Ning Bing gave Fang Yuan a glance, saying: "A hundred and fifty thousand."

Fang Yuan shrugged.

This bid was obviously Shang Ya Zi finding problems with them. Bai Ning Bing was in the same room as Fang Yuan, thus she was targeted by Shang Ya Zi, she was really under fire for no reason.

"A hundred and fifty thousand for a frost arrow Gu... hmph, I want you guys to suffer!" In fifth private room, Shang Ya Zi laughed sinisterly, not bidding anymore.

Although Bai Ning Bing bought the frost arrow Gu, she paid forty thousand extra.

"It seems Shang Ya Zi is here with a vengeance." Wei Yang sighed.

Shang Xin Ci also frowned, feeling worried for Fang Yuan.

Chapter 307: Auction (3)

"Take a look everyone, this is a thousand year wind willow." The female Gu Master pointed at the item on the stage and introduced.

"Wind willow is a rare type of plant that is used in refinement as material. It only grows in a location where there is sufficient wind energy to sustain its growth. Because Ju Feng mountain has winds all year round, they can produce large amounts of wind willows."

"An ordinary wind willow is only a few decades old, or a few centuries. But the current auction item, it is a thousand years old, able to be used in rank five Gu refinement! The base bid is fifty thousand primeval stones, the auction starts now."

Once she said so, people started bidding.

"Fifty-five thousand!"

"Fifty-eight thousand."

"Sixty-five thousand."

"Seventy thousand."

The bids went up, as many people participated, most of them were professional refinement Gu masters.

A thousand year wind willow is rarely seen, even Ju clan who had lived on Ju Feng mountain for hundreds of years, had only eighteen remaining.

Wind willow did not have tree branches, there is only the roots underground, and one stem.

When the winds blow, this sole stem would sway with the winds, like seaweed underwater.

The thousand year wind willow on the stage had been coiled up, but its length definitely exceeded a hundred meters.

Fang Yuan tried to intervene and bid, but that Shang Ya Zi immediately raised the bid by five thousand.

Eventually, a refinement master obtained the wind willow, spending almost a hundred thousand.

"The thousand year wind willow is the eighth item, during this period, whenever I bid for something, Shang Ya Zi would interfere. If I do nothing, he would remain silent too. It seems his sole purpose here today is to oppose me." Fang Yuan's gaze shone, gaining a deeper understanding of Shang Ya Zi's narrow-mindedness.

Time continued to pass.

Ninth item, tenth item...

"What is displayed next is the twelfth item. This is a chasing wind Gu, rank four movement Gu, it allows the Gu Master to have the speed to chase after winds. Base bid is a hundred and eighty thousand." The female Gu Master's delicate voice reverberated in the entire auction house.

"A hundred and ninety thousand."

"Two hundred thousand!"

"Two hundred and twenty thousand!"

"Two hundred and fifty thousand!"

...

Chasing wind Gu was a popular auction item, once it appeared, the first climax of the auction house appeared.

Many people participated and bid, even the quiet private rooms started to bid for the item.

Wind, light, lightning, cloud, these four types of Gu were outstanding movement Gu worms. Chasing wind Gu was a rank four Gu, it gave a great boost to the Gu Master's speed.

Fang Yuan tried to bid, but Shang Ya Zi immediately followed after.

Fang Yuan no longer said anything, as their bids were buried under the other people's voices.

At times, new competitors entered the bidding, but more people gave up after seeing the absurd prices.

When the chasing wind Gu's price rose to three hundred and fifty thousand, only two Gu Masters were left competing.

One was Yi clan elder Yi Bu Hui, the other was Fei clan elder Fei Luan Feng.

Yi clan and Fei clan did not have a good relationship, the two competed as sparks arose.

Eventually, the chasing wind Gu was bought by elder Yi Bu Hui using four hundred and forty thousand.

Although Fang Yuan had over two million primeval stones, he did not participate.

Chasing wind Gu contained the Dao mark of wind, if he used it, his beast phantoms would cause a huge disturbance to the Gu, causing the effect to weaken. Thus, chasing wind Gu was not a good choice for Fang Yuan.

"If this was the rank four fairy wind Gu, I would buy it, too bad this was merely a chasing wind Gu."

Fang Yuan had a recipe, he could use fairy wind Gu, seven shining stars Gu and a few other materials to refine the fixed star Gu, which was the main ingredient in refining fixed immortal travel Gu.

Dream Travel, Carefree Travel, Fixed Immortal Travel, Liquor God Travel, these were the four great movement Gu.

All of them were rank six Gu.

Dream travel could allow Gu Masters to enter other people's dreams. Carefree travel was best at dodging attacks. Fixed immortal travel could allow a Gu Master to teleport themselves to anywhere they want to go. Liquor god travel was the most special, and first appeared in \<\<Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, but that story is for later.

Fang Yuan had his previous life's memories, thus he had the carefree travel Gu and fixed immortal travel Gu's recipes. Among them, the fixed immortal travel Gu was most needed by Fang Yuan, but the success rate of refinement was extremely low, and he did not have enough materials for it either, thus he could only set it aside for now.

"Alright, for our thirteenth item, it is a... bitter strength Gu!"

The female Gu master introduced on the stage, but even without her explanation, many Gu Masters' eyes were shining brightly.

"I have to obtain this bitter strength Gu no matter what, no one can stop me, two hundred thousand primeval stones!" Before the female Gu Master gave the base bid, Fang Yuan quickly shouted.

Fang Yuan's words made Ju Kai Bei unhappy: "Youngsters are so anxious, I bid two hundred and fifty thousand."

"Three hundred thousand." Shang Bi Xi also bid quickly.

"Five hundred thousand!" Fang Yuan reported a frightening price.

The entire auction house went wild.

"That voice, I think it is Gu Yue Fang Zheng!"

"He sure is rich, bidding five hundred thousand just for a bitter strength Gu."

"He had won so many times on the battle stage, he is affluent and loaded."

People sighed, while some strength path Gu Masters had a bitter expression, they held some expectations towards the bitter strength Gu, and wanted to try bidding, but with Fang Yuan's bid, they were kicked out of the race before even beginning.

Even the female Gu Master on the stage was shocked.

Bitter strength Gu was rank four, but strength path Gu worms had little requirements towards the Gu Master in terms of primeval essence, rank three could barely activate them. Its market price was around three hundred and eighty thousand, lower than the chasing wind Gu.

To think that Fang Yuan bid five hundred thousand immediately, a hundred and twenty thousand above the market value.

"Youngsters these days sure have vigor." Ju Kai Bei sighed, no longer competing. Half a million primeval stones was enough for him to buy a few other useful Gu worms.

"Eighth brother, ninth brother..."Shang Bi Xi looked at the two young masters hesitantly.

Ninth brother Shang Suan Ni did not say anything, only looking at Shang Pu Lao.

"Tenth brother, this depends on you. If you want to compete for it, we as brothers will support you all the way." Shang Pu Lao smiled and encouraged.

Shang Bi Xi gritted his teeth: "Five hundred thousand... it's too much of a loss. Nevermind, let Fang Zheng take it."

He also gave up.

Fang Yuan's determined display removed two competitors for him.

"Five hundred thousand, going once."

"Five hundred thousand, going twice."

"Five hundred thousand, going thric..."

"Hold on, I bid five hundred and ten thousand." Right before the female Gu Master slammed the hammer, Shang Ya Zi said slowly in his private room.

"Hmph, Shang Ya Zi, you think you can stop me? Six hundred thousand." Fang Yuan immediately followed, speaking with strong disdain.

Shang Ya Zi laughed coldly: "I'll play with you if you want to Fang Zheng. Six hundred and ten."

The people in the auction house started chattering.

"Fang Zheng and Shang clan young master are at odds!"

"How can this be?"

"Fang Zheng has the purple thorn token, and is an esteemed guest in Shang clan, he has no fear towards Shang Ya Zi's young master identity. But Shang Ya Zi is in charge of all the shops in Shang clan, and has great wealth. This will be a battle among tigers and dragons!"

...

"Seven hundred thousand!" Fang Yuan shouted: "Shang Ya Zi, you lost to me previously, you are a loser. It seems you have not been punished enough."

Shang Ya Zi retorted: "Complete bullshit, we'll see who teaches who a lesson! Seven hundred and ten!!"

Once he said that, the crowd went wild.

Shang Ya Zi and Fang Yuan's dispute was no secret to Shang clan city's higher ups. But to ordinary Gu Masters, it was news to them.

At once, people started guessing why Shang Ya Zi has a grudge against Fang Yuan.

"Evidently, Shang Ya Zi lost in a fight to Fang Zheng before, and wants to take revenge."

"Why bother with the reasoning. Young master Ya Zi is well known for his pettiness, even if a bystander knocks into him, he will take revenge. Fang Zheng is a lawless brute, it is no wonder that they would have conflicts."

"You are both wrong, I heard already, Shang Ya Zi and Fang Zheng went to Qin Yan brothel before, and were interested in the number one lady there. But eventually Fang Zheng got her, and that led to Shang Ya Zi's animosity."

"Real or fake?" Someone expressed doubt.

The person who spoke earlier, showed a fearless expression, pointing at a seat: "Look there, that is lady An Yu, you don't have to doubt me, just ask her."

Thus, everyone sent a curious gaze towards her.

Lady An Yu was stunned too, not expecting herself to get involved, but she suddenly saw among the people, her pimp was winking at her.

She immediately understood, this was a way to get famous. For a brothel prostitute like her, only such news would be able to raise her worth.

She did not answer, but lowered her head, blushing. Once she did that, most of the suspicious people believed it.

"So that's what happened."

"Looking at Lady An Yu's expression, the answer is clear!"

"You guys do not know the true story, but I do. In history, beauties are always paired with heroes, why do you think Lady An Yu likes Fang Zheng?"

"Why?"

"Hehe... because Shang Ya Zi is thin and weak, he has a 'weak' lower body. But Fang Zheng is strong and energetic, every one of his 'strikes' carries the all-out effort Gu's vigor. The impact of the wild boar, the slamming of the brown bear, the twisting of the crocodile tail, the force of the horse, the stamina of the green bull, and the endurance of the stone turtle... Hehe, such a man, which lady would not like him?"

"Ohhh!" Immediately, many men understood.

Some girls squeezed their thighs together, their faces blushing as they were deep in their imaginations.

Lady An Yu's head was lowered even further, thinking happily in her heart: "I'm on fire, I'm going to be famous!"

Just as the auction house was filled with rumors and guesses, Fang Yuan and Shang Ya Zi's competition had reached eight hundred and ten thousand.

"Fang Zheng, with me here today, you are bound to lose. Give up, you are not my match." Shang Ya Zi laughed happily, he added ten thousand every single time to piss off Fang Yuan.

"You think I am afraid of you! It is merely eight hundred and ten thousand, so what." Fang Yuan snorted coldly.

"Young master, this is enough, we should stop now." A servant carefully observed and advised.

Shang Ya Zi hesitated: "I know. Fang Zheng is adamant on getting the bitter strength Gu! After he bids, I am going to bid once more, and stop. This idiot, spending more than eight hundred thousand to buy a bitter strength Gu, it is almost twice the market price. I can finally vent this anger, it feels so good. Hahaha!"

At this time, Fang Yuan continued.

"But this time, I shall let you off. You can have the bitter strength Gu."

Servant: "..."

Shang Ya Zi: "..."

Chapter 308: Auction (4)

"Haha, I'm afraid Shang Ya Zi's face is green now." In the ninth private room, Wei Yang laughed uncontrollably: "But brother Fang Zheng, is it really okay for you to not get the bitter strength Gu?"

Beside him, Shang Xin Ci gave Fang Yuan a look of concern.

Fang Yuan laughed: "I must get the bitter strength Gu no matter what, but I am not idiot, spending eight hundred and ten thousand primeval stones on a Gu. I would rather refine it myself, eight hundred and ten thousand... it is enough for many tries."

"The chances of failure is very high, it will harm your body brother Hei Tu." Shang Xin Ci expressed her worry.

Fang Yuan shook his head slowly, he had others plans for this, but he could not tell them.

"Heh! This Fang Zheng played Shang Ya Zi like a fool. He spent eight hundred and ten thousand on a bitter strength Gu." The spectators watched with shining eyes.

"Shang Ya Zi, that idiot, this is a disgrace to all of us young masters!" The Shang clan young masters were furious.

"To say the truth, Fang Zheng's acting was superb, even I was fooled by him." Someone sighed.

"The person on the spot is baffled, the onlooker sees clearly. I knew something was amiss long ago." Someone claimed that he knew.

"Shang Ya Zi is so petty and enjoys revenge, thus he kept raising his bid. But Fang Zheng also failed to get the Gu he wanted, thus they were both losers. This is why you cannot bring feuds into the auction house." Ju Kai Bei thought in his heart.

"The real winner is the auction house."

"Ju clan must be overjoyed, one bitter strength Gu for eight hundred and ten thousand!"

Everyone discussed among each other.

But the truth is, they forgot one big winner.

That is, Lady An Yu who shot to fame.

Clink.

Shang Ya Zi smashed his cup on the ground, breaking it.

In fifth private room, the servants knelt on the ground, breathing as silently as they could.

Shang Ya Zi sat on his seat, breathing roughly as veins popped up on his forehead, his face flushing with rage.

He was tricked!

Eight hundred and ten thousand, spent on a bitter strength Gu he could not even use.

Shang Ya Zi felt his own heart bleeding!

The truth is, he was smart, after that setback, he learnt his lesson and became wiser. For the last two years, he worked hard and managed the shops very well.

But character decides your fate.

He was petty and spiteful, hatred made him lose his rationality, thus falling for Fang Yuan's trap.

"Fang Zheng, Fang Zheng, if not for the poison vow Gu, I will definitely kill you, I will chop you into a million pieces!!!" Shang Ya Zi screamed in his heart.

The auction continued.

Fourteenth item, fifteenth, sixteenth... eighteenth... twenty-eighth...

Another climax occurred, as the atmosphere livened up, and people quickly forgot Fang Yuan and Shang Ya Zi's conflict.

"The thirty-second item — rank four atmosphere Gu." The female Gu Master said.

Atmosphere Gu was shaped like a butterfly, having a pair of blue wings, each time it fluttered, there would be sparkling dust created in the air, it was a very attractive sight.

Atmosphere Gu was a unique Gu, it absorbed life energy and was born from the wind, it was a natural Gu. Up till now, no recipe master had been able to develop their recipe.

There were three types of recipe masters. Those that looked at the past, studying the ancient strength path, qi path and other Gu worms recipes, attempting to restore them. Some looked at the present, studying naturally formed Gu, attempting to produce their refinement recipe. And those who looked at the future, creating new and innovative refinement recipes from afresh.

Atmosphere Gu was not only created in a unique way, its use was also unique.

It could be used on a race or group, using an invisible force to create a habit or hobby that affected the entire group.

In ancient times, Gu Masters used it to deal with beast groups. If they were dealing with a group of steel needle boars, the Gu Master would use the atmosphere Gu and target them, giving them the habit of rubbing their skin on rocks.

The steel needle boar's fur were like steel needles, it was offense and defense in one. After rubbing on the rocks, they would get damaged, and the Gu Masters would be able to deal with them easily.

But later, Gu Masters eventually realized that the atmosphere Gu was the perfect weapon in ruling tribes or clans.

Some clans lacked food, but loved to brew wine. After using the atmosphere Gu, they removed the habit of brewing wine, and they had more food to eat, allowing the clan to develop better.

The atmosphere Gu could not only be used to deal with internal habits, but also external.

In history, there was a very famous example.

Two clans were in conflict, the weaker one used the atmosphere Gu and caused the stronger clan's women to have the interest to bind their foot.

The caused the women in this clan to become unable to carry out laborious tasks. The female Gu Masters also experienced a fall in strength, eventually the weaker clan overthrew and wiped them out.

At the end of the day, this was a Gu world, and there were all sorts of unimaginable Gu worms.

The female Gu Master introduced the Gu before saying: "Atmosphere Gu, base bid is two hundred and sixty thousand primeval stones."

"Three hundred thousand." Yi clan elder Yi Bu Hui bid first.

"Three hundred and fifty thousand." Fei clan elder Yan Luan Feng was equally tough.

"Three hundred and seventy thousand." A recipe master shouted.

"Three hundred and eighty thousand." Wei Yang spoke, he was in charge of Feng Yu Manor, he wanted to use this atmosphere Gu to make his subordinates work better.

"Five hundred thousand!" Fang Yuan shouted.

The crowd was silent.

Fang Yuan was silent for a while, but this voice made everyone recall, it was the person who tricked Shang Ya Zi previously.

"Five hundred thousand for an atmosphere Gu? Fang Zheng, you still want to con me? Do I look like an idiot!" Shang Ya Zi gritted his teeth, his eyes burning with rage.

He had just spent eight hundred and ten thousand primeval stones, if he spends another five hundred thousand, he would go bankrupt.

"Five hundred thousand, going once... twice... thrice... sold!" The female Gu Master announced.

Five hundred thousand was slightly above everyone's budget, no one bid anymore.

The atmosphere Gu was effective on a clan or force, but had little use towards individuals, it made many people feel indifferent towards it.

"Brother Fang Zheng, you could've gotten this Gu for four hundred and sixty thousand." Wei Yang sighed.

Shang Xin Ci had a different interpretation: "No, considering Yi clan and Fei clan, those two elders might compete and raise the prices above this. Bidding five hundred thousand made both of them reluctant to bid, it was a good call."

"Four hundred and sixty thousand... five hundred thousand... it is only forty thousand more. Brother Wei, I will keep this Gu then." Fang Yuan waved his hand, not bothered by it.

"Why, don't tell me you want to rebuild Gu Yue village?" Wei Yang was shocked, not expecting Fang Yuan to be interested in the Gu.

Earlier, he thought Fang Yuan was bidding for his sake.

"Of course I need this Gu, but the reason will have to kept secret for a while longer." Fang Yuan smiled, but did not elaborate.

"Hmph, acting secretive." Bai Ning Bing hated this side of Fang Yuan, she knew he was scheming again and kept her guard up.

After the atmosphere Gu, it was a set of eating wind Gu.

Thirty-eight eating wind Gu, grouped into one set and auctioned together.

Eating wind Gu was only rank two, but had a great use, it allowed the Gu Master to consume wind and fill their stomachs.

Ju clan was situated on top of Ju Feng mountain, they specialized in wind type Gu. The eating wind Gu was one of their specialties.

Time continued to pass.

Thirty-four... thirty-five... thirty-eight... forty-four...

Fang Yuan did not bid anymore, but Wei Yang tried once and successfully bought a light type Gu, getting what he wanted.

Bai Ning Bing also bid three times, eventually getting a rank three tornado Gu.

Just as Fang Yuan lost all his interest, the final forty-ninth item was displayed.

"This is the greatest treasure we have for this auction. It is not a Gu worm, and is not a precious refinement material, but it is a recipe." The female Gu Master introduced.

Next she added: "This recipe, because it is extremely precious, it has not been appraised yet.

This sentence made everyone curious.

Normally, precious refinement recipes would have to be appraised carefully. Because, once the recipe is handed to a recipe master to appraise, there is a danger of it leaking.

Recipe, recipe, it is best if less people know about it. A recipe that is known by everyone, is worth less than a blank piece of paper.

The female Gu Master was experienced, thus she did not speak but let everyone digest the information.

Seeing everyone deep in thought, but gathered their gaze on her once again, the female Gu Master smiled, throwing a bomb at them: "This recipe, is regarding the Heavenly Essence Treasure Monarch Lotus."

"Heavenly Essence Treasure Monarch Lotus? Did I hear wrongly!"

"Rank three Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, rank four Heavenly Essence Treasure Monarch Lotus, rank five Heavenly Essence Treasure King Lotus... This series of Gu worms are too famous, I can easily recite them."

"This is the Immortal Venerable Genesis Lotus' core Gu. I heard whoever is able to refine the rank six Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus would be able to receive the Immortal Venerable Genesis Lotus' inheritance ground!"

"To think Ju clan had such a treasure..."

The people in the auction house were bursting with excitement.

The female Gu Master continued: "Since everyone has an understanding of the heavenly essence treasure lotus, I shall not explain further. This is a recipe involving the refinement of the heavenly essence treasure monarch lotus. The starting bid is five hundred thousand!"

The price of the recipe was much higher than Gu worms.

The recipe of the rank four heavenly essence treasure monarch lotus was even more expensive than the monarch lotus itself.

Give a man a fish and you feed him for a day; teach a man to fish and you feed him for a lifetime. In theory, with the recipe, you will be able to create many heavenly essence treasure monarch lotus.

"Hold on, I have a question. Does this recipe require the heavenly essence treasure lotus as the refinement material?" Fang Yuan suddenly asked, shouting at the top of his lungs.

The female Gu Master's expression changed, she did not want to answer, but Fang Yuan was the owner of a purple thorn token.

She had been avoiding this question, but did not expect Fang Yuan's mind to be so astute, asking the most crucial question.

She had no choice but to confess: "Although in principle, we do not reveal the details of the recipe, but with Shang clan's integrity, this recipe does indeed need the heavenly essence treasure lotus as the main ingredient."

Everyone gasped.

"The heavenly essence treasure lotus is needed as the main ingredient, where are we going to find one?"

"No wonder Ju clan did not refine the heavenly essence treasure monarch lotus despite having this recipe."

"What use does this have? We can't do anything with it, this is too awkward."

"That was close, thankfully Fang Zheng asked that question."

"Mostly importantly, this recipe's authenticity has not been appraised yet."

"This recipe was kept as a treasure by Ju clan, it definitely is something good. I will bid five hundred and twenty thousand." A recipe master bid.

Even so, the recipe regarding the heavenly essence treasure monarch lotus still had great attraction to some Gu Masters.

"Five hundred and fifty thousand."

"Five hundred and eighty thousand."

The bids went up, slower and slower, until it stopped at six hundred and sixty thousand.

"Six hundred and seventy thousand." Wei Yang was the last to bid, as he obtained this recipe eventually.

Chapter 309: Xin Ci’s aspiration

With Wei Yang's successful bid of heavenly essence treasure monarch lotus's recipe, the auction ended.

Ju clan was after all a clan which had stood for centuries; it possessed deep foundations. Many auction participants obtained something from their collection while others were able to experience new perspectives.

"It is rare for everyone to gather together, do not leave now, let me host a feast." Fang Yuan urged everyone to stay.

In a restaurant, there were all kinds of delicacies, fine food and liquor, placed on jade plates.

"Brother Fang Zheng, this is the recipe you wanted." After three cups of wine, Wei Yang took out a heart engraved Gu and gave to Fang Yuan.

Heart engraved Gu was like a ladybug and was finger sized. Its whole body was scarlet red, and on its round carapace were four white heart shaped spots.

Heart engraved Gu was a storage type Gu.

It was almost the same as bookworm; they were used to store information.

Heart engraved Gu was a series of Gu that could range from rank one to rank five. A rank one heart engraved Gu only had one white heart shaped spot on its carapace, while rank two had two and so on.

This heart engraved Gu Wei Yang took out had four spots which meant it was rank four.

But, using a rank four heart engraved Gu to store the recipe of heavenly essence treasure monarch lotus was also normal.

Fang Yuan had spent six hundred and seventy thousand primeval stones for this recipe. He had made Wei Yang bid to avoid suspicions.

Seeing this heart engraved Gu, Fang Yuan did not accept it but said: "Since Brother Wei Yang had already refined it, it will be better for you to use it now so that I do not have to refine it again."

"That works too." Wei Yang nodded his head and poured his primeval essence.

The heart engraved Gu turned into a thin flow of pink light with a soft crackling sound. Under Wei Yang's control, the light flow entered Fang Yuan's heart and disappeared instantly.

Immediately, a recipe appeared in Fang Yuan's mind containing the method to refine heavenly essence treasure monarch lotus.

The main Gu worm for the fusion, all the supplementary materials, every step and every matter that needed attention was mentioned in it.

The contents could not be forgotten even if Fang Yuan wanted to forget them as if they were deeply imprinted into his heart. This was the ability of heart engraved Gu; granting a deep memory like it was etched into one's bones and heart.

A feeling of happiness emerged in Fang Yuan's heart: "I have heavenly essence treasure lotus but it is only rank three. It is still worth using now, but when I reach rank four, its use will immediately dwindle. Now that I have this recipe, if I can refine heavenly essence treasure monarch lotus in the future, it will no doubt be a great help to me."

Fang Yuan did not know heavenly essence treasure lotus' recipe. Obtaining this recipe was an unexpected joy.

Although this recipe had yet to be appraised, with Fang Yuan's plentiful experiences, he was able to give an initial judgement that the probability of this recipe being fake was very small. Otherwise, Shang clan would not have put it in the auction.

"But I still need some Gu to deduce it further and prevent any traps or errors."

"Now that I have bought this recipe, I am afraid some people have some thoughts about it. There will definitely be many people guessing if I have a heavenly essence treasure lotus."

"However, heavenly essence treasure lotus might be rare and precious, but it is not one of a kind and troublesome like the blood skull Gu. Otherwise, I would not be able to brazenly buy this recipe. Now, my Gu set assembly is nearing completion and with my cultivation breakthrough, I have fewer worries and there are not many problems in buying this recipe."

If it was before, Fang Yuan would not have bought this recipe so openly.

But now, he was only half a step away from rank three upper stage which he could reach in a few days.

After that, he would use white silver relic Gu and reach rank three peak stage!

His strength was completely different from when he first came, with the purple thorn token protecting him, plus most people were only guessing, the consequences were something he could accept.

"Calculating the time, Fang Zheng had already been in Shang clan city for over two years. His rapid development was really shocking. Heavenly essence treasure lotus..." Wei Yang thought while drinking wine, but did not speak out.

"Could it be Big Brother Hei Tu has heavenly essence treasure lotus?" Shang Xin Ci also inwardly guessed but did not ask.

On her first day of cultivation, Shang Yan Fei told her about the many taboos of Gu Masters. One of the taboos was to not casually inquire about the Gu worms other Gu Masters possessed.

To Gu Masters, their Gu were their butter and bread. It was their private matter, their secret and their trump card.

Once their Gu worms were exposed, it was very easy for others to target them.

Thus, among Gu Masters, it was a great taboo to ask what Gu worms the other held.

"Fang Yuan has heavenly essence treasure lotus, so he bought the recipe. This is understandable. But why did he give up bitter strength Gu to buy atmosphere Gu?"

Bai Ning Bing was sitting without speaking. She thought for a while but she could not see through Fang Yuan's move.

"Sigh, it would have been good if I was able to become a young master. Shang clan young master has an opportunity to apply for three Gu worms every year from the clan and the clan will search for the Gu without any charge." Shang Xin Ci said with a sigh.

This was a great policy by Shang clan to nurture their young masters. As long as the requests were not absurd, Shang clan would gather its strength to get the Gu the young masters wanted.

If Shang Xin Ci became a young master, it would be as easy as flipping her palm to get a bitter strength Gu by borrowing the whole clan's strength.

Fang Yuan had been searching for bitter strength Gu since long ago. One finally appeared in the auction, but Shang Ya Zi prevented him from obtaining it. Shang Xin Ci wanted to help Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan patted Shang Xin Ci's shoulder and smiled: "It does not matter. Who knows, maybe that Shang Ya Zi might hand over the bitter strength Gu to me."

"Second brother spent eight hundred and ten thousand to buy that bitter strength Gu, he has already become a laughingstock due to it. Wanting him to hand it over of his own accord, I am afraid it would not be possible..." Shang Chi Wen shook her head from the side, thinking Fang Yuan was indulging in fantasy.

"Could it be Big Brother Hei Tu has already thought of a plan?" Shang Xin Ci's eyes flashed with brilliance.

Wei Yang and others also looked over curiously.

Fang Yuan pointed at Bai Ning Bing, looking confident: "Everything is thanks to Ning Bing."

"Me?" Bai Ning Bing was stupefied.

"Speak quickly, what clever idea do you have?" Everyone could not help becoming more curious.

"You will find out in two to three days. Please wait till then." Fang Yuan laughed.

He then looked at Shang Xin Ci with a solemn expression: "Xin Ci, do you really want to become a young master? Becoming a young master means entering the political whirlpool and you will no longer have the freedom to act independently. You are now clearer of Shang clan's situation than me. The competition between Shang clan young masters is very intense, the struggle is even more bloody. If you want to become a young master, you will fall into this dangerous conflict."

This was the most crucial of matters; Fang Yuan needed a clear answer.

If Shang Xin Ci did not have such an aspiration, there was no point in helping her.

Under Fang Yuan's shining gaze, Shang Xin Ci smiled: "Big Brother Hei Tu, even now, do I really have freedom? I am also completely helpless in this."

"The whole journey to Shang clan city after joining the caravan was filled with untold dangers, I narrowly escaped death many times. I have reflected upon it; the world is an ocean and we are small boats on it. The small boats seem to be drifting freely with the flow, but most of them are helpless. Only with high cultivation and influence, can the small boat turn into a big boat and be able to resist the trials and hardships, to provide a safe area for the ones we care about."

Shang Xin Ci's words were ordinary and did not seem to contain any passion, but everyone could feel a heroic emotion from her.

"Great. You have aspiration." Wei Yang laughed.

Shang Chi Wen also threw an amazed look.

She had interacted with Shang Xin Ci for a fairly long time now but had never expected the latter to conceal such grand aspirations under her gentle appearance.

"My missy is a genius in business, she is more than capable of being a Shang clan young master." Xiao Die stood behind Shang Xin Ci and interjected proudly.

"Xiao Die..." Shang Xin Ci was embarrassed as she gave Xiao Die a stare.

Xiao Die simply stuck out her tongue.

"Haha, she is right. In that case, both of us will lend you a hand and help you become Shang clan young master." Fang Yuan laughed loudly as he felt a relief.

It was not strange for Shang Xin Ci to have such an aspiration.

Poor children matured early, Shang Xin Ci's childhood was not blessed as she was frequently bullied by her clansmen. She became clear of the cruelty of the world even more in the caravan due to her own negligible weak self. No matter how gentle the person was, they would still be greatly affected by such experiences.

However, Shang Xin Ci's nature was kind, different from Fang and Bai. She wanted to become strong, not only for herself, but more for the happiness of the people around her.

"Hehehe, this year's young master examination has already passed. Sister Xin Ci will have a chance in the coming year. But, the competition for the young master's position is very intense. Lord father has a lot of children; while there is only one young master position available every year, the number of competitors can amount to hundreds." Shang Chi Wen chuckled and gave advice to Shang Xin Ci.

However, she disapproved of this in her heart.

Shang Xin Ci's cultivation was very low, only at rank one upper stage now. Her aptitude also was not enough, not even having a B grade aptitude, so she did not have potential for development.

Her mother was from Zhang clan which had deep hatred against Shang clan. This was her greatest political disadvantage.

She was alone with no supporters, who would help her?

Her only advantage was that Shang Yan Fei doted on her. For her, Shang Yan Fei paid an enormous price, almost defying heaven, changing her hopeless aptitude into one which could cultivate. This was a treatment that none of his other children received.

However, this advantage was also a disadvantage in some aspect.

Shang Xin Ci was isolated. And even Shang Chi Wen was envious of her inwardly.

All these reasons made Shang Xin Ci unlikely to get the young master position, the chances were extremely slim.

Fang Yuan naturally was clear of these disadvantages. In his previous life, Shang Xin Ci became a young master only after six years. But things have changed, Shang Xin Ci was a lone force in his previous life, but in this life she has Fang Yuan's help...

"Xin Ci, do not worry. With me helping you, there is no need for next year, I will help you become a young master this year!" Fang Yuan laughed loudly

"Then I will wait and see." Shang Chi Wen had a smile on her face while inwarding curling her lips in disdain, feeling that the more Fang Yuan spoke, the more unreasonable he became, boasting so wildly.

Wei Yang put down his wine cup: "Brother Fang Zheng, the competition for Shang clan's young master position is not a small matter. As an elder of the clan, I cannot interfere in this."

"There is no need for Brother Wei Yang's help. The plan had already been made two years ago, and it is all thanks to Ning Bing." Fang Yuan smiled.

"Eh?"

Instantly, the gazes of everyone concentrated on Bai Ning Bing.

Becoming the center of attention, Bai Ning Bing still maintained her indifferent expression, but doubts started rising in her mind and she could not help but curse secretly.

"What does this have to do with me?"

"Ning Bing, Ning Bing, calling my name so affectionately, does he really think our relation is that great!"

Chapter 310: You shameless scoundrel!

In the blink of an eye, three to four days passed.

"Bitter strength Gu..." In the study room, Shang Ya Zi held the Gu in his hand, his eyebrows folding into a crease, as he had an overwhelming urge — to crush this Gu worm to death!

But he had to control himself.

This bitter strength Gu cost him eight hundred and ten thousand primeval stones, if he crushed it, his heart will ache.

Every time he looked at this Gu, Shang Ya Zi felt extremely gloomy.

He had an illusion that the bitter strength Gu was soundlessly mocking him, reminding him of his stupidity every single second!

At the auction a few days ago, he was tricked by Fang Yuan in front of everybody.

Right now, he was a laughing stock. Even his surrounding clansmen refused to meet him.

Nevermind if he was an idiot, but he was a Shang clan young master, such a deed brought shame to the entire Shang clan!

As a Shang clan young master, Shang Ya Zi's every action represented Shang clan and carried its image. His performance at the auction was not only a humiliation to himself, but also dragged the pride and glory of his Shang clansmen through the mud.

As for Shang Yan Fei, he did not say a word regarding this matter.

But this made Shang Ya Zi feel even more uneasy.

"No, I must salvage my reputation. I have to make sure father looks at me in a different light, I must change my clansmen's impression of me!" Shang Ya Zi gritted his teeth, deciding in his heart.

"Fang Zheng, you dare to oppose me, and played me like a fool. I will make sure you pay a terrible price!" His eyes shone with a dark sinister glow, flickering as he thought of ways to deal with Fang Yuan.

After this matter, his hatred towards Fang Yuan had reached a tipping point, it was hatred that seeped into his soul.

"Young master, young master, there is trouble!"

At this moment, a loyal servant came over, shouting in front of the study room.

"Why are you so frantic, is this the proper decorum? Get in here!" Shang Ya Zi scolded unhappily.

The room door was pushed open, as the servant kneeled on the floor, his face flushed with terror: "Young master, there is trouble. There's a rumor going around, it has spread all over Shang clan city. It says that you and Fang Zheng had once competed for Lady An Yu but you lost to him. That resulted in a grudge between you two, thus you went to find trouble with Fang Zheng."

"Lady An Yu? That Qin Yan brothel's prostitute? What rubbish is that." Shang Ya Zi curled his lips, laughing in disdain.

But the servant continued: "They are also saying, you had a secret deal with Fang Zheng in order to pass the yearly assessment, and... and faked the accounts."

"What?!" Shang Ya Zi heard this and howled, his expression changing. He jumped out of his seat, causing the brush and ink on his table to vibrate and fall.

The servant continued carefully but anxiously: "Young master, the rumor is so elaborate, they even have the transaction time, and the exact amount of the account is circulated. It seems the clan's internal affairs hall has been alerted, and they are sending Gu Masters here to investigate the matter."

"Huh?!"

Shang Ya Zi was dumbfounded, as if lightning struck his brain.

At that instant, his face went pale, like blood drained out of his body.

His heart palpitated, his body went soft as he almost fell onto the ground. Holding on to the study table weakly, he propped himself up.

This impact was too quick, too heavy, too sudden!

"I'm finished, completely finished. Once the matter of the fake accounting is exposed, I will lose the position of young master. This violates the clan rules, even mother cannot protect me. There is no point in begging father either! Once I lose this position, there are countless people waiting to devour me."

As the crisis struck, Shang Ya Zi was extremely frightened, falling into a state of panic.

"How can such news circulate? I was completely careful during the deal, other than Fang Zheng, no other person knew. Impossible, it's impossible..."

Shang Ya Zi muttered to himself as his expression was in a daze.

He was still too young, without any life-threatening dangers to train him, although he managed the shops for two years, and had good management skills, he only scratched the surface. Once a problem occurs, he becomes shocked and helpless.

...

Nan Qiu garden, the pavilion in the middle of the lake.

Light winds blew, causing small waves to form on the surface of the lake.

The lake was not big, the edges were made of stacked up rockery stones.

On the surface of the lake, there were large lotus leaves, connected together like a chain, the pink-white flowerbud had not opened yet. Gold and orange carps swam in the water, surfacing at times.

The pavilion was made of bricks and had a colorful roof and red pillars, it was obviously meticulously designed.

In the pavilion there was a chessboard, and two youngsters were playing.

One young man wore black clothing, his eyes dark like the abyss. The other was a female wearing white clothing, having silver hair and blue eyes, showing a cold expression.

It was Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing played for a bit, before looking outside at the lake: "This Shang Ya Zi is really stupid, his reaction speed is so slow. I sent out the rumor long ago, why hasn't he come here yet?"

"No worries, I have instructed the guards to let him in, he will come." Fang Yuan smiled, showing his confidence of being in control of the situation.

After panicking, Shang Ya Zi would definitely suspect Fang Yuan. Thus, he would come over and investigate the situation, even if he had no suspicions, he would come to convince Fang Yuan to cover up for him, to survive this investigation by Shang clan.

Bai Ning Bing squinted her eyes, sighing: "Fang Yuan, I am really impressed, you actually managed to exploit this 'loophole' in the poison vow Gu. You planned this from two years ago, didn't you? Just waiting and enduring, until the time was ripe to activate this trap."

Fang Yuan smiled, playing his chess piece as he answered: "Shang Ya Zi is a petty man, he will definitely take revenge. Why would I leave such a threat around? I did not use this earlier because Shang Xin Ci just had arrived in Shang clan and did not have a foundation. Gone with Shang Ya Zi, and in comes Shang Xin Ci, that is beneficial to both of us."

Bai Ning Bing did not speak anymore, but her eyes were shining with blue light.

In her heart, she felt a chill.

Fang Yuan's schemes came one after another, closely connected, once a person steps into it, it is like being in quicksand, trapped and helpless. The most shocking part was, he planned this two years ago after predicting this situation. Such foresight, it gave people chills, Shang Ya Zi was courting death by being enemies with him!

"Fang Zheng, where are you? Get out here now!" Shang Ya Zi's furious screams finally came.

The pavilion on the lake was not concealed at all, after Shang Ya Zi was informed by the doorboy, he quickly found Fang and Bai.

"Fang Zheng, you still have the mood to play chess? Do you know how far the rumors have spread? Tell me, was this all done by you!" Shang Ya Zi came to the pavilion, pointing at Fang Yuan as he shouted furiously.

Fang Yuan turned his body around, speaking plainly: "If this was done by me, would I be alive? Shang Ya Zi, I can't believe you are getting dumber and dumber. Did you forget that we used the poison vow Gu together?"

Shang Ya Zi snorted, his anger subsiding slightly. Fang Yuan was right, if he was the culprit, he would have been dead already. Now that he was sitting there safe and sound, it meant the rumors were not due to him.

But Fang Yuan's next sentence sent him into pure rage.

"Although I did not create the rumor, my companion Bai Ning Bing did."

Shang Ya Zi was stunned, his relaxed face turned bright red, like a meteor entering the atmosphere.

An intense rage grew in his heart.

"It was you, it was done by you! You bitch, I am going to kill you!" He screamed, his eyes red with anger, as he stared at Bai Ning Bing like he was going to devour her. His aura was insane, like a leopard or wolf trying to attack its prey.

"Oh? You want to strike here? Attack me?" Bai Ning Bing slowly stood up, her absolutely stunning face was cold as ice, as her icy tone contained strong disdain: "I am rank three peak stage, I have never lost a single battle in the battle stage, and I possess the purple thorn token, do you really want to fight to the death with me?"

Shang Ya Zi's facial muscles twitched, as he gritted his teeth, his eyes burning with fire as he stared fiercely at Bai Ning Bing.

He did not attack in the end.

He was rank three upper stage, and lived in an ivory tower all his life, he was not Bai Ning Bing's match. At the same time, Bai Ning Bing had the purple thorn token, something Shang Yan Fei gave her personally.

"Fang Zheng, you went back on your word, you will die a painful death! How did she know our deal? No wait, you went back on your word, why are you still alive?! Did you find some way to disable the poison vow Gu?" Shang Ya Zi turned to look at Fang Yuan, feeling uncertain.

"No, no." Fang Yuan shook his head: "The poison vow was — You and I will keep it a secret, and we 'cannot divulge the information to an unknowing third party'. But before the poison vow Gu was used, I already told Bai Ning Bing this matter. Thus, she was a 'knowing third party'. The rumor was also not let out by me. It was all Bai Ning Bing's effort. Thus, I did not violate the poison vow at all."

Shang Ya Zi opened his mouth wide, showing a dumbstruck expression.

Now that Fang Yuan mentioned it, the vow was indeed like this.

Then why did he not find out this loophole back then?

One, because of his mindset, he did not think Fang Yuan would tell Bai Ning Bing before they even discussed the issue. 'Cannot divulge the information to an unknowing third party', just looking at this sentence, there was no problems.

Second was because he was the one who initiated the use of the poison vow Gu, Fang Yuan looked unprepared and caught off guard, but he had actually predicted it long ago and was just trying to numb Shang Ya Zi's senses.

Third, Shang Ya Zi wanted to remain as a young master, and had no other ways. He was anxious and because the vow reciting was extremely painful, he could not think properly.

But now that he knew, it was already too late...

"Fang Zheng, you shameless scoundrel! You dare to trick me and deceive me like this! You are a despicable scum, so extremely despicable and shameless!"

Chapter 311: Actually, I am a kind person

Shang Ya Zi breathed raggedly, the more he scolded Fang Yuan the angrier he got.

"Ah!" He howled, no longer able to suppress his anger, and flipped the stone table.

The chess pieces were sent flying, and the table almost hit Fang Yuan's leg, but he dodged in time.

Shang Ya Zi took three steps backwards, his head dizzy and two traces of blood flowed down his nose.

"Shang Ya Zi, I'd advise you to calm down. The poison vow states you cannot harm me. Thank me for dodging, if the stone table hit my leg, your injuries would be more severe." Fang Yuan laughed lightly.

"Ah! Fang Zheng, I will tear you to shred, I want to pull out your tendons, skin you alive and devour every drop of blood and piece of flesh you have!"

Fang Yuan's smile became wider.

Bai Ning Bing frowned: "Shang Ya Zi, you had better shut up. If not, I'll throw you out by force! You are a Shang clan young master now, but that does not mean you'll stay one for long. You are finished now, the internal affairs hall has started investigating, you do not have many days left here."

Her words were like a bucket of cold water pouring on Shang Ya Zi.

That's right, he was going to lose his young master position! Saving his position was the crucial thing!

But how could he save it?

Whoever started the trouble should end it, he had to look at the source. He could only ally with Fang Yuan, to announce his innocence and deny any acts of fake accounting.

In fact, his original intent in coming to Nan Qiu garden was to find Fang Yuan to collude with him!

Shang Ya Zi felt a disgusting sickness in his heart as he thought about it.

"These two scoundrels, they are the culprits in causing my situation! I want to eat their flesh and drink their blood, but now I have to beg them to cooperate with me?"

Shang Ya Zi could not accept such an ending, his heart could not take it.

Fang Yuan observed his expression, and saw Shang Ya Zi in turmoil, thus he said: "Shang Ya Zi, I am actually a kind person, I always repay kindness with gratitude and hatred with revenge. If you did not find trouble with me multiple times, caused trouble for me secretly, even going to the extent of snatching the bitter strength Gu from me at the auction, why would I find trouble with you?"

"I admit, the poison vow did contain a loophole. But it has been two years since I came to Shang clan city. Have you seen me use it? If it was not you who went overboard, why would we reach such a state? All of these problems were single-handedly caused by you. I told the guards to let you in because I want you to know — your Shang clan is strong and I cannot afford to offend it, but you are just a young master, I am not afraid of going against you. Leave, I do not wish to make your life harder."

"Loosening the reins to grasp them better... what beautiful words." Bai Ning Bing glanced at Fang Yuan, a cold ridicule showing in her eyes.

But Shang Ya Zi did not leave.

He stood on the spot, motionless like a wooden pole.

His expression was constantly changing, turning pale and green alternatively, sometimes he looked ruthless while at times he frowned in deep thought. In no time his forehead was full of sweat, as he had evidently fallen into great conflict with himself.

Fang Yuan's words made Shang Ya Zi realize that their relationship had not reached the worst stage yet, there was a chance to salvage the situation.

It also reminded him that the bitter strength Gu was the reason for this.

"To protect my young master position, I have to make sure Fang Zheng cooperates with me. Cooperate..." Shang Ya Zi gritted his teeth, thinking of the bitter strength Gu.

"Do I really give it to him? I spent eight hundred and ten thousand on this!"

"What would others think of me if I give it to him? They might laugh their socks off!"

"But if I don't, how can I show my sincerity? How could I salvage our relationship?"

"I am indignant, in the end, I bought the Gu just for his sake! This is the biggest humiliation of my life!"

"Because of Fang Zheng, I spent eight hundred and ten thousand to buy a bitter strength Gu, causing everyone to mock me. Now, I have to hand the Gu over to him, isn't this just pathetic?"

"No, the bitter strength Gu is not the point, what's important is protecting my young master position. Without it, I am nothing, I will have nothing..."

In a short period of time, Shang Ya Zi considered his options, thinking until his ear were buzzing.

Fang Yuan knew it was time when he saw that pale face, dazed look, and swaying body.

"Shang Ya Zi, we told you to leave, why are you still here? Forget it, you pitiful soul, I do not want to bully you. Let's go Bai Ning Bing, I heard Ju Kai Bei and Yan Tu are fighting in the battle stage today. If we want to dominate the battle stage, we need to battle them, this is a good opportunity to learn about them." Fang Yuan sent a signal towards Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing stood up and pretended to leave, just as she took two steps, Shang Ya Zi spoke.

"Please stay here." His voice was coarse.

As he spoke, he called out the bitter strength Gu, and held it out with shaking arms.

"Fang Zheng, it was my fault earlier. This is the bitter strength Gu as an apology." As he said this, Shang Ya Zi felt extremely reluctant, but he got used to it as he spoke, and towards the end, Shang Ya Zi felt the huge burden lifted off his shoulders.

"This is the bitter strength Gu?" Bai Ning Bing stopped her steps, taking a glance.

This bitter strength Gu was like a beetle. A small body and large body, it's body was oval and palm-size. Its body was yellow brown, and had an uneven surface, as lumps grew on its back.

"He handed over the bitter strength Gu as expected, Fang Yuan must be overjoyed now huh?" Bai Ning Bing sighed in her heart, Fang Yuan's grasp at human behavior was way beyond her level.

Fang Yuan laughed loudly, but said: "Shang Ya Zi, I know what you mean, but do you think I can't survive without the bitter strength Gu? Although it is hard to refine, if I persevere, I will eventually obtain it. Do you think you can create problems for me when you feel like it, then reconcile when you need to? Fighting when you want to, making peace when you feel like it, is this world such an easy place? I, Gu Yue Fang Zheng, have my own dignity, are you trying to humiliate me?"

"You are mistaken." Shang Ya Zi quickly explained.

Fang Yuan snorted.

Shang Ya Zi elaborated anxiously: "I, Shang Ya Zi, swear, from today onwards, I will not create problems for you. The two of us can become good alliance mates, fighting among ourselves will only entertain outsiders. Other than the bitter strength Gu, I can make other compensations. Primeval stones, Gu worms, Gu refinement material, I am in charge of the shops, I can give them to you."

"Is that so..." Fang Yuan's expression relaxed.

Shang Ya Zi continued urging.

Bai Ning Bing became an outsider, watching this speechlessly.

Shang Ya Zi not only took out the bitter strength Gu, begging Fang Yuan to take it, but also had to compensate other materials.

But she knew that he was just trying to get over this crisis. Shang Ya Zi was a petty man, he would definitely take revenge in the future.

"I'll keep the bitter strength Gu, I need time to think about it." Eventually, Fang Yuan did not make a decision.

But this was enough for Shang Ya Zi to rejoice.

He thought that Fang Yuan was too proud and was trying to make use of the situation to ask for more compensation.

"I'll agree to all of them, in the future, I'll make sure you die horribly!" Vicious thoughts appeared in Shang Ya Zi's mind, as he smiled even more sincerely.

"Brother Fang Zheng, I am very sincere. Please do not take too long to consider, the internal affairs hall's investigation will be held these few days. Without the young master position, I would not be able to compensate you."

Fang Yuan nodded, no longer talking.

Shang Ya Zi left in a better mood, as Fang Yuan look at him from behind, he said to Bai Ning Bing: "Okay, you can go report the case at the internal affairs hall already."

Bai Ning Bing nodded, thinking: Tonight, I must go back and reread the vow I made with Fang Yuan, word by word!

...

A few days later.

In the study room, a sigh was echoing.

Shang Yan Fei placed his paperwork down expressionlessly.

The content was sent from internal affairs hall, involving Shang Ya Zi's fake accounting case.

Such a thing, it was okay to do it secretly. But once exposed, how could the clan tolerate it?

Shang Ya Zi was Shang Yan Fei's second son, the sigh earlier was a father's disappointment in his son.

"Revoke his young master status and punish him to join the slave capturing group, he is not to return here for three years." Shang Yan Fei raised his brush and wrote the punishment for Shang Ya Zi.

He is the Shang clan leader, because of this identity, he had to represent the entire clan. His every action and word had considerable consequence.

"Fang Zheng, Bai Ning Bing..." Shang Yan Fei's eyes were glowing with a bright light.

After settling Shang Ya Zi's case, this matter was not over.

Shang Ya Zi was a young master of Shang clan, but was schemed by two young outsiders, this was not respecting Shang clan, and him Shang Yan Fei!

"Hmph, Shang Ya Zi is after all my second son, is my son someone you guys can just toy with?"

Although Fang and Bai had once saved Shang Xin Ci, family was still family, in Shang Yan Fei's heart, his bloodline was closer.

Thus, he willed.

A bright red paper crane Gu flew out.

"Scheming against my son, as his father, I will have to take revenge for him! This is the punishment for you two, but it is also a test." Shang Yan Fei muttered.

The paper crane Gu's speed was extremely fast, entering a secret room.

"The clan leader has sent a letter!"

"Clan leader wants us to forcefully challenge Fang Zheng and Bai Ning Bing?"

In the secret room, there were two people.

One was tall as a tower, the other was thin like a matchstick, both of them looked at this letter and each other wordlessly.

It was the rank four Gu Masters Ju Kai Bei and Yan Tu!

Weren't they at odds?

If outsiders saw them sitting peacefully together, discussing matters, their jaws might drop.

Both of them were rank four initial stage, dominating the battle stage as they competed against each other. They both swore that they will not leave the battle stage unless they defeat the other.

But the truth is, they were Shang Yan Fei's secret pawn pieces.

Shang clan had rules, any Gu Master who dominates the battle stage, and reach Wei Yang's level, would be promoted to an external clan elder in Shang clan.

Ju Kai Bei and Yan Tu were Shang Yan Fei's way of controlling the battle stage!

Chapter 312: Rank Three Peak Stage once again

Nan Qiu garden, secret room.

The room was covered with darkness, the only source of light was a thin ray of starlight that was flowing like water towards the center of the room.

At the center, Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing were sitting cross-legged on mats. Bai Ning Bing's palms were placed on Fang Yuan's back; she was transferring rank three peak stage snow silver primeval essence to Fang Yuan.

It was completely silent in the secret room.

However, in Fang Yuan's heart, waves continued to surge.

Rumble!

A snow silver waterfall - chilly and majestic - came crashing down into Fang Yuan's primeval sea from his aperture.

It was the rank three peak stage snow silver primeval essence that had gone through bone flesh unity Gu.

Rank three Gu Master's primeval essence was silver. Initial stage primeval essence only had a thin layer of silver color, thus was called light silver primeval essence. Middle stage had varying amounts of silver color; some a lot and some little, thus was called blossom silver primeval essence.

Upper stage primeval essence was shining silver thus was called bright silver primeval essence.

Peak stage primeval essence was snow white silver, a magnificent sight, and was called snow silver primeval essence.

Right now, Fang Yuan was using snow silver primeval essence as the primary force and blossom silver primeval essence as supplementary; under his control, they formed surging waves and continually cleansed the aperture walls.

The aperture that was originally a water membrane, with light flowing as water, was shaking. After the cleansing process went for a while, the quantitative change accumulated to become a qualitative change; light poured out of the water membrane and just like water freezing into ice, it no longer moved, settling down to form stone membrane.

The stone membrane was radiant and glorious, and was even thicker and more stable than the water membrane.

With the formation of stone membrane, Fang Yuan advanced from rank three middle stage to rank three upper stage.

Building a stable foundation, success will come naturally.

Since the cultivation was finished, Bai Ning Bing slowly withdrew her hands, her blue pupils fluctuating with emotions.

With her help, Fang Yuan's cultivation had advanced rapidly and was finally catching up with her step-by-step.

She knew Fang Yuan still had a white silver relic Gu on him. He had not used it and was saving it for this moment.

That is to say, after tonight, Fang Yuan's cultivation would advance to rank three peak stage, at the same level as her.

"This guy is a cunning fox and is extremely treacherous. Although I haven't found any flaws in the poison vow, that doesn't mean there are no flaws within the poison vow." Bai Ning Bing was silent but her thoughts kept on moving rapidly.

Shang Ya Zi's downfall was a grim reminder.

The mental pressure Fang Yuan was giving her was becoming bigger and bigger, and now she was starting to have some doubts.

"Don't worry, I am sincere in cooperating with you. There are no problems with the poison vow." As if he knew what Bai Ning Bing was thinking, Fang Yuan suddenly opened his mouth.

"Hmph." Having her thoughts exposed, Bai Ning Bing's eyes revealed a trace of chill and said with cold irony, "I hope so."

Fang Yuan heaved a sigh, he had already expected Bai Ning Bing's reaction when he planned against Shang Ya Zi.

Everything had its merits and demerits.

Now, Shang Ya Zi was removed from his position, leaving a young master's seat vacant and gave an opportunity for Shang Xin Ci to advance. However, this created a crack in Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing's collaboration.

At the same time, it also forced Shang Yan Fei to make his move.

Just yesterday, Ju Kai Bei and Yan Tu had issued forced challenge towards Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing at the same time.

Once the news spread, it immediately caused a huge commotion in the battle stage and attracted countless people's attention.

Ju Kai Bei and Yan Tu were both rank four initial stage Gu Masters and were also called 'half the sky of the battle stage'. With two 'half skies' cooperating, they became the entire sky.

These nicknames gave a clear description of their status and strength.

Fang and Bai were the two rising stars of the battle stage. They were dazzling, winning all their matches without a single loss. Such strength was rarely seen in the battle stage even in the past.

Ju Kai Bei and Yan Tu were the two heroes of battle stage, standing proudly at the summit. These few years, there were many Gu Masters who wanted to stand out and become an external elder of the Shang clan, but they were stopped by these two and lost their hopes of advancing.

But now, these two jointly challenged Fang and Bai, naturally making everyone curious and also doubtful.

Someone said Fang and Bai were advancing too strongly, causing the seniors Ju Kai Bei and Yan Tu to feel uneasy and thus they were going to eliminate this problem early. Another said, Ju and Yan made a bet, and were using Fang and Bai to determine victory or defeat.

Almost no one thought Fang and Bai had the chance of winning against these two.

The formidable strength of Ju Kai Bei and Yan Tu was already deeply engraved in people's hearts. Even more importantly; one side was rank four Gu Masters, while the other side was rank three Gu Masters. There was a huge difference between their levels.

As Gu Master advance to higher ranks, the difference between each realm gets bigger and fighting across ranks become extremely difficult.

....

From behind, there was the sound of Bai Ning Bing standing up.

"Tomorrow is the match between you and Yan Tu, how are your preparations going, do you need my heavenly essence treasure lotus? According to our vow, I will do my best to help you." Fang Yuan slowly spoke from the darkness.

"No need." Bai Ning Bing coldly replied.

Fang Yuan was sitting cross-legged, he said without turning around: "You are really confident."

"So what if he is rank four? In these two years, you are not the only one who improved." Bai Ning Bing turned around and left.

Heavenly essence treasure lotus was Fang Yuan's, it would not represent Bai Ning Bing's true strength.

She wanted to check her progress using the match with Yan Tu.

The door to the secret room opened and closed.

After Bai Ning Bing left, the corner of Fang Yuan's lips slightly raised into a smile.

"Rejecting heavenly essence treasure lotus... it seems a trace of self-doubt has grown in her heart. This insecurity is very small, maybe she herself might not be aware of it. Bai Ning Bing, you are still too inexperienced..."

Fang Yuan muttered before organizing his cluttered thoughts.

He took out white silver relic Gu.

This Gu was like a round pearl and was white silver in color, with a size of a finger.

Since rebirth, Fang Yuan had seen it once on Qing Mao mountain. It was during the Jia clan's caravan, the white silver relic Gu was priced at fifty thousand primeval stones, it was an unattainable dream for Fang Yuan at that time.

The series of Relic Gu were extremely expensive. After all, with one use, they could raise a Gu Master's cultivation by a small realm, saving a lot of time and energy. At the same time, they provided a stable foundation and did not have any side-effects.

Gu worms were bought to be used.

Fang Yuan did not have any hesitation in activating white silver relic Gu; immediately, dazzling and magnificent lights shone upon the aperture walls.

About four hours later, Fang Yuan had leaped from rank three upper stage to rank three peak stage.

"Since rebirth, I have once again reached rank three peak stage!" Fang Yuan's eyes shone brilliantly and he could not help but clench his fists, his heart surged with emotions and joy.

It was different from the time on Qing Mao mountain, Fang Yuan had used stone aperture Gu at that time and paid a disastrous price of losing his future prospects to advance to rank three peak stage.

This time, Fang Yuan advanced to rank three peak stage while retaining his enormous potential for development. After all, he has A grade aptitude now.

Looking at the Spring Autumn Cicada.

After recuperating for over two years, its condition was recovering at a rapid speed.

Its withered body was gradually becoming glossy. The wings that were dried up like dead leaves, now had a layer of green that was full of life energy.

Its recovery naturally caused great pressure on Fang Yuan's aperture.

However, compared to the previous time, Fang Yuan's cultivation was rising rapidly because of Bai Ning Bing and bone flesh unity Gu, his rank three peak stage aperture was still enough to bear this pressure.

The situation had been truly pressing back at Qing Mao mountain, but now Fang Yuan was handling this with ease.

"But I cannot relax yet. Spring Autumn Cicada's recovery gets faster and faster. My cultivation speeds needs to surpass it, otherwise the same situation will happen again."

Time quietly passed and soon it was the next day.

The audiences were all waiting for the battle between Bai Ning Bing and Yan Tu.

There were green grass all over this super-size battle stage.

This was a grass terrain and was very commonly seen at Northern Plains.

A crowd of spectating Gu Masters had formed a circle around the battle stage, all of their gazes landing on the two protagonists on the battle stage.

The match had not started but the people were already commenting.

"Everything is against Bai Ning Bing this time!"

"Facing Lord Yan Tu, she is certain to lose."

"She is as beautiful as a fairy, it really makes people sympathize with her. Just thinking about her suffering a defeat breaks my heart into pieces..."

In the course of over a year, Bai Ning Bing had earned an impressive reputation, receiving strong publicity. Her appearance and temperament that was like a snow fairy got her a huge amount of attention.

On the stage, Bai Ning Bing and Yan Tu stood opposite each other.

Yan Tu was an old man and had a head full of unkempt and long hair.

He was thin like a stick and his legs were bare. Whether it was his fingernails or toenails, they had not been cut for a long time and were long and crooked.

He was wearing rags and had a hunched back, like an old beggar on the roadside.

"Hehehe, little girl you have such smooth skin, you are really beautiful." Yan Tu sized up Bai Ning Bing and said with a hoarse voice.

Wearing a white robe, the blue pupils and silver hair Bai Ning Bing immediately frowned, killing intent filling her heart: "Old geezer, stop your shamelessness."

"Little girl, you have no manners." Yan Tu laughed dryly, his ten fingers rubbing each other: "It seems I have to teach you how important it is to respect your seniors."

"Pointless banter." Bai Ning Bing had a cool expression, her gaze cold as ice as she stared at Yan Tu, her every movement containing vigorous fighting spirit.

Ding.

The sound of the bell signalled the start of the match.

Icicle Gu!

Fire pellet Gu!

Almost at the same time, Bai Ning Bing and Yan Tu made their moves.

Four white icicles and three balls of fire pellets shot towards one another.

Bang.

An icicle and a fire pellet collided in midair; the icicle melted, but the fire pellet still flew towards Bai Ning Bing, just that its power had greatly fallen.

Bai Ning Bing's icicle Gu was only rank two, while Yan Tu's fire pellet Gu was rank three.

Naturally, fire pellet was a notch above the icicle.

"I can only suppress the fire pellet if I use ice explosion Gu to detonate the icicles. However, my primeval essence will be greatly expended if I do that. This battle had just started..."

Bai Ning Bing's blue pupils flashed with an eerie light.

She jumped agilely and dodged the fire pellets, causing them to miss their target.

At the same time, she waved her hand.

Whooshh.

Three icicles flew towards Yan Tu.

Yan Tu gave a dry laugh, he took a step forward and twisted his body, dodging the icicles with a weird body posture as he began running at the same time.

His index finger repeatedly pointed and balls of fire pellets formed into a dense attack as they engulfed Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing coldly snorted; not to be outdone, she also repeatedly stomped and struck back with icicles.

For a moment, the two kept on contesting against each other while running around the big grassland. Icicles and fire pellets flew, the two dodged and attacked without stopping.

The match had just begun but its intensity had already surpassed everyone's expectations.

Chapter 313: Bai Ning Bing vs Yan Tu

Time slowly passed, the spectators were gradually moved by the match.

"To think Bai Ning Bing is actually so strong, being able to fight so evenly against Lord Yan Tu."

"She is using rank two icicle Gu against Yan Tu, but isn't at a disadvantage."

"Being able to use Gu worms to attack properly while moving is basic in Gu Master battles, but Bai Ning Bing is executing it perfectly."

"No doubt, Bai Ning Bing is a genius and her foundation is also extremely sturdy. No wonder, she has not been defeated till now."

Fang Yuan was among the crowd and was watching the match calmly.

Wei Yang and Shang Xin Ci had also come, and were standing beside him.

The three were in disguise, hiding among the crowd.

"Bai Ning Bing is fighting very forcefully. Even though she is using icicle Gu, once the numbers of icicles go up, her primeval essence consumption will also go up." Wei Yang was worried.

"There is a difference between the primeval essence of rank three and rank four. But Yan Tu is similarly using fire pellet Gu and his primeval essence is also continuously depleting. He might be rank four but he only has B grade aptitude. Bai Ning Bing is using the primeval essence recovery speed of her A grade aptitude to contend Yan Tu's rank four cultivation." Fang Yuan understood Bai Ning Bing's battle tactic with one glance.

"If that is so, then this will be an uphill battle for Bai Ning Bing." Shang Xin Ci exclaimed.

Now, she was also a Gu Master. With Shang Yan Fei's careful teachings, her vision was expanded and she could see through a lot of things.

As the three conversed, the situation on the battle stage suddenly took a turn.

"Little girl, you really like jumping around." Yan Tu's lips curled into a smile that did not resemble a smile. He suddenly raised his right hand and grabbed towards Bai Ning Bing from dozens of steps away.

As his right hand made a clawing motion, the imprint of a Gu worm on his palm flashed.

Whoosh!

There was the sound of flames blazing and in a blink of an eye, a giant fiery claw formed and flew towards Bai Ning Bing.

The giant claw only had three fingers, looking like an eagle's claw, except it was orange-red. Flames were scorching and even before the claw reached her, Bai Ning Bing could already feel the intense heat.

This was a rank three fiery claw Gu!

Bai Ning Bing immediately used her movement Gu to increase her speed and pull apart some distance between them.

She had already inquired about the information on Yan Tu and made preparations. She knew this fiery claw's attack range was smaller than fire pellets; it could only move several meters away from Yan Tu.

However, Yan Tu cackled and used his movement Gu as well, quickly closing in on Bai Ning Bing.

His movement Gu was rank four and had superior effects compared to Bai Ning Bing's. Thus, not only was Bai Ning Bing not able to widen their distance, Yan Tu was getting closer instead.

The fiery claw continuously descended on her and made grabbing motions.

It was difficult for Bai Ning Bing to evade the fiery claw as it was quick and stable under Yan Tu's skilled manipulation.

Bai Ning Bing's situation was becoming more miserable as she repeatedly rolled on the grassland.

Boom.

The fiery claw brushed past Bai Ning Bing's shoulder and fell on the grassland, immediately setting that part of the grassland on fire. The flames blazed furiously and started spreading.

Yan Tu willed it and the fiery claw once again rose from within the flames, it was just that it looked less threatening than when it had just been summoned.

However, with a slight decrease in Yan Tu's primeval sea level, the fiery claw instantly regained its splendor, wiping away all sluggishness.

Frost arrow Gu!

Bai Ning Bing regained her footing and stretched out her little finger; frost arrow Gu was residing in it and had formed a blue tattoo.

A ball of icy blue vapor condensed.

In a blink of an eye, the frost vapor formed into an arrow.

The arrow struck the fiery claw and suppressed its imposing flames.

Frost arrow Gu was a rank four Gu bought by Bai Ning Bing during the auction. It immediately established its dominance once used.

The fiery claw looked like it was about to be extinguished; Yan Tu slightly furrowed his brows, then without considering the expenditure, he poured in primeval essence and the fiery claw showed signs of recovering.

However, how could Bai Ning Bing let him do as he wanted?

Whoosh whoosh whoosh

She activated icicle Gu and at the same time, secretly activated ice explosion Gu.

Bang, the icicles exploded as they struck the fiery claw. The violent explosion completely extinguished the fiery claw.

Fiery claw Gu flew back, Yan Tu did not want to lose it so he immediately took several steps and used his hand to catch the fiery claw Gu as it turned back into an imprint.

Bai Ning Bing did not miss this chance; she formed two long ice blades, dual wielding them as she slashed towards Yan Tu.

Before the blades reached his body, Yan Tu felt the intense killing intent blowing at his face like an icy wind.

"That's a good blade!" Yan Tu gave a weird smile and then suddenly snorted, two fiery snakes flew out of his nose.

The fiery snakes were initially only the size of a necklace but rapidly expanded, and in the blink of an eye, changed into two large pythons that were several meters long and had the width of a bucket.

A fiery snake moved ahead in front of Bai Ning Bing and blocked Bai Ning Bing's two blades; while the other fiery snake wriggled around from the side to the back of Bai Ning Bing and started its attacks.

"They appeared, Lord Yan Tu's twin snake attack!"

"Sigh, I was defeated by this move."

"Yan Tu's control over the two snakes is really exquisite; the opponent is left unable to defend against both, they are really difficult to deal with."

The blazing snakes caused an uproar in the audience.

Bai Ning Bing's expression was solemn, the fighting intent in her blue pupils gathered into ice. The fiery snakes gave her a tremendous pressure, but this instead stimulated her fighting spirit even further.

Bai Ning Bing wielded her two blades and fought the two fiery snakes while Yan Tu stood outside the range of the battle and manipulated the snakes.

Yan Tu was able to use his mind to do three tasks at once; although he was only controlling two fiery snakes now, the movement was exquisite and the control was precise, this instead caused him to expend more of his mental energy.

Fiery snake Gu was a rank four Gu and under the pincer attack from two rank four Gu, Bai Ning Bing was slowly falling into a disadvantage.

She was finding it more and more difficult to defend against the attacks, after all her movement Gu and defensive Gu were not outstanding.

Bai Ning Bing was an offense type Gu Master and her Gu set placed attack as the main priority, while movement and defense were on the weaker side.

There was nothing she could do about this.

Gu Master's primeval essence had a limit and was not infinite. Thus, one needed to allocate the use of their primeval essence properly. Bai Ning Bing proportioned most of her primeval essence into the attack aspect while the primeval essence left for movement and defense were relatively lower.

Because of this, the movement Gu and defensive Gu she assembled were the Gu which consumed less primeval essence.

The Gu worms that consumed less primeval essence were naturally slightly less effective. After all, you get what you pay for.

"These two fiery snakes are restricting Bai Ning Bing's options. Just look, if the fiery snakes gets damaged from Bai Ning Bing's attacks, Yan Tu will just expend his primeval essence and heal them. It won't be good if this continues." Wei Yang stood beside the stage, his brows furrowed.

Fang Yuan's gaze flashed, he didn't speak but was looking forward to Bai Ning Bing's response.

Bai Ning Bing suddenly burst out with attacks.

She used frost breath Gu and frost arrow Gu one after another.

The continuous frost aura slowed and restrained the fiery snakes' offense.

However, this barrage of attacks sharply increased her primeval essence expenditure.

"Little girl, stop struggling." Yan Tu laughed and shot out balls of fire pellets.

Some of these fire pellets shot towards Bai Ning Bing, forcing her to dodge and waste her energy. The other pellets shot towards the fiery snakes and fused into them, causing the weakened fiery snakes to become even more vigorous.

This was the combination battle tactic of fire pellet Gu and fiery snake Gu.

Yan Tu had refined and perfected this tactic after having gone through hundreds of battles at the battle stage.

Compared to him, although Bai Ning Bing had the talent, was smart and had high comprehension, the time she had spent was too short and did not have as much accumulated experience as Yan Tu.

Bai Ning Bing wanted to make explosive attacks and defeat the two fiery snakes, but this was seen through by Yan Tu and he immediately struck back, twarting Bai Ning Bing's attempt and displaying his shrewdness as well as his experience.

"How is she going to deal with this?" Wei Yang's brows were tightly knitted.

"The situation is not looking good..." Shang Xin Ci also slowly analyzed the match.

Bai Ning Bing's dark blue pupils flashed with a decisive light.

Ice crystal Gu!

She used her vital Gu, her true trump card!

She had not intended to use it this early, but she could do nothing about it; since the match started, besides the deadlock at the start, Yan Tu was gradually gaining the initiative and suppressing her.

Bai Ning Bing was an attack type Gu Master, if she wanted to take back the initiative, she had to increase her offense even more!

Creak...

Bai Ning Bing's whole body emitted creaking sounds like water freezing into ice.

In a blink of an eye, she changed into a humanoid ice crystal. Her body slightly expanded and her silver hair was covered with frost, becoming rigid. Ice crystals spread towards the two ice blades, making them sharper, colder and even more firm.

"Oh, little girl, you're going all out now?" Yan Tu spoke but soon his smile froze on his face.

Bai Ning Bing's whole body turned into ice crystals and had no more hesitation as her attack and defense had integrated into one. She directly charged through the fiery snakes' attacks, heading towards Yan Tu.

To shoot a horseman, first shoot his horse. To catch bandits, first catch their ringleader.

Yan Tu immediately mobilized another fiery snake and blocked Bai Ning Bing.

Frost breath Gu.

Bai Ning Bing breathed out blue frost.

In her ice form, the frost aura that she breathed out was of a higher level.

The fiery snake immediately shrunk from this frost breath aura.

Bai Ning Bing continued to charge towards Yan Tu: "Old man Yan Tu, come fight with me if you have guts!"

Yan Tu turned grave, he did not specialize in close combat. Bai Ning Bing's might was awe-inspiring, he would definitely be in trouble if he fought with her in close combat.

He might be at rank four and walked the powerful fire path, but Yan Tu's fighting style was hit-and-run and because of his shrewd nature, he was not incited by Bai Ning Bing's remarks and started retreating with his movement Gu.

Bai Ning Bing's heart sank.

Her body had turned into that of ice crystals, so her movement Gu was less effective than before.

She would have to slow down Yan Tu if she wanted to catch up to him.

Thereupon, Bai Ning Bing repeatedly shot out frost arrows; the cold, frosty aura of the frost arrows had the effect of freezing muscles and blood, thus slowing down the target's movement.

However, Yan Tu easily dodged with his superb technique; none of the frost arrows landed on him.

The frost arrows could not hit Yan Tu, causing the distance between Bai Ning Bing and him to become larger.

Yan Tu laughed coldly, he felt no embarrassment while being chased by a junior.

He made the best judgement.

Ice crystal Gu could not be used frequently; if it was used for longer periods of time, it could cause the user to completely change into ice crystal and become an ice sculpture.

Thus, Bai Ning Bing used vitality Gu at the same time as ice crystal Gu, to maintain her life force.

However, even vitality Gu could only prolong the time the ice crystal Gu could be used.

Yan Tu knew this clearly. Bai Ning Bing had investigated him, he had also investigated Bai Ning Bing. As long as he prolonged this match, victory would be his for certain.

Although such a method did not display even a little of the dominance of fire path Gu Masters, this was no doubt the most optimal tactic.

Bai Ning Bing stopped.

"I am not able to strike this old guy, only that move can change the situation now."

Her eyes flashed with a trace of hesitation.

"Should I use this move or not?"

Chapter 314: Victory and Loss (Double chapter)

Bai Ning Bing hesitated for only a second before her blue eyes shone with decisive light.

"Ice blade storm, reappear once more." Bai Ning Bing sighed softly.

She raised her arms, sharp ice blades acting as an extension of her arms.

Her ice crystal form gave a grim domineering aura. Vitality Gu gave out a warm current and flowed through her heart, liver and other organs, maintaining a part of her life force and preventing Bai Ning Bing from completely turning into ice crystal.

Vitality Gu had another advantage, that is once activated, it turned into a warm current filled with vitality and moved by itself. There was no need consciously control it.

Swirl Gu!

Tornado Gu!

Bai Ning Bing successively used these two Gu.

Swirl Gu was a movement Gu that increased the Gu Master's turning speed. Now that it was activated, Bai Ning Bing's whole body started rotating rapidly.

And the activation of tornado Gu immediately created a whirlwind. The whirlwind covered Bai Ning Bing and in a few seconds, enlarged into a tornado.

The dark blue tornado was like a young blue dragon rising into the air.

Ice edge Gu, ice crystal Gu, swirl Gu and tornado Gu; Bai Ning Bing was using her mind to do four tasks at once.

No, it was still not over.

Frost breath Gu!

Bai Ning Bing exhaled and frost aura instantly pervaded her surroundings.

With her mortal flesh body, she could only activate frost breath Gu in intervals to prevent her mouth and tongue from freezing. However, after turning into ice crystal, she could continuously breathe out the frost breath.

The frost aura mixed into the tornado, changing it into an icy tornado.

The wind blew everywhere, grass was sent flying, a light blue icy frost formed on the grassland.

At this moment, Bai Ning Bing was doing five tasks at once!

This was the talent of the ten extreme physique that could look down upon the world. On this aspect, Bai Ning Bing had already surpassed Fang Yuan.

The killer move appeared again, ice blade storm!

Cold wind rose, and the temperature in the surroundings drastically fell. The sharp ice blades gave the tornado even more power.

The two fiery snakes ignorantly charged towards the tornado and suffered severe injuries. The snake heads as well as most of their bodies were cut down by the icy storm.

The fiery snakes hurriedly retreated.

Flames merged into them, as the snake heads and their bodies reformed again. But their bodies were not even half the size of before.

The icy storm was increasing in power, large amounts of frost spread over the grassland.

The parts of the grassland that were burning were already showing signs of extinguishing because of the frost.

Yan Tu's eyes shrunk at this sight and he recalled the fiery snakes back into his nose.

"What move is this?"

"I have never seen Bai Ning Bing use this move."

"Killer move, this is absolutely a killer move!"

The audiences were thrown into a commotion as they started discussing loudly.

Even Wei Yang showed an amazed look: "Such an extremely powerful killer move. How many Gu did Bai Ning Bing use for this attack?"

Shang Xin Ci's gaze were nervous and expectant: "This move is so strong, she might be able to win against Yan Tu."

Fang Yuan was silent as he concentrated on the match.

He had already seen Bai Ning Bing use ice blade storm before, but the power of the ice blade storm now had jumped to a whole new level.

Bai Ning Bing's growth was astonishing.

She had exceptional aptitude and talent, combined with her Gu set, she was a unique Gu Master.

Looking at it now, she had not discarded her meticulously designed killer move, ice blade storm, but instead improved it.

"You still had such a trump card left..." Yan Tu was no longer calm, the moment the ice blade storm appeared, he lost a bit of his confidence.

His heart started to palpitate rapidly. He was actually getting such a feeling from a junior, a rank three Gu Master!

Bai Ning Bing's strength surpassed Yan Tu's expectations and caused him to feel an intense threat.

Killer move.

Often formed by using several Gu worms at once, through meticulous pairing, an extremely strong move is born.

A killer move was not something all Gu Masters possessed. Only those with plentiful experiences or great talent could develop their killer moves.

Killers moves often consumed a lot of primeval essence and was very taxing on the mind, but their might were no doubt formidable beyond imagination.

"This is not good, this move is getting stronger, I have to suppress it early. If I let it grow and accumulate momentum, it will truly be unstoppable." Yan Tu was a veteran with great experience and soon saw a weakness.

If it were other Gu Masters, most of them would be scared witless and choose to watch the change quietly. However, Yan Tu was extremely shrewd and saw through this killer move's weakness.

"It will be difficult to restrain her with ordinary moves, I will just be wasting primeval essence. Since it is so... I shall use my killer move against her killer move!" Yan Tu resolved himself.

Fuel oil Gu!

He opened his mouth wide and spurted out large amounts of fuel oil.

The amber colored fuel oil gave a pungent odor. Yan Tu used all his strength in activating the fuel oil Gu, not daring to have the slightest of reservation.

The fuel oil poured out like a small waterfall onto the grassland and became waves. The fuel oil waves submerged the whole battlefield within seconds.

Ice blade storm was getting bigger and bigger, the cold aura spreading further; the fuel oil's momentum immediately slowed down as it approached the storm, as large amounts of oil was sent flying.

Ice blade storm had explosive power but the the coldness was not enough to freeze the fuel oil.

At once, fuel oil rained down on the whole battlefield.

Besides the vicinity of the ice blade storm, a thick layer of fuel oil covered all the other areas of the grassland, almost forming a swamp.

Fiery snake Gu.

Yan Tu snorted and the earlier two fiery snakes appeared again.

Twenty percent of yellow gold primeval essence was spent to let the fiery snakes get back to their peak size and power once more.

The fiery snakes landed on the ground and immediately created blazing flames.

The red flames quickly spread, as the whole battle stage instantly changed into a sea of fire.

The flames blazed intensely on the grassland, the green grass wilted and turned into ashes which then further fuelled the growth of the blazing fire.

Only one place remained safe from the fire in the super-size battle stage, and was instead frozen in ice.

That was where Bai Ning Bing's ice blade storm was at.

She and Yan Tu had changed the grassy terrain into one of ice and fire, the clash of two extremes.

The two fire snakes moved in the sea of fire with joy, circling the rotating ice blade storm and were not in a hurry to attack.

Bai Ning Bing's ice blade storm was also continuously enlarging and accumulating in power, the top of the tornado had already changed into a dome shaped form due to the constant movement..

Whoosh whoosh whoosh!

The icy tornado created violent sounds and gave a majestic aura; causing the audience to smack their lips in anticipation.

"I'm not done yet, fiery claw Gu!" Yan Tu suddenly shouted.

He had four fiery claws Gu on him, and right now he sent them all out.

His primeval essence took a severe hit, the primeval sea in his aperture rapidly fluctuated as the brilliant golden sea level fell sharply.

The four fiercy claw Gu did not charge towards the ice blade storm, instead they flew towards the fiery snakes and merged.

In an instant, the two fiery snakes grew a pair of claws.

Snakes with claws were no longer snakes but dragons!

The two fiery dragons flew with their heads high in the sea of fire, brandishing their claws and revealing a defiant aggressiveness.

"Lord Yan Tu has combined fiery snake Gu and fiery claw Gu to display a portion of the might of the rank five fiery dragon Gu."

"To think that in this match, we would get to see Lord Yan Tu's killer move — fire sea twin dragon kill."

"Bai Ning Bing is just a newbie, she can be proud of herself, being able to force Yan Tu into using his killer move!"

The audiences were all excited at this scene.

Both sides brought out their killer moves, the battle had suddenly reached the climax.

Killer move vs killer move!

Would the winner be Yan Tu's fire sea twin dragon kill with its huge and majestic power? Or would it be Bai Ning Bing's world engulfing ice blade storm that will beat 'half the sky of the battle stage'?

Everyone fixed their gaze on the battle stage, waiting in anticipation.

The fiery dragons raised their heads and let out a soundless hiss before pouncing forward from two sides.

The fiery dragons struck the icy storm, tearing at it with their fiery claws. Their entire body coiled around the icy storm.

The white and blue ice storm was like a huge pillar, standing straight against the attacks.

The sharp ice blades clashed against the fiery claws and continuously slashed the fiery dragons' bodies.

After some time, the two fiery dragons could no longer endure it and retreated.

They submerged into the sea of fire and absorbed the flames, immediately recovering their power.

The grassland was burning, this overflowing inferno provided enough replenishment for the fiery dragons!

Yan Tu had fully used this grassland.

The two fiery dragons attacked again and again, and were defeated each time.

After the defeat, they would attack again relentlessly.

"Fire sea twin dragon kill can't push down Bai Ning Bing?"

"Is the sky collapsing? If this goes on, Bai Ning Bing has hope of winning against Yan Tu!"

The audience were amazed again and again.

"No, ice blade storm has been restrained. The wind flow has been forcefully cut and can't accumulate more power. Bai Ning Bing should start moving and start kiting her opponent!" Wei Yang's expression was grave, his specialty in battle was kiting.

Fang Yuan's brows slightly furrowed, an obscure light flashed in his eyes.

He could tell something was wrong.

With Bai Ning Bing's wisdom, she definitely knew that she could not resist it head on and should fight while moving. However, she did not do that.

"It seems, this killer move is still imperfect..." Fang Yuan inwardly speculated.

Right now, Bai Ning Bing was powerless to dictate her movement!

This was the first time she's used the revised ice blade storm in battle, she had planned it well but now she discovered a serious problem.

The ice blade storm lacked a forward momentum, it could only rotate on the spot. This was truly an unspeakable embarrassment.

"I changed into ice crystal form and continuously used frost breath, now the tornado has become too dense and there is no way I can move forward!"

Bai Ning Bing used all her effort to activate her movement Gu to change this situation.

However, she was already doing five tasks at once and this was her limit, her mind was already stretched to its limit and did not have any spare energy left.

Fortunately, Yan Tu had still not discovered this.

He took the initiative to attack to block Bai Ning Bing from accumulating more power, but this instead helped her to cover this fault.

"There is only one method left now, to continue walking down this desperate path. Continue to expand the ice blade storm, maybe the wind flow will become strong enough to move it."

Bai Ning Bing's fighting spirit had not disappeared, this predicament instead bolstered it.

However, whether it was her or Yan Tu, both of their primeval essence were sharply decreasing.

The audience had also fallen into silence.

The majestic ice blade storm and the terrifying orange sea of fire divided the battle stage into completely different terrains.

The barrier around the battle stage isolated most of the power, but wind still blew out.

This wind was sometimes hot and sometimes cold, giving the audience a personal experience of the intensity of the battle.

The sea of fire blazed, the two orange fiery dragons shook the ice blade storm. They were defeated again and again, but charged forward each time, advancing without losing their spirits.

"This is the strength of Lord Yan Tu, the power of a rank four Gu Master." Someone sighed.

"Being able to fight Lord Yan Tu to this extent, Bai Ning Bing can be said to be the third strongest in the battle stage." Someone commented with a visible shock on his face.

In the battle stage, Yan Tu and Ju Kai Bei had fought dozens of battles, but a clear winner had not been determined. They were the strongest two in the battle stage.

Through this battle, Bai Ning Bing's battle strength was also recognized by the people and was regarded as third strongest.

Time passed by minutes and seconds, the ice blade storm gradually slowed down, as the wind flow decreased.

Meanwhile, the blazing inferno was also mostly extinguished.

The fuel oil was expended and the green grass had all turned into ashes.

However, the fiery dragons were mighty as before; they not only had the replenishment from the sea of fire, but also the support of Yan Tu's yellow gold primeval essence.

Bai Ning Bing's primeval essence gradually became insufficient in supporting her expenditure, at this stage, the gap between the cultivation levels was clearly shown.

If she had the heavenly essence treasure lotus, she could still have the strength to fight on. Unfortunately, she refused Fang Yuan's good intent.

"It is over." Yan Tu laughed and with a shift of his mind, the two fiery dragons suddenly merged into one, forming an even larger fiery dragon.

This change made many people involuntarily gasp in surprise.

This move was Yan Tu's secret move and had never been revealed, but now he no longer cared about secrecy in order to pierce Bai Ning Bing's ice blade storm.

The fiery dragon opened its mouth, the four fiery claws waved together and ruthlessly clawed at the ice blade storm.

But suddenly, the storm exploded.

Bai Ning Bing furiously activated frost breath Gu and froze all of the fiery claws!

Ice blade storm suddenly inflated and engulfed most of the fiery dragon's body like a monster!

"What?!" Yan Tu turned pale with fright, he suddenly realized that the weakening earlier was only Bai Ning Bing's pretense.

He immediately willed the fiery dragon to retreat.

The fiery dragon suffered serious injuries, its might had diminished; it lost two fiery claws and its size also decreased to less than half.

The audiences immediately rose in uproar at this.

"Is Bai Ning Bing going to win?"

"They had been fighting intensely for so long but she actually has energy left?"

Yan Tu's expression was grave, Bai Ning Bing's sudden attack inflicted a disastrous damage to him.

In an instant, he had lost a fiery snake Gu and two fiery claw Gu.

The ice blade storm suddenly dispersed completely.

Bai Ning Bing revoked the ice crystal Gu and returned to her original mortal body. She had used up her primeval essence, her aperture was completely dry.

"I admit defeat." She coldly announced.

There was a temporary silence, but the whole battle stage erupted in an uproar next.

Bai Ning Bing was admitting defeat?

The audience had not expected this.

"She should have exhausted all her primeval essence when she used that final explosion to inflict heavy losses to Yan Tu." Fang Yuan realized.

Even if I cannot win, I will make you feel worse.

Bai Ning Bing's choice was sensible and she did it decisively and ruthlessly.

After realizing this, Yan Tu was furious but a formless force pressed down from above and suppressed him.

He could not move.

This was the ability of the battle stage.

The hosting Gu Master walked into the battle stage that had changed beyond recognition and announced the result.

According to the rules, the winner has the right to demand the loser to hand over a Gu.

"I want your ice crystal Gu." Yan Tu said with hatred.

"Take it." Bai Ning Bing coldly snorted and handed over the ice crystal Gu.

The two completed the transfer on the spot.

Ice crystal Gu was Bai Ning Bing's vital Gu, the moment she lost it, blood flowed out from her seven orifices.

Yan Tu's expression was still unsightly, he had chosen ice crystal Gu to teach Bai Ning Bing a lesson. But even so, his losses were much greater, a rank three ice crystal Gu could not cover his losses.

After this battle, Bai Ning Bing might have lost but it established her fame.

One could say, she had gone down in flying colors.

Shang Xin Ci let out a breath of turbid air and calmed down her mind.

"It is a pity, if Bai Ning Bing had listened to my advice and chose frost demon Gu at that time, the situation would have been much better." Wei Yang lamented.

Ice crystal Gu was suitable for men while frost demon Gu was suitable for women.

"Bai Ning Bing lost ice crystal Gu, maybe this is a chance for her to choose frost demon Gu." Wei Yang said with an expectant tone.

Chapter 315: Hard Qi Gu

"Did you see that battle? It was really splendid!"

"Bai Ning Bing suffered her first defeat and Yan Tu's victory was also not easy."

"My heart ached when I spent twenty primeval stones to watch the battle, but after the match, I feel that it was truly worth it."

Bai Ning Bing and Yan Tu's battle was like a boulder falling into the lake, the ripples spreading all over Shang clan city.

In every street, people were discussing the match.

"Old ginger is hotter than young ginger, Lord Yan Tu won in the end."

"But Bai Ning Bing lost gloriously. Fighting to that level, it shows that her future is limitless."

"It is so unfortunately that I couldn't see that match."

"Bai Ning Bing might have lost her vital Gu and suffered a backlash, but ice crystal Gu is easy find, this will not have too big of an influence on her."

"I am now really looking forward to the match between Fang Zheng and Ju Kai Bei."

"Right, that is sure to be a battle between dragon and tiger!"

The match between Fang Yuan and Ju Kai Bei was scheduled seven days later. And because of Bai Ning Bing's outstanding performance, their match received countless attention.

Bai Ning Bing, however, went missing.

After that match, she did not return to Nan Qiu garden.

"Did something happen to her?" Shang Xin Ci was worried.

"Don't worry, I understand her. She has a very prideful nature, after suffering such a defeat, she needs some time alone." Fang Yuan comforted Shang Xin Ci.

Bai Ning Bing might have a female body but her heart was that of a man.

All men were like lions and wolves; when they received injuries, they would look for a secluded place and silently lick their wounds.

Women were different; when they felt wronged, they would want to pour out their grievances. They thirst for protection and comfort.

Shang Xin Ci nodded, her beautiful and gentle eyes looked at Fang Yuan with concern: "Is it possible to not fight? That Ju Kai Bei is as famous as Yan Tu. Big Sister Bai Yun lost and had to give up her ice crystal Gu. Ju Kai Bei is a strength path Gu Master, if Big Brother Hei Tu loses all-out effort Gu..."

Bai Ning Bing lost ice crystal Gu but it could be replenished. However, if Fang Yuan lost all-out effort Gu, he had no way to get another.

Fang Yuan smiled: "Precisely because of that, I cannot lose. Alright, I will be secluded cultivation for a few days to refine a Gu. You should go back first."

Fang Yuan had already made inquiries on Ju Kai Bei's strength. After the match of Bai Ning Bing and Yan Tu, he was able to make even more conjectures.

Ju Kai Bei was a rank four initial stage Gu Master and was equally matched with Yan Tu. Fang Yuan estimated he only had thirty percent chance of winning against Ju Kai Bei with his current strength.

Thirty percent chance of victory did not look high. But in actuality, if you consider the gap between the two large realms, thirty percent was rather outstanding already.

"If I am successful in refining that Gu, I will have sixty percent chance with its help! I can only hope that the refinement succeeds."

Fang Yuan entered the secret room and began refining.

...

First inner city.

In a study room, bright and gentle lights were on.

Shang Yan Fei quietly looked at a ball of colorful smoke floating in the air. The colorful smoke churned and unfolded the scene of the match between Bai Ning Bing and Yan Tu.

Shang Yan Fei watched this battle from start to finish and then put away the colorful smoke.

Bai Ning Bing had lost.

She lost her vital Gu and also suffered from backlash.

According the intel from Feng Yu Manor, Bai Ning Bing was recuperating at Doctor Su Shou's place.

With this, she had received the punishment and a lesson for scheming against his second son.

Shang Yan Fei closed his eyes and leaned against the back of the chair.

Bai Ning Bing lost, she did not pass the test, but her innate gifts and talent were already recognized by the public. Given some time, she was certain to surpass Yan Tu and have great accomplishment.

This was a true genius.

Shang Yan Fei cherished and was fond of talented people.

Seeing Bai Ning Bing's performance, he had an even greater desire to recruit her for Shang Xin Ci.

"Next, it is Fang Zheng's turn. I wonder what surprise he will give me. Hmm, I heard he might have a heavenly essence treasure lotus..."

Heavenly essence treasure lotus, there were two of these in Shang clan city's living treasure door. There was also a heavenly essence treasure monarch lotus as well.

However, they would have to pay an even greater price to take out these treasure lotuses.

Living treasure door guarded the treasures and even Shang Yan Fei, the clan leader, had to comply with the rules set by his ancestors.

"Fang Zheng is a strength path Gu Master, heavenly essence treasure lotus will not be able to show its true worth in his hands. It is better for Xin Ci to have it."

Shang Yan Fei pondered for a while while sitting upright. After thinking through, he sent out a paper crane secret letter.

The paper crane followed the dark path and flew inside a secret room.

Ju Kai Bei and Yan Tu soon felt a reaction and gathered in the secret room.

"Master has sent a secret letter again!" Yan Tu unfolded the secret letter and after glancing at it, he gave it to Ju Kai Bei, "It is for you."

Ju Kai Bei skimmed through the secret letter and muttered: "Master thinks Fang Yuan might have a heavenly essence treasure lotus. If I win this battle, he wants me to try and request for this grass Gu. Furthermore, even if he doesn't have it, I am not allowed to choose all-out effort Gu."

Ju Kai Bei's brows furrowed after he read this.

He had planned to demand Fang Yuan's all-out effort Gu. This legendary Gu was extremely attractive to a strength path Gu Master like him.

Unfortunately, Shang Yan Fei sent such a command.

"Master loves talents and wants to protect that Fang Zheng's growth." Yan Tu analyzed.

He raised his head and looked at Ju Kai Bei's frown, and mediated: "Brother Ju, take note of your mental state. We are the hidden elders of Shang clan and must follow clan leader's commands. Times are different from when we freely roamed the world and did whatever we wanted."

Ju Kai Bei nodded his head solemnly and said with remembrance: "Those were memorable times. Walking in the world alone, free and unrestrained."

"Could it be Brother Ju is thinking of becoming a demonic Gu Master again?" Yan Tu's tone was solemn.

Ju Kai Bei scoffed: "Brother Yan Tu, do you still not know me? It was just a casual remark. Demonic Gu Masters might be free and unrestrained, but the pressure and risks are huge. Their corpse might be found in the wild one day and there wouldn't even be people to retrieve the corpse."

Yan Tu's expression relaxed at this.

Ju Kai Bei and Yan Tu were once solitary demonic Gu Masters.

They had even made a name for themselves while roaming around southern border and had endured for ten years. However, they were becoming tired as the time passed; demonic Gu Masters lived extremely free lives, but there was a huge pressure on them, they would have to keep on worrying about the food for their Gu, primeval stones, their own safety and other things.

The two were slowly fed up with such a life, but they did not have the courage to change their ways.

Until one day, when these two encountered each other in the wild.

There was an extreme lack of trust between demonic Gu Masters. The moment these two noticed the other, they immediately attacked to ensure they held the initiative.

Who would have imagined these two were evenly matched and fought from day to night. They used their intelligence, traps, and every kind of trick they knew with all their strength.

When dawn arrived, the two did not have strength to continue their battle; their primeval essence were fully expended and their bodies were covered with wounds. They were both within each other's reach, but they did not have strength to make the final strike and kill the other.

When the morning light shone on their faces, these two both made an identical decision.

"I am tired of this life. Sigh, if I can survive this battle, I will go to Shang clan city and join the righteous path." Yan Tu softly mumbled.

"I am so sick of it, after this battle, I will go to Shang clan city and fight for that external elder's position!" Ju Kai Bei fiercely cursed.

They did not know why, but the two spoke at the same time.

After they finished speaking, the two looked at each other.

After a moment of silence, the two laughed heartily at the same time.

This was fate, it was like heaven's will. On this day, two veteran demonic Gu Masters with not the least bit of trust, gained a best friend for life.

As if they wanted to completely discard their past, they began changing and chose to trust each other.

This trust was a trust without any reservations. The two went from one extremity to another extreme.

"Returning to the topic, Brother Yan Tu, you suffered great losses this time, you ended up in a pathetic state." Ju Kai Bei mocked while winking.

No outsider would imagine he could make such an expression. Normally, Ju Kai Bei was solemn as iron and was very meticulous. But in reality, this was only a mask he had worn when he was walking the demonic path.

Only in front of Yan Tu, his best friend, did he display his true nature.

Yan Tu coldly snorted, he sighed as his brows relaxed: "This Bai Ning Bing is not simple, one day she will surpass us. I only won by a small margin, if she was rank four, the battle could go either way."

Ju Kai Bei nodded: "I disguised myself to watch your match. It is indeed the rise of a younger generation."

Yan Tu patted Ju Kai Bei's shoulder: "That Fang Zheng is as famous as Bai Ning Bing. They came to Shang clan city together and also lives together, their relation is definitely not normal. They are called the twin stars of the battle stage and some people even call them the black and white demons. Bai Ning Bing already has such strength, Fang Zheng definitely won't be any weaker. Brother Ju, your strongest moment is also your weakest, you need to be careful."

Ju Kai Bei proudly smiled: "Brother, guess what this is."

He took out a Gu from his aperture.

This Gu was like a beetle, it was black as iron and was fist sized.

"Eh, hard qi Gu!" Yan Tu was astonished before joy filled his face, "This is great, Brother Ju. Your defense falls when you use your killer move. This Gu will make up for your weakness. This Gu is precious and rare, you need to raise it carefully."

Ju Kai Bei nodded and put back the hard qi Gu, he then let out a sigh: "It is such a pity that it is only a hard qi Gu and not strength qi Gu. If it was strength qi Gu, my battle strength would undergo a qualitative transformation and surge by two or three times..."

Yan Tu laughed loudly: "This is just your greed, like a snake trying to swallow an elephant! The ancient qi path has already disappeared, strength qi Gu is extinct. It is your great luck that you could obtain a hard qi Gu, don't be greedy."

Ju Kai Bei also laughed: "Yeah, but endless greed is also human nature, hahaha..."

Ancient qi path had appeared earlier than strength path.

Qi path Gu worms could alternate between form and formless, their ability were extremely wondrous. In ancient times, when qi path flourished, eight out of ten Gu Masters would walk the qi path.

However, flowers bloom and wilt, powers rise and fall; this is the natural law and qi path was not exempted from it.

After its peak, qi path gradually declined and was replaced by strength path.

Bai Ning Bing's vitality Gu, Ju Kai Bei's hard qi Gu and Fang Yuan's atmosphere Gu were all related to qi path.

Chapter 316: Absolute Victory, Demonic Heart

Seven days passed, and the battle stage held the largest battle seen in a long time.

Ju Kai Bei forcefully challenged Fang Yuan, the former was an experienced senior expert, his fame deeply entrenched in the city. The latter was a rising star in the last two years, shining like the night sky, a young expert of the newer generation.

Other than the excitement of this battle, right before this, Bai Ning Bing and Yan Tu had a battle, it perfectly led up to this climax.

After seven days of circulation, the entire Shang clan city was hyping over this match.

Thus, at the battle stage today, it was packed with people.

The battle stage had also purposely promoted this battle, making it turn into a grand event. The person in charge of the battle stage Shang Chi Wen gained a huge boost to her business revenue and was extremely happy the last few days.

Before the battle started, people already started chatting among themselves.

"Will the more experienced expert Ju Kai Bei win, or will Fang Zheng overcome the odds?" Some people were discussing this, the fight between a veteran and rising star was a popular topic to explore.

"The two of them are strength path Gu Masters, this is the resurrection battle of the strength path!" Many strength path Gu Masters were proud, having strong anticipation towards this battle. In their eyes, this had great meaning for them.

"No matter what, Fang Zheng has to fight with all his strength. Otherwise, his all-out effort Gu will be taken by Ju Kai Bei."

"Fang Zheng is only rank three middle stage, although he is very adept at fighting, his cultivation is even lower than Bai Ning Bing, not to mention in contrast to Ju Kai Bei." After tens of battles, Fang Yuan's strength could not be concealed anymore, most people did not think he could win, because the difference in cultivation was too great.

"Fang Zheng is here!" Someone shouted.

Fang Yuan walked slowly, entering the battle stage with a peaceful look.

This was a super-size battle stage, black stone forest terrain.

Fang Zheng stood at the center of the stage, folding his arms and taking a look at his surroundings.

The black stone pillars, thick and tough, were placed all over the forest terrain.

Outside, people were crowding and completely surrounded the stage. This was the most people Fang Yuan had seen at one battle in his two years of battling.

Fang Yuan knew clearly, Shang Xin Ci and Wei Yang were among the crowd, even Bai Ning Bing was here, but disguised. He even heard Shang Xin Ci say that some Shang clan young masters were here.

This reminded him of his first battle.

Back then, there was barely any spectators, Fang Yuan was still a nobody.

But now, he was already famous, had become someone who gathered attention.

"This is the final battle." Fang Yuan sighed in his heart.

Three kings inheritance was starting, considering the time taken to travel, there was no time left.

After winning this, he still had to assist Shang Xin Ci and make her a young master. It was crucial for his future plans.

The day Shang Xin Ci becomes a young master would be the day Fang Yuan leaves Shang clan city.

Regarding Ju Kai Bei and Yan Tu's secret identity, others did not know it but Fang Yuan knew clearly.

As long as one dominates the battle stage, they will become Shang clan external elder.

Fang Yuan had never thought of dominating the battle stage. The identity of Shang clan external elder, it might be the dream of many people.

The sparrow makes a nest in the house, only an eagle can build their nest beside a cliff.

Not just the external clan elder of Shang clan, Fang Yuan does not have any interest even in the Shang clan leader position.

All these roles, although glorious, were chains of fame and wealth.

Pitiful.

Among those that live in the mortal realm, who knows how many people these chains have binded.

Ju Kai Bei arrived on the stage too.

A tower-like body, a steel like expression. He had a large body frame and even denser muscles, it gave people a strong oppressing feeling.

In Fang Yuan's previous life's memories, at the great righteous demonic battle of Yi Tian mountain, Ju Kai Bei had a great performance too. He killed many established demonic Gu Masters, and was one of the capable generals of Shang Yan Fei.

In him, the aura of rank four flowed. Before the battle even began, he already exerted mental pressure on Fang Yuan.

In terms of cultivation, Fang Yuan was at a disadvantage. He was rank three peak stage, but used the breath concealment Gu, thus on the surface, he was rank three middle stage.

But even if he has lower cultivation, so what?

Hehehe.

Fang Yuan squinted, his eyes glowing with brilliance. A few days ago, he had successfully refined that Gu, and his chances of winning rose to sixty percent. Even though his opponent was strong, Fang Yuan was confident of winning.

This was not overconfidence nor pride, and certainly not arrogance, but an attitude.

Demonic heart!

Cannot lose, cannot fall, must win, must win at all cost!

Even with less than ten percent chance of winning, even without any chance of winning, he had to have an attitude of absolute victory.

For a demonic Gu Master, once they fail, it leads to disaster. Thus, he has to succeed, winning every time, there is no 'if', there is no 'what if'.

His five hundred years of experience allowed Fang Yuan to develop such a mindset.

Winner takes all, stepping on others' corpses and climb higher, rising to the apex! Only I can let the world down, whatever justice and integrity, fame, fortune and beauty, hatred and kindness, they will not be an obstacle but merely tools to use.

This was where Fang Yuan differed from Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing had a heart to pursue victory, but Fang Yuan had a heart of absolute victory!

Nothing can stop me, not even demise will subdue my demonic heart.

Ju Kai Bei walked towards Fang Yuan, standing still and maintaining silent.

He did not like to talk.

Similarly, Fang Yuan hated trash talking.

The two look at each other, ignoring the outside noises, one with a firm iron gaze, while the other had dark abyss-like pupils.

Ding!

As the bell rang, the battle began.

All-out effort Gu!

In an instant, light burst from Fang Yuan's eyes, and he injected his primeval essence, causing a horse phantom to appear behind him.

The horse raised its head as it charged.

With the strength of a horse in him, Fang Yuan activated the vertical crash Gu.

Swoosh!

He charged towards Ju Kai Bei, his speed as fast as a galloping horse!

But when he got to Ju Kai Bei, the horse phantom vanished, and turned into a boar phantom.

The boar had scarlet red eyes, as its tusks stabbed forwards, giving off a fierce aura.

Horse strength made charging faster, while boar strength made the impact of hitting stronger, Fang Yuan was already able to swap his beast phantoms at will now.

Seeing Fang Yuan coming at him, Ju Kai Bei opened his mouth emotionlessly.

His mouth was full of clean white teeth, at this moment, two fangs grew quickly, coming out of his mouth as two elephant tusks appeared.

The tusks bent inwards, its sharp and curved tip stabbing into Ju Kai Bei's chest.

But there was no blood at his wound, instead, a pure white armor formed at the area of contact.

Like a milky layer of ice, the armor quickly formed on his upper body.

Fang Yuan came over imposingly.

"Good timing." Ju Kai Bei did not dodge but instead took a step forward, bending his waist a little and taking Fang Yuan's charge head-on.

Bam.

A loud crashing sound, and the two's shoulders collided.

Fang Yuan took five steps back, while Ju Kai Bei was sent flying.

This caused many to scream out in shock.

"How can this be? Ju Kai Bei is not Fang Zheng's match?"

"The all-out effort Gu is really too powerful."

"Weird, why does Fang Zheng have rank three peak stage cultivation?!"

Once Fang Yuan attacked, the breath concealment Gu's effect was overwritten, and his rank three peak stage aura was exposed, as many people noticed quickly.

Ju Kai Bei showed a little surprise in his eyes, but it quickly vanished.

He got up from the ground, not having taken much damage. Only his shoulder armor was cracked and broken.

But quickly, these cracks vanished.

The armor continued to extend, after a while, his arm and waist was covered.

This was the ivory armor Gu's effect that Ju Kai Bei had been using.

Ivory armor Gu, a rank four Gu with strong defense. But the weakness was, it needed some time to grow, and had no malleability. After the battle ends, the Gu Master has to break it themself.

Fang Yuan moved his shoulder, feeling a little ache.

Earlier, he did not use the golden shield Gu, just the combination of bronze skin, iron bones and steel tendons, made his defense extraordinary.

Strength affects both oneself and foe, there were great requirements in terms of defense for a strength Gu Master.

The attack earlier was just a small test.

"This Ju Kai Bei has great physical strength, since my rebirth, he is the strongest opponent I've faced. He is an enemy with great physical strength and defense." Fang Yuan's gaze was dark and eerie as he pounced again.

Bam bam bam.

The two exchanged blows, landing their punches every time, as Ju Kai Bei was at a disadvantage.

Fang Yuan naturally did not give him any opportunity to continue growing, as the ivory armor broke many times from Fang Yuan's iron fist, unable to reach its complete form.

But Ju Kai Bei's strength was getting stronger, he was suppressed initially, but started being tied with Fang Yuan.

That was not surprising, Fang Yuan knew from Ju Kai Bei's information that he had a rank four habitual strength Gu.

The all-out effort Gu was extinct long ago, thus to replace it, current strength path Gu Masters created the habitual strength Gu.

The lower rank of the habitual strength Gu is the rank three store strength Gu.

The store strength Gu can store energy, and release it slowly attack after attack. But it needed time to do so, and during that period, the Gu Master cannot move at all, thus it is not commonly used.

But at rank four, after the store strength Gu refines into the habitual strength Gu, this weakness is eliminated.

The habitual strength Gu after activation, would cause Ju Kai Bei's strength to accumulate over time. At the same time, he is allowed to move freely.

Bam!

Fang Yuan's fists landed on Ju Kai Bei's chest, while Ju Kai Bei's palm chopped on Fang Yuan's shoulder.

Both of them took six steps back, this time it was a draw.

But Fang Yuan's fist was numb. In contrast, Ju Kai Bei's chest was covered by the ivory armor, and there was only some cracks on it.

As time passed, Ju Kai Bei continued to move about, and the ivory armor became thicker, causing Ju Kai Bei's skin to become monstrously thick.

Ju Kai Bei's strength was starting to show.

Not only does he have rank four yellow gold primeval essence, he also had rank four Gu worms.

Just the ivory armor could compete with Fang Yuan's steel tendons, iron bones, and bronze skin combination.

Chapter 317: Fang Yuan vs Ju Kai Bei (1)

Hook, palm strike, elbow jab, kick...

Fang Yuan and Ju Kai Bei fought head-on, exchanging moves after moves.

Punches and kicks collided, producing intense tremors.

The two moved while striking each other, any stone or tree they struck would collapse with a loud sound.

"Fang Zheng is falling into a disadvantage." Gradually, the spectators understood the situation.

"To deal with Ju Kai Bei, one needs to take him down as soon as possible and not give him any time." Someone sighed.

Ju Kai Bei had habitual strength Gu; his strength grew the longer it stayed active.

"Easy for you to say, who can knock him down at the start? He has rank four cultivation, the ivory armor Gu and plentiful battle experience. Being able to fight him to this extent, Fang Zheng could be said to be pretty good."

Bai Ning Bing watched the match quietly from within the crowd.

She had experienced the pressure Fang Yuan was on right now. Only those who had personally fought against rank four Gu Masters would know the huge gap between rank three and rank four.

"Brother Hei Tu..." Shang Xin Ci clenched her fists tightly, her beautiful eyes followed Fang Yuan.

Wei Yang's brows gradually furrowed.

Howl!

Suddenly, the roar of a wild beast burst out.

A dragon-elephant phantom suddenly rose up behind Ju Kai Bei; showing a tremendous might.

Dragon-elephant refers to a huge elephant who possesses dragon's blood. Its physique was larger than a mammoth, it was a humongous beast. If lions and tigers came across it, they would detour around it and not dare to attack.

There was a great possibility of obtaining dragon-elephant huge strength Gu by killing this type of ferocious beast.

Dragon-elephant huge strength Gu was a rank four Gu; while the galloping horse strength Gu, green bull labor Gu and other Gu used by Fang Yuan were only rank three.

Since Ju Kai Bei became rank four Gu Master, he had used three dragon-elephant huge strength Gu and created three beast phantoms for himself.

Right now, he was punching with the strength of a dragon-elephant!

Fang Yuan's pupils rapidly shrunk. At this moment of crisis, he quickly put up his two arms.

All-out effort Gu — Stone turtle strength!

A huge turtle phantom appeared behind him.

BOOM!

Ju Kai Bei's bowl-size fist ruthlessly struck Fang Yuan's arms.

A huge force emerged from the collision; Ju Kai Bei only took a step back while Fang Yuan was sent flying.

Stone turtle phantom collapsed with a loud bang; while dragon-elephant phantom flew higher into the sky.

Stone turtle strength was clearly not dragon-elephant strength's match.

Fang Yuan was sent flying for almost thirty steps and crashed through two stone pillars before finally stopping.

Fang Yuan got back to his stance again and shook his aching and numb arms. He might look pitiful but was not the least bit harmed. The combination of iron bone, steel tendons and bronze skin gave him a very strong defense.

"Ju Kai Bei punched with the strength of a dragon-elephant!" Outside the stage, many spectators cried out in surprise.

"He has been using habitual strength Gu since the start and now his strength has become exceedingly high. This is still only the strength of a dragon-elephant, senior Ju Kai Bei has a total of three dragon-elephant phantoms in him. I once saw him strike with the strength of three dragon-elephants, he instantly crushed his opponent's skull!"

"Fang Zheng can't hold back Ju Kai Bei. Ju Kai Bei striking with dragon-elephant strength is a prelude to his dominance of this match."

Fang Yuan was expressionless as he charged towards Ju Kai Bei once again.

The two exchanged moves again.

Snow silver primeval essence continually poured into all-out effort Gu.

Boar, brown bear, crocodile, green bull, horse, stone turtle, white elephant and black python; eight beast phantoms flashed by one after another.

After the stone turtle strength Gu, Fang Yuan had used white elephant primeval strength Gu and black python coiling strength Gu to gain white elephant phantom and black python phantom.

Eight beast phantoms were Fang Yuan's body's limit. Thus after using black python coiling strength Gu, he no longer used other strength Gu.

On the stage, Fang Yuan unleashed a flurry of attacks, his punches broke through the wind and were extremely violent.

Such terrifying offensive power birthed fear in the spectators.

Ju Kai Bei had just burst out the strength of a dragon-phantom and his strength was now back to before, habitual strength Gu started to accumulate power once again. Seizing the opportunity, Fang Yuan started going all out, immediately taking back the initiative.

His eight beast phantoms flashed continuously in the air, while the dragon-elephant phantoms appeared only occasionally.

However, every time dragon-elephant phantom appeared, it would send Fang Yuan flying.

As time passed, Fang Yuan's injuries accumulated; bronze skin could not resist Ju Kai Bei's enormous strength and was lacerated.

Ju Kai Bei's whole body was covered with a layer of ivory armor, so although there were many scars and cracks on it, he stood straight from the start, like an iron tower standing tall on the earth.

After some time.

There was a chance!

Ju Kai Bei made a very tiny mistake which might only appear once in a blue moon.

Fang Yuan grabbed this transient opportunity and suddenly moved to Ju Kai Bei's back and smacked.

Brown bear phantom.

If this enormous and heavy force struck, Ju Kai Bei would definitely be spurt out large amounts of blood.

Ju Kai Bei had no time to stop it so he could turn around and sweep his arms.

Howl!

Suddenly, there was the trumpet of an elephant; dragon-elephant phantom appeared and completely suppressed the brown bear phantom.

Fang Yuan was instead sent flying. This was the eighth time.

The frequency of dragon-elephant phantom's appearance became more frequent. When it did not appear, Fang Yuan held a slight initiative. But once it appeared, none of Fang Yuan's phantoms were its match.

Fang Yuan's beast phantoms were all ordinary wild beasts, but dragon-elephant had a trace of dragon bloodline in it and was considered a mutated beast!

After one hour since the match started....

Howl! Howl!

Two dragon-elephant phantoms appeared at the same time behind Ju Kai Bei.

His two fists ruthless struck Fang Yuan's chest and sent the latter flying far away.

Fang Yuan spurted out a mouthful of blood in the air and his vision shook.

Thump thump thump thump thump...

He smashed through five stone pillars before falling down on the ground; dust rose and covered his figure.

"So miserable!" Many Gu Masters' eyes twitched at this scene. Fang Yuan's current state was too appaling.

"Rank three beast phantom are not the rank four dragon-elephant phantom's match."

"Fang Zheng might have all-out effort Gu, but he can only use one beast phantom at a time. On the contrary, Ju Kai Bei's habitual strength Gu is much better."

"How could this be? All-out effort Gu is a legendary Gu but is actually inferior to the ordinary habitual strength Gu?" Someone shouted in surprise.

Soon, someone explained: "This is not the problem of all-out effort Gu, but rather the problem lies in Fang Zheng. Fang Zheng has the strength of eight beasts in him; they are like a huge water jar but the outlet is only a small bamboo pipe. All-out effort Gu can let this small bamboo pipe discharge water in top speed; while habitual strength Gu is like a bucket that needs to draw water from the water jar. All-out effort Gu allows the continuous flow of a thin stream, while habitual strength Gu accumulates before erupting."

"Brother Hei Tu..." Shang Xin Ci's heart jumped and she felt suffocated as she saw Fang Yuan's figure covered with dust.

However, soon, the spectators saw a black figure slowly standing up from within the smoke.

"Three ribs have fractured, and there seems to be internal bleeding. Such a powerful attack...."

Intense pain attacked Fang Yuan, but the corner of his lips instead rose into a smile.

He had a steel willpower, what was this little bit of pain? What was this little bit of injuries?

His battle intent rose with the pain like burning fire! His blood boiled like boiling water!

"This type of battle is the most satisfying! It is only interesting when defeating such a strong enemy! Hehehe... hahaha!" Fang Yuan stood from within the dust with his head high and started laughing without restraint.

"What is Fang Zheng saying? He seems to be laughing?"

"Was his brain damaged by Ju Kai Bei?"

Because of the barrier around the stage, the spectators could not hear clearly.

Ju Kai Bei, who had an indifferent look since the start of the battle, had a change in his expression for the first time after he heard Fang Yuan's crazed laughter!

"This kid..." His expression turned grim as he got a familiar as well as strange feeling from that laughter.

With a little bit of thinking, he immediately realized.

This was the aura of the demonic path!

A killing intent as sharp as a knife, a crazed will to destroy the world, an arrogance that looked down on the world, a ruthlessness that trampled on all living things...

This laughter seemed to have made Ju Kai Bei return to the past.

That painful and unbearable past.

He had to engage in slaughter almost every day as if walking alone in an endless darkness, with no one to talk to, an endless loneliness repressed into fear, the life of the demonic path that was worse than death...

You must keep going forward and you must keep on winning. It was like walking on a steel rope between cliffs, your nerves stretched to the limits and you had no moment to relax. With just one loss, you could fall into the abyss, consigned to eternal damnation.

Ju Kai Bei was fed up with such a life so he threw in his lot with Shang clan and became a hidden elder. These years, he felt like he was a person who had climbed ashore after struggling and almost drowning in the sea of bitterness.

He was already standing on the shore, but Fang Yuan's laughter was like a tide making him look back at the sea of bitterness.

This laughter evoked a trace of fear in Ju Kai Bei!

I cannot go back to my past...

I don't want to think about the past...

I have turned over a new leaf, I have already begun a new life, I am already a member of the righteous path!

Righteous could not coexist with demonic!

Ju Kai Bei's face shook to reveal a sinister expression, he felt an extreme hatred towards Fang Yuan from the depths of his heart.

Dragon travel tiger steps Gu!

Ju Kai Bei took the initiative to attack, he took large strides like a tiger or dragon and charged into the dust.

His every step was accompanied by the dragon's cry and tiger's roar.

This was the rank four dragon travel tiger steps Gu and it allowed Ju Kai Bei to move rapidly. It was also similar to charging crash Gu and used the charging and crashing force to bring out Ju Kai Bei's stored strength.

Ju Kai Bei charged fiercely into the dust, straight towards Fang Yuan.

Howl!

Dragon-elephant phantom appeared again.

It was only one phantom and not two phantoms.

However, this was enough to suppress Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan did not avoid it and took it head-on; stone turtle phantom soared behind him.

The two fiercely collided.

The collision created a fierce wind wave, blowing away the dust.

Ju Kai Bei had a flabbergasted look as he retreated five steps; while Fang Yuan did not budge even a bit.

There were only bewilderment outside the stage.

"What in the world is going on?" This scene was beyond almost everyone's expectations.

It was the same stone turtle strength against dragon-elephant strength, but why was the result completely different?

Ju Kai Bei gritted his teeth as he pounced forward again.

Bang!

A loud sound. He was sent flying by Fang Yuan like a sandbag before crashing onto the ground.

He got up with difficulty and stared deadly at the space above Fang Yuan.

In the air, brown bear phantom and boar phantom slowly disappeared.

"Using two beast phantom at once!"

"How is this possible?"

"This goes against common sense!"

There were cries of surprise and alarm from the spectators.

Chapter 318: Fang Yuan vs Ju Kai Bei (2)

"Two beast phantoms... my eyes did not deceive me, right?" Yan Tu's eyes were wide open.

"What Gu is he using to bring out two beast phantoms at the same time?" Ju Kai Bei's expression turned grave as he looked fixed at Fang Yuan. His pupils suddenly shrunk: "Come!"

Vertical crash Gu!

Fang Yuan's expression was emotionless and his eyes as dyed in a deep miasma. He charged towards Ju Kai Bei.

At the same time, a horse and boar phantom appeared above his head.

Boar strength increased the force of his charge while horse strength increased his speed instantaneously, making his charging speed even quicker.

With the empowerment of two strengths, Fang Yuan seemed to have turned into a fierce boar charging with the speed of a raging horse; his figure quickly enlarged in Ju Kai Bei's eyes.

Dragon travel tiger steps Gu!

Facing Fang Yuan's powerful attack, Ju Kai Bei jumped along with the cry of a dragon and the roar of a tiger.

This time, he dodged of his own accord and brushed past Fang Yuan.

Vertical crash Gu's weakness was exposed, it could only charge in a straight line; the opponent could easily determine the direction and dodge, causing the attack to fail.

"Ju Kai Bei has taken the initiative to dodge!"

"He had always been attacking head-on and rarely dodged. Since the battle started, this is the first time he has dodged without tanking the hit."

"Fang Zheng is able to bring out two beast phantoms at the same time while Ju Kai Bei's habitual strength Gu has to accumulate strength again, dodging is a sensible move."

"Fang Zheng is still too inexperienced, although he has high quality Gu worms, his battle experience is far inferior to Ju Kai Bei. This attack was a wasted attempt... ugh."

This spectator were still commenting when there was a sudden change in the stage.

After Fang Yuan brushed past Ju Kai Bei, he suddenly stopped using all-out effort Gu. The two beast phantoms disappeared, his charging force immediately diminished as he smashed into a black stone pillar.

As the black stone pillar collapsed, Fang Yuan's momentum stopped.

Horizontal charge Gu!

Fang Yuan turned his body and charged horizontally, his two arms attacking straight. Two large phantoms of brown bear and white elephant suddenly rose up.

The distance was too close and Ju Kai Bei was caught unprepared; the attack hit him violently and sent his tall body flying!

The person who had just evaluated Fang Yuan as 'too inexperienced' was tongue-tied.

Many spectators' eyes brightened.

Fang Yuan's attack seemed ordinary, but it involved many factors and was an exceptionally brilliant move.

All-out effort Gu could unleash formidable offensive power when activated, it could also be revoked.

The constant switch between activation and revoking let Fang Yuan move smoothly with great flexibility.

At the same time, he used the terrain to stop his momentum.

Ju Kai Bei was struck by Fang Yuan, not because he was not intelligent but because he was used to habitual strength Gu and his plentiful experiences instead created a blind spot in his thoughts.

Fang Yuan charged again!

Ju Kai Bei rose to resist, but Fang Yuan's two beast phantoms burst out like a crazed lion, the ferocious roar even caused the spectators' hearts to palpitate.

Ju Kai Bei became a sandbag, left with no way to retaliate, he held his breath as he defended desperately.

"Heavens, Fang Zheng is merely rank three peak stage but is actually suppressing Ju Kai Bei!"

"Such an unimaginable scene is actually happening in front of my eyes."

"All-out effort Gu is after all a legendary Gu, it is powerful and has marvelous uses, even rank four habitual strength Gu cannot compare to it!

"Fang Zheng has already perfected the use of all-out effort Gu. He might not have plentiful experience, but his innate battle talent is enough to make up for everything else."

The spectators were clamoring.

Bam!

Dust rose up, Ju Kai Bei's tower-like body was like a sack as he smashed through several thick black stone pillars.

Cough!

He again spurted out a mouthful of blood. He struggled to get up but Fang Yuan was already upon him and did not give him any chance to take a breather.

He stomped on the ground; horse and green bull beast phantoms appeared at the same time.

Ju Kai Bei rolled on the ground, dodging the attack in a sorry state.

Fang Yuan's right leg stamped on the ground fiercely; a dull sound echoed, soil and stones split and flew, the whole battle stage seemed to be slightly shaking.

A clear concaved depression appeared immediately below his legs.

Vertical crash Gu!

Fang Yuan charged, brown bear and white elephant phantoms simultaneously appeared.

"Damn it!" This time, Ju Kai Bei did not have enough time to dodge, he could only grit his teeth and raise his huge arms to resist.

Howl! Howl!

Behind him, two dragon-elephant phantoms suddenly appeared and rose to the air; Fang Yuan's brown bear and white elephant phantoms immediately paled in comparison.

Fang Yuan strongly collided into Ju Kai Bei; Ju Kai Bei was only pushed back a little, while Fang Yuan himself was sent flying away.

Two beast phantoms could suppress one dragon-elephant strength. However, Fang Yuan would lose against two dragon-elephant strength.

"Finally, two dragon-elephant strength came out..." Ju Kai Bei let out a breath of turbid air, he was shocked by Fang Yuan's violent strength. Only when two dragon-elephant strength burst out, did he reclaim his footing.

Habitual strength Gu might be rank four but it was indeed inferior to all-out effort Gu.

Ju Kai Bei had to continuously accumulate and increase his strength by activating habitual strength Gu, then summon the beast phantom. However, even he did not know when it would appear. If he attacked, and one dragon-elephant strength appeared, he would have to accumulate strength all over again which caused his battle strength to temporarily fall.

Ju Kai Bei's strength was like a water jar and his habitual strength Gu was like a bucket, he needed to draw the water from it every time.

In contrast, all-out effort Gu was a stream and could be used anytime, able to be unleashed whenever Fang Yuan willed. In fact, if Fang Yuan did not want to use it, he could even turn it off. With such a flexible use, Fang Yuan could advance or retreat, he could use to attack or move away quickly.

"If I was the one with all-out effort Gu... sigh! Unfortunately, even if I win, Shang Yan Fei would not allow me to claim it." Ju Kai Bei felt regret.

He had complete freedom when he was a demonic Gu Master and could do whatever he wanted. By submitting to the righteous path, he gained safety and stability, had enough resources, but he felt his hands and legs bound when doing things.

"If I choose the all-out effort Gu disregarding his orders, what would happen?"

This thought was immediately dispelled the moment it appeared.

If he really did that, it was no doubt offending Shang Yan Fei. Shang Yan Fei was not only a rank five expert, he also controlled Shang clan. If Ju Kai Bei disobeyed him, even if he escaped, his future would never be peaceful.

"Wait a moment! What am I thinking about, the crucial thing now is to defeat Fang Zheng!" Ju Kai Bei's gaze concentrated, activating dragon travel tiger steps Gu and attacking Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan spurted a mouthful of blood from the attack, his iron-like arm bones were fractured.

The intense pain struck him, but Fang Yuan instead grinned and laughed.

All-out effort Gu!

Brown bear, white elephant and green bull; three phantoms burst out together!

Even Ju Kai Bei could not help but stare with wide eyes, revealing a stupefied expression.

What had just happened to Fang Yuan, happened to himself immediately after.

Ju Kai Bei had thought of taking the chance to attack quickly and had taken the initiative to attack, but he was instead sent flying. There was a huge hole in the thick and solid ivory armor on his chest. He spurted out a huge amount of blood and smashed through the black stone pillars before collapsing on the ground, as a dust cloud appeared. Ju Kai Bei clenched his teeth as he hurriedly got up.

"Three beast phantoms!" The spectators were stupefied.

The scene was extremely clear. Fang Yuan struck with three beast phantoms!

"How did he do it?" Many spectators looked at each other.

"He had just attacked with two beast phantoms, but now there's three..." Many were speechless.

But even more people already had guesses: "Could it be..."

Ju Kai Bei stared at Fang Yuan fixedly as he squeezed out a name from his teeth: "Bitter strength Gu!"

That's right, it was bitter strength Gu.

Bitter strength Gu was a rank four Gu and was the perfect companion for strength path Gu Masters; the more injuries the Gu Master suffered, the greater the pain he felt, the more strength they could bring out.

Naturally, there was a limit to the strength the Gu Master could display and it depended on the Gu Master's foundation.

Fang Yuan possessed eight beast strength phantoms, the strength he contained was like a large water vat. All-out effort Gu was like a bamboo pipe that could be opened and closed at will and could continually draw water from the vat.

Right now, as Fang Yuan suffered injuries and used bitter strength Gu, it was as if many holes appeared on the water vat. All-out effort Gu added in bamboo pipes to all these holes and allowed Fang Yuan to use them as he wished.

Just with all-out effort Gu, Fang Yuan only had a single bamboo pipe to draw the water and thus could only use one beast phantom. But now, under the effects of his injuries and the bitter strength Gu, it was like adding two new outlets to the water vat.

Thus, when Fang Yuan used all-out effort Gu now, he could simultaneously use three beast phantoms.

"To think he has a bitter strength Gu! Didn't Shang Ya Zi buy this Gu in the auction? Is this bitter strength Gu the one Shang Ya Zi owned?" Yan Tu guessed the answer.

His eyes narrowed and his expression was unprecedentedly solemn.

"If the bitter strength in Fang Zheng's hand is not Shang Ya Zi's, then he no doubt toyed with Shang Ya Zi in the auction. But if this bitter strength Gu was the one Shang Ya Zi bought, then the situation is terrifying! Shang Ya Zi had been ousted from his young master position not long ago because of false accounting with Fang Zheng. Maybe this bitter strength Gu is the fruit of Fang Zheng's victory! This kid is not simple. Brother Ju, you have to be careful..."

Yan Tu could not help but worry about Ju Kai Bei's situation.

Ju Kai Bei only felt bitterness in his mouth.

First, the all-out effort Gu, now the bitter strength Gu... these two Gu were both what he, Ju Kai Bei, yearned for everyday and had bitterly searched for them fruitlessly.

However, Fang Yuan who was so young was holding both Gu, such luck caused this senior to become green with envy.

With bitter strength Gu, the heavier the injuries Fang Yuan suffered, the more holes there would be on his water vat and he would also become stronger.

In another words, every time Ju Kai Bei inflicted damage, he would instead be increasing Fang Yuan's battle strength.

It was an unpleasant feeling. His mental endurance also took a hit, not wanting to fight with Fang Yuan anymore. The more Fang Yuan fought, the stronger he got; the heavier the injuries he suffered, the higher his strength. The most important thing was he possessed eight beast phantoms, if they all burst out together, even if Ju Kai Bei's three dragon-elephant appeared together, it would be useless.

What lowered Ju Kai Bei's morale even more was that he knew Fang Yuan possessed a self-reliance Gu.

Self-reliance Gu's healing effects was extremely potent towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was being healed while suffering injuries, maintaining his strength at a terrifying level.

All-out effort Gu, bitter strength Gu and self-reliance Gu; these three formed a tight combination, creating a secure and solid foundation.

Reaching this step, the Gu set that Fang Yuan planned earlier had already reached initial success, forming the skeleton. Their effects were outstanding and even the rank four Ju Kai Bei was suffering from this combination.

Fang Yuan had been in Shang clan city for over two years now, already accomplishing something most Gu Masters would not be able to accumulate even after spending most of their lives. Even a veteran like Ju Kai Bei was jealous and green-eyed.

Chapter 319: Fang Yuan vs Ju Kai Bei (3)

"Even if Fang Zheng has bitter strength Gu, the strength he can release is at most eight beast phantoms. Bitter strength Gu cannot raise his strength limitlessly."

"Shang clan leader ordered me to not take all-out effort Gu, I can only choose this bitter strength Gu!" Ju Kai Bei's eyes brightened as he thought of this.

Whether it was all-out effort Gu or bitter strength Gu, they were both extremely attractive to strength path Gu Masters.

"I still haven't lost! I am at rank four initial stage, I am superior in terms of primeval essence, and I also have my killer move."

Ju Kai Bei possessed plentiful experience and was able to put his disorganized mind in order after pondering for a short period. He was invigorated and his low morale rose up.

The two began exchanging moves again.

The battle could not longer be described as intense; desperate was more suitable.

The two punched and kicked one after another, attacking and defending.

Ju Kai Bei's ivory armor was being broken continuously and while repairing itself. From time to time, he would spurt out mouthfuls of blood.

Fang Yuan was also not much better, he was restraining self-reliance Gu which caused his whole body to be full of injuries and blood seeped out continuously, his bones fractured and endless pain continued to assault his mind like tides.

The heavier the injuries he suffered, the stronger he got. Not long later, he could bring out five beast phantoms.

Ju Kai Bei fell into a much more dangerous situation and was almost suppressed to the state where he could not even lift his head.

This was something he had never experienced at the battle stage.

Even Yan Tu was only his equal.

"Junior, you are too arrogant!" Ju Kai Bei furiously swept his arms.

Three dragon-elephants!

He suddenly erupted, as the enormous dragon-elephant phantom appeared behind him.

Fang Yuan was sent flying.

Three dragon-elephants could suppress five beast phantoms.

Fang Yuan's arms were twisted due to the attack, they were completely fractured. His left arm was even folded into a right angle and the fractured bones were exposed with fresh blood flowing down.

Fang Yuan clenched his teeth and endured the pain as he activated self-reliance Gu.

Such injuries already affected his combat capability and he had to heal it.

He first healed his right arm before twisting his left arm back to its proper state, forcefully joining the broken parts as he activated the self-reliance Gu.

The broken bones began to grow again and join together. Then it was the pieces of flesh and finally the skin.

During the healing process, Fang Yuan constantly evaded Ju Kai Bei's attacks using horizontal charge Gu and vertical crash Gu, contending with Ju Kai Bei by doing three tasks at once.

When he attacked, he attacked fiercely with a domineering might. But when he dodged, it was a completely different style; he was calm and not flustered in the face of danger, like a slippery loach.

He used the black stone forest terrain to his maximum advantage, so although Ju Kai Bei's dragon travel tiger steps Gu was faster than Fang Yuan, he could not catch Fang Yuan.

After the healing was finished, Fang Yuan turned around and started attacking again.

Time passed by, the battle situation became more desperate. Fang Yuan's phantoms gradually rose from five to six then seven until there were eight phantoms!

At the start of the battle, there were spectators who commented and shouted from time to time, but as the match progressed, the audience had gotten silent.

Fang Yuan and Ju Kai Bei's terrifying strength caused their hearts to feel cold and astonished.

"Too terrifying!"

"Such power, one can only imagine how flourishing the ancient strength path must have been."

"If it was me, I would have already turned into meat paste no matter which one I fought among them."

...

The spectators were speechless but even more secretly felt admiration towards the unyielding spirit of Fang Yuan and Ju Kai Bei. These two were true warriors of steel.

No one had predicted such a result.

Fang Yuan was strong and after he brought out eight phantoms, he was suppressing Ju Kai Bei most of the time.

However, Ju Kai Bei was not weak, his healing Gu was also quite outstanding. The combination of dragon guts Gu, dragon travel tiger steps Gu, and dragon-elephant Gu formed a resonance of Dao marks due to their similar law fragments; this greatly raised the probability of bringing out his dragon-elephant phantom.

Sweat formed in Shang Xin Ci's clenched hands.

Wei Yang's frown became deeper and was turning into a knot.

He could see Fang Yuan was getting exhausted.

Even Fang Yuan's iron body could not endure unleashing the strength of eight beast phantoms; sweat fell down his body like rain and his muscles were already aching and turning numb.

There was another even greater danger.

Being able to simultaneously summon eight phantoms signified his injuries were extremely severe and he was in danger.

Fang Yuan was walking on a steel wire, if he was struck by Ju Kai Bei's three dragon-elephant phantoms, he might die from the attack!

He was risking his life in battle!

This was a battle of extremes.

From start till now, it had already been over two hours.

The match gradually reached the climax, the two had reached their limits; their attacks were clearly starting to slow down.

However, the match was instead becoming more thrilling and even Bai Ning Bing's expression was solemn.

The whole scene was silent, all the spectators were concentrating on the match.

Ju Kai Bei finally lost his patience.

He might be able to strike with three dragon-elephant strength, but it all depended on luck and there was no assurance.

Sometimes, the phantoms came out at the wrong timing and Fang Yuan would easily dodge or resist it.

"Why has his primeval essence not been exhausted?"

Even the rank four strength path Gu Master Ju Kai Bei did not have much primeval essence left at this stage.

However, Fang Yuan, a rank three Gu Master, actually appeared to have abundant primeval essence and was very energetic.

"Could it be, he really has a heavenly essence treasure lotus?" Ju Kai Bei could not help but recall that secret letter sent by Shang Yan Fei.

"If Fang Zheng really has it, his luck is simply too heaven defying!" Ju Kai Bei gritted his teeth, the expected superiority in primeval essence did not exist, causing his fighting spirit to dampen.

But the truth was, Fang Yuan not only had heavenly essence treasure lotus, but also blood skull Gu and four flavor liquor worm. If Ju Kai Bei knew this, his expression would definitely be spectacular.

"I can't lose! It seems I can only use my killer move!!" Ju Kai Bei made his decision.

Dragon travel tiger steps Gu!

He suddenly retreated and this unusual movement immediately attracted Fang Yuan's attention.

However, Fang Yuan could not catch him.

Dragon travel tiger steps was really fast, far surpassing horizontal charge Gu and vertical crash Gu. Even considering this terrain, it was disadvantageous to pursue him.

Almost instantly, all the spectators gazed at Ju Kai Bei, many realizing something.

"This is bad..." Wei Yang's expression suddenly changed at this scene and he could not help but cry out in surprise.

"What is it?" Shang Xin Ci immediately looked at him.

"Ju Kai Bei is about to use his killer move! This match has finally reached the climax." Wei Yang's voice was deep and sweat seeped out of his forehead.

He was extremely nervous as he explained hurriedly: "Ju Kai Bei's killer move has a flaw. If Fang Zheng can grasp this flaw, he could clinch victory! If not, I am afraid Ju Kai Bei will be the winner."

Wei Yang had just finished speaking, when there was a change in the stage.

Djinn heart Gu!

Djinn body Gu!

Djinn mind Gu!

Three rank four Gu were simultaneously activated.

Body, heart, and mind combined; essence, qi, and spirit merged!

Ju Kai Bei's physique suddenly enlarged by three times, a white aura appeared around his body as if signifying the descent of a deity. Along with it, his domineering presence increased greatly.

This was his killer move — Djinn transformation! It increased the Gu Master's strength by three times and even his mental energy was raised by three times.

Gu Master consumed their mental energy to control Gu worms. If they overused it, their mind would feel sluggishness.

But Ju Kai Bei's mental energy was raised now and he became energetic again.

At the same time, his strength was increased by three times; three dragon-elephant strength became nine dragon-elephant strength!

Once the nine dragon-elephant phantoms burst out, the eight beast phantoms would be crushed and Fang Yuan would certainly lose.

Ju Kai Bei reached his strongest state.

However, right at this moment, the ivory armor covering his whole body broke due to his size.

Many defensive Gu could not be stretched with the user and ivory armor was one of them.

"At this moment, he is completely defenseless. His strongest moment is also his weakest! Quick, grab this single opportunity for victory!" Wei Yang's eyes widened as he mumbled with clenched fists.

At another corner of the room, Bai Ning Bing's eyes also suddenly brightened.

As if he heard Wei Yang's suggestion, Fang Yuan adopted a posture of attacking, but suddenly his movement stopped.

The excited and happy look that had just appeared on Wei Yang's face froze.

"Strike!" He could not help but shout, his heart pulsed rapidly. Unfortunately, the barrier around the stage isolated sound; the spectators nearby casted strange glances at him.

Fang Yuan did not move but calmly observed.

The broken ivory armor was starting to grow, the new armor covered tightly around Ju Kai Bei's whole body.

Fang Yuan's chance at victory was slipping and becoming indistinct.

Wei Yang stomped his feet with anxiety but it was no use.

He raised his head and heaved a long sigh: "Sigh, Fang Zheng lost, he lost his only chance..."

Fang Yuan did not attack and that was quite a surprise to Ju Kai Bei. He had expected Fang Yuan to attack him, and had already made preparations for that, but Fang Yuan, however, made no such attempt.

It was a real pity!

Because, just earlier, he had activated hard qi Gu.

Hard qi Gu turned into a ball of formless air covering his whole body. At that moment, he looked like he had no defense, but in truth his defense was extremely tight and solid like a boulder.

He had covered up his greatest weakness with the hard qi Gu.

If Fang Yuan had attacked, he was certain to meet with Ju Kai Bei's frontal assault and was likely going to lose.

However, Fang Yuan did not move.

Ju Kai Bei had even slowed down the regeneration speed of the ivory armor to entice Fang Yuan, but he did not move and quietly watched like a spectator.

"Did he detect it? Impossible. Hard qi Gu is formless. I got it just recently and have never used it before."

"Hmph, since you are not attacking, then let me make the move." Bright rays exploded and flashed in Ju Kai Bei's eyes.

Djinn transformation was a killer move created from using three rank four Gu; whether it was his yellow gold primeval essence or mental energy, they were both decreasing rapidly.

Physical strength and mental energy were both increased by three times. But at the same time, the consumption was also increased by three times.

Ju Kai Bei's djinn transformation could not be maintained for long.

Dragon travel tiger steps!

Ju Kai Bei charged at Fang Yuan.

Horizontal charge, vertical crash!

Fang Yuan retreated and avoided the attack.

Ju Kai Bei was bewildered.

Fang Yuan changed his style and suddenly retreated, was it to stall for time?

Pointless!

"My body is three times larger now and every step I take is three times as far. With dragon travel tiger steps Gu, my speed is even faster!" Ju Kai Bei scoffed inwardly.

It was pointless even if Fang Yuan used the black stone forest terrain.

By now, almost all the black stone pillars were destroyed. Moreover, djinn transformation could completely crush everything in its path; to the current Ju Kai Bei, the terrain was as flat as a pancake!

Chapter 320: Tear through the sky

Seeing that Fang Yuan about to be caught, Shang Xin Ci's heart tightened.

Fang Yuan had severe injuries on him, if he was hit by Ju Kai Bei's nine dragon-elephant strength, it meant death! Right now, Ju Kai Bei was the oppressing one, if Fang Yuan was caught up in close combat, his situation would be dire.

But unfortunately, Fang Yuan's movement speed was inferior to Ju Kai Bei. The only way out was if he had a strong long range attack to restrict Ju Kai Bei.

"Fang Zheng, you lost." Ju Kai Bei took big strides and approached, he knew Fang Yuan had a blood moon Gu, but such a weak attack could not stop him.

An ordinary long range attack could not stop him at all. Even in the entire battle stage, only Yan Tu's Fire Sea Twin Dragon Kill could stop the assault of his Djinn Transformation.

"Fang Zheng is about to lose!"

"In the end, Ju Kai Bei is the victor of this battle."

"Experience is still the deciding factor..."

The people discussed outside the stage, the situation was extremely clear now.

"Sigh..." Wei Yang sighed deeply.

Shang Xin Ci shut her eyes in pain.

Even Bai Ning Bing's gaze dimmed.

"Hehehe." Yan Tu laughed lightly, once Fang Yuan lost, Shang Yan Fei's mission would be completed!

Unless, Fang Yuan had a strong long range attack that could stop Ju Kai Bei's advancement.

But...

Strength path Gu Masters are mostly close range fighters, they had little to no long range methods, it was mostly situational techniques. This was a common weakness of strength path Gu Masters these days, a weakness easily exploited.

Yan Tu and Ju Kai Bei had many intense battles, a portion of their battles relied on Yan Tu using long range attacks to restrict Ju Kai Bei, then winning by an extremely small margin.

All other situations where Yan Tu failed to restrict Ju Kai Bei resulted in a loss after he got close.

Close range, long range, it was the crux of battling a strength path Gu Master, in fact, it was the deciding factor in a battle!

"It's over." Ju Kai Bei was already extremely close to Fang Yuan, as many people sighed.

But at this moment, Fang Yuan's lips curled into a faint smile.

His dark eerie eyes burst forth with a cold glare, it was time!

Eight phantoms instantly appeared behind him.

Next, he activated his Gu worm, and pointed with his finger.

The snow silver primeval essence in his aperture fell drastically, over forty percent was expended in an instant!

Some mystical change had occurred, the beast phantoms originally manifested from the Dao marks, had become more solid, turning from hollow to real.

From a hollow phantom, they became solid phantoms!

Boar, brown bear, crocodile, green bull, horse, stone turtle, white elephant, black python, with a loud roar, they descended from the sky, charging towards Ju Kai Bei.

At this moment, everyone was stunned.

Change had occurred so quickly, Ju Kai Bei could almost see Fang Yuan losing under the might of his fist. Yet at the next moment, the eight phantoms charged towards him, from all directions, encircling him!

Wild boar charged, brown bear smacked, crocodile bit, green bull attacked with its horn, horse stomped, stone turtle suppressed, white elephant attacked with its tusks, and black python coiled!

Bam, bam, bam...

Howl, howl howl...

Boom, boom, boom...

The eight beast phantoms went into a frenzy, assaulting Ju Kai Bei ferociously.

Smoke rose and rocks flew, Ju Kai Bei was pummelled by the eight great phantoms while being surrounded in the middle!

Being attacked from all directions, Ju Kai Bei's giant body that was three times the original size, became a giant punching bag.

His ivory armor could not take it anymore, breaking as the white fragments flew, at areas where it did not break, cracks appeared.

Many people stared at this scene in shock, opening their eyes and mouths wide, speechless.

There was almost a thousand Gu Masters watching this, yet no one said a word, as they observed the eight ferocious phantoms engulfing Ju Kai Bei.

A moment later, the eight phantoms turned hollow again, as they vanished without a trace.

The smoke dispersed, and Ju Kai Bei half kneeled on the ground, hugging his head as he breathed roughly.

"It's finally over?" He slowly lowered his arms, staring at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was holding two primeval stones, recovering his primeval essence as much as he could.

He had A grade aptitude and the heavenly essence treasure lotus, now he multitasked, absorbing the essence from both primeval stones, his primeval essence had already recovered to seventy percent.

Seeing this, Ju Kai Bei's eyes twitched.

He loosened his tightly clenched teeth, throwing up blood and broken teeth fragments.

Intense pain assaulted him from all parts of his body, causing him to feel dizzy as his ears buzzed.

He was thrashed really badly.

"If I had not activated the ivory armor Gu so desperately, I might've fainted already..." Ju Kai Bei felt some afterfear, but because he did this, he did not have much yellow gold primeval essence left.

He did not expect this change of event, when he thought of using the dragon travel tiger steps Gu to retreat, it was too late.

The eight beast phantoms surrounded him and prevented him from getting away.

Ju Kai Bei assessed, there was more than ten areas in his body where bones were broken. With such injuries, he could only choose to heal the important areas, as his primeval essence was running low.

He had primeval stones on him as well, but he could not absorb the natural essence during battle.

Fang Yuan would not give him the chance.

To do so, he needed a good opportunity. Like earlier, when Ju Kai Bei was beaten till he was helpless, Fang Yuan had free time to use his primeval stones.

Even so, Fang Yuan was taking a risk. He was doing two tasks at once, absorbing the essence from his primeval stones while controlling his beast phantoms, his control of his Gu was lowered during the period.

"What did I see earlier?"

"Unbelievable, the beast phantoms turned into solid attackers?"

"Since when did strength path Gu Masters become so strong? They had such a strong attack!"

After a while, the spectators finally reacted, asking out in shock.

Outside the battle stage, chaos ensued again.

Shang Xin Ci stared with her eyes wide-open, shocked and overjoyed, brilliant light shone in her eyes.

"Good lad!" Wei Yang punched his fists, shouting excitedly.

Although Bai Ning Bing was quiet, her eyes were shining with an eerie blue light.

"Able to turn the hollow beast phantoms into solid figures. Such a Gu worm, could it be?!" Yan Tu's expression was solemn, as he thought about the Gu that Ju Kai Bei desired for such a long time, and had constantly told him.

"What you used earlier, is it... strength qi Gu?" Ju Kai Bei slowly stood up, his voice was hoarse as a hint of bitterness could be heard.

He did not attack, and Fang Yuan was happy about that as he absorbed the natural essence, saying: "You guessed right, it is the strength qi Gu."

Ju Kai Bei blanked out for a bit before showing a complicated expression, containing envy, jealousy, helplessness, and bitterness.

"Strength qi Gu, strength qi Gu... hehe." He sighed as he raised his head.

Ancient strength path Gu worms were nearly extinct. Whenever any news of them appeared, it would make Ju Kai Bei extremely interested. He had searched for many years, but to think that he would experience the strength of the strength qi Gu from this young Fang Yuan.

Beast phantoms were the traces of Great Dao, hollow and immaterial, they could not attack directly.

But, once a Gu Master had the strength qi Gu, the Gu Master can activate it and create the formless Qi of Strength.

The beast phantoms leave Fang Yuan's bodies, and attach themselves to the qi of strength, gaining the ability to attack directly.

After that qi vanishes, the beast phantoms would lose their host, and dissipate, returning to Fang Yuan's body.

Fang Yuan's strength qi Gu, was the product of his closed door refinement.

The main ingredient to create the strength qi Gu, was the rank four atmosphere Gu.

When Fang Yuan saw it at the auction, he got the idea of buying it immediately.

Atmosphere Gu, strength qi Gu, they were both qi path Gu. The laws in them were similar, thus, they could be converted to one another using refinement.

This conversion recipe was extremely complex. Using more than twenty ingredients, to carry out reverse refinement, there were more than thirty steps in this. The heat and timing have to be controlled precisely, and there cannot be any errors. The success rate was not low though, it was more than eighty percent.

Strength qi Gu, was only a rank three Gu.

Fang Yuan spent many days and nights, staying in the secret room without any rest, using his rich experience and calm attitude to successfully refine the strength qi Gu.

In his previous life, only after two hundred years did this recipe become popular among recipe masters, and become publicly known.

As for now, the recipe master that created this was not even born yet. Of course nobody knew about it.

"There is no need to continue. I surrender." Knowing that Fang Yuan had the strength qi Gu, Ju Kai Bei lost his will to fight, surrendering.

With this Gu, Fang Yuan had a strong long range attacking method.

Close range, long range, being extremely strong at both. This was the way of the true ancient strength path!

Ju Kai Bei could no longer get close to Fang Yuan, even if he used djinn transformation.

In contrast, Fang Yuan had many ways to finish him. The attack of the eight phantoms, Ju Kai Bei did not want to experience it again.

Of course, Ju Kai Bei knew the weakness of the strength qi Gu very clearly.

It expended a lot of primeval essence, five percent of snow silver primeval essence was needed to contain one beast phantom.

Eight beast phantoms would amount to forty percent.

Even in Fang Yuan's peak state, having ninety percent primeval essence, he could only use this move twice.

And this was only in theory.

In a real battle, Fang Yuan needed to use his movement Gu, defense Gu, all-out effort Gu, and others, his primeval essence would be expended in more ways, and the number of times he could use the eight phantoms would only be once.

Such a move could not be used easily, because of the great consumption, if it bore no results, the Gu Master would be weakening himself.

Thus, Fang Yuan left it to the end.

After Ju Kai Bei used djinn transformation, he relaxed his mind. Such an attitude was captured by Fang Yuan, thus he managed to injure him heavily.

When Gu Masters battle, they use Gu worms, but the person himself was still the key.

Once a person reveals a flaw, that would be the greatest loophole.

At this time, the hosting Gu Master came up and announced the result.

"Ju Kai Bei admitted defeat?" Many people could not accept this.

"Fang Zheng really shot through the sky!"

"The world is changing, the world is changing!"

Ju Kai Bei was called 'half the sky of the battle stage', but now this 'sky' could not contain Fang Yuan anymore.

After this battle, Fang Yuan's reputation tore through the sky!

Chapter 321: Shang Clan City Uproar

"Despite using rank three peak stage cultivation against a rank four, Fang Zheng still won. Not only did he overcome the odds, he even defeated such a strong expert like Ju Kai Bei! He is truly a promising young man!"

"This is no doubt a grand victory. Ju Kai Bei even used his killer move djinn transformation, but was still beaten till he sprawled on the ground by Fang Zheng, forced to admit defeat."

"The attack of the eight beast phantoms is truly terrifying... to think Fang Zheng had the strength qi Gu, he is too lucky, I heard this Gu was a prized treasure of his original clan."

In the tea houses, restaurants, and streets, people talked in their free time, discussing the battle of Fang Yuan and Ju Kai Bei.

At a point where both were at their peak, defeating a rank four with rank three cultivation was truly spectacular.

There was almost a thousand spectators at the battle stage, everyone watched the whole process. Fang Yuan won fair and square, there was no trickery or schemes, he completely dominated Ju Kai Bei through pure strength.

As for the origin of the strength qi Gu, Fang Yuan gave out fake news and caused everyone's guesses to link to Gu Yue clan.

"From today onwards, Lord Fang Zheng is my role model!"

After this battle, many people started calling Fang Yuan 'lord'. His battle strength had gained everyone's recognition.

"Lord Fang Zheng is truly awe inspiring, Ju Kai Bei's era has ended." A few female Gu Masters said with shining eyes.

"The newer generation replaces the old, as Ju Kai Bei topples, it all contributes to Fang Zheng's reputation." Some old Gu Masters exclaimed, feeling the rise of a new era.

"Fang Zheng defeated Ju Kai Bei, I wonder if he can defeat Yan Tu. If he beats Yan Tu as well, he would be the only person to dominate the battle stage in all these years. As long as he defends his position for eighteen battles, he would become an external elder of Shang clan!"

This battle created trembles in the battle stage.

The old structure was torn down, and a new force emerged.

People started to look at Fang Yuan's future, feeling excitement and anticipation.

Shang clan had not gotten an external elder for over ten years.

If Fang Yuan defeated Ju Kai Bei with a mild advantage, and had a tough time, their expectations might not have been so great.

But after Fang Yuan displayed overwhelming strength that crushed Ju Kai Bei, they started to analyze —

"Fang Zheng has the all-out effort Gu, bitter strength Gu, self-reliance Gu, and strength qi Gu, even an ancient strength path Gu Master could only reach this level!"

"The all-out effort Gu allows his attacks to be ferocious and dominating! The bitter strength Gu allows him to get stronger as he battles, paired with the self-reliance Gu, it was simply perfection. The strength qi Gu allows him to have a strong long range attack, and completely eliminates his weakness. The scene of the eight beast phantoms attacking together is simply terrifying. This is Fang Zheng's killer move!"

"Ju Kai Bei's loss was no fluke. Although he is rank four and had the advantage of cultivation, the strength path has little use for primeval essence, limiting that advantage he had. Furthermore, Fang Zheng's Gu worms are simply too good, they form into a powerful set, and are all closely related together. Ju Kai Bei probably admitted defeat after being disheartened."

"How can a person's luck and encounters be this good? Fang Zheng's luck is off the charts. He had only been in Shang clan city for a few years, yet he is already this developed. His Gu set is so strong, enough for him to spread his name in the southern border and gain his own title."

"Title? He already has it... many people are calling him and Bai Ning Bing the Black and White Demons. But even more people are calling Fang Zheng the Little Beast King."

Fang Yuan controlled the eight beast phantoms, and had a ferocious battle style, charging and crashing, the title of Little Beast King suited him well.

As for why he is not called 'Beast King'.

That is because Beast King is already an established demonic Gu Master. He occupied Bai Shou mountain, using the hundred beasts as his army, and was a rank five Gu Master, unreasonable, ruthless and evil. He was a troublesome person for both the righteous and demonic faction.

Fang Yuan was still rank three peak stage, although he defeated Ju Kai Bei and gained fame overnight. He was still very far from being at the level of 'Beast King' who was a rank five Gu Master.

From another aspect, people calling him Little Beast King meant that they are thinking highly of Fang Yuan and his future.

"I am looking forward to his battle stage defending battles. Every dominating expert's defense battle is a classic. Back then, Lord Wei Yang used rank three middle stage cultivation, even weaker than Fang Zheng now, to dominate the battle stage. Every one of his battles was a classic!" A senior Gu Master recalled.

Soon, many people started discussing Fang Yuan's future prospects.

"At this point, how many are Fang Zheng's match? Ju Kai Bei, Yan Tu, oh right, and Bai Ning Bing."

"But, Ju Kai Bei had already lost his djinn mind to Fang Zheng, he was really ruthless. Among djinn body, djinn heart, and djinn mind, djinn mind was the hardest to obtain. Without it, Ju Kai Bei's killer move is not complete. To Fang Zheng, that is one less threat."

"Yan Tu is now Fang Zheng's greatest competitor. He and Ju Kai Bei were each 'half the sky of the battle stage', his strength is no joke. But Fang Zheng is able to defeat Ju Kai Bei, and has the strength qi Gu to eliminate his weakness, there is a high chance of defeating Yan Tu."

Someone mentioned Bai Ning Bing as well: "Bai Ning Bing is not to be underestimated, after she lost to Yan Tu, during her next match, she had already broken through to rank four initial stage! A rank four at this age, what sort of talent is that. But she and Fang Zheng have a deep relationship, she might admit defeat when they meet to help Fang Zheng."

Bai Ning Bing and Fang Yuan staying at Nan Qiu garden together was no secret. Many people guessed that they had already done intimate acts.

But then, just as the discussions were at their peak, Fang Yuan suddenly announced he was retiring from the battle stage.

Once news got out, everyone was shocked.

"Why did Fang Zheng give up such a good chance?"

"External elder after dominating the battle stage, it is right before him."

Many people sighed in pity.

"Are there any hidden circumstances?" The demonic Gu Masters started guessing.

"Could it be, Shang clan does not want external elders anymore, and forced Fang Zheng to give up?" Demonic Gu Masters often lacked a sense of security.

"Or is it that Shang clan wants to revise their policy, and remove the external elder position?"

Suspicion caused many to become uncertain.

Shang clan's recruitment of demonic Gu Masters as their external elder was the only case in southern border.

In southern border, many clans have battle stages. The largest and most popular battle stage lies in the number one clan of the southern border — Wu clan.

But these battle stages were mostly for their own clansmen, rarely for outsiders. Shang clan's external elder policy became extremely popular as a result, attracting numerous talents.

Even when they traded outside, many demonic Gu Masters do not rob the Shang clan caravans. That is because of the external elder policy, and these demonic Gu Masters needed a backup plan for themselves.

Shang Yan Fei felt something amiss, and quickly clarified the issue.

Although he had secretly use the two pawns Ju Kai Bei and Yan Tu to control the battle stage, such a thing cannot be exposed.

Shang Yan Fei's authority quickly caused this matter to close.

Soon after, a few days later, Fang Yuan announced in public, he was going to assist Shang Xin Ci and help her ascend to the position of young master.

Immediately, everyone's attention shifted from the battle stage to the young master competition.

Because Shang Ya Zi's fake accounting was exposed, his young master position was revoked and there was a spot empty now.

Many of Shang Yan Fei's children were looking at this position with extreme greed.

"I heard long ago, this Fang Zheng is loyal and righteous. He had his life principles, repaying a drop of water received in need with a spring, and exacting revenge for hatred a hundred times over. He truly is responsible." Someone praised him.

"In order to assist Shang Xin Ci to attain the position of young master, he even gave up the identity of external clan elder that was in sight. This is truly..." Some people could not understand.

"Maybe he and Shang Xin Ci has some underground relationship. If it was me, I would make such a sacrifice too."

"That is possible, wait. If that's the case, what about Bai Ning Bing?"

People had their gossiping nature, and it spread like wildfire. Fang Yuan, Bai Ning Bing and Shang Xin Ci's triangle relationship become a hot topic.

Soon after, in a few days' time, Bai Ning Bing also retired from the battle stage.

"Bai Ning Bing also went to assist Shang Xin Ci!" Someone exclaimed.

"What has this world become? Nobody wants to be an external elder?" Some people's worldview were tarnished.

"Bai Ning Bing has great courage, reluctant to let him go. For love, she decided to interfere, actually the three of them and their intertwined relationship begun the moment they met." Rumors started to spread again.

Countless scenarios were conjured by the people, there were even plays and dramas appearing in Shang clan city depicting the triangle relationship of Fang, Bai and Shang.

And it was selling like hotcakes!

Forget these details, but Fang and Bai's change in position did successfully make Shang Xin Ci the center of attention.

Bai Ning Bing was now rank four initial stage, a rank four Gu Master was a clan leader in middle or small sized clans!

Although Fang Yuan was rank three peak stage, his battle strength was on par with rank four Gu masters. Once he becomes rank four, who can imagine how strong he would become?

They were both very young, and had room to grow, thus there were a lot of positive remarks about them.

Getting two experts' help, Shang Xin Ci immediately become the second most popular person vying for the young master position.

Before her, people thought that the person with the highest hope of becoming a young master was Shang Yi Fan.

After Fang and Bai assisted her, the situation changed, and it became a contest between the two sides.

...

Shang Yi Fan was not tall, in fact he was slightly short. Eagle nose and tiny eyes, he had a sharp gaze.

"Shang Xin Ci..." He sat on the wooden chair in his study room, muttering as his gaze shifted uncertainly when thinking about this person.

Before him was one person.

It was none other than Shang Ya Zi.

"Little brother Yi Fan, I am here to help you. Shang Xin Ci has Fang and Bai's help, she will be your biggest competitor. Especially that Fang Zheng, you have to be careful, he is scheming and devious, he caused my downfall!"

Shang Ya Zi gritted his teeth and spoke.

Chapter 322: Competitive Pressure

Shang Ya Zi said: "I lost, but I have not failed completely yet. Father sent me to the slave capturing group for three years, but after three years, I will be back. But before that, I have some things to give you."

Saying so, Shang Ya Zi passed a few documents to Shang Yi Fan.

Shang Yi Fan took the documents and gave them a look. The documents contained Shang Ya Zi's secret assets, his spies and some close aides.

"Brother Ya Zi, this is..." Shang Yi Fan gave a shocked expression.

"Brother Yi Fan, you are the person most likely to become young master among our siblings. I will lend you a hand here and hope you manage to win. As for these resources, feel free to use them. After three years, I will be back, just return them to me then." Shang Ya Zi sighed.

He was forced to train in the slave capturing group, he could not bring his servants and subordinates along. He was not going there to enjoy, but to be punished.

Now that he lost his young master identity, these forces would collapse eventually, he might as well hand them to Shang Yi Fan while he still had the power and let him take care of them. After three years, Shang Ya Zi will return, and would not have to restart all over again."

Shang Yi Fan quickly stood up, cupping his fists: "I will not forget brother Ya Zi's help. In the future, if I become young master, I will repay you tenfold."

"Sigh, we are brothers, there is no need to talk about repayment. Hehehe..." Although he said so, Shang Ya Zi's lips curled into a smile.

After they conversed, Shang Yi Fan sent Shang Ya Zi to the door as he left.

Seeing he had left, Shang Yi Fan's smile turned cold.

"Shang Ya Zi, what a great plan you have, wanting me to preserve your forces for you? Hehe, then I shall use this opportunity to take over all of your assets and absorb them, this is called borrowing without returning."

He knew Shang Ya Zi's plan from the start.

"Three years? Many things can happen in three years, do you still think you have a chance. Hmph, naive! Such naivety, no wonder Fang and Bai tricked you. You are a disgrace to us Shang clan!" Shang Yi Fan laughed.

But thinking of Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing, his expression turned dark.

"Shang Xin Ci..." He kept muttering her name.

As Shang Ya Zi fell, he thought this young master position was in the bag. But to think Shang Xin Ci appeared out of nowhere and became his biggest obstacle.

Shang Yi Fan's eyes squinted, as he analyzed to himself with shining eyes: "Shang Xin Ci's greatest advantage is father's affection. Father dotes on her more than his other children combined. But there are clan rules, as everyone competes for the young master position openly, father would not be able to cheat blatantly."

"In fact, because of lord father's favor, it caused our other siblings to have ill feelings towards Shang Xin Ci, or even hostility. Shang Xin Ci's greatest advantage is also her greatest weakness."

"Shang Xin Ci's second advantage is her actual strength, that is Fang Zheng and Bai Ning Bing! These two are truly..."

Thinking of the two, Shang Yi Fan's face showed strange, envious, jealous, and unbelievable expressions.

"These two, I don't know what they are after! They rejected the role of external elder to help Shang Xin Ci!"

This feeling, is like someone giving up on a watermelon to pick up sesame seeds.

"How did Shang Xin Ci convince them? Her luck is really good, easily getting these two strong generals. That Bai Ning Bing is already rank four, and Fang Zheng can even defeat Ju Kai Bei!"

She gained two Gu Masters with rank four battle strength just like this.

Even their eldest brother Shang Qiu Niu did not have a rank four subordinate.

Among the ten current young masters, only the young clan leader Shang Tuo Hai had two rank four subordinates.

But those two subordinates were not Shang Tuo Hai's private force, but sent by the clan to assist him.

As the young clan leader, Shang Tuo Hai controlled a caravan. When he traded outside, he needed sufficient strength to deal with all sorts of situations.

But now, Shang Xin Ci was not even a young master, yet she already possesses the help of two rank four experts.

This situation caused many of Shang Yan Fei's children to feel jealousy and fear.

"But, even with help from those two, so what? The position of young master belongs to me!" Shang Yi Fan licked his lips, as he thought of something, his spirit was lifted.

...

At the same time, at Nan Qiu garden.

"Shang clan has a complex and complete system of clan rules. Especially the part on successors, the rules are extremely rigid." Wei Yang stood beside Fang and Bai, in front of Shang Xin Ci, as he explained.

"If Lady Xin Ci wants to ascend to young master, you will have to pass the Shang clan test. This test is a tradition, and there is only one type of test, which is trading."

Shang clan used trade to flourish, the development of Shang clan cannot be separated from business. When Shang clan chooses a new young master, they would test their business skills.

"Do not look down on trading, thinking this is only a method to earn money. Trading can assess a successor's qualities, as many problems often occur when you do trade. The test is on your intelligence and planning, how you adapt to situations, your cultivation strength, and others."

"The clan will give any competing children a start-up fund of a hundred thousand primeval stones. Three months later, whoever earns the most would become the new young master."

Wei Yang was clear of the clan's rules.

Then, how much do we need to earn to win this competition?" Fang Yuan asked.

The Shang clan young master competition was well-known in the city, the entire Shang clan placed great attention on it. Fang Yuan knew that he had to follow the rules here.

"Normally, as long as Lady Xin Ci has around three hundred thousand by the end of the three months, she would eliminate most of her competitors. If she has six hundred thousand, there would be a high chance of winning. Seven to eight hundred thousand is the first class result of previous years' assessments. But..." Here, Wei Yang paused.

"This time, among the competitors, there is one whose mother is Lord clan leader's cousin. In Shang clan, he has a rather big force, he is called Shang Yi Fan, the most favored competitor in this young master competition. With his mother helping him secretly, he would at least have six hundred thousand at the end. If you want to beat him, Lady Xin Ci would need even better results."

Shang Yi Fan would have at least six hundred thousand, thus to get the young master position, Shang Xin Ci would need to get first class results.

But Shang Xin Ci had no authority or force in Shang clan, her mother was even a Zhang clansmen, causing her political weakness. She would not receive any help unlike Shang Yi Fan.

Her only backer is Shang Yan Fei, but as the clan leader, he cannot side with her openly.

Thus, the pressure on her was extremely high now.

After Wei Yang finished speaking, he looked at Shang Xin Ci worriedly. He knew that earning seven to eight hundred thousand was usually due to special circumstances. Very few young masters in the previous years could achieve this. This needed talent, help, and more so, luck.

Originally, Shang Yan Fei did not expect Shang Xin Ci to vie for the young master position so quickly.

It was all due to Fang and Bai influencing her.

After Shang Xin Ci heard Wei Yang's words, she was quiet for a while before asking: "May I know, what was the best result in Shang clan city's history?"

"Wei Yang was stunned: "Of course it exceeded eight hundred thousand, reaching nine hundred thousand. But very little people in history managed this, the total is less than twenty. Our current young clan leader Shang Tuo Hai only got to eight hundred and ninety thousand, and that caused a huge commotion already. But your father, back then, he reached nine hundred and twenty thousand. Just this alone, it went into Shang clan's historical records."

As he spoke, Wei Yang paused again: "But, the best result in Shang clan history is one million one hundred and ten thousand. He is called Shang Gui Cai, having a monsterous talent, but unfortunately he was a ten extreme physique..."

"Nine hundred and twenty thousand, one million one hundred and ten thousand..." Shang Xin Ci listened as her eyes glowed brightly, as she clenched her fists tightly.

She had great talent in doing business. Although Fang Yuan greatly encouraged her for this competition, she was a willing participant herself, and was not forced to do so.

Seeing Shang Xin Ci's expression, Wei Yang felt assured: "Alright, I have to go. But before that, I'll give you some advice. Shang clan's entire attention is on this competition, do not try to take shortcuts or loopholes, and violate the rules. Trust your brother Wei, all those who tried cheating in the past had never succeeded."

Young masters were the future of Shang clan, it was extremely important and no mistakes could be tolerated.

Shang Ya Zi was a young master, but because of one fake accounting, he was exiled, it shows how much importance Shang clan places on the young masters and their actions.

Shang Yi Fan had his mother's clan's backing, but they could only help him within the boundaries of the rules, they did not dare to cheat.

Soon after, Wei Yang gave a few more heartfelt advice before leaving Nan Qiu garden.

He was an important elder of the clan, and was Shang Yan Fei's aide, according to rules, he should avoid meeting them. But he still entered and left Nan Qiu garden, explaining so much for Shang Xin Ci, it showed how much of a friend he was.

"Brother Wei is taking on a lot of pressure for us. We cannot trouble him any further." Shang Xin Ci said.

Fang Yuan remained silent.

Bai Ning Bing frowned: "Earning six times the initial amount in three months of business, it is easier said than done."

Although she was a natural genius, she had zero talent towards trading and business, feeling extremely troubled now.

But Shang Xin Ci's eyes shone as she smiled, saying confidently: "Actually I have a good plan. As long as we succeed, I'm sure we can earn six hundred thousand."

"Oh, what plan?" Bai Ning Bing asked.

Shang Xin Ci looked deeply at Fang Yuan, stating her plan: "I got my inspiration from brother Hei Tu's battles when I went to watch him in the battle stage, we can do business regarding intel."

"Selling information?" Bai Ning Bing frowned.

Chapter 323: Start of Three Kings Inheritance

"That's right, information business. Shang clan's battle stage has over a hundred battles daily, there are so many opportunities hidden in the battle stage that we can use. I've thought about it, we can collect the Gu Master information of the battle stage participants, and sell them. We can hire a few famous people to do predictions before a battle, and critique after the battle, and so on." Shang Xin Ci smiled as she answered.

"Brilliant!" Bai Ning Bing cheered.

This idea was ingenious!

Bai Ning Bing had participated in many battles, she knew deeply how brilliant this idea was. Immediately, she knew this idea could bring in huge profits for them.

Even Fang Yuan looked at her in surprise.

He has thought of this idea in his previous life, even using it in Wu clan. Wu clan's battle stage was grander and had an even livelier atmosphere. Fang Yuan's idea created a huge commotion and earned him lots of money everyday. But not long after, Wu clan interfered, and all sorts of competition and suppression came, in just a few months, his profits sank and his business was forced to close after half a year.

Fang Yuan reflected, he was able to come up with this idea because of his memories of Earth. But Shang Xin Ci being able to think of that as a native was extremely impressive, it showed her superior talent in business and trade!

Although this idea was good, Fang Yuan shook his head.

Shang Xin Ci gritted her teeth: "Does brother Hei Tu think this idea is bad?"

"The idea is good, but it won't work. Xin Ci, do you trust me?" Fang Yuan looked at Shang Xin Ci deeply.

Shang Xin Ci smiled gently.

"My life was saved by brother Hei Tu, what is there not to trust?"

Bai Ning Bing snickered in her heart, but remained silent.

She was an insider, along the way, she was extremely clear: Shang Xin Ci's misery was singlehandedly caused by Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan nodded: "Since you trust me, listen to me. We just need twenty days to triple your primeval stones."

"Really!" Shang Xin Ci expressed her curiosity: "Then I will listen to brother's instructions."

"What scheme is he coming up with this time? Who is he planning to harm?" Bai Ning Bing looked at Fang Yuan with the corner of her eye, guessing in her heart.

...

San Cha mountain, situated in the middle of Zuo clan's Leng Zhan mountain, and Che clan's Fei Lai mountain.

Zuo clan and Che clan, the former had six hundred years of history, while the latter had five hundred and eighty.

The two were enemies, centuries of hatred and grudge, causing the two clans to be mortal enemies.

For the past hundred years, the two clans were expanding, and in order to occupy San Cha mountain, they fought.

On the mountain waist of San Cha mountain, an intense battle had occurred, and it was nearing the end.

Blood flowed on the ground, as tens of Gu Master corpses laid on the ground. There were seven people still standing.

Three from Zuo clan, four from Che clan.

Zuo clan elder Zuo Wu Sheng's chest had a deep hole, as blood flowed out. He pressed down on his injury as he stood in front of Zuo Chan Yu, with a solemn expression: "Big Missy, leave now, we will block them!"

Zuo Chan Yu was Zuo clan leader's eldest daughter, having A grade aptitude and was the future hope of Zuo clan. She was young and pretty, rank three middle stage cultivation before even twenty years old, she could not afford to die here.

"Elder Wu Sheng..." Zuo Chan Yu showed deep hesitation and dismay.

"Want to leave? Dream on!" Che clan elder Che You Yin sneered as he walked out.

"Old man Wu Sheng, to think this day would come. Hehehe, today, I will make sure all three of you die without a proper burial!" His killing intent burst out.

But after saying so, he instructed a young female Gu Master beside him: "Xiang Er, you have an injury on you, later when we fight, stay back and keep a lookout for us."

Che Qiao Xiang instantly frowned: "Father, I only have a slight injury, it is no matter. I want to fight beside you!"

She was very worried.

Zuo Wu Sheng was her father's rival for tens of years, they were about the same strength. Although Zuo Wu Sheng was injured, it would not be easy to kill him, his dying counterattack would be terrifying.

"Nonsense!" Che You Yin chided: "Be obedient and listen to father, this is an order."

Che Qiao Xiang pouted, about to rebuke, but suddenly heard a laugh.

"Hahaha... hehehe.... huhuhuh..."

This was a weird laugh, making someone feel an evil wind blowing when they heard it.

Following this laughter, someone appeared on a mountain rock.

This person was extremely handsome, wearing a flowery robe that had pink butterflies. He wore a floral crown on his head, and there was a red flower ball sewn onto the crown. As he laughed, the ball vibrated, causing him to look like an extremely hilarious clown.

But be it Zuo Wu Sheng or Che You Yin, when they saw him, there was no laughter but intense fear instead.

"Ah, you are the 'Pink Butterfly Gentleman'..."

"Kong Ri Tian!"

The two spoke out, revealing his identity.

This moment, the other people's expressions also changed. Especially Zuo Chan Yu and Che Qiao Xiang, their faces went pale and they became extremely nervous.

This Kong Ri Tian was a demonic Gu Master, having a vile reputation. He loved to wear a flower robe that had pink butterflies, thus he was called 'pink butterfly gentleman'.

But the truth is, he was a serial rapist, targeting virgin women. He was extremely hated by everyone, and thus was a loner.

Most importantly, he had rank four cultivation, once he appeared, the battle situation changed.

Zuo clan and Che clan were at their wits end, their main fighter Che You Yin and Zuo Wu Sheng were injured, and only had rank three cultivation.

"Hahaha... hehehe... huhuhu... That is right, I am Kong Ri Tian!" Although he was exposed, pink butterfly gentleman was extremely happy, laughing in that weird manner again.

Suddenly, he waved his sleeve, and injected his primeval essence, causing a flower petals to rain on the battlefield.

The pink petals turned into butterflies, flying in the air.

At once, fragrance spread throughout the battlefield.

Zuo clan and Che clan quickly defended and unleashed their abilities.

Kong Ri Tian used this opportunity to attack, causing the flower rain to intensify as his body moved around quickly.

After eight to nine rounds, Kong Ri Tian's body flashed, as he retreated and left the battlefield.

"He retreated!"

"That was close..."

Che You Yin and Zuo Wu Sheng sighed together, but their expressions changed soon.

"My dear Chan Yu!"

"Qiao Xiang! Scoundrel, release my daughter!!"

The two elders were burning with anger.

"Hahaha... hehehe... huhuhu..." Kong Ri Tian laughed, as two ladies were on his left and right hand respectively.

It was Che Qiao Xiang and Zuo Chan Yu, having fallen unconscious as they were captured by him during the chaotic battle.

Kong Ri Tian specialized in dealing with female Gu Masters.

"Great rewards today, to think I'd find two beauties here. Hahaha... hehehe... huhuhu!" Kong Ri Tian was extremely satisfied, when suddenly a change occurred.

The entire San Cha mountain started trembling, as mountain rocks fell due to the tremors!

"What is going on?"

"What in the world is happening?!"

As everyone shouted in shock, three light pillars burst out from the three mountain peaks of San Chan mountain. Three giant light pillars, yellow, blue, and red extended all the way into the sky, above the clouds.

At this point, a voice was heard among all present on San Cha mountain —

"Three Kings Inheritance opens today, regardless of righteous or demonic, only fate matters."

Everyone stared at this scene in shock.

Even Kong Ri Tian forgot the two beauties in his arms.

Three kings inheritance... it is actually the three kings inheritance!

Everyone reacted and showed an extremely excited expression.

Three kings inheritance, oh god, all three kings were rank five Gu Masters, this is their inheritance, this is actually their inheritance!!!

...

Three days later, in Shang clan city.

Nan Qiu garden, study room.

Placing a document lightly on the table, brilliance shone across Fang Yuan's eyes.

"Three kings inheritance has finally opened..."

Looking at the date, it was the same as his previous life. This shows that in this world, even though rebirth can alter history, significant events cannot be changed easily.

"Now that the three kings inheritance has opened, I have little time left. Once Shang Xin Ci becomes the young master, I will have to set off."

Fang Yuan felt an urge in his heart, he needed to act faster.

The three kings inheritance was different from ordinary inheritances.

The flower wine inheritance and white bone inheritance he took previously were only one inheritance each. But this time, it was three collective inheritances in one place.

If he could obtain all three, Fang Yuan's strength would increase by many times, and the rank four Gu worms he needed would be mostly filled. At least before rank five, he would not need to worry about resources anymore.

But the three kings inheritance was a demonic inheritance, it was dangerous. There were many dog groups inside, and many checkpoints to pass through. In his previous life, countless lives were sacrificed, and only after half a year did someone reach the end and obtain the inheritance.

Thus, there was no point in going at the moment.

"News of the three kings inheritance cannot be hidden. How can those three pillars reaching into the sky be concealed?"

Fang Yuan knew these three pillars were the inheritance entrance. But to enter, there were certain requirements.

"Now, I can finally mass purchase dog enslavement Gu, paper crane gu, and exploding egg Gu." Fang Yuan analyzed.

Before this, although he had cash on hand, he secretly bought the three types of Gu in the market.

He had a vigilant nature, he did not go all in.

Only when the news of the three kings inheritance was released, he knew the time was ripe.

Bulk purchase!

Five days later, Fang Yuan bought a large number of rank one dog enslavement Gu, rank two paper crane Gu, and rank one exploding egg Gu. Not only Shang Xin Ci's hundred thousand primeval stones, but also the three hundred thousand he had just gotten from Bai clan.

Fang Yuan had once extorted three million primeval stones from Bai clan, they had paid almost half of it already.

Adding in Bai Ning Bing's money, Fang Yuan's purchasing plan was a big success.

Chapter 324: Earning a fortune

"Shang Xin Ci used all her funds to buy these three Gu worms?" In the study room, Shang Yi Fan was holding onto a piece of paper.

This document was sent over by his mother.

Shang Yi Fan's mother was Shang Yan Fei's cousin, she had great influence and many informants.

"Rank one dog enslavement Gu, rank two paper crane Gu, and rank one exploding egg Gu, what use do they have?" Shang Yi Fan frowned deeply, thinking hard but could not arrive at an explanation.

"I heard Shang Xin Ci gave the entire hundred thousand to Fang Zheng. Although Fang Zheng is strong in battle, I've never heard of his talent in business. Randomly purchasing like this would only cause harm to himself. Did I overestimate them?"

Shang Yi Fan pondered.

Although he did not have high cultivation, he had trained his own ability in doing business, he had great understanding of the market.

Generally speaking, buying Gu worms in bulk like this, any experienced trader would not choose such a method.

Because this investment had no prospects!

But as Shang Yi Fan continued thinking, the uneasiness in his heart did not go away. He felt that he had missed something, as if there was a deep scheme behind this nonsensical bulk purchase.

At this moment, the old steward reported outside the door: "Young master, something huge has occurred, I need to report to you."

"Oh, please come on Old Zhang." Shang Yi Fan quickly asked him to come in.

This Old Zhang was his mother's capable subordinate. He had rank three peak stage cultivation, able to hold his own and had great experience. Shang Yi Fan could not treat him like an ordinary subordinate.

Shang Yi Fan's mother had also instructed him, to be courteous to Old Zhang and seek advice from him to learn more about trading.

Old Zhang walked in, his expression solemn: "Young master Yi Fan, things are not looking good, there are news from San Cha mountain, that someone had discovered the correct method to enter the inheritance."

Although the three kings inheritance opened earlier, separated into three pillars of yellow, blue and red light, there were special criterias set by the inheritance and nobody could enter.

During these few days, after many people experimented and tested, they finally found the way to enter the three kings inheritance ground.

Hearing Old Zhang's words, Shang Yi Fan showed intense curiosity: "Oh, what does one have to do to enter the three kings inheritance? Wait, don't tell me..."

Suddenly his expression changed, as he stared intently at that document on the table.

He thought of a possibility, as he slowly stood up.

Old Zhang laughed bitterly: "Young master Yi Fan guessed it, that is correct, to enter the inheritance, three different Gu are needed. To enter the yellow pillar, the inheritance of King Quan, a Gu Master needs to refine the rank one dog enslavement Gu. To enter the blue pillar, King Xin's inheritance, the Gu master needs to have paper crane Gu. If they want to enter the red pillar, King Bao's inheritance, they will need at least one exploding egg Gu."

"How can this be?" Shang Yi Fan screeched.

He fell on his seat, dejected.

He finally understood, why Fang and Bai bought these three Gu in bulk, so this was the reason.

Right now, news of the three kings inheritance had spread all over the southern border. The inheritance of three rank five Gu Masters together, who knows how many people would gain interest and want to go and get their share of the pie.

But to enter it, one needs at least one of those three Gu.

But right now, in Shang clan city, all of these three Gu belonged to Shang Xin Ci. As long as one is not a fool, they can imagine how much profits she can earn by sell those Gu worms!

Shang Yi Fan was not stupid, in fact he was smart, at least more than Shang Ya Zi.

"Where did they get such information? And so precise!"

"No, now is not the time for that, it is no longer important. More importantly, how am I going to stop them!"

An eerie light continued to flash in Shang Yi Fan's eyes, as he concentrated and thought.

But a moment later, he showed despair and helplessness.

There was no way!

Shang Xin Ci did an excellent job here. It was a very normal investment, but because of the three kings inheritance, it became a completely different story.

When they purchased the Gu, Shang Xin Ci used way more than a hundred thousand primeval stones, but that was not against the rules, at most it was a curveball.

As long as they can earn primeval stones, and calculate her profits based on her initial capital, there was no problems...

If Shang Yi Fan wanted to find problems here, he had no reason to. That is because he also borrowed forces from his mother, such as Old Zhang. To speak the truth, his curveball was way worse than Shang Xin Ci's.

"Young master Yi Fan, the other party had the most accurate information this time. After they deal, their capital can at least triple. We cannot find any problems with them, nor can we use any underhanded means. We have to use our remaining time and do our own business. With madam's influence in the city, in three months, you will have at least six hundred thousand. Young master, we can still win." Old Zhang explained.

"Yes, we can only hope so..." Shang Yi Fan breathed out deeply, but the worry in his heart did not go away.

Regarding the young master competition, this was just the start but he had already received such a 'surprise'. Who knows what might happen later on.

The confident Shang Yi Fan started to become doubtful.

...

Three kings, they referred to King Quan, King Xin, and King Bao.

Their origins were traced back to three hundred years ago.

The three kings came from Wang clan. Wang clan was exterminated by their mortal enemy Wu clan[1], but they missed out three children from Wang clan.

These three children, two males and one female. The eldest was eight, he would become the future King Quan. The youngest was five, he was King Bao. As for the female, the future King Xin, she was only six at the time.

Wu clan was busy absorbing their remnant forces, to completely digest their gains from Wang clan.

What could three children do?

They were not even Gu Masters, thus they did not bother with the children, only sending out an arrest warrant and forgot about them.

The person sent to kill them was also a lazy man, he picked three kids to kill, faking that he had completed his mission and returned. Thus, the three children were unintentionally saved.

They experienced hardship, suffering, and barely stayed alive. As they supported each other, they developed a deep relationship.

As they grew older, their hatred for Wu clan deepened.

But after Wu clan absorbed Wang clan, they got much stronger, and was a large clan that owned three mountains. After years of operating, their forces were even more deep-rooted. The three kings were alone, not even given the chance to awaken their aperture. It was an impossible dream for them to take revenge on Wu clan.

But life was uncertain, and fate worked in mysterious ways. You can never know what your fate might be in the future.

During one time when they risked their lives, collecting herbs on the mountain to sustain their livelihood, the three were thrown into an ancient inheritance ground.

This was not an ordinary inheritance, it was left behind by a mysterious rank six Gu Immortal.

The three kings thus, experienced a change in fate. They each inherited a portion of the rank six Gu Immortal's inheritance, and worked hard to cultivate for nearly a hundred years.

The three encouraged each other and worked hard together. When they all got to rank five, they felt that the time was ripe, and thus, left the inheritance grounds to exact revenge on Wu clan.

At that time, Wu clan was at the peak of their development.

The three kings did not use any schemes or plot, but went straight to their doorsteps. Wu clan leader was a rank five Gu Master, how could he endure the assault of three rank five Gu masters?

Especially when these three rank five Gu Masters inherited an ancient inheritance.

King Quan summoned his army of hounds, as he waved his hand, it was a mighty army. The hound groups were like the sea, engulfing Wu clan village.

King Xin was speedy and agile, moving like a spectre, she killed all of Wu clan's higher ups, causing them to have no leaders and fall into chaos.

King Bao was violent and direct, once he attacked, it shocked the heavens, as he triggered the explosion of the mountain rocks.

The strong and invincible Wu clan, was exterminated by the three kings in three days.

The three mountains' spirit springs were destroyed, as corpses lined the mountain trails, blood pouring on the ground, it was a grotesque sight.

Wu clan was completely wiped out, but the three kings paid a heavy price.

However, they were willing to do so for the sake of revenge.

After getting their revenge, the three kings felt that life had lost its meaning, they did not want to rebuild Wang clan, as a clan, no matter how strong they were, could not defend against true experts.

They started living in seclusion, no longer coming out. They vanished like three shooting stars, after causing the huge event in southern border, they disappeared quickly, never to be heard from again.

Nobody knows what happened to the three kings after that, until recently, when their inheritance appeared.

"King Quan has at least three rank five dog enslavement Gu. With them, one can enslave myriad beast kings, and command an army, conquering the world!"

"King Xin is most skilled at refining Gu, she developed a unique set of Gu worms from the common rank two paper crane Gu, allowing her to easily get information. It was because of her that King Quan and King Bao found out the security loophole in Wu clan village. She was a huge factor in eliminating Wu clan."

"And there is King Bao, his temper was like fire, every time he attacked, it would cause huge explosions that shook the lands. His power is wild and overbearing, whoever receives his inheritance would be able to stomp on the world!"

"Three rank five inheritances, getting one would allow one to rise to power, two would allow them to leave their names in history, and three would breed the ultimate overlord!"

"This is a huge opportunity, I will not be satisfied unless I try my best."

"I have to hurry there, if I am late, and others get it, I would regret it for life!"

As news of the entry method of the three kings inheritance got out, many people went wild in Shang clan city.

"I want to buy the exploding egg Gu."

"I want the paper crane Gu!"

"I want dog enslavement Gu, paper crane Gu, and exploding egg Gu!!"

"What, why are these Gu so expensive? The prices are three times as before!!"

"Tsk, get lost if you're poor, there are lots of people waiting to buy."

"Damn it... I'll buy it!"

"I want to buy, I have to buy it!"

Numerous people gritted their teeth, scolding the unscrupulous merchant under their breaths, but still took out their hard-earned money in great pain.

[1] Another Wu clan, not the overlord. Back

Chapter 325: Immortal’s Blessed Land

"During these last ten days, we earned twenty thousand on average a day. In total, the initial hundred thousand had already tripled, we have three hundred thousand now!" Holding onto the account book in her hand, Shang Xin Ci was surprised and delighted.

Ten days into the young master competition, Shang Xin Ci had already tripled the initial capital in her hands, she immediately pulled apart from her competitors.

Three hundred thousand, and this is only the amount earned from the young master's capital. Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing had also invested much into this, right now they earned a fortune. Fang Yuan's primeval elder Gu was no longer enough, as he bought two more, his total asset had reached two million and four hundred thousand.

Bai Ning Bing also earned a lot.

Shang Xin Ci's servants, Xiao Die and Xiao Lan, looked at Fang Yuan with a colorful gaze.

They knew that this amazing result was all due to Fang Yuan.

A good start was half the success. The two servants were doubtful of Shang Xin Ci competing for the young master position, but now they had much more confident.

"But, how did Fang Yuan know such accurate information about the three kings inheritance?" Bai Ning Bing sat at one side as she felt suspicion.

The reason Fang Yuan was able to use this opportunity and earn this time was all due to the information he had.

Does that mean, Fang Yuan had some secret regarding the three kings inheritance? Or did he have a mysterious source of information?

No matter which it was, the truth shows that Fang Yuan was not simple at all.

Although Bai Ning Bing earned a lot as well, she felt a strong pressure in her heart.

She had spent a lot of time with Fang Yuan, she found that often, Fang Yuan would bring her some surprise when she least expects it.

Although he does not appear mysterious at all on the outside, he is, in fact, shrouded in a thick layer of fog.

Precisely because she had spent so much time with him, she could feel this and experience how unfathomable Fang Yuan was!

"Brother Hei Tu, thank you so much this time. With this three hundred thousand, I can better execute my plans now." Shang Xin Ci smiled and said.

But Fang Yuan waved his hand: "No worries, Xin Ci, you had a great idea, but it is very difficult to execute."

He continued: "A business that sells information in the battle stage is unlike us purchasing Gu in bulk. This time, I struck when your competitors were caught off guard, but most important, it was because Shang Ya Zi who controlled the shops was gone, and there was no one managing the Shang clan shops. Without a firm leader, even if others wanted to interfere, they could not do so, and could only watch us earn this profit."

"But an information business is different. To start this, not only do you have a great need for resources, you also need manpower and a huge network to assist you. Otherwise, your competitors will suppress and attempt to ruin your business. Our foundation is weak, we cannot afford any failed attempts. Once we invest in a business, it has to succeed. Thus, we need to make preparations."

Shang Xin Ci's expression turned solemn, nodding: "Brother Hei Tu, you are right. But it has only been a few years since I came to Shang clan city, I only have Xiao Die and Xiao Lan to help me. As for network, I barely have any contacts."

Xiao Die was a servant she brought over from Zhang clan, she was loyal and now that she was nurtured as a Gu Master by Shang Xin Ci, she had decent aptitude of B grade.

As for Xiao Lan, she is a rank three healing Gu Master that Shang Yan Fei sent to assist Shang Xin Ci, she was reliable and trustworthy.

Fang Yuan laughed: "Xin Ci, don't think too lowly of yourself. Shang Chi Wen who controls the battle stage has a good relationship with you."

"We can relate to each other because we are girls. At the same time, an intel business helps her revenue, I believe she will not object." Shang Xin Ci analyzed and said.

"Xin Ci, I said I'd help you get the young master position, I have my plans, and ample confidence of winning. No need to worry, just do what I say, there is a high chance of winning." Fang Yuan reassured.

"I will listen to Brother Hei Tu's instructions." Shang Xin Ci laughed, replying with no hesitation.

Fang Yuan sat on the chair, his strategizing posture gave Shang Xin Ci a strong sense of security.

"Xin Ci, firstly, you have to recruit people. If you want to do this business, you need a large number of loyal subordinates. But before that, you need a manager. He needs to have rank three cultivation and must be able to hold his own, being experienced and capable at trading. I have already found such a person, his name is Zhou Quan, he was a shopkeeper under Shang Ya Zi." Fang Yuan continued to plan.

Shang Xin Ci was slightly dejected: "Zhou Quan? I know him. But he is a rank three Gu Master, he is arrogant and proud. He was once Zhou clan's clan leader, having rank four cultivation. But after there was an internal strife, and the clan got slaughtered by demonic Gu Masters, he escaped with heavy injuries, thus only having rank three upper stage cultivation left. He takes care of the shops and always has the best performance among all the other shopkeepers. But even Shang Ya Zi could not get his loyalty, such a person, I am afraid..."

Fang Yuan waved his hand: "How would you know if you don't try? Xin Ci, you have to become confident, trust me, you have a unique charisma. In the future, many people will serve you willingly and fight for you. Zhou Quan is a difficult target, you might not succeed, but as long as you display your sincerity, your hard work will definitely pay off."

"Yes, Brother Hei Tu, I will work hard!" Shang Xin Ci clenched her fists.

Fang Yuan nodded: "Good, then go ahead."

Not longer after Shang Xin Ci left, Wei Yang arrived at Nan Qiu garden.

Fang Yuan attended to him at the lake pavilion: "I understand why brother Wei is here, please take a seat."

Saying so, Fang Yuan poured Wei Yang a cup of tea.

Wei Yang laughed: "Brother Fang Zheng is wise, then please tell me about it."

Fang Yuan used the three kings inheritance to earn a fortune, it was all because he had secret information about it in advance.

Shang Yan Fei was no fool, he immediately knew Fang Yuan possessed valuable information.

The three kings inheritance was the largest event for the last fifty to sixty years. Right now, it had affected the entire southern border, and attracted the attention of many forces. But because in the southern border's mountain terrain, danger lurked everywhere, it was not easy to get to the inheritance ground. Even so, many clans, as long as they could, sent out their respective groups of Gu Masters.

The inheritance of three rank five Gu Masters, even the super-class Shang clan would be moved.

"My information came from Bai Gu mountain. Grey Bone Scholar had once explored the three kings inheritance grounds, and gathered some information. The truth is, the three kings inheritance ground they discovered now is an ancient Gu Master's blessed land." Fang Yuan answered in a half-truth manner.

His information was obviously not from Bai Gu mountain. But the information about the blessed land, it was true, he had confirmed it in his previous life.

"Blessed land?" Hearing this phrase, a brilliant light flashed across Wei Yang's eyes.

Blessed land, blessed land, it is the land of blessings, the place of residence for Gu Masters after they become immortal.

In the blessed land, the scenery is like a drawing, having a unique atmosphere and large amounts of treasure and precious materials. The primeval essence inside is often dozens of times thicker and denser than the outside world.

A blessed land was an independent small world, a utopia, isolated from the world. The Gu Immortal rules the land, and anyone who lives in it can experience serenity and happiness.

"Brother Fang Zheng, are you serious?" Wei Yang's tone became more anxious.

He had to be serious.

Rank five was mortal, rank six was immortal. Between rank five and six, there was a qualitative difference that made them world's apart.

The inheritance of three rank five Gu Masters could only pique Shang clan's interest. But if it involves the inheritance of a rank six Gu Immortal, then all of the super clans in the southern border would go crazy over it!

The inheritance of a rank six Gu Immortal was simply too valuable. It was so important that even those secluded rank six Gu Immortals would appear one after another!

Fang Yuan laughed: "I am not sure about the exact details, but in Grey Bone Scholar's notes, that is what was written."

He was not afraid of exposing this information earlier, because there was no bad consequences in doing so.

According to his memories, in just a few days, people will start to develop an understanding of this. Anyway, after a short period, Shang clan would also learn of this. He might as well tell Wei Yang in advance to earn their trust.

"Brother Wei, calm down. Although this is a blessed land left by a rank six Gu Immortal, it had long been degenerating. Right now, it is on the brink of collapsing. Back in the day, this blessed land was occupied by the three kings and they dug out all of the resources and treasures inside. Right now, the three kings used this blessed land to build their inheritances, causing the blessed land to feel even greater pressure. Eventually, it will face destruction, and vanish into thin air." Fang Yuan said slowly.

"Oh, is that so?" Wei Yang blinked, as he rapidly processed the information.

"These were all recorded in Grey Bone Scholar's notes, but to ensure my safety, I had already destroyed all these documents, I cannot show them to you." Fang Yuan smiled lightly.

"Brother, this is too big of a matter. It is not that I do not trust you, but I have to report to lord clan leader, and let him decide." Wei Yang was solemn.

Fang Yuan expressed his understanding: "If Shang clan wants to send out an exploration team, I have some information here that might be helpful."

Fang Yuan had some understanding of the things inside the inheritance.

"Haha, in that case, I cannot let you lose out. Give a price." Wei Yang was in charge of Feng Yu manor, and controlled intel in the city.

Fang Yuan thought about it, and said four hundred thousand.

Wei Yang frowned: "For information on the inheritance of a rank six Gu Immortal, four hundred thousand is... too little. But the reliability of the information has yet to be confirmed, I will pass you four hundred thousand first. After a while, when it is evaluated, no worries little brother, with your brother Wei here, you will not lose out."

"I am assured by brother Wei's words." Fang Yuan laughed.

After getting this information, Shang Yan Fei paid great attention to it, sending three teams to San Cha mountain. Each team had at least three elders, it was a strong investment.

A few days later, Fang Yuan received the compensation from Wei Yang regarding the information.

The information he provided had helped Shang clan's teams greatly, and avoided many deaths.

After getting the funds, Fang Yuan approached Li Ran.

Li Ran was a spy sent by Wu clan, right now he was inside third inner city battle stage, his identity was still a secret and nobody knew except Fang Yuan.

"I have some information about the three kings inheritance, I am sure your Wu clan would be interested." Fang Yuan met with Li Ran in secret and immediately said.

Chapter 326: Nine Eyes Liquor Worm

Days went by and with the news of the three kings inheritance, a time of unrest began at San Cha mountain.

Many formidable demonic Gu Masters, righteous Gu Masters and people of all occupations and goals rushed towards San Cha mountain.

At first, Shang clan controlled the situation, continually sending reinforcements and tyrannically occupying the inheritance entrances, displaying their determination towards obtaining this inheritance.

However, Wu clan moved and broke the blockade of Shang clan.

After that, news continued to spread. The fact that the site of three kings inheritance had been rank six Gu Immortal blessed land caused a huge uproar and countless people flocked towards San Cha mountain. Several other top ranked clans were also alarmed by the news and dispatched groups of formidable Gu Masters one after another.

With this, even Shang clan and Wu clan could not block the huge wave of people.

San Cha mountain fell into chaos.

There were casualties every day. To seize the chance to enter the inheritance, there were intense battles between righteous and demonic; demonic and demonic; righteous and righteous.

Every change in the situation in San Cha mountain affected the hearts of many people.

Fang Yuan was also paying close attention to this.

After the inheritance opened, close to a month had passed. Some people already gained some benefits in the inheritance, stimulating the passion of many others to explore the inheritance.

However, Fang Yuan did not care about these benefits. With the memories of his previous life, he knew that the true essence of three kings inheritance lied in the depths of the inheritance ground. There were at least a hundred barriers before one could reach there and it was a time and energy consuming process. Sometimes, people would be lost and trapped in fog, and not be able to find the exit. Sometimes, there would be attacks from dogs and many Gu Masters would die under these dogs' sharp canine teeth.

The three kings were demonic Gu Masters; this was a demonic inheritance.

There were dangers lurking all over in demonic inheritances. In many cases, one needed to risk their lives to explore them.

"It is still too early to go to San Cha mountain, the time is not ripe yet. It is better to benefit from other's efforts and preserve my strength. When they remove the barriers and clear the obstacles, that will be the time I seize the rewards. For now, I should refine Gu." Fang Yuan had already made a plan.

The Gu he was going to refine this time was none other than liquor worm!

Rank one liquor worm could purify green copper primeval essence by a small realm. Rank two four flavors liquor worm could purify red steel primeval essence by a small realm. Rank three seven fragrances liquor worm could purify white silver primeval essence by a small realm. Rank four nine eyes liquor worm could purify yellow gold primeval essence by a small realm.

Rank five liquor worm, however, did not exist. The recipe grandmaster who researched liquor worm's recipe had an outstanding talent, but he was killed by enemies when he was young and died prematurely.

Geniuses only represented a possibility.

There were many cases of geniuses who were killed before they matured.

However, the current Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing could already be said to have matured; killing them would not be easy.

After Fang Yuan fused liquor worm into four flavors liquor worm, he had not used it and had only been raising it.

It was because he had bone flesh unity Gu and Bai Ning Bing's help that the four flavors liquor worm lost its worth. However, it was different now.

Bai Ning Bing was now rank four while Fang Yuan was rank three peak stage; he would also advance to rank four initial stage not long later. At that time, their cultivation would be the same.

The help that bone flesh unity Gu could offer to Fang Yuan would decrease by a lot. At that time, a rank four nine eyes liquor worm would make his cultivation speed faster.

Refine the nine eyes liquor worm!

While Shang Xin Ci was starting to recruit Zhou Quan, Fang Yuan chose to go into closed door cultivation to refine Gu.

Bai Ning Bing also chose to go into closed door cultivation, refining Gu secretly.

To refine four flavors liquor worm, two rank one liquor worms and wine of sour, sweet, bitter and spicy flavors were required. To refine seven fragrances liquor worm, two four flavors liquor worm and seven types of spices were required.

To refine nine eyes liquor worm, one needed two seven fragrances liquor worm and eyeballs of nine different hundred beast kings.

Right now, Fang Yuan was at Shang clan city and had a huge advantage. If it was at other places, he would have to spend large amounts of energy to search for materials to refine liquor worm. However, at Shang clan city, he could easily buy them as long as he had money.

Fang Yuan already possessed a four flavors liquor worm. He bought two liquor worms and fused them into the second four flavors liquor worm.

He then fused these two four flavors liquor worm into seven fragrances liquor worm.

The process till this stage was smoothly finished by him. However, he ran into difficulty while refining the second seven fragrances liquor worm.

While he was fusing the third four flavors liquor worm and the second seven fragrances liquor worm, the fusion failed. The primeval stones spent on it were all wasted. He had to buy the supplementary materials and restart it again.

Fortunately, fusing the two seven fragrances liquor worm was completely smoothly. Three days later, Fang Yuan obtained a nine eyes liquor worm.

Nine eyes liquor worm was like a silkworm and was pure white like a pearl. There were no eyes on its head, but rather it had nine colors that resembled eyes - red, orange, yellow, green, blue and so on - as if they were precious gems embedded on its body.

Nine eyes liquor worm could purify yellow gold primeval essence by a small realm!

Fang Yuan had spent a lot to refine it, his expenses almost reaching two hundred thousand primeval stones.

No Gu Masters could avoid failures in refining Gu. Fang Yuan might have failed many times, but his luck was pretty good.

His failures was all concentrated in the early stage of refining four flavors liquor worm and seven fragrances liquor worm. At the final juncture, he had succeeded in one try.

What Gu Master feared the most in refining Gu was failing at the latter stage. That kind of loss was disastrous.

"I have nine eyes liquor worm now." Fang Yuan observed the Gu for a while before satisfiedly putting it into his aperture.

He was still only at rank three peak stage now and could not use the nine eyes liquor worm; he could only wait till he reached rank four before he used it.

Bai Ning Bing could use it.

However, yellow gold middle stage primeval essence had a strong cleansing effect towards the aperture walls. Bai Ning Bing possessed northern dark ice soul physique, and from what she said, her aptitude had already increased to ninety-six percent now. Nine eyes liquor worm would do more harm than good to her.

"When I reach rank four initial stage and use this nine eyes liquor worm, I will have yellow gold middle stage primeval essence. At that time, the quality of my primeval essence will, for the first time, surpass Bai Ning Bing." Fang Yuan could sense he was not far from reaching rank four realm.

Although they had undergone a 'vow', he had never forgotten the danger called Bai Ning Bing.

------------

Time passed day by day. A great demonic path figure appeared at San Cha mountain inheritance grounds after Kong Ri Tian.

He was Long Qing Tian, 'he who once dyed the sky jade-green', a famous poison path Gu Master. When he appeared in the inheritance grounds, he killed three Shang clan elders with poison and gave a huge boost to the demonic path's morale.

Fortunately, two days later, Wu clan sent the rank four Elder Wu Tong Shen to hold back Long Qing Tian. This brought back the situation in San Cha mountain to an equilibrium.

On Shang Xin Ci's side, she, as expected, met setbacks when recruiting Zhou Quan and her progress was slow. Zhou Quan was proud and arrogant, his attitude did not ease even a little and his tone also seemed like he had no intentions to discuss.

After Fang Yuan succeeded in refining nine eyes liquor worm, he was putting all his energy in cultivating.

Because Bai Ning Bing was continuously supplying him with yellow gold primeval essence, his cultivation speed accelerated and was quickly approaching rank four realm.

However, these days, Spring Autumn Cicada's recovery speed was also becoming faster and its pressure on Fang Yuan's rank three aperture had become more obvious.

On this day, Shang clan city welcomed the Auspicious Festival.

This was Shang clan's traditional festival, it was an important celebration that commemorated the ancestor, who founded Shang clan thousands of years ago, setting up a stall for the first time.

Shang clan's first ancestor was a legendary figure.

He was originally a mortal who lived in poverty and made a livelihood by trading. On one certain transaction, he unexpectedly obtained a Gu Master's inheritance token.

He relied on this token to inherit the legacy of the Gu Master and stepped into a whole new world. He moved forward steadily and step by step, his wealth and power expanded continuously until he finally founded Shang clan city.

Thus, on the day of the festival, Shang clan inner city was decorated with lanterns and colored banners. All large stores, brothels, restaurants and so on closed their business for the day. People were in a joyous mood and excitedly walked on the streets, setting up stalls. Men, women, old and young, all immersed in this lively atmosphere of the festival; on this day, buying and selling were treated as an interesting game.

However, the joyous atmosphere of the festival seemed to have no effect on Shang Xin Ci.

The young girl sat in front of a table with her beautiful brows in a slight frown as she looked at the several invitation cards on the table with melancholy.

These invitation cards all came from the nine young masters.

During Auspicious Festival, the young masters would hold grand banquets, inviting people of all sides and reward them.

"Big Brother Hei Tu, what should I do?" Shang Xin Ci was in a dilemma and subconsciously looked at Fang Yuan for guidance.

"Xin Ci, our sales have tripled your hundred thousand capital and you are now one of the most popular candidate to win the young master competition. They will naturally invite you to participate."

Fang Yuan smiled and continued: "However, we can only choose one of these nine invitations. On the surface, this looks like a joyous and harmonious banquet, but it is actually a political move to determine where you stand."

Fang Yuan explained the deep political meaning behind these invitations.

Shang clan only had ten young masters, there were alliance between these ten young masters and also internal conflicts.

Shang Xin Ci was competing for the young master position and was also one of the most popular candidates. Naturally, the nine young masters paid close attention to her. Shang Xin Ci had yet to become a young master but they were already trying to rope her in.

One had to make compromises in this world.

To be part of Shang clan's higher-up, one could not avoid being engulfed by the political whirlpool.

"Should I choose Shang Chi Wen's invitation? After all, she is in charge of battle stage and will be a great help to our later plans." Shang Xin Ci voiced out.

Fang Yuan shook his head: "It looks like there are nine invitations, but actually that is not the case. The biggest power among Shang clan young masters is Shang Qiu Niu who is the eldest son of the first wife and thus has the greatest advantage. Second faction is the alliance of Shang Pu Lao, Shang Suan Ni and Shang Bi Xi; this faction is currently in the limelight. Third faction is the alliance of Shang Chao Feng and Shang Fu Xi who are currently biding their time. Among the rest, Shang Chi Wen does not have any ambitions while Shang Pi Xiu is too playful..."

"Xin Ci, your foundation in Shang clan city is too weak. If you are going to choose, you need to choose between these three factions to make up for your weakness. As for Shang Chi Wen, there won't be much of a difference whether you choose her or not."

"So it was like this..." Shang Xin Ci's eyes brightened as she listened.

Hearing Fang Yuan's words, she felt like she had dispelled the fog around her and was looking at the clear sky.

The bewilderment she was feeling earlier was swept away. She thought a little and made her choice.

She chose the third faction, Shang Chao Feng's invitation.

"Among the three factions, the first and second faction are competing against each other; I will definitely be offending the other if I choose one of them. It is better to choose the third faction and enter this political whirlpool, but still stay out of it for the time being." Shang Xin Ci explained to Fang Yuan.

Shang Xin Ci immediately understood with her high intelligence.

Fang Yuan was happy at this but also felt a little irony.

In his previous life, Shang Chao Feng and Shang Xin Ci fought and contended for Shang clan leader's position. To think that in this life, these two arch-enemies would instead choose to walk together.

Chapter 327: Beautiful and Talented, Xin Ci’s Brilliance

"Little brother here toasts to big brother." Shang Yi Fan stood up and bent his back while raising a cup of wine with a smile.

There were splendid lights all over the hall; singing and dancing were being performed, and traditional music flowed to everyone's ears. Everyone was enjoying the feast and the atmosphere was intense.

"Good." Shang Qiu Niu was standing on the main seat. He raised a cup of wine towards Shang Yi Fan and downed the wine in one gulp.

Shang Qiu Niu's advisor spoke, "Master Yi Fan, choosing to participate in young master Qiu Niu's banquet is no doubt a sensible decision. Do not worry, my young master will not treat you unfairly."

"Eldest brother Qiu Niu has always been my role model. In truth, I have always been wanting to get closer to eldest brother and learn many things under you." Shang Yi Fan smiled.

Shang Qiu Niu was head of the first major faction among the current young masters and he happened to have deep relation with Shang Yi Fan's mother's side. If Shang Xin Ci chose Shang Qiu Niu's side, she was certain to be pushed aside by Shang Yi Fan.

However, Shang Qiu Niu had already taken the initiative to send an invitation to Shang Xin Ci.

He would definitely be happy if Shang Xin Ci came.

Why?

Because on Shang Xin Ci's side were Fang and Bai, two great rank four experts.

This was something no other young master had, and many were envious of this.

"Young master, subordinate has inquired, that Shang Xin Ci went to ..." At this moment, a Gu Master entered the hall and whispered to Shang Qiu Niu's ear with his waist bent.

Shang Qiu Niu's gaze turned slightly gloomy when he got the information.

Shang Yi Fan cautiously observed Shang Qiu Niu's expression and pondered, "Looks like Shang Xin Ci didn't choose eldest brother's faction, did she go to Shang Pu Lao's faction?"

Shang Qiu Niu had already experienced a lot of things, thus his feelings did not show clearly on his face. His expression also had no change, so Shang Yi Fan could only guess without any clues.

However, a short while later, Shang Yi Fan also received the news. Shang Xin Ci had accepted the invitation to participate in Shang Chao Feng's festival banquet.

This signified she chose Shang Chao Feng's faction.

Shang Yi Fan could not help but be secretly delighted immediately upon receiving the news, "Shang Chao Feng and Shang Fu Xi might be the third faction but they have been pressured from the start, how could they be Eldest Brother Qiu Niu's match? I have now even more chance to take the young master position!"

However, the old steward Zhang shook his head, his expression heavy, "Master, young master Qiu Niu's faction and young master Pu Lao's faction are locked in a fight. I am afraid the possibility of master borrowing the help of young master Qiu Niu to deal with Shang Xin Ci is not very big."

"This..."

"At this critical moment, young master Qiu Niu cannot afford to make another enemy. Shang Xin Ci's choice is clever. She has avoided the political whirlpool and managed to watch from the sidelines for the moment. By the time the two factions resolve their issues, the competition for the young master position will already be over."

"Shang Xin Ci has two great rank four experts, any faction she chooses will readily accept her and make an alliance. Young master Shang Chao Feng will definitely help her."

Old steward Zhang gave an incisive analysis of the situation.

"That is to say, even though I joined Shang Qiu Niu's faction, I still can't deal with Shang Xin Ci?" Shang Yi Fan's expression became unsightly.

"I can only say that we cannot borrow Shang Qiu Niu's strength." Old steward Zhang stroked his grizzled beard, " However, Shang Xin Ci's problem is also not small. The most important thing is that she still lacks capable manpower. I heard that she has been trying to recruit Zhou Quan. Hmph, how can that even be possible?"

Old steward sneered and continued, "Zhou Quan was once a clan leader; he is proud and arrogant, and his ability is ten times of mine. How would it be possible for such a man to attach himself to this inexperienced little girl? I have already secretly mobilized people to create all kinds of rumors and slanders. Zhou Quan cares for his reputation very much, and the rumors have already prevented him from joining Shang Xin Ci. Shang Xin Ci is trying to recruit Zhou Quan secretly, but by failing to do so, she will lose a lot of her prestige and will have a disadvantageous beginning; she might even become a laughing stock. Hehehe..."

When he reached the end of his words, steward Zhou started laughing evilly.

Shang Chao Feng's study was arranged in a simple fashion; there was a wide stone table and wide backed stone chairs which gave a boorish and strong aura.

Just as Shang Yi Fan and old steward Zhang were talking, Shang Chao Feng, Shang Xin Ci along with Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing were also discussing something.

This discussion had already continued on for a while.

In truth, Shang Chao Feng was somewhat surprised at Shang Xin Ci joining his side.

He had thought Shang Xin Ci would join Shang Qiu Niu or Shang Pu Lao. His own faction was only ranked third and they were currently just watching from the sidelines while accumulating their strength. In normal times, they were very low key and would choose to retreat when there were problems or contradictions. They had never thought they could obtain Shang Xin Ci's interest.

Shang Xin Ci's cultivation was only at rank one, while her aptitude was worse and she had almost no foundation in Shang clan city.

However, she had Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing.

These were two great rank four powers; even Shang Yan Fei when he was a young master, did not have such experts with him.

To be able to have two such experts under her, there were no young masters who did not feel envious.

Shang Chao Feng had also naturally sighed inwardly at Shang Xin Ci's luck.

Now, if he accepted Shang Xin Ci, he could indirectly obtain Fang and Bai's help. This was a temptation Shang Chao Feng could not refuse.

The atmosphere in the study was harmonious.

In the talk just earlier, Shang Chao Feng already sincerely expressed his intention to whole-heartedly support Shang Xin Ci in the young master competition.

"Sister Xin Ci, you have already earned three hundred thousand primeval stones from selling Gu worms. We can say that you are at the top currently, but just three hundred thousand is far from enough. What do you plan on doing next?"

Shang Chao Feng then added, "Just say it and I will help you to the best of my abilities."

Shang Xin Ci glanced at Fang Yuan; Fang Yuan faintly nodded his head.

She then said honestly, "I won't hide it from Big Brother Chao Feng, I am thinking of doing information-gathering business."

"Information-gathering business?" Shang Chao Feng could not help but raise his brows.

"Yes." Shang Xin Ci started to explain her plan in detail.

Who knew Shang Chao Feng's expression would change and shake his head after hearing it, "You want to do information-gathering business regarding the battle stage? It is not suitable, not suitable."

He said 'not suitable' twice, expressing his clear disagreement with Shang Xin Ci's plan.

"Ah, what could be wrong about it? Please teach me Big Brother Chao Feng," Shang Xin Ci said in a sincere voice.

"Xin Ci, I urge you to change this plan. You are a newcomer and so you aren't clear about it, it is understandable. You should not bump about with the battle stage randomly."

Shang Chao Feng heaved a sigh and continued, "Shang clan city's battle stage is different from other clans' battle stage. Here, demonic Gu Masters can become our Shang clan's external elders. This is a policy exclusive to our Shang clan and we have been able to obtain many talents from this. At present, there are five great elders in Shang clan, among which three are external elders."

"However, this policy has both advantage and disadvantage. The greater the benefits, the higher the chance of malpractice. External elders are the higher ups of our Shang clan, and if some trouble enters through it, it will be a great disaster to our Shang clan. Demonic Gu Masters are after all demonic Gu Masters, and even if they change and become righteous, their loyalty can still be questioned. At the same time, besides the demonic Gu Masters, there are also those righteous path clans with unfathomable motives. Thus, Shang clan's battle stage is the place which has always been attached with the most importance by Shang clan higher-ups."

"There was once a young master who suddenly got an inspiration to start a betting house for the battle stage's matches. The result was that he earned five hundred thousand primeval stones after just two days of opening the betting house. However, on the third day, the betting house was closed down and the young master was demoted and exiled. This is the best warning that shows that the battle stage cannot be touched randomly."

Shang Chao Feng spoke of a story only known to insiders.

This information was something Fang Yuan, Bai Ning Bing and Shang Xin Ci did not know.

Fang Yuan might have the memories of his previous life, but it was normal to not know of this small secret historical incident about the Shang clan's internal affairs, even more so when it was closed down so fast.

The battle stage was a forbidden zone. That young master touched this place and lost his young master position and was even exiled from the clan.

At present, Shang Xin Ci was still not a young master but had a plan towards the battle stage. This made Shang Chao Feng realize that ignorance was truly blissful.

"Xin Ci, your plan is a new approach and you have thought of it properly. If it is done, you will definitely make large amount of profits every day. However, the possibility is too low, don't take your own future prospects as a joke. I am in charge of the Gu battle zone and your thirteenth brother is in charge of the auction sites; you can lend us a hand in this field and will be able to go head to head against Shang Yi Fan." Shang Chao Feng gently persuaded.

Shang Xin Ci was silent.

Bai Ning Bing furrowed her brows.

The corner of Fang Yuan's lips curled up into a smile and he was about to speak, but after taking a glance at Shang Xin Ci, he changed his decision and swallowed up the words that were just about to come out of his throat.

For a moment, the atmosphere in the study room had become heavy.

After quite a while of intense pondering, Shang Xin Ci suddenly smiled: "Big Brother Chao Feng, I have a different viewpoint regarding the battle stage. This is well worth doing!"

"Huh?" Shang Chao Feng frowned and fixed his gaze at Shang Xin Ci.

Under the pressure from Shang Chao Feng's gaze, Shang Xin Ci instead smiled and showed her confident look.

She continued, "The young master before failed after opening the betting house, he was like a moth attracted to fire and was looking for his own doom. His punishment was only by being expelled from the clan; this can be considered merciful from our Shang clan. Why?"

In the study, only Shang Xin Ci's gentle voice continued to sound out.

"Like Big Brother Chao Feng said, our Shang clan's battle stage is of the highest importance and has been extremely guarded by the higher ups. Opening a betting house for battle stage to earn huge money will likely give rise to people who will manipulate the battle stage's result from behind the scenes. This will greatly wreck the Shang clan's external elder policy. It looks like one can make enormous profits from the betting house, but to the Shang clan's battle stage, it is a very large vermin. Sacrificing Shang clan's benefits to fill oneself, such actions definitely need to be eliminated and only then can it let the battle stage continue to mature."

Shang Chao Feng continuously nodded his head; Shang Xin Ci's words were incisive and had a type of aura that made people want to have faith in it.

"But the information business I want to do has a completely different nature from the betting house. I know Shang clan's biggest information organization Feng Yu manor has always been investigating into the demonic Gu Masters at the battle stage. They must investigate properly, to know whether these demonic Gu Masters harbor evil intentions. However, these investigation are done in secret and never openly. Why?"

"Hehe. This is because most of the demonic Gu Masters are filled with distrust, doubts and even are overly suspicious. They live in danger all year round in a situation where their life hangs on a thread, so the mental pressure on them is so great that they cannot even relax a bit. And if they were investigated after coming to Shang clan city, they would definitely react badly and be filled with hatred. If Shang clan wants to absorb even more and even better talents, they naturally can't investigate openly. However, not investigating is even more impossible and the clan cannot be at ease."

"In this situation, I am going to do information-gathering business. I am going to investigate every Gu Master's general strength, Gu worms and battle achievements, and sell this information. At the same time, I will be requesting experts and authority to forecast the results of important matches and make a ranking. This will be very important information to the Gu Masters participating in the battle stage. Many Gu Masters wish to obtain an external elder's position and they hope for more fame, and also wish to see their names on the rankings."

"These information will naturally not touch upon secret matters and will only be a summary and comparison of the strength showed by the Gu Masters. To demonic Gu Masters on the battle stage, this will be a great help. At the same time, this will allow the Shang clan to strengthen their grasp more on the battle stage. I think my lord father will definitely be happy about this, why would he suppress such a thing?"

Shang Xin Ci finished explaining her reason and looked at Shang Chao Feng with a smile.

At this moment, her eyes were burning bright with wisdom and confidence, displaying unlimited elegance.

Bai Ning Bing's brows had also smoothed out.

"This is it..." Fang Yuan inwardly smiled.

Shang Chao Feng slightly opened his mouth, looking at Shang Xin Ci with a stupefied expression.

After several seconds, he came back to his senses and could not help applauding and praising her, "Good point, your analysis is brilliant. Sister Xin Ci, you have a truly unique vision, a pure heart and spirit, I can't help but admire you. I will definitely help you with all my strength for this business. You lack manpower now, I can give you people from my side! You can have as many as you want!"

Shang Xin Ci shook her head, "Thank you Big Brother Chao Feng, but I have already made my choice regarding the manpower."

Shang Chao Feng looked like he wanted to help Shang Xin Ci on the surface by sending people, but actually, he wanted to place his own people to control this information-gathering business and also strengthen his control over Shang Xin Ci.

However, Shang Xin Ci immediately saw through it and tactfully refused.

Not all help comes with good intentions.

However, Shang Chao Feng was not willing to let it go; the information-gathering business he was avoiding so much earlier had become a rich treasure right now.

He continued to persuade: "Sister Xin Ci, I know you have been trying to recruit Zhou Quan recently, but this person is very proud and contemptuous. Shang Qiu Niu had personally tried to recruit him before, but was refused and was even reprimanded with the words: 'an inexperienced junior dares to recruit me, a hundred year old man?'."

Zhou Quan was now already over a hundred years old, and would not willingly submit to someone, especially a junior.

Shang Chao Feng was not optimistic about Shang Xin Ci recruiting Zhou Quan.

Zhou Quan had the ability and was also recognized for it, but he was too arrogant.

"Let's take a step back and say that you managed to recruit Zhou Quan. What can one man do? You still don't have middle and lower level subordinates. These people also must have some ability, most importantly they should be loyal to you. Establishing such force requires time, a long time. With subordinates that you don't feel at ease, even if you do this information-gathering business, it might very well be destroyed by Shang Yi Fan and he can even steal your gains." Shang Chao Feng might have his own intentions but his words were very reasonable.

Shang Xin Ci's beautiful brows could not help but furrow when she heard it.

"Regarding this... young master Chao Feng does not need to worry. I already have a plan." At this time, Fang Yuan suddenly spoke.

Chapter 328: Eating will be eating

"Is that so." Shang Chao Feng replied curtly.

Fang Yuan had personally rejected his proposal for Shang Xin Ci, he could not force them.

Fang Yuan had defeated Ju Kai Bei, had rank three peak stage cultivation but his actual fighting strength was rank four. At the same time he had the purple thorn token, and was an esteemed guest in Shang clan. Because of all these, Shang Chao Feng had already been showing goodwill towards Fang and Bai.

But he was scoffing in his heart.

"Hmph, trying to establish a force. It needs time, how can they succeed instantly? Nevermind, I'll let you guys learn from mistakes. When you fail, I will come out and help you, I would be able to earn more then." Shang Chao Feng contemplated, but he still smiled warmly.

The two discussed for a while more, before Shang Chao Feng sent Shang Xin Ci and the others personally to the exit.

To outsiders, this was an obvious political signal.

After saying bye to Shang Chao Feng, Shang, Fang, and Bai walked onto the streets.

Today was the Auspicious Festival, most of the shops were closed, and two rows small temporary stalls were on the two sides of the road.

"Come, come, come, sour and sweet candied fruits!"

"Let me tell you, this old jade was passed down by my ancestors..."

"Selling rice, selling rice, a bag of five fragrance oil rice for half a primeval stone."

The small stalls were situated one after another, selling all sorts of things. The two rows spread out as far as the eye could see, as people squeezed about as they tried to buy things, while others watched in a circle, some were bargaining and some were looking around.

The Auspicious Festival was held once a year, be it Fang Yuan, Bai Ning Bing or Shang Xin Ci, they were not foreign to it.

"Counting the days, we have already been in Shang clan city for nearly three years." Shang Xin Ci suddenly said in an emotional tone.

"Too many things had happened in the last few years." She sighed, continuing: "If it was before, I would never have guessed I would be Shang clan leader's daughter."

Next, Shang Xin Ci looked at Fang Yuan, smiling slightly, showing her pure white teeth: "If it was not for Brother Hei Tu, I would not have made it this far."

Towards Fang and Bai, Shang Xin Ci always felt extremely grateful to them.

Bai Ning Bing looked speechlessly, the corner of her eyes twitching.

"Indeed, I did not think your father would be the famous Shang Yan Fei! But, it was fate that I saved you. People come and go, that is natural in this world." Fang Yuan looked ahead as he answered.

Shang Xin Ci's expression changed, she understood what he meant: "Brother Hei Tu, you are going to leave Shang clan city?"

"That's right. Soon, I will have to leave Shang clan city with Bai Ning Bing, heading towards San Cha mountain." Fang Yuan said.

Shang Xin Ci gritted her teeth, she wanted to tell him to stay, but she did not say it in the end.

She had spent a lot of time with Fang Yuan, although they never talked about it, she could feel the ambitions in his heart.

This man's ambition was too great, a place like Shang clan city could not hold him.

"But there is no need to worry. Before I leave, I will make you a young master, and make sure you sit there securely." Fang Yuan laughed: "Let's go, I'll bring you to recruit some subordinates. Today, let's complete the foundation for your future force."

"What, brother Hei Tu, you have ideal candidates already?" Shang Xin Ci asked in surprise.

Organising a force takes a very long time.

It takes years of nurturing to obtain loyal subordinates.

Fang Yuan's tone made Shang Xin Ci feel that loyal and capable subordinates were like cabbage, easily found in the market.

On what basis was he so confident and assured?

Not just Shang Xin Ci, even Bai Ning Bing was curious.

"Just follow me." Fang Yuan walked ahead, leading the way.

After many twists and turns, they finally arrived at a small alley.

In the middle of a lantern shop and silk shop, there was a small stall.

Fang Yuan walked towards the front of this stall.

Behind the stall, there was a young man lying down.

This young man wore tattered clothes as he leaned on the wall, his eyes half-closed, in a dazed expression as his complexion was poor. He looked like he was drunk, and had completely given up on life.

"Is this young man the person brother Hei Tu is looking for?" Shang Xin Ci analyzed.

Bai Ning Bing used her sharp instincts to assess this man. Although he was a Gu Master, he only had rank one middle stage cultivation, from his appearance, he was not young already, but only had this cultivation, it was pathetic.

"Hi brother, what do you want to buy... oh, Lord Fang Zheng!" The young man sensed people and opened his eyes, but halfway through his words, he showed shock and fluster.

Fang Yuan was now a famous person in Shang clan city, without concealing his appearance, many people could recognise him.

"Lord Bai... Bai Ning Bing." Immediately after, he recognised Bai Ning Bing, and he stammered.

Although he did not know Shang Xin Ci, from her Gu Master aura and her beautiful appearance, he felt dazed.

"This is ten primeval stones, I am buying everything here, you can leave now." Fang Yuan tossed a bag of primeval stones.

The young man's face showed joy and exhilaration.

But next, he was slightly hesitant.

The stuff he was selling here were the things his grandfather left behind. From his appraisal, all these were scrap and trash, there was nothing valuable.

But why, why did Lord Fang Zheng want to buy them? Was there really a treasure among them?

If there were treasures, would it not be a loss if he sold them?

Just when he was still pondering, Fang Yuan already tossed the primeval stones to him.

"What are you thinking about? You didn't listen to what I said? Hmph, it is your honor that I wanted to buy these. You can scram now, if you don't, you will not have the chance to leave this place." Fang Yuan threatened.

The young man was scared until he trembled.

He stammered as he shivered: "Lord... Lord Fang Zheng, you cannot do this. In business, we emphasize on will... willingness. You cannot forcefully buy them like this, you are someone with great reputation... and this is Shang clan city..."

Smack.

Fang Yuan gave him a tight slap and this young man fell on the ground.

"Scram." Fang Yuan declared, using an icy gaze to look at this young man, speaking emotionlessly.

The young man held his face as he trembled under the great fear. He raised his head to look at Fang Yuan, but immediately looked away when he made contact with the abyss-like pupils. He fumbled his way out of the alley silently immediately after.

"Brother Hei Tu..." Shang Xin Ci looked at his background, her conscience unable to stand it.

Bai Ning Bing was expressionless, completely unmoved.

"Xin Ci, I am a demonic Gu Master, I have my ways of doing things, I emphasize on straightforwardness." Fang Yuan explained casually in a righteous tone.

The surrounding stall owners looked towards him.

He gave a sweeping glance, and everyone looked away, afraid to make eye contact.

If it was Fang Yuan in the past, he would have to control himself and use coaxing, lying methods to buy the item in the stall peacefully.

But now, his strength had surged, and his status was much higher, thus he can use the most direct method. It saves energy and time, why not do this?

People from the righteous path loved their reputation, and liked showing off their 'kindness', often doing good deeds for the weak.

But Fang Yuan was not righteous, he was from the demonic path.

Since ancient times, big fish eats small fish, small fish eats shrimps, this was the law of the jungle, the survival of the fittest.

Demonic cultivators were used to tearing apart flesh and blood, devouring them whole. Righteous cultivators however, will shed crocodile tears while they ate, claiming that they had no choice.

Many stupid people will fall for their deception. Or maybe they were lying to themselves, unwilling to accept the cruel reality.

Hehe.

The truth is, eating will be eating.

Usurper eats the usurped, invader eats the invaded, the strong eats the weak, the suppressor eats the suppressed, the higher-ups eat the lower levels...

All livings beings eat, if not, they would not survive. It is just that they have different eating habits.

Fang Yuan chased that stall owner away and lowered his body, picking a token from among the items in the stall.

This token was made of black steel, ugly and dirty, with half a piece remaining. There were words carved on it but after so long, and without the other half of its body, the words could not be discerned.

But Fang Yuan knew this word was 'Fan'.

Three hundred years ago, a demonic Gu Master was heavily injured and fell into the water, eventually saved by a young lady who was at the river.

The young girl was very kind, after saving the demonic Gu Master, she placed him in the shed and gave him food to eat daily.

After the demonic Gu Master recovered, to thank her kindness, he made a black steel token, carving a 'Fan' word.

He split the token into two, giving half to the girl while keeping the other half himself.

Before the demonic Gu Master left, he instructed the girl: In future, if you have any difficulties, you can go the Dan Huo mountain's Gui Ku cave, and find me for help. Even after you pass away, this promise will still be effective to the future owner of the half-token.

The young girl engraved his words into her heart, but after less than fifty years, there was a huge battle on Dan Huo mountain, and the volcano erupted, destroying Gui Ku cave. That demonic Gu Master was captured by Tie clan and thrown into the demon suppression tower.

This half-token lost its use after that. It was passed around by the young girl's descendants.

Because it involved the demonic path, when the young girl died of old age, she did not reveal the secret to her children, bringing this information to her grave.

The young girl's descendants were chased away by the clan, and eventually settled down in Shang clan city, as the lineage declined. Descendants were untalented and unfilial, after several generations, only this young man remained.

This young man was spoiled from young, having a 'young master' temper, and loved to gamble, drink, and visit prostitutes. After his parents died, he would rely on selling his family assets from time to time to survive.

But one time, during the auspicious market festival, his life changed.

Three brothers who were demonic Gu Masters came here to shop, and accidentally found the half-token displayed in the stall.

Chapter 329: Three brothers of Xiong clan

The three instantly became overjoyed, taking out the other half of the token and formed the whole token on the spot.

So it turns out, the demonic Gu Master back then had his descendants too. Before he was arrested by Tie clan, he instructed his descendants, to remember this incident and, if possible in the future, repay that kindness.

The three brothers were descendants of this demonic Gu Master, after seeing this token, they immediately explained the matter to this young stall owner, asking him if he needed any help; they would do their best to assist him.

This young man was very crafty.

He immediately replied, he lacked three subordinates and there was nobody around to help him.

The three brothers glanced at each other, before kneeling down together, promising that they would serve the young man for twenty years.

They would listen to all of his orders for twenty years, but after that, they would be free.

These three brothers were famous in the battle stage, they each had rank three cultivation, and were most skilled in multi battles.

The young man relied on the strength of the three brothers, living the next twenty years in luxury. During the period, he asked the three brothers to get food, water, primeval stones for him, and they acceded to all of his requests.

But after twenty years, the three brothers repaid the favor and left. He had long forgotten how to work, and was too ashamed to beg, in fact, he did not even restrain himself, continuing to live like a king. Less than half a month later, he died.

Of course, all these happened in Fang Yuan's previous life.

At the moment, the three demonic Gu masters have not found the half-token yet. And this token was already in Fang Yuan's hands. As for that young man, who cares if he dies?

According to his memories, this half-token would only be discovered by the three demonic Gu Master brothers next year.

But now that Fang Yuan held the half-token, he brought Bai Ning Bing and Shang Xin Ci to find them directly.

The three brothers also opened a stall before their home, enjoying the festive mood and were having fun.

"Ah? It is Lord Fang Zheng! And Lord Bai Ning Bing." Seeing Fang and Bai, the three quickly got up.

They had all been thrashed by Fang Yuan or Bai Ning Bing before in the battle stage.

In this world, strength was everything, even more so for demonic Gu Masters. Bai Ning Bing had rank four cultivation, while Fang Yuan defeated Ju Kai Bei, there was no demonic Gu Master who did not respect the two.

"I am here today to find the three of you." Fang Yuan observed the three brothers emotionlessly.

These three brothers all had the surname Xiong.

The eldest was called Xiong Tu, shortest among the three, humble and honest. He was an earth path rank three upper stage Gu Master.

Second was Xiong Huo, wearing a sleeveless shirt and shorts, his body was bright red. He was a fire path rank three middle stage Gu Master.

The youngest was Xiong Feng, wearing a bamboo hat, having sharp tiny eyes, and enjoys squinting when he looks at people. He was a wind path rank three initial stage Gu Master.

Hearing Fang Yuan's words, the three brothers became uneasy.

Xiong Tu quickly cupped his fist, greeting Fang Yuan: "Lord Fang Zheng, may I know what is the issue? If my brothers had offended you unknowingly, I apologise to you here."

Fang Yuan frowned slightly: "I'm sure you've heard, I had given up on the battle stage to assist Shang Xin Ci in becoming a young master. We are lacking manpower over here, I want all three of you to join us."

"This..." The three Xiong clan brothers frowned.

They came to Shang clan city and entered the battle stage for only one reason: to become Shang clan's external elder.

But now that Fang Yuan wanted them to assist Shang Xin Ci, it was very different from their goals. Shang Xin Ci was just an inexperienced girl, and only had rank one cultivation with poor aptitude. The three of them all had B grade aptitude, and their combination strike could temporarily match a rank four Gu Master.

Asking them to go under Shang Xin Ci and be her subordinate, the three brothers were unwilling.

If others said this, the three brothers would have attacked already, beating the guy to a pulp. But it was Fang Yuan who said it, causing the three to be in a difficult position.

Fang Yuan had defeated Ju Kai Bei in a battle, they had watched it personally, even if they joined forces, they could not defeat Fang Yuan.

"Fang Zheng is here with ill-intention."

"He is obviously trying to forcefully subdue us!"

"Sigh, what bad luck to have been targeted by Fang Zheng. All three of us cannot defeat him, and he even has Bai Ning Bing beside him. Moreover, the purple thorn token..."

The three brothers looked at each other, knowing each other's emotions. The three of them were unwilling, but circumstances forced their hand, they could only choose to give in.

But Fang Yuan suddenly said: "I do not wish to force you, come if you are willing to, if not, I will not force you."

The three brothers glanced at each other, unsure if Fang Yuan was speaking the truth, or just trying to act graceful.

But Xiong Feng who was the youngest, was the most daring, as he said carefully: "Lord Fang Zheng, to speak the truth, we are used to freedom. We do not want to be involved in Shang clan's young master competition. Thus, thus..."

The other two smiled meekly, as they bowed towards Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing apologetically.

"Oh?" Fang Yuan's brows raised, as a cold light shot out of his eyes: "The three of you are really daring, you dare to reject my invitation?"

The three brothers' heart thumped.

Xiong Tu quickly cupped his fists, explaining in a hurry: "That is not the case, that is not the case. Lord Fang Zheng, please do not misunderstand, it is our honor to have received your invitation. My brother was too nervous, he did not know what he was saying. Actually what he wanted to say was, we would be glad to go under Lady Shang Xin Ci's wing."

"Yes, yes, that was what I meant." Xiong Feng continued.

"Hehe, in that case, I am assured. The three of you are so eager, Xin Ci, accept them." Fang Yuan turned around, saying to Shang Xin Ci.

Beside him, Bai Ning Bing frowned. Forcing them to join like this, he would not get their loyalty, such a distant subordinate, what use would it be?

Shang Xin Ci had the same worry, but she still chose to believe Fang Yuan. She took a step forward, saying to the three brothers: "From now on, please work hard."

"Yes."

"The three brothers of Xiong clan pays respect to Lady Xin Ci."

The three cupped their fists and bowed, replying listlessly.

"Hahaha..." Fang Yuan raised his head and laughed.

The three brothers thought: This Fang Zheng is too despicable, leading the life of a whore but still expecting a monument praising chastity[1]. Speaking in a righteous manner but acting like a despicable crook.

"That's right, I forgot something, take a good look." Fang Yuan stopped laughing, and took out a half-token, tossing it to Xiong Tu.

Xiong Tu caught it subconsciously.

"What is this?" The other two brothers glanced curiously.

But immediately, the three brothers were stunned.

"This, this is?!" The calm and stable Xiong Tu cried out.

Xiong Huo grabbed the token, inspecting it closely.

Xiong Feng also understood what happened, as he urged his brother Xiong Tu: "Brother, quickly take out our token."

Under Bai Ning Bing and Shang Xin Ci's weird gaze, Xiong Tu took out the other half of the token.

The two half-tokens perfectly fit into one, and a illusionary fire started to burn on the token.

"This, this is real!" Xiong clan's three brothers stared with wide-opened eyes.

Xiong Tu held the token with shivering arms.

"What is going on?" Bai Ning Bing and Shang Xin Ci had no clue what was happening.

"The three brothers of Xiong clan, did you really think I came here without a reason? Why are you hesitating?" Fang Yuan spoke at an appropriate moment.

His words woke them up.

"Grandfather once said, no matter who the token's owner was, even if it was an enemy, we have to repay the kindness from back then!"

"That's right, although grandfather is trapped, we cannot ruin his reputation."

"From now on, Lady Shang Xin Ci is our new master. But, only for twenty years. Twenty years is sufficient to repay the debt."

The three brothers discussed among themselves quickly.

Next, all three of them kneeled on one knee in front of Shang Xin Ci, cupping their fists.

"Xiong Tu, Xiong Huo, Xiong Feng, the three brothers greets Lady Xin Ci!" They shouted loudly, with a different tone from before, filled with drive and excitement.

"Brother Hei Tu, what is happening?" Shang Xin Ci found out that they were sincerely joining her, and felt extremely curious.

Fang Yuan snickered: "It is a long story. We will talk about it next time, now, let's go recruit some more members."

The gang of six arrived at the slave market.

In the world, there was slave trade. Any strong or affluent first-class clan, or super clan, would engage in slave business.

Shang clan's slave trade was handled by the head of the five clan elders, Shang Bu Li personally.

Slave trade was too profitable, the higher-ups were not confident of letting an external elder handle it. In history, only Shang clansmen were in charge of it.

Fang Yuan had planned early on, and investigated clearly. He walked ahead, leading the way, quickly arriving at a cage.

Within the cage, there were many people.

"Lady Xin Ci, Lord Fang Zheng, Lord Bai Ning Bing, are you here to purchase slaves? If that is the case, I do not advise you to buy the people inside this cage." A Gu master in charge of handling business quickly came over.

"Oh? What is that so?" Shang Xin Ci asked.

"Lady Xin Ci does not know, these people are from Wei clan. Wei clan had a political uprising some time ago, and Wei clan leader was overthrown by his younger brother. The people inside this cage are from the previous clan leader's faction. They are being sold now by the current Wei clan leader." The Gu Master answered.

Xin Ci immediately understood why he advised them not to buy these slaves.

Wei clan was a first-class clan. Although it was smaller than Shang clan, it was still a famous clan in the southern border.

Wei clan's political turbulence was said to be supported by Shang Yan Fei. The current Wei clan leader even sent the clansmen to Shang clan as hostage. Many Wei clan elders also secretly transferred their assets to Shang clan.

Wei clan could be said to be Shang clan's puppet already.

For Shang Xin Ci who was competing to become Shang clan young master, these people were trouble.

But Fang Yuan quickly said: "We are buying these people."

[1] Chinese idiom which means: "Doing bad deeds but still expecting good reputation and praise" Back

Chapter 330: Wei De Xin

"This... Lord Fang Zheng, are you certain on buying them?" The Gu Master in charge hesitated.

"Why, are you doubting my decision?" Fang Yuan gave him a plain glance.

This Gu Master laughed, he was a Shang clansmen, he was not afraid of Fang Yuan like the Xiong clan brothers.

"I wouldn't dare, I wouldn't dare." He cupped his fists, turning to Shang Xin Ci: "If I am not wrong, Lord Fang is buying these slaves to act as subordinates for Lady Xin Ci. But they are really bad news for those competing for the young master position. Lady Xin Ci, you are so intelligent, what do you think?"

Shang Xin Ci's eyes were focused on Fang Yuan, she smiled and replied : "Brother Hei Tu's decision is my decision. Just do as he says."

"Is that so." The Gu Master in charge was stunned, before smiling: "Since Lady Xin Ci says so, I will do so accordingly. To speak the truth, I am your supporter Lady Xin Ci..."

"You are speaking too much." Fang Yuan gave the Gu Master a cold stare, interrupting him coldly.

"Hehe." The Gu Master laughed: "Then I shall settle the procedures for you, but there are too many people, there will be a lot of procedures to go through, you need to wait a day. A day later..."

Bam!

Fang Yuan raised his leg and kicked.

That Gu Master did not expect Fang Yuan to strike, and was caught off guard and hit on the stomach.

Flying over thirty steps away, he knocked onto a bystander and landed on the ground, falling unconscious after vomiting blood.

"Who dares to fight in Shang clan city?"

"Are you tired of living?!"

"Quickly surrender yourself!"

Such commotion immediately attracted attention. The slave market was heavily guarded in the first place, quickly, three groups of Gu Masters came and surrounded them.

"It was me." Fang Yuan had no fear, standing up.

"It's Fang Zheng!" The riled up group saw Fang Yuan and immediately lost their vigor.

Fang Yuan had rank four battle strength, they were only rank two and their leader who had the highest cultivation was rank three initial stage. They could not even be side dishes for Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan stood on the spot and took out his purple thorn token.

The Shang clan Gu Masters saw the token and their aura diminished once more.

The leader's fierce and terrifying face quickly changed, as he smiled and politely said to Fang Yuan: "Lord Fang Zheng, we all know you are Shang clan's esteemed guest. But even a guest cannot resort to force in Shang clan, you even injured our clansmen. According to the rules..."

"According to the rules, I will be fined forty-nine primeval stones." Fang Yuan immediately said.

The leader was shocked, not expecting Fang Yuan to be so well-versed with Shang clan's rules.

Fang Yuan tossed out a bag of primeval stones, waving his hand: "There are fifty primeval stones inside, keep the change."

The leader received the primeval stones, feeling like a beggar. He had a shocked and dazed expression as he left with the others.

If Fang Yuan did not have strength, even with the purple thorn token, he would not have gotten out of it so easily. But now that he was strong, even in Shang clan city, if he beat up a Shang clansmen, as long as it was not someone important, there would be no consequences.

The Gu Master in charge was beaten unconscious by Fang Yuan, the slave market quickly sent out another Gu Master to attend to them.

We are buying everyone in this cage." Fang Yuan pointed at the cage and said.

Inside the cage, the people looked at Fang Yuan; most of them had a dazed or numb expression, but a few stared at him in rage.

Fang Yuan's casual attitude of purchasing made them feel extremely humiliated.

"Yes, yes, yes." The new Gu Master wiped his sweat as he attended to Fang Yuan politely.

In less than fifteen minutes, all the procedures were done.

"This is the rank three poison scorpion Gu, please keep it well Lord Fang Zheng." Lastly, the Gu Master handed Fang Yuan a Gu worm.

This poison scorpion Gu had a white body, like a flawless porcelain, and was the size of two fingers.

This was a rank three Gu, with only one ability: defecating.

The scorpion faeces it produced was black as bean, it was a rank two Gu.

The saying goes: Scorpion faeces are one in the world.

This scorpion faeces Gu, each one had a unique poison. Once used on someone, they needed the corresponding poison scorpion Gu to detoxify them once every seven days.

This was the most common method to control slaves.

Although there is also the slavery Gu, with better effect, but it was rank five. It was expensive and rare, it could not be commonly used.

Poison scorpion Gu, although Shang Xin Ci could not activate it, and could not make it defecate, she could make it sting someone without using any primeval essence.

Fang Yuan planned to first refine this poison scorpion Gu before passing it to Shang Xin Ci and letting her refine it; it was too difficult to let her do it herself.

...

"What did you say? Someone bought those Wei clan slaves? What did I instruct you, I told you to pay attention to them. Wait a few days for me to settle it out with Shang Qiu Niu, and buy them after the situation calms down!" In the study room, Shang Pu Lao had an ugly expression as he scolded the Gu Master in charge.

The Gu Master in charge was lying on a bed with a pale expression.

After being kicked by Fang Yuan, he had just woken up when Shang Pu Lao came to question him.

"Young master Pu Lao, I tried my best already. I wanted to sow discord among them, but that Shang Xin Ci listened to Fang Zheng like a lamb. I tried stalling but before I finished my words, Fang Yuan sent me flying and knocked me unconscious." The Gu Master in charge listlessly explained as he laid in bed.

"Sigh... these Wei clansmen were once authoritative figures, controlling Wei clan's operation. They have high cultivation and experience in management. If I can get them, I can create half a Wei clan myself. Among them, Wei clan's first lady Wei De Xin is most skilled at nurturing guards. Wei clan leader's guard troops had once been famous, successfully blocking many assassination attempts, even blocking the attack of five rank three Gu Masters at once. If not for that internal crisis, how could they fall apart so easily?"

Shang Pu Lao heaved a long sigh.

"I am asking you now, can the situation be salvaged?" He stared sharply at the Gu Master in charge.

The Gu Master shook his head, explaining in a crying tone: "They were all brought away already, the entire procedure was proper and there were no problems at all. Young master, I have failed you."

"Nevermind, have a good rest." Shang Pu Lao heard this and lost his interest all together, giving a word of consolation before taking his head.

Morning of the next day.

In Nan Qiu garden's residential square, over thirty members of Wei clan stood.

Fang Yuan and Shang Xin Ci came together.

Earlier, Fang Yuan had helped Shang Xin Ci to refine the poison scorpion Gu. A rank three Gu was still too strong for her, thus, Fang Yuan chose some other Gu worms to assist her in controlling the poison scorpion Gu.

"From today onwards, Shang Xin Ci is your new master, why are you not greeting her?" Fang Yuan handed the poison scorpion Gu to her in front of them.

Wei clansmen slowly kneeled on the floor, paying respects to Shang Xin Ci. Their voices were listless, filled with helplessness and numbness, they were all behaving like puppets.

They were banished from the clan, all these authoritative figures who lived a good life had become slaves. Their dejected and low-spirited behavior was completely natural.

Looking at these people, how could anyone feel assured using them?

Shang Xin Ci felt pity for them, but also worry for herself.

"Wei De Xin, come out. I want to have a private talk with you." Fang Yuan stretched out his arm, pointing at one of the women.

They suddenly became energetic, as many of their dazes expressions became fierce and strong.

"What do you want?" Many people moved their bodies, shielding Wei De Xin.

"I am warning you, do not lay a finger on her." One of them pointed his finger at Fang Yuan, showing great alertness.

Smack!

Fang Yuan's expression turned dark, as he took a few steps forward and gave a slap.

The person who pointed at him was sent flying by an overwhelming force. His mouth was full of blood as his broken teeth fell on the ground.

"It seems you are not clear of reality yet. Although I spent a lot of money to buy all of you, I am not against killing some of you for fun. So what if I want to do anything to your clan leader's wife, what can you do to stop me?" Fang Yuan had a cruel expression and his voice was like cold as ice.

"You..." Wei clan's gang were outraged, some youngsters clenched their fists, but they did not dare to speak out again.

"All of you stand down." Wei De Xin made them stand aside as she walked out.

Although her face was filthy, it could not hide her beautiful peach-like appearance.

She bowed to Fang Yuan: "What does Lord Fang Zheng need from this lowly servant?"

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, using a fierce gaze to inspect her body: "Lady Wei, you speak too much. Just follow me and obey what I say."

Saying so, he turned around.

As meat on the chopping block, Wei De Xin was helpless too, she gritted her teeth and followed Fang Yuan to the lake pavilion.

A cool breeze blew, causing ripples on the surface of the lake. Carp swam in the lake, and lotus leaves filled the surface of the water, with red and white flower buds within the leaves.

Such beautiful scenery caused Wei De Xin to relax slightly.

But Fang Yuan's next sentence made her nervous. He said: "Lady Wei, I am very interested in you."

Wei De Xin quickly kneeled on the ground: "This servant is lowly, it is my great honor that my appearance had attracted Lord Fang Zheng's attention. But I do not dare to offer my soiled body to lord's grand and masculine body."

"Hahaha." Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "Wei De Xin, don't be mistaken. I am very interested in your talent, your body and appearance is just a pair of skeleton in my eyes. Next, I want you to nurture a group of loyal female guards for Shang Xin Ci. At the same time, you have to motivate your Wei clansmen properly, tell them to work hard and have a positive attitude."

Hearing fang Yuan say so, Wei De Xin breathed a sigh of relief, as she promised: "Yes, this servant will follow Lord's orders."

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan laughed deeply again, saying with deep meaning: "Lady Wei, I know you are pregnant, and I know your intentions. You want to preserve your husband's only bloodline, and at the same time contact your younger brother Wei Shen Jing to exact revenge for you, am I right?"

As he said so, Wei De Xin's face went pale as her delicate body shuddered.

Chapter 331: Advancement to Rank Four

Wei De Xin knew she was pregnant from her own recent bodily reactions.

The new life in her womb gave her great hope.

This was her greatest secret and she had never expected that just a few days later, an outsider would expose it directly.

How could this not shock her, how could she not panic?

In Fang Yuan's previous life, it was Wei De Xin who helped Shang Pu Lao to win against Shang Qiu Niu and become the most popular candidate for young clan leader's position at one time.

However, in the great battle between righteous and demonic, Wei De Xin and Wei Shen Jing secretly contacted each other, and helped Wu clan to scheme against Shang clan; eradicating Wei clan in one fell swoop and taking revenge for the murder of her husband. After this was revealed, Wei De Xin gained fame for being the first person to make Shang Yan Fei suffer a loss.

Shang Pu Lao was thus implicated and banished from the clan, having a miserable end. One could say both his success and defeat were due to Wei De Xin.

Wei De Xin's talent was outstanding and had now fallen into Fang Yuan's hand. Controlling her and making her work for Shang Xin Ci was not a difficult thing for Fang Yuan.

"Wei De Xin, you don't need to be afraid. As long as you do your best to help Shang Xin Ci, I won't do anything to you. I might even help you raise the child in your womb properly. Also, I advise you to not go searching for your younger brother Wei Shen Jing for some time. He has already been recruited by Wu clan now and is being monitored all the time. If you don't believe me, you are welcomed to find out for yourself."

Fang Yuan stroked his fingers, he was sitting on the stone chair with his back straight, and his tone gave a feeling that everything was in the palm of his hand.

Wei De Xin was completely dominated by his attitude.

The expression on her face as she kneeled on the ground, changed. She opened her mouth several times as if to say something, but finally chose to keep quiet.

In the end, she deeply bowed her head towards Fang Yuan, her forehead touched the ground and she spoke in a respectful tone: "I..."

However, she had just opened her mouth when she was interrupted by Fang Yuan: "No need to say anything else, there is no point. You and your clansmen's performance will be the best answer. You can leave now."

Fang Yuan waved his hand.

Wei De Xin could only leave.

Fang Yuan sat inside the pavillion without getting up for some time.

He watched Wei De Xin's figure as it gradually vanished within the rows of green trees. He knew that after this talk, she would assist Shang Xin Ci with all her strength.

After all, in his previous life, Shang Pu Lao also took advantage of the child in her womb to entice her into fully helping him.

Cold wind blew. Fang Yuan gazed at the lake surface. The shimmering lake was reflected in his abyss-like dark eyes.

He was silent.

"Now, Shang Xin Ci has the Wei clansmen to act as her middle and lower foundation. With Wei De Xin, she can organize female guards and form a powerful and stable armed force. There are also the three Xiong brothers who will be her generals. And she has her personal servant Xiao Die and Xiao Lan as trustworthy assistants ."

"With this, the general framework of her force has been constructed. It is enough to deal with this young master competition. But if we can recruit Zhou Quan and make him the steward, this young master's position will definitely be in the bag! Wei De Xin, Xiong clan's three brothers, Xiao Die, Xiao Lan are all generals while Zhou Quan will be the commander."

Fang Yuan was very clear that with the help of Zhou Quan who had plentiful experience and outstanding talent, Shang Xin Ci would definitely win the young master's position and it would even be more stable. Even if Shang Xin Ci did not work hard, with Zhou Quan's help, her forces would become firmer and slowly increase to an enormous size.

Only Zhou Quan could keep these subordinates of Shang Xin Ci under check.

Right now, Shang Xin Ci could not awe these talents. After all, she was still too young, her aptitude was not high and her cultivation was not enough.

In the Gu Master world, rules are cruel and real, the first thing one looks at is strength. The rest are supplementary.

However, subduing Zhou Quan will not be so easy. Especially now that the rumors of Shang Xin Ci's failure in recruiting Zhou Quan over a dozen times had spread and were given a vivid description.

Fang Yuan knew someone was secretly doing this to cause trouble and strike at Shang Xin Ci's reputation.

But although Fang Yuan knew it, he did not stop it.

The timing was still not ripe yet and he already had a plan.

Several days later, at night, in a secret room of Nan Qiu garden.

Swish swish swish...

Waves surged in the aperture and thousands of white silver snowflakes swirled up.

Under Fang Yuan's will, the peak stage rank three primeval essence rushed at the aperture walls.

Like the prancing of ten thousand beasts or the movement of the galaxy, the ninety percent primeval sea swept through everything with a force majestic and boundless, far above middle and lower grade aptitudes.

Primeval essence continuously cleansed the aperture walls.

The cleansing slowly and quietly caused a hidden change in Fang Yuan's aperture walls.

When this change accumulates to a certain degree, it would cause a qualitative transformation and cause his cultivation to breakthrough rapidly to another realm.

This realm was rank four!

Fang Yuan used relic Gu to advance to rank three peak stage. And then with the help of Bai Ning Bing and bone flesh unity Gu, his cultivation had been making rapid progress. Every day, he made such progress that it was beyond normal people's imagination.

"Rank four, I am only a step away..." This sensation was becoming more and more intense in Fang Yuan's heart.

However, the surface of the primeval sea continued to decrease.

Snow silver primeval essence violently attacked the borders of rank four realm, consuming huge amounts of primeval essence. Ninety percent primeval sea was of no help and the aperture walls were already cleansed to sparkling pure, but there was no change.

Although rank four was only a step away, this step was like a deep gully which was very difficult to cross.

No one knew how many Gu Masters were stumped at the border between rank three and rank four and how many grand ambitions were stifled.

As Fang Yuan looked at the empty aperture, right at that instance, a stream of yellow gold waterfall fell down from the aperture.

This came from outside world; it was reinforcements by Bai Ning Bing through bone flesh unity Gu!

Although it was only rank four initial stage light gold primeval essence, but the moment it appeared, Fang Yuan's aperture trembled.

Under Fang Yuan's will, the waterfall-like primeval essence turned into a tidal wave and charged towards the aperture walls, following the steps of the snow silver primeval essence.

All the accumulation before this burst out at this moment!

Crack.

Following a soft sound, tiny cracks started to appear on the aperture walls.

Dazzling white light burst out of the cracks.

The cracks continued to enlarge and the crystal walls started to collapse like the collapse of an iceberg; pieces started falling towards the bottom of the primeval sea and turned into nothingness.

Two whole hours later, under Bai Ning Bing's unceasing support of primeval essence, this transformation ended.

The crystal walls were no more to be seen, replaced by a layer of thin light membrane. However, this white light was even more dazzling and shone upon the whole aperture.

A drop of light gold primeval essence floated up from the bottom of the sea.

Yellow gold primeval essence!

Fang Yuan advanced into rank four realm!

"I have finally reached rank four! With just two to three years in Shang clan city, I made such huge progress." Fang Yuan slowly opened his eyes; bright, sharp light flashed through them and drew a ray of lightning through the dark secret room.

He was pleased with this result.

To be able to advance to rank four using a short period of two to three years, he had to first give credit to bone flesh unity Gu, Bai Ning Bing and then the favorable environment of Shang clan city.

At the same time, the credit also went to his plentiful experience from his previous life and his own efforts.

Advancing to rank four meant stepping into a whole new world! In the mortal world, rank one and two were only low levels, rank three was middle level, while rank four and five were the high levels.

Elders of many clans were all at rank four realm. If Gu Yue mountain still existed, Fang Yuan could now fight for the clan leader's position!

Whether it were Southern Border, Central Continent or other places, rank four cultivation was enough to let a Gu Master roam everywhere.

Gu Masters with rank four cultivation were a force to reckon with.

Many clans only had one or two rank four Gu Masters.

After reaching this stage, Fang Yuan could be said to have grown and exceeded most Gu Masters.

"Since rebirth, my cultivation has now reached rank four. Compared to my previous life, this speed is faster by countless times. By taking a step first and then moving step by step, I have accumulated my advantage continuously and reach today's accomplishment. All these were due to the help of my previous life's experience. All thanks to Spring Autumn Cicada ..."

Fang Yuan was more and more aware of how formidable the rank six Gu Spring Autumn Cicada was.

It was because of Spring Autumn Cicada that he could have another chance.

"However, although I have advanced to rank four, Spring Autumn Cicada's recovery speed is getting faster as well. The pressure it is exerting on the aperture is also becoming bigger."

"Rank four is a brand new starting point, I can use many more rank four Gu with the light gold primeval essence. Next, I need to refine charging crash Gu. But before this, I still have something I need to do...."

...

Fourth inner city.

"This is the manor Zhou Quan is in charge of?" Fang Yuan stood inside a courtyard with hands behind him and his tone indifferent.

Instantly, he got the answer from a subordinate: "Yes, Lord Fang Zheng."

Right now, standing behind Fang Yuan were Bai Ning Bing, Xiao Die, Xiong brothers along with Wei De Xin and her people who had recovered some of their strength after refining some Gu just recently.

"It is this place. Missy and I came here so many times, but we were given cold shoulder every time." Xiao Die added in angrily from the side.

"Lord, if you wish to see my master, please pass us your visiting letter. My master is currently taking an afternoon nap." The doorboy walked over and said with an arrogant

He recognized Xiao Die and understood these were Shang Xin Ci's people.

"Afternoon nap? Visiting letter? Hehehe." Fang Yuan laughed coldly before his expression immediately turned dark; he waved his hand: "Go, smash the door!"

"Hehehe..." Everyone was stupefied for a while, as the three Xiong brothers took the lead and walked forward with large strides.

"You... what are you trying to do?!" The doorboy was feeling extreme panicked and could not help but shout.

"You puny thing dares to block our way, get lost!" Xiong Huo gave an evil grin and kicked, sending the doorboy flying.

Bang!

Xiong Tu used his brute force to forcefully smash the large manor door.

"What are you doing?" Some servants ran over at the commotion, but with one look at the group of fiendish Gu Masters, they stood still in terror.

Crash Bang Crash Bang...

Slam Slam...

Fang Yuan's group intruded Zhou Quan's manor and starting charging around violently; smashing everything they saw and beating people up. Xiong Feng even took liberties with some pretty looking servants.

The manor was in chaos. Some servants ran around panicking and in fear while some cried, screaming for help and forgiveness.

Chapter 332: Zhou Quan’s shock

"What do we do master?" The steward frantically ran towards Zhou Quan, asking for instructions.

Zhou Quan was shocked awake earlier, seeing that Fang Yuan created a din his house, he was livid.

"This Fang Zheng is completely lawless, he actually dared to use force in Shang clan city! Wait... this aura, rank four, oh god, how old is he, he advanced to rank four already?"

Zhou Quan observed secretly, but suddenly his eyes opened wide, as he was completely stunned.

He was once a rank four Gu master, the leader of a clan. But he only reached rank four realm when he was near fifty years old. Fang Yuan's age was well known in the battle stage, he was only twenty!

What godly talent was this!

Zhou Quan felt lamentation and jealousy, anger and helplessness: "Fang Zheng also advanced to rank four, he is a true rank four Gu Master. He also has the purple thorn token, and has good relationships with Shang Xin Ci and Shang Chao Feng. He is too stubborn, previously he caused trouble in the slave market, but was only fined forty-nine primeval stones. He has a bright future ahead, he is likely to reach rank five. According to the rumors, even Shang Yan Fei thinks highly of him, and now the entire Shang clan is turning a blind eye to his actions. How can I compete with him? But, if I can't afford to offend him, can't I just hide?"

Thinking of this, Zhou Quan sighed, saying to his old steward: "Quickly pack our things, we're going to hide in the shop. They are coming full force at us, we have to avoid them during this period."

"Yes, master." The old steward quickly went to pack up.

A moment later, the gang flipped the manor upside down, the place which was elegant and quiet had become a warzone.

"Lord, we have searched, we did not find Zhou Quan." Xiong Tu reported.

"Mm, he must've snuck out from the backdoor. He couldn't have gone too far, he's probably hiding in the shop. But all these are within my expectations, I purposely left the backdoor intact, hehe." Fang Yuan chuckled.

Zhou Quan thought Fang Yuan would respect Shang clan and stop making trouble. But who was Fang Yuan? In his heart, even the super-size Shang clan was just a slightly larger stepping stone for his ambitions.

"Have you prepared what I instructed you to do?" Fang Yuan turned around, asking Wei De Xin.

Wei De Xin quickly responded: "It has been prepared."

"Very good." Fang Yuan waved his hand: "Let's go."

The gang left the manor, and immediately caused a commotion.

Shang clan city had always been very peaceful and safe. Fang Yuan barging into someone's home and messing it up had already attracted a lot of attention.

Moreover, Fang Yuan instructed Wei De Xin to circulate news about this matter, thus, it became an even more sensational story in the city.

Numerous passersby were attracted towards the scene.

"Go." Fang Yuan led the way, bringing his followers as he roamed the streets, purposely keeping a high profile.

Along the way, the number of passersby increased, crowding until the road was packed with people.

"Master, master, that Fang Zheng is here again." The old steward reported frightenedly.

"No need to worry, this shop is owned by Shang clan, he wouldn't have the guts to barge in here." Zhou Quan stroked his beard, calming his steward.

Before his words were finished, he heard a loud sound.

Fang Yuan had sent the door of the shop flying with a kick in front of everyone, and took large steps into the shop.

"Stop there." A group of Shang clan city guards walked out with a grim expression.

Fang Yuan and gang were so noisy, the city guards were informed long ago.

"This is a Shang clan shop, you cannot enter by force. This is violating Shang clan city rules!" The guard leader shouted as he sweated buckets.

He was on duty today, if he did not speak out, Shang clan city will pursue his irresponsibility later.

But Fang Yuan ignored him completely, walking in without heeding a word.

The others followed suit.

Bai Ning Bing stayed outside, looking coldly at the city guard leader, emitting her rank four aura: "We are going in now, so what? Can you stop us?"

This rank two leader's heart was palpitating intensely.

He gulped, as he responded with a pale expression: "Even if I cannot stop you, we have to try. This is Shang clan city, that is our responsibility. You have to know, Lord Fang Zheng's actions had violated Shang clan city's rules, chapter three article twenty-five..."

"We know, a fine right." Bai Ning Bing raised her eyebrows, as she tossed a bag of primeval stones to the leader.

"There are five hundred primeval stones inside, keep the change. We have to continue thrashing the place later, this is an advance payment." After saying that, Bai Ning Bing entered the shop as well.

The leader stood frozen on the spot, as he held that heavy bag of primeval stones, he was completely stunned by Bai Ning Bing's aura.

"Too arrogant, way too arrogant!" The passersby were roaring.

"I've never seen anyone acting so lawlessly in Shang clan city."

"Fang Zheng and Bai Ning Bing are rank four Gu Masters, they have the ability. They even have the purple thorn token backing then, who can imitate them?"

"Even if I have the strength, I wouldn't dare to. The are simply too daring! Doing this in broad daylight, really..."

As some people discussed, more of the spectators were just dumbfounded.

Some wanted to enter the shop to watch the show, but they were either blocked outside by Fang Yuan's men, or chased away by the city guards.

"Leader, do we go in?" A city guard asked softly.

"Go in for what? To let them throw primeval stones at us?!" The leader screamed: "Wait, wait for lord elder to come and settle this himself!"

Back to Fang Yuan, who was entering the shop.

"Fang Zheng, what are you trying to do? Barging into a Shang clan shop by force, do you still want to stay in Shang clan city?" Zhou Quan's face was grim as he tried to suppress Fang Yuan's dominance using the name of Shang clan.

Fang Yuan sneered, looking at Zhou Quan in disdain: "Old man, weren't you taking a nap at home? Why are you hiding here? We are both smart people, let's not beat about the bush, I am here for you. You have two choices now, submit to me, or die. Choose now."

"Hehehe. Young man, I would advise you to stop your arrogance." Zhou Quan squeezed out a smile, his prideful character taking over, refusing to lower his head: "You want to harm me, can't you see where we are right now? Hmm?"

Fang Yuan laughed loudly.

"Why are you laughing?" Zhou Quan's face was extremely ugly as he questioned.

"You've lived for so many years, your foresight is getting worse. Can't you see, I am different from Shang Xin Ci? Nevermind, I shall show you mercy and give you a chance, a chance to fully understand me."

Fang Yuan said, suddenly shouting and striking.

Zhou Quan did not expect Fang Yuan to be so uncontrollable, after being assaulted, he was immediately sent sprawling on the ground and nearly fainted.

But he still had his rich experience, quickly getting up and engaging Fang Yuan in battle.

Bam bam bam...

The sound of battle spread outside.

The crowd standing outside the shop stirred.

"They fought, they fought!"

"He really attacked, this Fang Zheng's guts are made of steel, he is too crazy."

"Zhou Quan is so unlucky to have met him."

Everyone sighed, no one thought Zhou Quan would win.

They were right.

The battle in the shop quickly ended, Zhou Quan was not Fang Yuan's match at all. He still had some hidden injuries, even though he was rank three peak stage, against the overbearing Fang Yuan, there was no way he could win.

The shop was thrashed during the fight, almost half the place was destroyed. After the smoke dispersed, everyone saw Zhou Quan sprawled on the ground, bleeding and having bone fractures, immobilized.

Fang Yuan was standing on the ground, as he stepped on Zhou Quan's head, giving off a dominating aura.

"Lord Fang Zheng, what have you done?" Three Shang clan elders came together, shouting.

"Where are your eyes? Can't you tell from looking? I'm teaching people a lesson!" Fang Yuan rolled his eyes, replying loudly.

The crowd laughed.

"Lord Fang Zheng, we are not here for jokes. This matter is too severe, do you know the consequences?" The clan elders said solemnly.

Zhou Quan who was trampled by Fang Yuan sneered, as blood flowed out of his open mouth.

"Fang Zheng was too rash!"

"He made the matter too severe, how is he going to get out of it this time."

"Although Fang Zheng is a talent, he is after all, not a Shang clansmen..."

Under everyone's gaze, Fang Yuan laughed: "Of course I know the consequences. Not only that, I also know what's the consequences of killing a person!"

Saying so, he took out the purple thorn token.

"Elders, if I murder in Shang clan city, it would ruin Shang clan's peace. According to the rules, I will lose the purple thorn token, is that right?" Fang Yuan questioned.

"Yes." An elder immediately answered.

After getting a clear answer, Fang Yuan's lips curled up as he showed a callous smile.

He exerted strength, and crushed the purple thorn token into powder.

This action caused the crowd to scream in shock, as the elders' pupils shrunk.

"Fang Zheng destroyed the purple thorn token!"

"That is a purple thorn token, he destroyed it, what a huge waste!"

"Fang Zheng abandoned even the purple thorn token, he clearly wants Zhou Quan's life..."

"Zhou Quan is too arrogant, rejecting Shang Xin Ci's invitation so many times. He angered Fang Zheng because of this, what bad luck!"

...

Seeing the fragments of the purple thorn token land on the ground, even hitting his own face, Zhou Quan's smile froze.

This was a purple thorn token!!

"Fang Zheng destroyed even his purple thorn token, he wants my life. Is he... he... is he insane?!"

Zhou Quan was completely horrified by Fang Yuan's madness, recklessness and insanity.

Chapter 333: Leaving Shang Clan City

He had assumed Fang Yuan was trying to teach him a lesson. But he did not expect Fang Yuan to have killing intent, even willingly giving up the precious purple thorn token!

"Just because of me, you acted so ruthlessly, was it worth it?" Feeling Fang Yuan's 'determination', Zhou Quan wanted to cry.

He was a normal person.

He also feared death.

If not, after Zhou clan was wiped out, and he became alone and injured, he would've died already.

But he lived.

The desire to live was every living being's instinct.

He rejected Shang Xin Ci because he looked down on her. He was a proud man, once the leader of a clan, how could he submit to a weak and powerless girl like her?

But he did not think the matter would escalate to this extent!

Now, he was facing the threat of death! Fang Yuan's insanity was something he did not expect.

"Had I known this would happen, I would've accepted her invitation. To think it would end up like this!" Zhou Quan felt intense regret.

Although he was prideful, he was not stupid.

Survival and pride, he obviously chose the former. If not, he would not have stayed alive like a beaten dog for all these years.

"That's right, I understand! My act of rejecting Shang Xin Ci was a heavy hit on her reputation. Fang Zheng is her greatest supporter, thus he has to eliminate me! Shang Yi Fan had misled me..."

Feeling Fang Yuan's intense killing intent, Zhou Quan quickly thought of the reason.

With his intelligence, with just a little analysis, he understood that the rumors earlier were all caused by Shang Yi Fan.

Back then, he was still gleeful and smug. These rumors were the best excuse for him to reject Shang Xin Ci. At the same time, he could feel that Shang Yi Fan valued him greatly from these rumors. In the worst case, he could go to Shang Yi Fan.

Whether it was Shang Yi Fan or Shang Xin Ci had no difference to him. As long as he was willing to help, he could make them young master easily.

This was Zhou Quan's confidence.

But now he was beyond regretful.

Because of this rumor, Fang Yuan wanted to kill him. It was already too late to go to Shang Yi Fan.

Fang Yuan was a maniac, he did not follow the rules. Zhou Quan had completely screwed up this time!

Zhou Quan sprawled on the ground, his bones hurting from the battle, as he was immobilized by Fang Yuan's leg on his face.

He wanted to open his mouth and beg for mercy.

But he could not say it.

"There are so many people watching, if I beg in public, my reputation will be tarnished. But if I don't, my life will be forfeited..."

Character decides fate.

At the crucial moment, Zhou Quan's arrogance was still influencing him.

"The saying goes, a wise man submits to circumstances. Zhou Quan, since you cannot understand your circumstance, you are no wise man. I wasted a purple thorn token to kill you, feel honored. Now die." Fang Yuan sneered as he exerted force on his leg.

Zhou Quan felt an intense pressure on him, he finally abandoned all hesitation and begged.

But because Fang Yuan was using so much force, his cheeks were squeezed together, he wanted to speak, but could not.

Zhou Quan was panicking!

"Wait, I don't want to die, I want to beg, I want to surrender, let me speak..."

He screamed in his heart, at the same time, he waved his limbs around frantically.

He grabbed Fang Yuan's leg, but Fang Yuan's body was as tough as steel, not even moving an inch.

"I'm dead meat..." Just as Zhou Quan was despairing, he heard a familiar voice.

"Brother Hei Tu, have mercy on him." Shang Xin Ci rushed to the scene.

"Xin Ci, it seems you still found out in the end. I know you treasure talents, but you don't have to beg for his sake. Such a person deserves death." Fang Yuan replied coldly, but stopped exerting force on his leg.

"No, brother Hei Tu, I have to speak." Shang Xin Ci was very determined.

She continued: "You did not spend much time with Sir Zhou Quan, I know him better. Sir Zhou had always been adamant on rebuilding Zhou clan. He bore a heavy weight on his shoulders, he is a person with noble aspirations in his heart. He had once told me with great pain that he could not forget his former clansmen. Before his wife passed away, she told him to rebuild their home. These years, he carried a heavy burden and have been working hard for it. He has his grievances..."

"Is that so?" Fang Yuan reduced the strength he placed on his leg, his expression changing.

"Why don't I remember ever tell you that?" Zhou Quan felt weird, when his wife died, he was not even at the scene.

But he immediately understood, this was an act Shang Xin Ci was putting on with Fang Yuan.

Actually, Fang Yuan and Shang Xin Ci were still trying to recruit him!

They used Shang clan as the stage and acted out a good show. Her words earlier were his ticket out of this mess.

It not only portrayed Shang Xin Ci's kindness and love for talented people, it also gave him a way out of this predicament.

"What a great scheme, great scheme indeed... I am the Zhou clan leader, but today I lost to these youngsters. Truly, the new generation is replacing the old." Zhou Quan gritted his teeth, sighing helplessly.

He felt anger, hatred, but also grief and helplessness.

"So that's it. To think that Sir Zhou was such a man with aspirations. But you are too stupid, assisting Xin Ci does not clash with your aspirations of rebuilding your home. You are not afraid of death because of your goals, I am impressed by you. But do you know, dying is easy, but enduring shame and staying alive for your ideals, moving forward with the pressure on you, that is true courage." Fang Yuan said loudly.

Zhou Quan heard this, and knew that this was an opportunity Fang Yuan was giving him.

This was most likely the last one as well.

If he does not accept it, his life would be over, there are no more chances left for him.

Thinking so, this old man said: "Sigh! A new generations breeds new geniuses, after listening to what you both have said, I am greatly enlightened!"

Fang Yuan loosened his leg.

Shang Xin Ci was overjoyed, helping Zhou Quan up.

Zhou Quan endured the pain on his body, slowly getting up, then paying respects to Shang Xin Ci: "Zhou Quan greets Lady Xin Ci."

...

"What did you say? Zhou Quan acknowledged that lass as his lord?" In the study room, Shang Yi Fan heard this and froze in shock.

"That is impossible! I know Zhou Quan's personality, even back then when Shang Ya Zi was in charge, and controlled all the shops, he could not recruit him. What abilities does this Shang Xin Ci have, to manage to gain his loyalty?!" Shang Yi Fan reacted and shouted in astonishment.

"This really happened." Old Zhang sighed: "Shang Xin Ci is still young, she naturally doesn't possess the ability. But she has Fang Zheng and Bai Ning Bing with her, to speak the truth, I underestimated Fang Zheng, to think that he is so scheming under that straightforward facade, he purposely made the matter impossible to resolve, and forced Zhou Quan to submit to her."

"If Zhou Quan did not submit, Fang Zheng would've killed him on the spot. Right now, the entire shop district is talking about the matter. There are rumors everywhere, saying that Zhou Quan had been living while enduring humiliation and shame, in order to rebuild his clan. After being enlightened by Fang Zheng, he decided to join Shang Xin Ci who had a love for talents. Shang Xin Ci's reputation has surged to a peak now!"

Shang Yi Fan heard that and raged: "That means all the effort we wasted earlier, spreading rumors around, has instead helped them out instead? Liar, they are all liars! All these rumors must be sent out by them, how could there be such a touching story, hmph!"

"Young master Yi Fan, calm down, the competition is not over yet, although Shang Xin Ci has some people now, they might not truly be loyal to her. Now, we still have madam's help, there is still a high chance of winning." Old Zhang analyzed calmly.

As he advised, Shang Yi Fan's emotions went back to normal.

He gritted his teeth, his eyes shining with an ominous light: "You are right, building a force takes a lot of time. All these people she recruited were either threatened or forced, how could she gain their loyalty? Hehehe, next, I will stir up discord among them, and then poach them over with money, I'm sure it'll work!"

...

With Shang Xin Ci in charge, Fang and Bai as guardians, Zhou Quan assisting, and the cooperation of Wei De Xin and Xiong clan brothers, the intel business in the battle stage was finally established.

As Shang Xin Ci predicted, once the business started, it caused a lot of commotion and reaction.

The first day they started, they recouped their invested capital.

On the second day, business was still booming.

On the third day, business was still on fire.

After seven days, Shang Xin Ci's three hundred thousand primeval stones grew to four hundred and forty thousand.

Shang Yi Fan's schemes did not make any progress. Shang Xin Ci's force was very united, and everyone could not be wavered. Such unity made the other young masters feel surprised.

Shang Yi Fan was panicking, because he knew: If Shang Xin Ci continued to develop like this, with her current reputation, she would definitely be the final winner.

Thus, he started using his mother's influence to affect Shang clan's higher-ups.

Shang Xin Ci's intel business involved the battle stage, it was a sensitive topic. Shang clan's higher-ups held a meeting and were about to stop Shang Xin Ci's business from operating, when Shang Yan Fei stood up, and swept away all objections, fully supporting his daughter.

Shang Yan Fei's attitude was the final blow to Shang Yi Fan.

Several months later, Shang Yi Fan and his mother's forces lost terribly to Shang Xin Ci.

Shang Xin Ci became one of the ten young masters succeeding Shang Ya Zi.

But the pain of separation overwhelmed her joy of success.

"Brother Hei Tu, are you in such a rush?" Shang Xin Ci walked outside the city, bidding farewell.

"You have already become a young master, with your talent, you will definitely grow well here. Xin Ci, there is no banquet that never ends, we will meet again in the future, do not be sad."

Fang Yuan consoled, but then changed the topic: "Before I go, I have something to remind you. Always maintain a wide vision and look ahead, above the ten young master position, there is still the young clan leader Shang Tuo Hai. Above Shang Tuo Hai, there are the five elders of Shang clan, your father Shang Yan Fei, and even the supreme elder of Shang clan..."

"Rest assured brother, back then, when Shang Tuo Hai became young clan leader, he had the perfect conditions. The other young masters also had favourable relationships when they rose to power. But I have neither of those, I can only invest in human capital, only with talents can I compete with them. Brother, if you need anything, inform me, I will do anything I can to help you!" Brilliance shone in Shang Xin Ci's eyes.

Her words caused Fang and Bai to take a second look at her.

As expected of the future Shang clan leader, the female talent that shook the world!

"Alright, until the next time we meet." Fang Yuan looked deeply at Shang Xin Ci, before turning around to leave.

Bai Ning Bing followed behind him immediately.

The two, one wearing black and the other white, gradually vanished into the mountainous terrain.

Shang Xin Ci and her two servants stood on the spot, staring at the two's background without moving.

"Brother Hei Tu, San Cha mountain is very dangerous, please take care!" Shang Xin Ci's eyes were watery as she prayed for him in her heart.

Chapter 334: Immortal Crane Sect, Fang Zheng

In the world of Gu, the regions were magical.

At the east, there was a huge sea, with islands which stood out like chess pieces on a chessboard. It was named Eastern Sea.

At the west, there was a huge desert, greenery was extremely rare, only yellow sand could be seen everywhere. It was named Western Desert.

At the north, there was a huge grassland, people called it Northern Plains.

At the south, there was a mountainous terrain, known as the Southern Border.

And in the middle of eastern sea, western desert, northern plains, and southern border, there was a central area, called Central Continent.

Central continent was over fifty million kilometers wide, primeval energy was extremely rich in the air, and many sects existed. There were many heroes and conquerors, both demonic and righteous, it was an area with plentiful human and natural resources. Its total strength was the strongest compared to the other four regions.

In the southern part of central continent, among tens of thousands of hills, there was a large mountain above the clouds, piercing through the skies.

Fei He mountain!

Fei He mountain was grand and majestic, floating on top of the sea of cloud.

Sunlight penetrated the clouds, and shone on the green forests on the mountain.

At the foot of the mountain, waves crashed as the tides rose and fell.

Whenever the winds blow, the sea of clouds would experience great movements, the bamboo forests would sway with the wind, as ten thousand cranes sang.

Ironbeak flying crane, fire pellet crane, tailwind crane, cloud mist crane, stellar light crane... over ten thousand types of flying cranes flew or rested in the pine trees. It was an overwhelming sight to behold.

The ten thousand cranes on Fei He mountain were famous in central continent. As for the Gu Masters on the mountain, they were famous throughout the world.

This was Immortal Crane Sect.

One of the top ten sects in central continent, possessing one of the strongest force in central continent.

Right now, there was a crucial battle happening in Immortal Crane Sect's sparring arena.

Two youngsters, wearing similar clothing, were engaging in a fight. The two moved about as they tangled and fought together.

"Too, too strong!"

"I cannot imagine, both of them are only around twenty years old."

Outside the arena, the spectators were watching this battle intently. Shock, admiration showed on their faces.

"Senior brother Sun Yuan Hua, he is a veteran expert. The number one in the previous third year small examination, I am not surprised he has such strength. But that junior brother Fang Zheng, it is shocking that he possesses such ability!"

"That's right, he is a black horse in this year's eight year middle examination. No one expected him to reach the finals."

"These years, junior brother Fang Zheng had been keeping a low profile, like an ordinary mountain rock. No one cared about him, he was completely not eye-catching. But who would have thought that during this examination, he would soar into the sky and have his name become renowned in Immortal Crane Sect."

Many people sighed as they showed admiration and jealousy.

Fang Zheng kept a grim expression as he had a sharp gaze, fighting evenly with Sun Yuan Hua.

These years, he had grown taller, his shoulder was broader, and his waist was thicker, he had become more mature and stable.

Suddenly, Fang Zheng unleashed a jade green wind, forcing Sun Yuan Hua to retreat.

"Senior brother Sun, just admit defeat." He said in an extremely confident tone.

"Little junior brother, show me what trump card you have." Sun Yuan Hua laughed, replying with the same level of confidence.

"Alright then." Fang Zheng whistled, as the sound travelled far. Soon, the cranes called back to him.

Everyone turned to look, and numerous eyeballs almost popped out as they stared with wide-opened mouths.

"An ironbeak flying crane group!"

"Oh heavens, so many flying cranes, is this an illusion?"

"How is that possible? This is a myriad beast king! Fang Zheng reaching rank four middle stage was already a god-tier talent! But he can actually control a crane group that is almost ten thousand in number, what method is this?"

Everyone gasped, feeling extremely shocked in their heart, some unable to believe the scene before them.

Even several sect elders stood up from their seats in shock.

Sun Yuan Hua's expression became extremely solemn.

Ironbeak flying crane group, coming with an imposing aura, and an advantage in numbers, it gave him great pressure.

But he did not intend to give up.

His eyes shone with determination: "Junior brother Fang, you are impressive. But can you really control so many flying cranes? I have not lost yet, because I have a crane group too! Come out!"

Fei He mountain had tens of thousands of flying cranes, such a territorial advantage was well used by the people in Immortal Crane Sect.

Fang Zheng had a crane group, but Sun Yuan Hua was also a genius in the sect that received ample nurturing, he also hid a crane group secretly.

Hearing Sun Yuan Hua's command, a group of cranes quickly flew out.

This crane group posed a stark contrast to Fang Zheng's ironbeak flying crane group, there was only a few hundred.

But the cranes Sun Yuan Hua controlled was different from the ironbeak flying cranes. On their bodies, they had white feathers, but there was blue color on the tips of the wings and tail, as well as their claws. Under the sunlight, they gave a metallic shine.

At the same time, when they flew, traces of blue static lightning could be seen on their bodies.

"Be careful, these flying cranes are illusion lightning cranes. They have a fierce nature and are skilled at fighting alone. Ordinary ironbeak flying cranes are not their match." Fang Zheng heard Lord Sky Crane from in his mind.

"I understand, master!" Fang Zheng replied immediately, his eyes shining brilliantly as he observed the illusion lightning crane group and manipulated his ironbeak flying crane group.

"They're going to crash!"

"The ironbeak flying crane group is too huge, it is like a giant monster. Senior brother Sun's crane group might not even make a dent in it."

"No, senior brother Sun still has a chance. Crane battles aren't about numbers, it depends on their control and manipulation."

"Senior brother Sun had been training hard all along, his control of the crane groups is definitely one of the best. It all depends on Fang Zheng's performance now."

"To speak the truth, I don't think Fang Zheng will win. Although he is a genius, he is still human. These few years, he had to cultivate to rank four, do the sect missions, and assemble his exemplary set of Gu worms, all these had used up much of his time. I don't believe he still had time left to train his crane group manipulation skills."

Everyone discussed with great fervor.

Such an intensive fight, it was rarely seen in the sect's three year small examination and eight year middle examination. Only in the fifteen year large examination, would it be seen occasionally.

Although Fang Zheng possessed a huge number of cranes, not everyone thought highly of him.

The scene now was like the fight between two armies.

Fang Zheng had almost ten thousand flying cranes, he had a large army, but because of the numbers, it was easy to lose control over them. He was only rank four middle stage, the strength of his soul was limited, he could only have that much mental energy.

Meanwhile, although Sun Yuan Hua had fewer cranes, all of them were elites, and he could manipulate them easily. With the amount of time he placed into controlling them, his crane manipulation skill was one of the best in the sect.

Seeing the two army about to crash in the air.

At this moment!

Sun Yuan Hua suddenly leapt.

He activated the Gu in his aperture, causing him to turn into a flash of lightning, closing in on Fang Zheng.

Fang Zheng did not expect him to strike so suddenly.

This way, he Sun Yuan Hua would fall into the encirclement of the ironbeak flying cranes, and get himself into grave danger.

Sun Yuan Hua attacked like a hurricane, like he went mad, his strength was something beyond what he had displayed earlier.

Fang Zheng lost the initiative and was suppressed, only able to defend with all his strength.

The two cranes engaged in the air, while on the ground, Fang Zheng and Sun Yuan Hua fought intensely.

Although the numbers of illusion lighting cranes were few, they were united, and charged together, tearing apart many ironbeak flying cranes.

In contrast, the ironbeak flying cranes, although many, were a mess, like a pack without a leader.

"The ironbeak flying crane group could not block this small number of illusion lightning cranes!"

"Senior brother Sun is amazing! His battle tactic was superb!"

"That's right, Fang Zheng has limited concentration, manipulating this large group of cranes is like a baby wielding a hammer, amateurish and unskilled. He himself is being attacked by senior brother Sun, he can't even defend himself properly, with his concentration on defending, how could he bother with controlling the cranes above him."

"But the ironbeak flying crane group is just too huge, there are many hundred beast kings, several thousand beast kings, and even a myriad beast king. In the illusion lightning crane group, there are only three hundred beast kings and one injured thousand beast king. In order to avoid these beast kings, the illusion lightning cranes have to attack from the right and left, even if they injured many ordinary ironbeak flying cranes, they are greatly injured themselves."

"Sun Yuan Hua and Fang Zheng are evenly matched, one attacks and one defends, they are extremely familiar with each other's moves, there is no clear winner. We can only look at the result of the crane battle." An elder saw the victory condition of this match.

If the ironbeak flying crane group can devour the illusion lightning crane group, then it was Fang Zheng's victory for certain.

But if the illusion lightning crane group rushes out of the ironbeak flying cranes' encirclement and goes to help Sun Yuan Hua, Fang Zheng would lose.

"Endure, endure for a bit more. Try and divert some attention to the ironbeak flying cranes and kill all the illusion lightning cranes! If you can do that, it would be a huge breakthrough, it would be extremely helpful to you in the future." In Fang Zheng's mind, Lord Sky Crane's voice continued to advise.

Fang Zheng exerted all his strength and followed what Lord Sky Crane said.

But right when he was about to succeed, Sun Yuan Hua would always break his concentration with a flurry of attacks.

Sun Yuan Hua was older than Fang Zheng, he had placed a lot of effort in manipulating cranes, under his control, although the cranes were injured, they were already about to break out of the ironbeak flying cranes' encirclement.

"Junior brother Fang Zheng, it is still too early for you to defeat me." He sneered.

Such words were heard by Fang Zheng, and it triggered the deepest part of his memory.

Back then, on Qing Mao mountain, Gu Yue village, he and his older brother Fang Yuan fought in the arena.

Fang Yuan said the exact same words.

"No, I cannot lose!"

"I have to take revenge for my clan, for my uncle and aunt, for my clan leader, for Lord Qing Shu!"

"Why have I worked so hard in these last few years? I must stand before my brother and defeat him. How can I lose to Sun Yuan Hua now?"

Flames burned in Fang Zheng's eyes.

He endured the pain in his head, and diverted his concentration!

The ironbeak flying cranes suddenly moved, like a huge beast opening its mouth, devouring the illusion lightning crane group.

Seeing this, Sun Yuan Hua's face went pale.

Victory!

The crowd cheered.

Fang Zheng was the number one in the eight year middle examination, defeating Sun Yuan Hua and became an elite disciple of Immortal Crane Sect!

Chapter 335: Gu Immortal Bai Hu’s Inheritance

Central continent's sect system was different from southern border's clan system.

In clans, blood ties sustained the hierarchy, and clansmen were the target for nurturing. But in sects, masters and disciples replaced the bloodline system. In sects, they recruited disciples and as long as one had good talent and character, they would be accepted.

Precisely so, Fang Zheng was absorbed into Immortal Crane Sect as one of its member.

In Immortal Crane Sect, from low to high, they were classified as, outer disciple, inner disciple, elite disciple, legacy disciple, sect elder, sect leader, and the supreme elder.

Three year small examination, was to choose inner disciples. Eight year middle examination was to choose elite disciples. As for the fifteen year large examination, it allows one to ascend to a legacy disciple.

Above the legacy disciple, it would be the sect elders.

The sect elders in Immortal Crane Sect had at least rank four cultivation. The sect leader would have rank five cultivation, and the supreme elders were rank six Gu Immortals, there was even rank seven among them!

Central continent was the strongest region compared to north, south, east, and west. Immortal Crane Sect was the top ten sect in central continent, it was even stronger than Shang clan.

The disciple selection did not involve place of birth, or any regional priorities. Thus, in Immortal Crane Sect, there were no C grade aptitudes.

B grade was the most commonly seen, but there were many A grades as well.

Fang Zheng was a genius with A grade aptitude no doubt. But in Immortal Crane Sect, in such a super-level force, there were many geniuses just like him.

"Fang Zheng, you were born smart and were willing to undertake hardships, now that you have rank four cultivation, you are already qualified to be a sect elder. But you have only entered the sect for a short time, you need to complete many sect missions to prove your loyalty. I hope you can continue to work hard, become victorious in the large examination, and become a legacy disciple." Immortal Crane Sect leader sat on his grand seat as he looked down at Fang Zheng, who was kneeling below the stairs.

"Yes, I will remember leader's teachings." Fang Zheng replied.

"Now, I have a sect mission to hand to you and a few elite disciples. Go back and read through the details, go." The sect leader said as a bookworm flew out.

Fang Zheng received it and took his leave.

Once he returned, he laid down on the bed and fell asleep.

Controlling Gu worms required a lot of concentration, he expended a lot of his mental energy in doing so, at times he had to multitask and do multiple things at once.

In the battle with Sun Yuan Hua, Fang Zheng used all his trump cards and truly expended all his means.

He was too tired, forcefully meeting the sect leader to finish the initiation for advancing to an elite disciple. His head was still hurting, like a hammer was hitting him, while his shoulders were so sore that they could barely support his neck. He was drowsy and felt light-headed.

Fang Zheng slept for two days and two nights, until a series of knocking woke him up.

Once he pushed the door open, he saw a group of elite disciples.

These disciples comprised both male and female, they were mostly rank three but there were a few with rank four cultivation.

Different from clans, which did not require loyalty to be tested, sects needed to do so.

The higher the hierarchy, the fewer the number of elite disciples, legacy disciples, and elders. Many cultivated to rank four, but were eliminated during the examinations. Thus resulted in many disciples and elders having the same rank four cultivation.

But regardless of their cultivation, the elders definitely had higher battle strength than disciples. That is because they were chosen strictly through examinations, and were the most talented among thousands.

"Fang Zheng, we have the same mission. On this trip, I hope we can take care of each other."

"Fang Zheng, I saw your battle with Sun Yuan Hua, it was very exciting!"

"I hope we can spar along the way..."

These people were very amiable. That is because they knew Fang Zheng controlled an ironbeak flying crane group that was ten thousand in number. Although he could not control them perfectly, such strength was still respectable.

"You are too polite, my fellow sect brothers. I am ashamed, these few days, I had been sleeping, I have not seen the mission details yet." Fang Zheng cupped his fists, admitting.

"I see, in that case, I will tell you directly, our mission this time is extremely important! Fang Zheng, a few months ago, a shocking event happened at Tian Ti mountain, do you know about it?" An elite disciple asked.

"Tian Ti mountain?" Fang Zheng nodded: "This matter was huge, I know about it. On Tian Ti mountain, Fairy Bai Hu's inheritance appeared. Fairy Bai Hu is a famous person in the righteous path, a rank six Gu Immortal, and owns the Hu Immortal blessed land. Once this inheritance appeared, many Gu Immortals came out. As long as one inherits this inheritance, they would gain her blessed land. Right now, Tian Ti mountain is heavily surrounded by many Gu Immortals."

"Fang Zheng, I'll tell you directly, our mission this time is to go to Tian Ti mountain and try to obtain this inheritance. The lord Gu Immortal of our Immortal Crane Sect has already come to an agreement with the lords of the other sects, in order to maintain peace, they will not strike, but instead, choose some elite disciples in their sect to compete in a fair manner."

Fang Zheng heard this, and his eyes widened, showing intense desire: "Are you serious?"

This was the inheritance of a Gu Immortal!

"Of course, if we are truly fated and become her inheritor, we would definitely shoot to success. In the future, we have a great chance of breaking through to Gu Immortal realm. But other than our Immortal Crane Sect, there is also Heavenly Lotus Sect, Spirit Butterfly Valley, Ancient Soul Sect, Heaven's Envy Sect and the other central continent's top ten sects. Thus, during this trip, we have to cooperate and stay united!"

"Of course!" Fang Zheng immediately replied.

...

Huo Tan mountain in southern border is a dormant volcano.

It is about three kilometers tall, and the peak of the mountain is flat with a hole that is flowing with magma within. Thick smoke rose from the funnel occasionally like a chimney.

The greatest resource on this mountain were charcoal stones, almost seen everywhere.

This type of charcoal stone burnt for a long time and emitted little heat, and did not give out smoke, it was most commonly used in Shang clan city, fifth inner city.

It had been numerous days since Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing stepped into Huo Tan mountain.

They had set off from Shang Liang mountain, to reach San Cha mountain, Huo Tan mountain was a necessary stop.

Stepping on the charcoal stones, one would feel the heat from below, as the air was dry and without moisture. Looking far, all one could see was dark red charcoal stones.

There were trees on this mountain too.

But these trees were short and thin, their branches were like needles and did not block sunlight.

Thus, on Huo Tan mountain, one could have a wider vision than compared to being on other mountains.

Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing travelled on the mountain, if birds flew in the sky and looked down, they would see two tiny ants crawling slowly.

The truth is, they were being observed.

"Hehe, they are finally here."

"Huo Tan mountain is a necessary location along the path, they will definitely pass by here if they want to go to San Cha mountain.

At an insignificant corner, two demonic Gu Masters were hiding.

They were two bald men, the older one was called Jiao Huang, while the middle-aged man was called Meng Tu, they were a famous assassination duo among the demonic Gu Masters.

"As long as we kill these two, Shang clan would have ten thousand primeval stones as reward, and we will also get a yellow pair token. How can we let go of such a good deal?" Meng Tu licked his lips excitedly.

"But they are both rank four Gu Masters, we are only rank three peak stage. This is a good deal, but the risks are higher! I'm not sure if it was a mistake to accept this..." Jiao Huang was older and wiser, showing worry on his face.

"Elder brother Jiao Tu, don't be frightened by their cultivation. So what if they are rank four, they are only rank four initial stage. Most of the Gu worms in their hands are still rank three. Moreover, it is not like we have not killed a rank four Gu Master before, remember that Xiao Fu Lu who was killed by us?" Meng Tu encouraged.

Once he mentioned Xiao Fu Lu, Jiao Huang frowned, as he said nervously: "Didn't I mention it many times, don't talk about Xiao Fu Lu. He is the grandson of Xiao clan's supreme elder, we offended a Gu Immortal when we killed him. Keep this matter in your stomach and never mention it again."

"Hmph, so what if he is a Gu Immortal? Haven't we lived free and safe all these years?" Meng Tu pouted indifferently: "Gu Immortals are not omnipotent, not to mention these two newly advanced rank four Gu Masters. Brother, don't forget that we've spent several days preparing that trap for them. Hehehe!"

Speaking of that trap, Jiao Huang's expression relaxed.

He muttered: "As long as they fall into the trap and engage in a fierce battle, their primeval essence will be depleted and we will have a chance to act!"

"Exactly." Meng Tu said, as his eyes suddenly glowed, saying softly but excitedly: "Quickly look, they fell for the trap!"

Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing stopped walking.

The nearby ground started shaking violently. Rock shrapnels fell down the cliff from both sides.

On the ground, the soil was moved away as lava crocodiles crawled out from the ground.

"It is a lava crocodile group, there is a thousand beast king!" Bai Ning Bing concentrated, looking at the leader of the group.

This lava crocodile king was huge, the size of three elephants.

Its body is covered with deep red scales, and four thick legs supported its huge body. A crocodile tail giving off a metallic glow was over ten meters long. On its back, there were two lumps, like two small volcanoes. As it breathed, two traces of black smoke rose from the volcanoes, thick and thin rhythmically.

As the lava crocodile king crawled out of the ground, it stared at Fang and Bai, but most of its attention was on Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing were rank four initial stage Gu Masters, but he had rank four middle stage primeval essence.

The lava crocodile king had sharp senses, it immediately sensed that Fang Yuan's aura was scarier.

It opened its mouth, and over a thousand lava crocodiles encircled Fang and Bai.

Facing such a dangerous situation, Fang Yuan laughed: "It is but a few crocodiles, Bai Ning Bing, cooperate with me and kill this lava crocodile king!"

"Okay." Bai Ning Bing replied plainly, but battle intent surged in her eyes.

Back then, when they first left Qing Mao mountain, they had also encountered a lava crocodile king, and stayed away from it.

But now, they were different, having rank four cultivation, even if this lava crocodile king was a thousand beast king, it could not stop their path!

Chapter 336: Hero saves the beauty

Rocks cracked and flew; the crocodile group hissed in pain.

The large battle was at its end; Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing stood high on Huo Tan mountain, surrounding them were corpses of lava crocodiles.

Meanwhile, that thousand beast king lava crocodile king was on the ground with all the bones in its body broken, the two protruding mini volcano on its back were also smashed apart.

It hissed in a soft voice as it laid flat on the ground with blood pouring out from countless wounds on its body. Its claws shook as it tried to rake the ground to drill underground, however it no longer had enough strength.

Its struggles continued to decrease till death finally descended on it.

With the death of the thousand beast king, the remaining lava crocodiles immediately scattered, drilling into the ground or fleeing in disarray.

After roughly clearing up the battlefield, Fang and Bai resumed their journey.

Jiao Huang and Meng Tu were hiding in a faraway corner without moving even a bit. These two famous assassins had quite an unsightly expression right now, just like zombies.

They were scared!

"Are these two still humans? They contended against the whole lava crocodile group with just their own strength!"

"Bai Ning Bing walks the ice path and greatly suppresses the lava crocodiles. That can't be helped, but the main thing is still that Fang Zheng, he is simply a monster in human skin. The more injuries he suffered, the stronger he became. At the end, he even sent the lava crocodile king flying easily."

Jiao Huang and Meng Tu glanced at each other, both saw palpitation in each other's eyes.

Fang and Bai's terrifying strength greatly exceeded their expectations.

They did not live in Shang clan city, so only after seeing the whole battle, did they become deeply aware of Fang and Bai's terror.

"These two youths are seriously only around twenty years old? Screw that, compared to them, we were simply living a dog's life for the last forty years of our career." Meng Tu cursed out in fear.

"Brother Meng Tu, don't say so. Hearing you say that, I am completely ashamed of myself." The older Jiao Huang heaved a deep sigh, "Undoubtedly, these two are geniuses! Comparing oneself to others will only make you angry. We are simply not their match. If I had known this early, I would have never accepted this deal."

"Brother Jiao Huang, your words have spurred on my competitiveness and made me more indignant. This is still not finished, although we can't defeat them, we still have a chance!" Meng Tu said as he spit out some saliva.

"Eh? What chance?"

"Think of it, brother Jiao Huang. They are going to San Cha mountain to seek benefits from the three kings inheritance. San Cha mountain is extremely chaotic right now with rank four and rank five experts everywhere. They will definitely have to clash with others once they reach there. We will look for an opportunity while they are there. If we can take advantage of the situation while they are in trouble, that will be the best!"

Jiao Huang's eyes brightened upon hearing this reminder.

He patted Meng Tu's shoulder: "Brother, what you said makes sense. Let's go, go to San Cha mountain!"

"There was something fishy about that group of lava crocodiles." Fang Yuan thought along the way.

The timing of the lava crocodiles and the area they appeared in were too coincidental. The moment they appeared, they firmly surrounded Fang and Bai. Bai Ning Bing did not sense anything wrong, but the astute Fang Yuan with his previous life's experience could smell a conspiracy.

Fang Yuan was very familiar with such situations.

"Someone intentionally designed this trap and wanted to deal with me. But which side is it? Wu clan, Bai clan or Shang clan?" Fang Yuan inwardly pondered.

"Because I know Li Ran's identity and I have now left Shang Liang mountain, there is a probability that Wu clan would make a move."

"As for Bai clan? I have become their enemy, I know the huge secret of their clan's spirit spring drying up and have extorted them of three million primeval stones. How could they not hate me?"

"There is also Shang clan. The amount of Shang clansmen I have offended are also many. Shang Ya Zi, Shang Yi Fan, after buying that group of Wei clansmen I also offended Shang Pu Lao. In Shang clan's young master competition, I was one of the forces of Shang Xin Ci and if I was to be eliminated outside, she would be greatly weakened."

"Forget it, let's not think too much about it. I will just deal with it as they come." Fang Yuan shook his head and threw the disorganized thoughts out of his mind, clearing his thoughts.

If it was before when he was weak, he would have to exhaust all his energy to plan for everything. But now, his strength had increased by a lot and he had the aura of someone who would not move no matter what wind attacked him.

...

Central Continent.

Wind whistled through the sea of clouds.

Ten thousand flying cranes were flapping their wings together.

Fang Zheng and the other elite disciples of Immortal Crane Sect stood or sat cross-legged on the flying cranes and hurried towards Tian Ti mountain.

"Boss Fang Zheng, your crane group is really mighty. We will definitely shine brightly on this trip to Tian Ti mountain and sweep through everything." An elite disciple said.

He used a Gu while speaking, so no matter how strong the wind blew, his voice was not obstructed and was clearly transmitted to everyone.

"You speak too highly of me. This time, the ones participating in the competition for Gu Immortal Bai Hu's inheritance are all elites from the ten great sects. If we want to get the inheritance, not only do we need strength, but also luck."

"Boss Fang Zheng, you are too modest. With your myriad crane group, who can stop us?" Immediately another elite disciple said.

"Boss Fang Zheng, you are my role model. No wonder you were dispatched to this mission by the sect leader after just becoming an elite disciple. On this trip to Tian Ti mountain, we will only be following your lead!" An elite female disciple said respectfully.

On the way, Fang Zheng had sparred with all the elite disciples.

He was very strong and also had a spirit incubating flea in his aperture. Lord Sky Crane's soul resided in the spirit incubating flea and would give guidance from time to time. There was also the support of the myriad crane group.

Because of this, Fang Zheng defeated all the other elite disciples.

He was not arrogant after his victory, he had a great bearing and was modest, easily winning everyone's good impressions and was pushed to become their head. They were all in admiration of Fang Zheng.

"Among the ten great sects of Central Continent, which one of them does not have deep foundations? I am sure they also have talented people among them. Although I have the myriad crane group, my weakness is that I can't control them fully. I still need to ask you all to provide guidance regarding the control of the flying cranes." Fang Zheng cupped his hands towards the people beside him.

"We wouldn't dare. It is our honor to be able to spar with Boss Fang Zheng."

"Boss, you have been cultivating so hard these days that it makes us blush with shame."

"Boss, your progress is remarkable, you have an innate talent in controlling the cranes. You only lacked practice before, and given some time, you are sure to surpass Sun Yuan Hua."

The other elite disciples said words of agreement.

Their words were from the depths of their hearts. On this journey, they could clearly notice Fang Zheng's progress.

Fang Zheng smiled. With Lord Sky Crane providing guidance and secret experiences, and even controlling his body sometimes, how could he not improve at a lightning pace?

After flying for some time, the ironbeak flying cranes started to cry out one after another.

Fang Zheng and the rest understood.

"Alright. It is time, we need to land and feed the flying cranes." Fang Zheng stamped, the flying crane group started to pierce down through the layer of clouds under his control.

For a moment, it was only a scene of white vastness.

Soon, the clouds and mist disappeared as the group flew down from the layer of clouds to the verdant and lush ground.

Flying cranes also needed to eat. The larger the scale of the crane group, the higher their demand for food. Fortunately, ironbeak flying cranes could eat anything. Sometimes, they even ate stones to fill their stomachs, thus were very easy to raise.

Fang Zheng possessed such a large scale crane group, but it was also equally troublesome. After every set intervals, he would need to fly to the ground and feed the crane group.

"Eh? There is a battle going on!" As they were descending down, an elite disciple suddenly spoke out.

Everyone immediately discovered the unusual state on the ground.

Four demonic Gu Masters were laughing evilly while surrounding three female Gu Masters and slowly nearing them.

"Tsk, it is the four great obscenities." Soon, an elite disciple exposed those four demonic Gu Masters' identity with a disgusted tone.

These four great obscenities were separately; Eastern Obscenity Chen Yi Dao, Western Thief Yu Ba Guang, Southern Disturbance Shi Bao and Northern Squandering Fan Chun Yao.

They had been travelling all over Central Continent and were all rank four Gu Masters. They were extremely strong and were even able to contend against rank five Gu Masters when they combined their strength.

"Look, they are actually surrounding Fairy Bi Xia of Heavenly Lotus Sect!" An elite disciple with sharp sight shouted.

"Hmph, demonic path's people, every single one of them needs to be executed!" Fang Zheng's expression turned incomparably cold and immediately commanded the crane group to charge down without thinking much.

"Hehehe, Fairy Bi Xia, it will be difficult for you to escape this calamity today!"

"To think our luck is so good today to be able to smell the aroma of Fairy Bi Xia. Even if we suffered heavy injuries, it is worth it."

The four great obscenities winked as they pressed on towards the three female Gu Masters.

"Damn it." Fairy Bi Xia gritted her snow-white teeth. She was seriously injured and did not have strength to break through.

Just as she was starting to feel desperation and was thinking of committing suicide, she suddenly heard the cries of a group of cranes from above her.

"Who is it?" The four great obscenities raised their heads and shouted.

"Immortal Crane Sect's elite disciple, Fang Zheng!" Fang Zheng was standing on the back of the ironbeak flying crane king, his tongue seemed to burst out with thunder.

He stood upright and proudly on the crane's back, his body was robust, his brows thick and his eyes like that of a tiger's. He fixed his gaze on the four obscenities and waved his hand.

The elite disciples behind him and ten thousand ironbeak flying cranes passed him and charged towards the four obscenities.

"Heavens, so many cranes!"

"It is one of the ten great sects, the elite disciples of the Immortal Crane Sect..."

"What bad luck, we have injuries and can't contend against this group, let's retreat!"

The four great obscenities sized the situation before turning to flee and soon, they had escaped far away, their figures disappeared from everyone's sight.

"These demonic path trash, they might not have other abilities but they are pretty quick in running." The elite disciples laughed loudly.

"Are you okay?" Fang Zheng got off from the back of the crane and approached Fairy Bi Xia, asking softly.

"I, I am okay... thank you young master Fang Zheng for saving me!" Fairy Bi Xia looked at Fang Zheng, her face blushed red and her gaze carried hints of infatuation.

She had thought she would not be able to escape this calamity, but a hero came falling from the sky.

Fang Zheng was like the hero saving the beauty and it left a deep impression on Fairy Bi Xia.

Chapter 337: Leaving somebody in the lurch

"Two young babies, leave behind your primeval stones, strip off your clothes and kowtow to your grandpa thrice, and I shall spare your little lives. Gahaha..."

A rank three old demonic Gu Master with dishevelled hair suddenly appeared and blocked Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing's way.

"Hehe, the old monster Hei Shi is making it difficult for newbies again."

"These two youths are out of luck considering they ran into the old monster Hei Shi."

"That girl looks quite pretty.Why does she look somewhat familiar? It is a pity the old monster Hei Shi is here, otherwise we would have made a move."

From within the darkness, many demonic Gu Masters looked here with sinister smiles on their faces.

Bam!

Fang Yuan's response was straightforward, he directly summoned his beast phantom.

The moment he made a move, the breath concealment Gu lost its effect, and his rank four aura was revealed in its whole.

Shock and desperation immediately showed on the old monster Hei Shi's face.

He wanted to escape but Bai Ning Bing also made a move at the same time and kept him in check.

The old monster Hei Shi was directly struck by beast phantom and turned into minced meat.

Blood, bone pieces and brain matter mixed together and splattered all around.

"I... what the f*ck...."

"Oh god, these two youths are both rank four Gu Masters!"

"I remember it now, they are black and white twin demons! One is called Fang Zheng and another is Bai Ning Bing, both are geniuses of the demonic path. They have made great names for themselves in Shang clan city's battle stage, especially Fang Zheng, people call him little beast king, almost having hegemony over the whole battle stage. Why are these two guys here?"

"The temptation of San Cha mountain's inheritance is too big, they were also attracted by it. Old monster Hei Shi kicked an iron board, his death was really tragic!"

Many Gu Masters watching from the darkness, as they opened their eyes wide in extreme shock and fear.

"Hmph!" Fang Yuan was not satisfied with killing the old monster Hei Shi. With a shift of his mind, he activated another beast phantom and charged towards a specific shadow.

Bam!

A huge sound resounded, the demonic Gu Master hiding in the shadow directly exploded into meat paste by Fang Yuan's attack.

Countless demonic Gu Masters drew in a sharp breath of cold air from the darkness.

"Jin Cheng En also died!"

"Little beast king has a heavy murderous nature, he doesn't let even spectators go."

"Let's go, let's go. Even the old monster Hei Shi could not resist their one move, it will be too late if we don't hurry now."

Trees shook, stones were lifted up; countless shadows scuttled out, fleeing towards every direction.

Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing quietly watched this and did not block them.

As they got closer to San Cha mountain, the demonic Gu Masters they ran into also increased.

During ordinary times, one could only occasionally run into these guys. However, San Cha mountain was like a fragrant honey that attracted all kinds of flies, bees and so on.

"We have yet to reach San Cha mountain, but we have seen all kinds of demons and ghosts fighting each other. It is obvious how chaotic the situation over at San Cha mountain is now." Bai Ning Bing's expression was indifferent but her tone was slightly heavy.

Several months had already passed since the three kings inheritance appeared on San Cha mountain, this caused a huge disturbance in Southern Border. Countless figures appeared one after another and rushed towards there.

Righteous path and demonic path fought against each other for a place in the quota to enter the inheritance.

San Cha mountain had already changed into a slaughterhouse. Every day, there was large amounts of lives lost in open fights and schemes.

"Kill them all, gain notoriety through killing. Kill until these people tremble in fear, only then will they not dare to lightly provoke us." Fang Yuan smiled coldly, his eyes filled with thick killing intent.

Fang Yuan was fully aware that reputation was very important when one went outside.

Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing were living in Shang clan city all this while, although their fame had spread, it was mostly limited to within the city.

Most people had not heard about Fang and Bai.

Killing all that stands in their way, killing to gain fame; this would be an enormous help to Fang Yuan's future plans.

"Alright. Let's continue using breath concealment Gu and hide our rank four aura. Killing like this is really splendid and very interesting. We can leave deep impressions on others and make them remember us for their whole lives." Bai Ning Bing smiled, her blue eyes shone with cold light. Her beauty was like that of a snow fairy, untouched by the mortal world. Her tone, however, was like a bloody, poisonous scorpion, and was filled with terrifying killing intent.

Breath concealing Gu was only a rank three Gu ; Fang and Bai were barely able to use it to conceal their rank four cultivation.

Fang Yuan advanced to rank four initial stage and he needed to replace many of his Gu. Bai Ning Bing was also the same.

"Three kings inheritance has many of the Gu I need. As long as I obtain those Gu, my set of strength path Gu worms will push towards completion. It will also provide me great help in advancing to rank five and allow me to dominate the mortal realm."

"Calculating the time, the Hu Immortal blessed land in central continent should also have opened. Fairy Bai Hu was a rank six Gu immortal and the inheritance she had left behind is intact, it is many times better than the three kings inheritance. Unfortunately, I am not in central continent. No, even if I were in central continent, I am not a disciple of the ten great sects and thus cannot participate in the contest at Tian Ti mountain. Sigh, such a pity..."

Fang Yuan gazed far away towards the direction of central continent before continuing to move forward.

Bai Ning Bing was silent as she walked alongside Fang Yuan.

The two crossed mountains and charged around everywhere; they would directly kill any demonic Gu Masters or righteous Gu Masters they met.

Their vicious reputation quickly spread.

In Fang Yuan's view, at every stage, there was an appropriate manner to developing oneself.

When one was weak, they should keep a low profile and do things secretly, suffering patiently and growing stealthily. When they were strong, they should spread their name and strike when the timing was right, making others feel fear and terror.

Sometimes, reputation was a much stronger weapon than strength.

Soon, Bai Ning Bing realized the advantage of reputation.

When they had just started on the journey, the Gu Masters along the way often tried to make things difficult for them. Just like that old monster Hei Shi, daring to jump out with just a mere rank three cultivation.

Fang and Bai were young, moreover Bai Ning Bing's stunning appearance caused others to have an impulse to commit crime.

Now, however, even though Fang and Bai were using breath concealment Gu and hiding their cultivation, their path was unimpeded, saving them a lot of trouble.

They had yet to truly reach San Cha mountain but their evil reputation had already spread till there.

Good deeds remain obscured while bad deeds spread over a thousand miles.

Such evil reputation was the fastest to spread.

Right now, everyone knew there were two terrifying demonic path rising stars, rank four geniuses, killing their way towards San Cha mountain, two who were very aggressive and easily killed people.

...

This day, they finally reached the foot of San Cha mountain.

Sounds of a fight suddenly came from ahead.

"Don't come here, don't come!" A female Gu Master shouted with terror all over her face and was faintly gasping; her clothing in rags, revealing her beautiful shoulders and thighs.

"Hehehe, little beauty, quietly obey us."

"If you resist anymore, be careful that I might just slash your pretty face!"

"Don't resist. Let us big brothers give you a taste of euphoria, hahaha...."

The demonic Gu Masters' eyes shone with a wolf-like green light as they continuously charged towards the female Gu Master.

The female Gu Master resisted with all her might, but she was alone and her strength was not enough; the situation was in full control of the several demonic Gu Masters.

"Damn it, damn it!" The female Gu Master bit her full lower lip with her pure white teeth, her face filled with anxiety and terror.

She retreated bit by bit, the clothings on her body were slowly cut open. Her smooth legs were exposed and her thick hair was in a mess. As she escaped, her chest bobbed like a white rabbit which provoked the attacking demonic Gu Masters to let out wolfish howls.

"Can anyone save me? Can anyone save me? I have thirty thousand primeval stones here!" The female Gu Master shouted, her weak voice further stimulate the desire in these Gu Masters.

"Nobody moves!"

"This little girl is our, Ten Tyrants', prey. Wait till our boss comes over."

"That's right, we don't want the thirty thousand primeval stones. We will enjoy this first, the rest of you can take turns later. Gahaha...."

Some righteous Gu Masters were just about to make their moves to rescue the girl, but when they heard the name of Ten Tyrants, they immediately chose to shrink back.

The boss of the Ten Tyrants was a rank four Gu Master!

"Who can save me, please save me..." The female Gu Master shouted sadly like the lament of a cuckoo. She kept on running, asking for help everywhere, but wherever she went, the Gu Masters would all retreat and avoid her.

Only Fang and Bai stood on their spots, watching indifferently.

"Two lords, please, I pray you for mercy, please save me." The female Gu Master's eyes shone with hope; the weeping beauty ran towards Fang Yuan and pleaded.

"Where did these two brats come from, mind your own business!"

"We are Nan mountain's Ten Tyrants, you two young juniors... eh? This can't be!"

These few demonic Gu Masters suddenly paled when they recognized Fang and Bai's identity.

"Although that person is disguising as a male, she is a female. These two, one man and one woman; black cloth, black hair and black eyes; white cloth, silver hair and blue eyes, aren't they the recently famous..."

"Black and white twin demons!"

The demonic Gu Masters immediately stopped, they fixed their gazes at Fang and Bai with profound fear.

Fang and Bai's reputation were the number one thing they heard recently.

These two might be young, but were true geniuses of the demonic path. They were both extremely ruthless and had a murderous nature. Most importantly, they both had rank four cultivation.

Such cultivation was terrifying!

Rank one were considered substandard, rank two could be said to be lackeys while rank three were the main pillars and held their own.

Rank four were already experts among Gu Masters, and were the leaders of ordinary clans. Even in Ten Tyrants, only their boss was at rank four middle stage.

As for rank five, they stood at the peak of the mortal world and were very few in numbers. Even in southern border with hundreds of thousands of mountains and countless heroes, there were only over a hundred rank five Gu Masters.

"Lord twin demons, save me, please save me!" The female Gu Master found a way out of her predicament and knelt on the ground in front of Fang and Bai, imploring.

The surrounding Gu Masters all casted their gazes here.

"These two are the black and white twin demons who just recently became famous, they are unexpectedly so young!"

"Ten Tyrants against black and white twin demons; one has been famous for a long time while the other are rising stars of the demonic path, this should be interesting."

"As long as the boss of the Ten Tyrants does not show up, they are no match for black and white twin demons. Black and white twin demons got a bargain, getting that beauty for free. Pfft, little beast king will have beauties on his left and right, he really has luck with women."

Under everyone's gazes, Fang Yuan took a light step back.

"Save you, why would I save you? Because of your superficial beauty, or do you think I am a kind person and like helping people?" Fang Yuan looked down at the kneeling Gu Master, his gaze cold and indifferent.

The female Gu Master stupidly raised her head to look at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan coldly smiled then looked at the Ten Tyrants' members behind him: "You can continue, I won't make a move. I've had such a tedious journey coming here, please do give me a good show."

Chapter 338: Hu Mei Er

Hearing Fang Yuan say that, a few members of Ten Tyrants showed a softer expression.

Next, one of them pounced and kept the female Gu Master on the ground.

The female Gu Master struggled to no avail, as this member of Ten Tyrants laughed and pulled with his demonic palm.

Tsk...

The silk clothing of the female Gu Master was torn open, showing her underwear.

Such a scene caused the people to howl like a wolf, as the demonic Gu Masters were very aroused.

Many righteous Gu Masters gritted their teeth secretly.

Someone wanted to stop them, but was stopped by another: "Don't do anything. There is not only the Ten Tyrants here, but also the black and white twin demons, are you courting death?"

"Moreover, that female Gu Master is not a righteous character. You don't have to involve yourself."

"Damn, members of the demonic path are truly scum of the world, unscrupulous and shameless!" Some Gu Masters were indignant, clenching their fists.

Many female Gu Masters looked away, shutting their eyes.

"No, no! I'm begging you, please stop..." That female Gu Master cried out in despair.

Bai Ning Bing was expressionless, as she stared at Fang Yuan. Fang Yuan was sneering, looking at the scene.

"My respects to the two black and white twin demons. We will report your act of friendship to our boss, since you gave the opportunity to us and merely watched." A Gu Master of Ten Tyrants walked up and cupped his fists towards Fang and Bai, smiling respectfully.

The other members walked to the female Gu Master.

One of them spit out some phlegm, cursing: "Little slut, do you think you can seduce the two lord black and white twin demons by begging? Naive! Stupid!"

"You sure ran fast, next I will make sure you enjoy yourself! Hehehe..." Another person laughed lecherously, looking extremely perverted.

As for the person on top of the female Gu Master, he was about to 'attack'.

At this moment, a pink light appeared from the female Gu Master's body, and exploded.

The male Gu Master was caught off guard and sent flying. He was like a comet, flying far away, landing after a hundred steps away, fainted.

"What?!"

"This female Gu Master is trying something funny, let's attack together!"

"What guts! You dare to resist us?"

The other members of the Ten Tyrants shouted as they pounced at the female Gu Master.

But the next moment, the pink light flashed again, and intense screams were heard.

The members of Ten Tyrant were sent flying all together.

The pink light displayed the female Gu Master's overwhelming battle strength, as she had a alluring and evil gaze, the disguise on her was completely removed, showing her true flirtatious appearance.

The members of Ten Tyrant were lying on the ground, shocked.

Who knows what methods she used, causing them to be weak and powerless on the ground, unable to get up.

The fierce and evil Ten Tyrant members were actually not the female Gu Master's match.

Such a sudden change caused everyone's expressions to change. Many people watched speechlessly, extremely surprised.

Only Fang Yuan's expression remained the same, as if he knew all along.

The female Gu Master laughed, after showing her true appearance, her alluring eyes were soul-stealing. A slender body with perfect curves, like a flowering peach in spring, made everyone extremely comfortable.

During this period, the members of Ten Tyrant got up.

Their strength slowly recovered.

But even so, the shock on their faces were still apparently. They felt a real rank four aura from the female Gu Master.

This female Gu Master's cultivation, was actually rank four!

Numerous people's expressions changed when they found out.

"Little beast king, you left a maiden in distress, are you a man?" The female Gu Master looked at Fang Yuan, showing an upset, annoyed expression, causing people greatly pity her.

At once, all the males stared at her fixedly.

Many Gu Master started to be jealous Fang Yuan. If this woman would give them one glance, it was worth dying for!

But Fang Yuan had no emotions, his tone was like ice, chilling to the bone: "Hu Mei Er, do you think this level of acting can trick me?"

The female Gu Master's pupils shrunk.

She did not expect Fang Yuan to expose her identity so easily.

But she quickly recovered, her lips pouting: "To think that my lowly name is known by lord little beast king. It is my great honor, but, before I exposed my true appearance, how did lord manage to find out?"

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "Before you showed your true self, I was only guessing. But whether I guessed right or wrong, I have no losses, am I right?"

Even if Hu Mei Er was a demonic Gu Master, upon hearing Fang Yuan's cruel words, her heart chilled.

"It is actually her..."

"This woman is famous in the demonic path, she is very scary. An expert at disguise, don't be moved by her appearance, she is a demoness that devours people whole, she is completely ruthless!"

"Hu Mei Er has a broad network, she has slept with many demonic Gu Masters, why did the Ten Tyrants provoke her?"

Ten Tyrant's members helped each other up as their faces were pale without a trace of blood.

By now, they had already understood, they were obviously toyed by Hu Mei Er.

Hu Mei Er had rank four cultivation, it was easy for her to deal with them. Her earlier disguise and performance was just to toy with them, she was trying to use them to probe and get close to the black and white demons.

But little beast king had sharp eyes, he actually saw through her disguise.

"Hahaha, Fang Zheng, you are truly heartless... But don't be too smug. You two have been too famous these few days, now the entire San Cha mountain knows that two demonic path geniuses are here. Be it righteous or demonic path, many seniors and experts are now trying to test you. You have offended many people, I advise you to stop here. Otherwise, you might lose your life when you ascend the mountain." Hu Mei Er laughed.

"Oh? That means, you are the first person sent to test us? Hehe, why are you worrying about our safety? As for offending people? The one thing I am not afraid of is offending people. So what if I offend every human alive?" Fang Yuan spoke plainly, but his words were chilling.

Hu Mei Er listened as her eyes glowed brightly, showing excitement in her eyes.

She laughed while covering her mouth: "Well said! What great courage, I like it. Not afraid to offend people? Then let me tell you, you looked down on my appearance, that is offending me. In this world, only villains and women are hard to please. I am not only a woman, but also a villain. Hehehe, little beast king, let's see who laughs till the end! I hope you can leave the mountain alive!"

Hu Mei Er said with a sharp gaze as she turned to leave immediately.

Everyone watched her pink dress flutter in the wind, her beautiful appearance as she left, leaving everyone speechless.

"Hu Mei Er..." Fang Yuan laughed coldly in his heart.

This Hu Mei Er was a demoness in the demonic path. She was very mysterious, no one knew her origins. In his previous life, she was very active, causing problems everywhere, sowing discord, causing fights and disputes wherever she went.

She cultivated the enchantment path, specifically, enchanting people. Using her appearance, she controlled many demonic experts, and she had many puppets all over southern border, among them, there were even rank five Gu Masters.

There were even rank four Gu Masters who fought due to jealousy over her.

However, others did not know her origins, but Fang Yuan knew.

This demoness had a great origin, she was the granddaughter of granny Mei Hua.

Granny Mei Hua was a rank six Gu Immortal in southern border, occupying the Mei Hua blessed land.

The demoness seduced men all over southern border, and had a specific interest in young men. In his previous life, a hundred years from now, she would gather her force and head to Xi Yang mountain.

Nobody knew what happened on the mountain, but the result was, she alone left the mountain.

What was worth mentioning was, she ascended the mountain as a rank four Gu Master, but she descended as rank five peak stage.

"This demoness has an unspeakable secret. Right now, she is starting to display her enchantment path and recruiting people. To think that she would develop an interest in me this time."

Fang Yuan compared his lives, and exclaimed.

He used the advantages of rebirth to grow quickly, and became chosen by Hu Mei Er. Hu Mei Er was interested in his potential, and wanted to seduce him into her puppet.

But how could that happen?

"Hmph, in the five hundred years of my past life, I had already eliminated my mortal desires. But the enchantment path has its strengths, I cannot be unguarded... Hu Mei Er must've gone to incite people to find trouble with me. She has the Gu from granny Mei Hua, if I want to kill her, I will need ample preparation and isolate that Gu from her. Hehe, I wonder which blind fool would dare to find trouble with me."

Fang Yuan analyzed in his heart.

Since he could not kill Hu Mei Er at the moment, he could only deal with the situation step-by-step.

Right now, Hu Mei Er's enchantment path had not reached greater success, she only had rank four Gu Masters under her charm.

As long as they are not rank five, Fang Yuan had no fear. He was confident that with his experience and this set of Gu worms, even if he cannot win, he will not lose.

...

Central continent, Tian Ti mountain.

Riding the flying crane, Fang Zheng and others travelled days and nights before arriving.

Before them, many elite disciples from the other ten sects had already arrived.

"It is the people from Immortal Crane Sect."

"Hmm? Why did Fairy Bi Xia from Heavenly Lotus Sect come with Immortal Crane Sect?"

"Who is that lad? Fairy Bi Xia is talking so happily with him, I have never seen Fairy Bi Xia speak so nicely to a guy from the same generation before."

Fang Zheng and the others' arrival attracted everyone's attention.

"Bi Xia, you arrived too. Do you know, since our last separation, I have been wanting to meet you again. This time, at the Hu Immortal Inheritance, I expected you to come. Thus, I begged my master to let me come here as well." A young man saw Fairy Bi Xia and quickly came over.

Bi Xia was speaking and laughing with Fang Zheng, but upon seeing him, her smile vanished.

Chapter 339: Trouble

"Oh, it is Sir Wei... no need to worry, thanks to young hero Fang Zheng, Bi Xia is safe and sound." Fairy Bi Xia avoided Wei Wu Shang's gaze and greeted.

"Young hero Fang?" Wei Wu Shang squinted, looking at Fang Zheng who was standing beside Fairy Bi Xia.

"Hello, I am Immortal Crane Sect's Fang Zheng." Fang Zheng smiled lightly, cupping his fists and greeting, oozing with friendliness.

"Young hero Fang Zheng, an elite disciple of Immortal Crane Sect, the number one in the most recent middle examination. He can control ten thousand cranes, thanks to these cranes, we could reach Tian Ti mountain so quickly."

Fairy Bi Xia said while looking at Fang Zheng, her face blushing shyly, as her tone carried a faint sweetness.

Along the way, she had conversed with Fang Zheng, and felt that they hit it off.

"Immortal Crane? These are just ironbeak flying ranes, although the number is a little large." Wei Wu Shang's eyes shone coldly, feeling extremely angry towards Fang Zheng.

He gritted his teeth, greeting Fang Zheng back: "Fang Zheng, you are an elite disciple of Immortal Crane Sect? That's great. I've long heard of Immortal Crane Sect's crane manipulation skill, I have always wanted to face-off against it. I would appreciate it if you would spar with me."

Saying so, Wei Wu Shang took large steps forward, his eyes glowing with overbearingness as he stared at Fang Zheng.

Fang Zheng was stunned, as he sensed animosity, feeling absurdity from the issue.

"Hahaha." In his mind, Lord Sky Crane laughed loudly: "A beauty's gratitude is the biggest problem, my disciple, the act of saving that little lass Bi Xia has brought you many enemies. This young girl Bi Xia is a great beauty, now that she likes you, you have trouble ahead. This Wei Wu Shang is your first challenger."

"Huh? Likes me?" Fang Zheng shouted in his mind.

Speaking of love, he felt a deep sorrow in his heart.

These years, he had a girl's image deep in his heart.

She was a mortal, she was very normal, very ordinary, and much much inferior to Fairy Bi Xia. But in Fang Zheng's heart, she had an extraordinary cuteness.

The times he spent with her, were the best memories in Fang Zheng's heart.

Unfortunately, she was already dead, no longer in this world.

She was Shen Cui, Fang Zheng's former servant.

Thinking of Shen Cui, Fang Yuan's heart sank: "The girl I liked is dead. Master, you know how hard I've worked these years, my biggest goal is to defeat my brother and take revenge for my ancestors, my uncle and aunt, Shen Cui, lord clan leader, lord Qing Shu, and fulfill their wishes. Although Gu Yue village was destroyed, the Gu Yue bloodline still exists!"

"Hahaha, my foolish disciple, even if that is what you want, this Wei Wu Sheng will not let you off. Since you decided to save Fairy Bi Xia, why didn't you realize that?" Lord Sky Crane laughed.

"But... I do not want to spar with him. I've heard of this Wei Wu Shang in Immortal Crane Sect. He is a healing Gu Master, a rising star in Heaven's Envy Sect, a strong A grade aptitude genius. He is most skilled in healing himself, often leaving unscathed after a battle. If I battle him, even if I win, my condition will not be at its peak. It will negatively affect my performance when competing for the Gu Immortal Inheritance."

Lord Sky Crane laughed heartily: "Don't worry, go ahead and fight. The Hu Immortal Inheritance on Tian Ti mountain is special. It will not make you compete in terms of battle strength, it is a contest of willpower and determination. With my soul assisting you secretly, you have a great advantage!"

After pausing for a while, Lord Sky Crane continued: "You are still too young, you do not know the usefulness of reputation. Sometimes, reputation is more useful than strength, this is a rare opportunity, defeat these challengers and improve your reputation. Use the flying cranes and don't worry about their deaths. We have lots of cranes in Immortal Crane Sect, even if you use them all, we can return to the sect and replenish your army."

Hearing his master say so, Fang Zheng sighed, saying to Wei Wu Shang: "Since you want to battle, so be it."

"Excellent! Please." Wei Wu Shang sneered, stomping and shooting into the air like lightning.

Fang Zheng did not show any weakness, waving his hand and stepping on a flying crane, as ten thousand cranes cried out together, as if greeting their king.

Once the battle began, everyone got excited.

"Boss Fang Zheng, all the best, defeat this sissy from Heaven's Envy Sect!" Immortal Crane Sect's elite disciples shouted.

"Junior brother Wei, teach this lad a lesson." Wei Wu Sheng had his supporters.

Wei Wu Shang nodded, intense battle intent burning in his eyes.

He was the leader of the elite disciples sent by Heaven's Envy Sect this time, Fang Zheng's ten thousand crane group could scare ordinary elite disciples, but not him.

He had his own trump card!

"Battle!" Wei Wu Shang activated the Gu worms in his body, as his body flashed in the air and vanished.

The next moment, the space was torn apart as he travelled through several hundred steps away, directly appearing in front of Fang Zheng.

"Space piercing Gu?!" Even Lord Sky Crane was shocked.

An intense battle unfolded.

At the same time, on San Cha mountain.

In a certain cave, the Ten Tyrants gathered.

"That means, you were all used by Hu Mei Er to test the Black and White Demons?!" The leader of Ten Tyrants, "Tyrant Heng Mei", muttered.

"That's right, boss, that demoness tricked us all, and even injured seventh and tenth brother. Boss, you have to avenge us!" The second brother of Ten Tyrants shouted.

Smack!

Tyrant Heng Mei slapped.

The second brother of Ten Tyrant was harshly slapped on his cheeks, his body turning on the spot.

"Bo... boss!" He held his face, looking at Tyrant Heng Mei in shock.

"Heavily injured? That is perfect, as long as they're not dead. You bunch with sperms for brains, control your lower body. I instructed you earlier to mind your actions and words already, do you really think this is still Nan mountain?!"

Tyrant Heng Mei scolded: "Wrong! This is San Cha mountain!"

"Be it Kong Ri Tian, Long Qing Tian, or Wu Shen Tong, Yi Chong, all of them can kill you like an ant easily. Although you have rank three cultivation, what is the most important reason you are able to stay here? Isn't it all due to me!"

"Hmph, this matter is a warning to all of you. I have to tell you, don't find problems with Hu Mei Er. This demoness seduces men to their death, she has a wide network. She is involved with Lin San Chi, has rumors with Li Xian, and even Mo Wu Tian."

Tyrant Heng Mei's words shocked the nine brothers.

Lin San Chi was a rank four demonic Gu Master, he was not only skilled in the metal path, but was also an earth path Gu Master. His metal and earth specialty was renowned through the land.

Li Xiao was similarly just as strong, he was not a native of southern border, but came from eastern sea. He was an unscrupulous merchant famous among the demonic path members, most skilled at finding opportunities to buy low and sell high. His network and human relationships were wide, many demonic Gu Master's loot were sold off by him.

As for Mo Wu Tian, he is even scarier.

He inherited a mysterious inheritance of an ancient Gu Immortal, and was the number one rising star of the demonic path, an absolute young genius.

Be it Lin San Chi, Li Xian, or Mo Wu Tian, they are all rank four Gu Masters.

"These famous people are all related to that demoness?" The members of Ten Tyrant heard this and went pale, their hearts palpitating with fear.

"I'll tell you one last time, this is not Nan mountain! Sigh, I asked you all to use your brains often and learn from mistakes, but you refuse to listen. Sigh, this three kings inheritance is not a small matter. Who knows how many formidable characters would show up." Tyrant Heng Mei sighed as he said.

The other brothers looked at each other, speechless.

Tyrant Heng Mei saw that the time was right, and changed the topic: "But no need to worry, on San Cha mountain now, the rank four and five Gu Masters are restraining each other, no one dares to act rashly. We the Ten Tyrants of Nan mountain are not to be trifled with. We cannot take this lying down, let's go, accompany me to find the black and white demons."

"Boss, you're going personally to find the black and white demons?" Someone expressed shock.

"Boss, you are rank four middle stage, a senior of the demonic path, when you were roaming in the world, they were still babies."

"That's right, boss, we'll go and ask them to come. You giving them an audience is their honor."

"Hmph, what do you know!" Tyrant Heng Mei chided: "The black and white demons are so young. The fact that they did not attack you this time means they know of my name, and know how to hold back. But they are youngsters, they love their 'face'. If I put down my ego and go to meet them personally, it is giving them full respect. Next, if I mention working together and come up with a plan to deal with Hu Mei Er, they are sure to agree. Hehehe..."

"Boss, I understand. You are using them as the vanguard!"

"Boss, you are a genius. This 'Black and White Demons' are only around twenty years old, they are too young. Now, they and Hu Mei Er are at odds, if they hear your suggestion, they would be extremely thrilled."

"Once boss plans, it truly is phenomenal!"

The Ten Tyrant members started bootlicking their boss.

"Hahaha." Tyrant Heng Mei laughed loudly, waving his hand: "Brother, come with me to visit the black and white demons!"

Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing looked up at San Cha mountain peak.

This San Cha mountain has a peculiar design, from the mountain foot, it goes up to three hills, looking from afar, it resembles a fork with three tips, pointing at the sky.

Above the three peaks are the entrances to the three kings inheritance.

Every once in a while, the mountain peak would shoot out three beams of light, and allow people to enter.

Once the number of people reach an amount, the light pillar to vanish, and the entrance would disappear.

After that, Gu Masters who failed to pass through the tests would be thrown out from time to time. Of course, there are also many deaths inside the inheritance every time.

"There is about eight days till the next opening of the inheritance. Let's find a place to settle down for now." Fang Yuan gave the surroundings a sweeping gaze as he saw a cave in the middle of the mountain waist.

Chapter 340: Beaten to a pulp

San Cha mountain was originally a place no one showed interest towards; and was a place Che clan and Zuo clan had interactions.

However, since the inheritance opened, it had become extremely lively and there would be people moving through the forests frequently.

Clashes and disputes occurred frequently, right now it was still relatively peaceful.

Every time the light pillar opened, the entry quota was limited. At that time, it would be a scene of carnage at San Cha mountain.

To fight for a chance to enter the inheritance, all the Gu Masters chose to stay on the mountain.

This led to a phenomenon. The stronger the Gu Masters, the closer towards the mountain peak they stayed. This caused them to be in a favorable position when the inheritance appeared, since they could much easily rush towards it.

The cave Fang Yuan chose was on the middle of the mountain. From the traces around the cave, there was clearly someone living in it.

Sure enough, when they got near the cave, a loud and clear voice was transmitted from within the cave: "This is my, Mang Kuang's, territory. Get lost, or else you will die a violent death!"

"Hahaha, Mang Kuang? What crap is that! This place is pretty good, I have taken a liking to it, get lost." Fang Yuan laughed outside the cave and issued an ultimatum.

"Screw your gr*ndmother, you want it the hard way! Since you are looking to die, then don't blame me for being ruthless!"

Following the voice, a burly man walked out of the cave.

His upper body was bare; he was wearing a worn-out hemp knitted shorts; cyan snake scales covered his whole body; his face was covered with long beard; blood veins showed on his eyes; and his black hair fell down his head in disarray. He walked out of the cave looking like a furious fiend.

"Two blind fools... eh?!"

Mang Kuang looked at Fang and Bai, he was cursing with his rough voice when suddenly his pupils shrunk and his jaw opened wide. His gaze revealed a bewildered expression.

"You two, could you be the black and white twin demons?"

"What do you think?" Bai Ning Bing laughed faintly, her blue eyes flashing with killing intent.

Mang Kuang only felt chills rising from his back and spreading over his body in seconds.

Black and white twin demons were rank four Gu Masters, while he was only at rank three upper stage. Moreover, he had heard about how these two killed without blinking their eyes, and how cruel their methods were.

"Damn it! I have been hiding here without doing anything, what did I do to deserve this? This really is misfortune dropping from the sky..." Mang Kuang's thoughts were in disorder.

In an instant, the vicious face suddenly changed; the raised eyebrows drooped, the wide opened eyes narrowed down to a slit, the bent corner of his lips immediately rose up into a smile; he did everything he could to show his goodwill.

"It is my greatest fortune in this life for both lords to take a liking to my cave!"

Mang Kuang bent his back and rubbed his hands, giving a flattering smile towards Fang and Bai.

His body was tall and robust but when he shrunk down and bent his back, his original rampant domineering aura immediately disappeared into oblivion; this matched with his boorish appearance was simply like a clown fiesta.

"Hmm, you are sensible, you can get lost now." Fang Yuan waved his hand.

"Yes, yes, yes." Mang Kuang seemed to have received an amnesty as he slipped out and immediately ran far away.

After forcing out Mang Kuang, Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing entered the cave together.

The cave was already arranged properly by Mang Kuang and they did not need to waste their energy to make any arrangements.

"San Cha mountain is filled with danger, we will take turns to stay guard at night for the next eight days. If one sleeps, the other must be awake." Fang Yuan warned Bai Ning Bing.

"Naturally." Bai Ning Bing nodded.

"Hui Mei Er won't leave it at that, we will be facing constant troubles in these eight days. However, it is also good that these people are sending themselves to us, we can establish our might and that matches with our intention."

Fang Yuan had just finished saying this when a voice came from outside the cave.

"Are black and white twin demons inside? I am Tyrant Heng Mei, I have long looked forward to meeting you two. This time, I especially came in to pay a visit."

"Tyrant Heng Mei? Isn't he the boss of Ten Tyrants? I heard he is very cruel, cultivates strength path, likes to eat little children's flesh and has spread fear over Nanshan." Bai Ning Bing glanced at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan sneered inside.

He had planned to go find trouble with this Tyrant Heng Mei, but to think the latter actually dropped in himself.

The two walked out of the cave and looked at the eight people standing outside the cave.

At the front was a robust body, bare and flat chest, black chest hair growing all over his chest. A dense aura of rank four middle stage was let out from all over his body.

However, this demonic path's figure famous for his savageness was wearing a smile right now. When he saw Fang and Bai, he immediately cupped his hands and one could only take him as an elegant black bear at first glance.

"To think the black and white twin demons had such large background." Tyrant Heng Mei had intentionally spoken in a loud voice and attracted the attention of many nearby Gu Masters.

"Even Tyrant Heng Mei came to pay a visit to them personally." Many were surprised.

"Fortunately, I ran out....when did Tyrant Heng Mei become so polite?" Mang Kuang still had not run far away, right now he touched his chest and felt the lingering fear.

"Tyrant Heng Mei, it is good you came, I was just about to visit you." Fang Yuan responded.

Tyrant Heng Mei's smile became even deeper, thinking Fang Yuan was going to pay a visit to him.

But who knew Fang Yuan's next words immediately caused his smile to stiffen.

"I heard you are also a strength path Gu Master, let's enjoy a battle of life and death and determine who is stronger. I, Fang Zheng, am walking the strength path and am going to become the number one in the strength path! Hand over your life!"

Finished speaking, Fang Yuan activated his Gu and directly launched an assault at Tyrant Heng Mei.

"What?!" Tyrant Heng Mei came back to his senses, he was startled and also furious.

He had broken the tradition and came to pay a visit, but to think this 'Fang Zheng' was an ungrateful guy and attacked him without saying anything further.

This, what kind of person is this?

Is this still a person? The nerves in his brain are jumbled up, right?!

Fang Yuan did not care about his thoughts as he charged quickly towards Tyrant Heng Mei.

All-out effort Gu !

Without saying any words, he directly attacked.

Grrr!

A brown bear phantom appeared from behind him.

Violent strength Gu !

Tyrant Heng Mei opened his eyes with anger, he did not dodge put put his arms up to block head-on.

With the activation of violent strength Gu, his body enlarged and increased his strength sharply.

Bam!

Fang Yuan fiercely smashed into Tyrant Heng Mei, sending the latter back by five steps while he, himself, bounced back from the terrifying strength.

Tyrant Heng Mei was at rank four middle stage and commanded the other nine members of Ten Tyrants. He had lorded over Nan mountain for many years and had deep foundations.

"Hmph! Little beast king, I gave you face but you don't know what's good for you." Tyrant Heng Mei shouted, but he did not take the initiative to attack.

He was at rank four middle stage and knew he was stronger after crossing one move with Fang Yuan since the latter was only at rank four initial stage.

However, there was not only one rank four on the scene, there was also Bai Ning Bing who was standing there.

Tyrant Heng Mei was sure of winning against Fang Zheng, but it would be very difficult for him to fight against two.

"Tyrant Heng Mei, why are you being so careful? Bai Ning Bing, you deal with the others, Tyrant Heng Mei is mine!" Fang Yuan laughed loudly and shrugged his shoulders before charging towards Tyrant Heng Mei again.

"I will give you five minutes, if you can't finish it by then, I will take over." Bai Ning Bing slightly raised her brows, her blue eyes flashing with sharp light.

"Boastful juniors!" Hearing Fang and Bai's casual conversation, Tyrant Heng Mei felt his anger was about to burst out.

He had a violent temperament, he already outdid himself by maintaining his patience till now. Knowing that the situation was hard to improve, he threw away his other thoughts and let the murderous aura in his mind surge forth.

Fight!

Two sides collided.

Fang Yuan against Tyrant Heng Mei while Bai Ning Bing suppressed the remaining members of the Ten Tyrants.

It was a chaotic battlefield!

Boulders were smashed, mountain creeks ran dry, caves collapsed, and there were sounds of thunder-like explosions.

Tyrant Heng Mei became more fearful. Fang Yuan possessed bitter strength Gu , his strength and fighting strength grew the more injuries he suffered.

When he crossed moves against Fang Yuan just before, he had thought the so-called little beast king was no more than that.

Reaching the halfway stage, his expression turned grave.

And when Fang Yuan burst out with six beast phantoms at the same time, Tyrant Heng Mei's face lost color.

"This little beast king, how could he be so strong?! Not only is his Gu worm combination superior to mine, he also has plentiful battle experience. How did he live to have such skillful and ruthless moves, there is not even a shadow of a young person in him. He is simply a hundred year old monster!"

"No wonder he acts so overbearingly, with such strength, even I would have no worries in acting like this. I have failed bad this time! I must retreat!"

Fang Yuan met frontal attacks with swift and fierce strikes, like a fierce tiger leaving the mountain or a flood dragon overturning the seas. Tyrant Heng Mei was gasping and his energy and blood were in disorder from Fang Yuan's attacks.

The main point was, every time Fang Yuan suffered injuries, he would become stronger.

Now, Tyrant Heng Mei was already not able to continue fighting against Fang Yuan. If Fang Yuan became even stronger, that would be too horrible!

Every time Tyrant Heng Mei thought of this, his fighting spirit decreased by a little.

As the fight continued, he did not dare to attack at all. There were clear opportunities to attack Fang Yuan, but he started hesitating.

"What should I do, attack or not?"

With such thoughts, how could he fight well?

Tyrant Heng Mei was slowly falling into a passive situation; Fang Yuan however, had let go of all his apprehension, his attacks were like the tides, coming waves after waves, continuous and endless.

Beast phantoms flashed one after another in the air, there would be violent sounds every time Fang Yuan attacked.

The explosive sounds came again and again, all the people who heard it felt their hearts throb in fear.

"What kind of fierce offense is this?!"

"Even a formidable senior like Tyrant Heng Mei is not Fang Zheng's match..."

"Fang Zheng is clearly at rank four initial stage but he is suppressing the middle stage Tyrant Heng Mei."

"Little beast king..." Many people were secretly observing the battle and thought over this nickname of Fang Yuan.

"Who is the tyrant here?" Mang Kuang felt quite helpless. He could tell Fang Yuan was more brutish and more unreasonable than Tyrant Heng Mei. The fiendish Tyrant Heng Mei paled in comparison to Fang Zheng.

"Fang Zheng, don't go too far!" Tyrant Heng Mei spurted out blood; his chest, arms and legs were all completely fractured. He wanted to retreat, but Fang Yuan had already seen through his plan. Bai Ning Bing killed the other members of the Ten Tyrants and firmly locked him down.

Howl howl howl!

Howl howl howl!

Fang Yuan pointed his finger, six large beast phantoms turned into solid forms and fell down from the sky, submerging Tyrant Heng Mei.

Bam!

A loud sound echoed and dust scattered everywhere.

Tyrant Heng Mei was beaten to a pulp, his internal organs and bone fragments splattered over the ground.

Gasp...

Countless sharp inhaling noises could be heard from the surroundings.

Chapter 341: What ferocity and wickedness!

Tian Ti mountain was the number one mountain in central continent. It was also called the land of inheritances and the mountain of sages.

Its height was over three thousand kilometers, it was imposing and had a grand presence. Its peak seemed to pierce through the skies and was hidden beyond the snowy fog and clouds.

What was extremely unusual was there were not many craggy rocks on the mountain.

Giant square shaped rocks reclined upon each other, stretching from the base of the mountain towards the top, forming stairs.

However, the scale of this stairs was so huge that there was an old legend about it in central continent saying the stairway reached the realm of the immortals and was a bridge connecting heaven and earth.

There were many touching, mysterious, tragic, and joyful stories revolving around Tian Ti mountain.

Tian Ti mountain became the holy land of central continent's Gu Masters, a place closest to the immortal court. Many Gu Masters seeked for immortality but failed, and before death, they would place their tombs here. At the same time, a large majority of them would also set up their inheritances here.

Tian Ti mountain hid countless inheritances, and only those fated could obtain them.

Every year, after clouds and mist that covered it dispersed, Tian Ti mountain would experience an enormous flow of people. Many inheritances would be inherited, and many new inheritances would be set up.

However, this year was different.

This year, the inheritance that opened at Tian Ti mountain was Hu Immortal blessed land which led to the appearance of Gu Immortals. After discussing, they made an alliance and locked this mountain, setting up a contest for their sect's juniors.

Right now, at the foot of Tian Ti mountain, an intense battle between the youngsters was already reaching its end.

Ten thousand cranes flew together and floated around Fang Zheng. Wei Wu Shang was panting and his clothes were in rags; he stared straight at Fang Zheng from within the layers of encirclement by the cranes.

"No, I haven't lost yet! I still have my trump card!" Wei Wu Shang was not resigned to admit defeat after being at the losing end.

If it was an ordinary situation, he would have conceded defeat already. But god knew how many elite disciples were fixing their gazes at this match.

Wei Wu Shang was not representing only himself but also the Heaven's Envy Sect behind him. At the same time, others did not matter but Fairy Bi Xia whom he admired was also watching the match.

"I cannot lose!" With this thought, Wei Wu Shang valiantly activated a Gu in his aperture.

He had always been hiding this Gu, not using it even at the important sect examination.

Once this Gu was activated, it created a colorless breeze.

The light breeze revolved around Wei Wu Shang's body, moving his clothes and caressing his hair.

However, Fang Zheng looked like he was facing a great enemy.

It was because Lord Sky Crane had already reminded him loudly: "Not good! This kid actually has injury wind Gu. Defend, defend with all your might, this Gu can whip up injury wind; it looks light and harmless, but it is extremely terrifying. Heaven's Envy Sect's junior was not weak indeed. This seems to be his trump card!"

Injury wind blew; Fang Zheng completely gave up on attacking and used all his strength to defend.

Injury wind looked gentle, but wherever it blew, the cranes cried out in pain; countless ironbeak flying cranes crashed down to the ground like their wings were broken.

Injury wind blew on Fang Zheng's body; the defensive light around his body continuously flickered.

Beads of sweat dripped from Fang Zheng's forehead, he gritted his teeth and transferred the primeval essence from his aperture to his defensive Gu endlessly.

The stalemate lasted a while, finally Wei Wu Shang sighed inwardly and stopped activating injury wind Gu.

It was not that he did not want to continue the fight, but his aperture was already close to drying up.

Gu Masters all had a common point, that was when primeval essence was consumed, the Gu Master's fighting strength would sharply decrease.

Rank one to rank five Gu Masters all suffered from the restraints of primeval essence. Only when they went beyond mortal and reached the realm of immortals, becoming a Gu Immortal, would they be able to have endless primeval essence.

"I lost." Wei Wu Shang's gaze was dark.

He had calculated it clearly: His primeval essence was exhausted and so he did not have any more strength to battle. However, Fang Zheng had been commanding flying cranes to battle from the start; his primeval essence consumption was relatively less and was sure to have some more primeval essence left.

"Brother Wei is worthy to be Heaven's Envy Sect's elite disciple, possessing such unusual and incisive methods; I have increased my knowledge and my horizons have been broadened. My primeval essence has also almost been exhausted by brother. How about we consider this spar as a draw?" Fang Zheng smiled.

"What?" Wei Wu Shang was stunned.

What was Fang Zheng saying? He was very clear of his own situation. How could he have a Gu that could exhaust Fang Zheng's primeval essence?

However, Wei Wu Shang immediately realized Fang Zheng was telling a lie.

"Fang zhen is giving me a way out of this situation." After understanding Fang Zheng's plan, there was a complex expression on Wei Wu Shang's face.

The disciples of every great sect could not casually make their moves.

Because they represented not only themselves, but also the sect behind them.

Moreover, with Fairy Bi Xia at the scene, Wei Wu Shang could truly not afford to lose this battle.

Since Fang Zheng gave him a way out, Wei Wu Shang quickly cupped his fists towards Fang Zheng after hesitating for a moment: "Brother Fang is a young hero, I am filled with admiration. Immortal Crane Sect indeed has deep foundations for being able to teach a figure like brother. I have benefitted from this spar and like brother Fang said, we will consider this match a draw."

Wei Wu Shang said so on the surface, but in truth, he secretly transmitted to Fang Zheng: "Fang Zheng, I, Wei Wu Shang, shall remember your leniency and will definitely repay it in the future. However, Fairy Bi Xia is my love, I will not concede on this. I will train harder and spar with you again in the future!"

Fang Zheng smiled, he nodded on the surface, but was inwardly feeling a headache.

Wei Wu Shang continued with the secret communication: "Fang Zheng, you need to be careful. Fairy Bi Xia has many admirers, not just me. Even with your formidable strength, you will still have four competitors. They are Heaven River Chen Da Jiang, Rising Purple Lightning Gu Ting, Nine Death Sorrowful Wind Tang Ru Qi and Tigress Zhao Shu Ye. You are so close with Fairy Bi Xia, they will definitely come find trouble for you. You better not lose."

Fang Zheng's gaze could not help but flicker at the mention of these four famous names, feeling that his headache had become worse.

As for Lord Sky Crane, he was laughing heartily in his mind.

Sure enough, like Wei Wu Shang said, three days later, disciples of Ancient Soul Sect arrived at Tian Ti mountain. Leading them was Gu Ting, and after knowing of the matter between Fairy Bi Xia and Fang Zheng, he immediately sent a challenge.

To avoid this unexpected calamity, Fang Zheng chose to avoid the fight.

Gu Ting naturally was not willing to leave the matter at that; he would visit Fang Zheng's residing cave every day and provoke him to a fight.

He continued this for seven days in a row.

His words became more vulgar as time passed. Immortal Crane Sect's other disciples were unsatisfied and went to find him but were defeated.

Ancient Soul Sect's momentum rose greatly, and at the eight day, everyone went to block Fang Zheng's cave entrance and cursed endlessly.

"Fang Zheng, you ostrich, still not coming out?"

"Fang Zheng you are hiding now, but can you hide for your entire life? Obediently stop getting in contact with Fairy Bi Xia and big brother Gu Ting will magnanimously spare you."

"Immortal Crane Sect is merely so, they actually taught such cowardly disciple."

...

At the mention of Immortal Crane Sect, Fang Zheng who was in the cave let out a sigh and helplessly walked out of the cave.

He could endure the curses directed towards him. However, once it involved his master, his temperament changed. Disciple needed to uphold the prestige of their masters, this was an important value of central continent. If he did not uphold it, then when he returned to Fei He mountain later, he would be impeached and even receive punishment.

Lord Sky Crane made a loud din inside him: "Gahaha... Fang Zheng, my disciple, do you understand now? What I have been telling you from the start is not wrong, right? Blindly enduring will let others misunderstand and bully you. In this world, the more harmless and cowardly you appear, the more people will appear that will want to bully you. Fight, defeat this Gu Ting! Shut the mouth of these people from Ancient Soul Sect! Improve your reputation!"

"Sigh... one has to compromise in this world, I really feel it now. I can only fight!" Fang Zheng gained an understanding with this event.

Gu Ting, come, let's fight!

...

At the similar time as the fight between Fang Zheng and Gu Ting, far away at southern border's San Cha mountain, a battle ended.

The battlefield was a mess; blood all over the ground, smashed rocks, destroyed trees and craters all around.

Fang Yuan stood proud on the battlefield while his opponent Fei Li was kneeling on the ground, kowtowing and begging for forgiveness.

"Lord Fang Zheng, please be magnanimous and spare me!" Fei Li continuously kowtowed while begging bitterly.

He had a cultivation of rank four middle stage and was also a strength path Gu Master. He had been full of spirits, but now his body was soaked with blood, his right arm broken and his two legs fractured, cutting out an extremely sorry figure.

"Since you are begging for forgiveness, then first hand over your expend strength Gu and I shall consider whether to accept it or not." Fang Yuan looked down upon Fei Li, cold light bursting out of his eyes.

Fei Li hesitated before handing over expend strength Gu.

This Gu was his vital Gu and also his core Gu, it made his enemies waste more strength when making any movements, doubling the expenditure of their stamina.

Handing over the expend strength Gu, Fei Li lost his vital Gu and suffered a heavy backlash, spurting out huge mouthfuls of blood.

Fang Yuan's gaze flashed as he accepted expend strength Gu: "I have considered, expend strength Gu is not enough to exchange for your life."

Fei Li's eyes opened wide and not considering the critical state of his body, he shouted: "Lord Fang Zheng, this is my most precious Gu!"

Bam!

With a shift of Fang Yuan's mind, beast phantoms directly pounced forward and turned Fei Li into minced meat.

"Pauper." Fang Yuan looked at the disfigured corpse below him and sneered.

Then his gaze swept through the battlefield.

The spectators were not few, but all of them subconsciously chose to avoid Fang Yuan's gaze.

Fang Yuan laughed loudly: "What's wrong? Sky Tiger Xue San Si isn't here? You guys tell her, we are both strength path Gu Masters, three days later, I will come visit her and exchange pointers!"

The moment these words came out, it caused an uproar.

Little beast king was too violent; a few days ago, he had killed Tyrant Heng Mei, and at this battle, Fei Li begged him for forgiveness, but he did not let him go and smashed him into minced meat.

Now, he was going to challenge Sky Tiger Xue San Si!

What ferocity and wickedness was this!

Chapter 342: Biao

"What, the little beast king is challenging me?" When she first heard the news, Xue San Si refused to believe it.

She was thinking, she had no relationship with the black and white demons, she had never offended them, not even meeting them before. How could they come to find trouble with her for no reason?

But soon, she investigated, and realized this was true!

"How can this be? What is this little beast king's brain made of? The three kings inheritance is opening in a few days, he still has the mood to challenge me? What did I do to you, why are you messing with me like this?!"

Xue San Si felt helpless and annoyed.

"Is it simply because we are both on the strength path, thus he wants to compare who is stronger? Sigh, this maniac!"

Xue San Si thought about it thoroughly, finally classifying Fang Yuan as a lunatic, unable to be understood by a normal human.

A few months ago, she had heard of the reputation of the black and white demons.

As the passed, the two of them got more famous, as rumors spread further and wider.

They are the publicly recognised new rising stars of the demonic path.

Initially, Xue San Si did not mind it, Fang Yuan and Hu Mei Er had a conflict, and she was gloating over it.

But now, she could not laugh anymore.

After the black and white demons came to San Cha mountain, they not only did not keep a low profile, but even create huge problems.

Especially that little beast king, he does things with no discretions, unreasonable and ruthless, causing people to feel threatened.

Tyrant Heng Mei from Ten Tyrants visited him out of goodwill, but was killed. Fei Li already begged for mercy, but Fang Yuan did not let him off, beating him to a pulp, into meat paste.

The thing is, those were rank four Gu Masters, with middle stage cultivation. But little beast king used initial stage cultivation to kill these two outrightly. Such battle strength bred fear in people's hearts.

Xue San Si also had rank four middle stage cultivation, she feels that her strength was about the same as Tyrant Heng Mei and Fei Li. Now that Fang Yuan was challenging her, her heart sank as she felt a great threat, even a trace of fear that she had to admit!

"This Fang Zheng is too cruel and unreasonable. He is trying to step on us, these seniors' corpses to strengthen his reputation. Fei Li was the sacrifice for his ambitions, now it is my turn."

Such arrogant acts, Xue San Si had done it when she was young.

But back then, she only killed rank three Gu Masters, she was nowhere near Fang Yuan's ruthlessness, choosing Gu Masters at a higher stage than him to battle.

To speak the truth, Xue San Si did not want to battle with this lunatic Fang Yuan. But unfortunately, her godfather was in closed cultivation refining a Gu recently, now that Fang Yuan publicly challenged her, she had to accept it.

In this world, people often had no choice.

If she, Xue San Si, did not accept the challenge, the reputation that she had built up all these years would go down the drain.

Xue San Si has been in the demonic path for many years. She had a clear understanding of this world's cruelty.

This was a difficult world to live in, for that chance of survival, all the different species fight it out with their lives!

The kinder and weaker you show yourself, not only would you not gain peace, but you would even get yourself into greater danger, and attract the greed of many.

Demonic path Gu Masters who got to Xue San Si's height have surely killed many people, and offended even more people.

The world was like this, if you did not kill people, and offend people, how could you gain the resources needed to advance your cultivation? How could you gain fame from battle results?

To defend her reputation, Xue San Si quickly agreed to Fang Yuan's challenge.

The two decided on a wide valley as the location for their battle.

Three days later, Xue San Si saw Fang Yuan for the first time.

She was shocked, Fang Yuan did not have the fierce appearance in her imagination, in fact he looked rather gentlemanly, without any boorish features, his eyes were dark like an abyss, extremely peaceful.

"Sky Tiger, I've heard of you, you offended a higher-up in your clan, and was exiled. You secretly worked hard, taking a risk to kill beast kings, and using the Gu worms u gained to arm yourself, finally becoming an expert slowly and steadily. After that, you went back and killed the numerous elders that framed you in the past. To be honest, I admire you quite a bit." Fang Yuan spoke.

Such a respectful tone caused people to listen in shock.

"Why did he change his nature? Speaking so politely?"

"Does he have an interest in Sky Tiger? To be fair, although Sky Tiger looks ordinary, she has the proper curves, her body is great, she is indeed a beauty."

"Hmph, is little beast king that kind of person? He disregarded even Hu Mei Er, he is ruthless and cold-blooded, a fearsome person. I've learnt from these few days, you guys should not place any hopes on him."

As the people discussed, Xue San Si replied Fang Yuan: "I'm flattered. Little beast king, the name of the black and white demons is renowned in this area."

Fang Yuan smiled lightly: "I cultivate the strength path, you are the same. If we spar, it will help both of us learn more. Before this, I have sparred with Tyrant Heng Mei and Fei Li, these two were great and gave me quite an experience. But such a sparring method is boring to me now. This time, why don't we change the sparring method."

Xue San Si listened, and raised her eyebrows: "Oh? What idea do you have, I'll listen to it."

"Simple, I'll stand here and let you hit me. After you finish, I'll hit you. Isn't that great and simple, it will end faster too. How about this, since you are a woman, I'll give you three hits, after that, I will only retaliate with one hit." Fang Yuan smiled as he said.

"Sparring like that?" Xue San Si's eyes glowed, attracted to Fang Yuan's proposal.

Fang Yuan staying still and letting her do three hits, such a suggestion was too alluring.

"Alright, let's do that." Xue San Si considered it through, agreeing.

"Please." Fang Yuan smiled lightly, staying still as he stretched out his right palm.

Xue San Si's eyes shone with brilliance, as her killing intent surged, shouting: "First move!"

Several Gu worms were activated at the same time in her aperture.

Her slim arms burst out in a bright light, turning into two tiger claws.

The tiger claws tore through the sky, hitting Fang Yuan harshly.

Fang Yuan vomited a mouthful of blood, flying out like a cannonball, landing on a huge rock behind him.

Bam!

There was a loud crash as the rock exploded, rock shrapnels flying everywhere.

"Good hit." Fang Yuan laughed loudly, standing up. His chest had an obvious concavity, at least four ribs were broken.

Not only that, Fang Yuan felt his intestines were bleeding too.

As the intense pain assaulted him, Fang Yuan endured it as his nerves were undergoing a huge trial.

Xue San Si's expression changed.

"That's right, Fang Zheng made a good plan. The more injured he got, the greater the strength he can use. Then do I attack harder or softer now?"

The harder she hits, the more injured Fang Yuan gets, and the higher his battle strength gets. If she hit softer, when it is his turn, she would be able to defend more easily.

'No, I should use all my strength to attack. Kill him in three hits!" Xue San Si considered as she made up her mind.

"Second move!"

She shouted and activated her Gu worm, as her body expanded over twice her original size, becoming a giant!

The hair on her body became longer, becoming brownish-yellow tiger fur.

Her eyes became tiger eyes, and her teeth grew out of her mouth, becoming fangs. On her forehead, there was a symbol.

Her strength more than doubled.

As she pounced on Fang Yuan, a beast phantom appeared behind her body.

A fierce tiger growling towards the heavens, giving off an imposing aura! Its body was covered in brownish-yellow fur, and it had a tough muscular body, most importantly, there was a pair of wings on its back.

A tiger with wings!

A fierce tiger that has wings!

That means it is a — Biao!

Tiger was the king of the hundred beasts. And Biao is a flying tiger, the king among the tigers. Three hounds and one molosser, five tigers and one Biao!

The strength of a Biao was five times of a tiger!

The beast phantom of a Biao can suppress three to four of Fang Yuan's ordinary beast phantoms.

Xue San Si's strength had already more than doubled, but now she unleashed the strength of a Biao!

Under this huge force, Fang Yuan flew away like a shooting star, landing several hundred steps way, crashing on a mountain wall.

Bam!

The entire mountain valley shook intensely.

The mountain rocks collapsed, engulfing Fang Yuan.

"Such strength!"

"Is Fang Zheng dead?"

"No, not yet, his aura is still around!"

The collapsed rocks were pushed away. Fang Yuan walked out, his arms were completely crippled, his iron bones were broken, his steel tendons were mushed, and his bronze skin was torn.

Every step he walked, his body felt weak and was on the brink of collapsing.

The Fang Yuan now could definitely unleash eight beast phantoms.

But these injuries were recovering.

Fang Yuan activated the self-reliance Gu, the healing effect now had far surpassed the flesh-bone Gu.

"Third move!" Xue San Si was anxious, not wanting to give Fang Yuan time to recover.

A pair of wings grew out of her back.

This large pair of wings was brownish-yellow in color, as it flapped, Xue San Si flew to the sky.

She flew higher and higher, until she was about one kilometer in the sky, before she dived down.

She had calculated it long ago, this was the limit to how high she could go. Any higher and she would get injured from the impact after diving down.

As everyone watched nervously, Xue San Si charged towards Fang Yuan.

The image of a Biao appeared again.

This time, it did not appear above her body, but directly overlapped her actual body.

This moment, she seemed to have become a true Sky Tiger!

"With this move, you are finished!!!" Xue San Si growled as her killing intent surged.

Activating two Biao phantoms in a row caused her to pay a huge price.

This was her strongest power, her strongest attack!

She was confident of killing Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan looked up at her, activating golden shield Gu.

But golden shield Gu was rank three, could it block Xue San Si's strongest attack?

Chapter 343: Shameless and Despicable

The lush valley enlarged rapidly in Xue San Si's eyes.

Wind blew past and buzzed intensely on her ears.

Xue San Si's face that had completely changed looked down at Fang Yuan with her tiger eyes, the corner of her lips already curled up into a bloodthirsty smile.

She could almost see little beast king being flattened into minced meat by her unprecedentedly fierce attack.

"There is no way he can survive such an impact!"

When she saw Fang Yuan activating golden shield Gu and his body covered by the golden light, she could not help but sneer inwardly.

"Rank three golden shield Gu? Even if it was the advanced rank four golden bell shield, it would not be able to defend against my attack."

The intensity of the battles between rank four Gu Masters was very high and was not something the defense of a rank three Gu could match.

"This time, I will let these juniors know what happens when they act so arrogantly!" Xue San Si's killing intent was already so overwhelming that it was threatening to burst out.

"Finished, Fang Zheng is finished this time!" When they sensed the fierce attack of Xue San Si, many of the spectators shouted out.

"This is good, little beast king had been too rampant, he should be taught a lesson!" Many righteous Gu Masters were feeling happy at this scene.

"Looks like little beast king wants to rely on golden shield Gu to resist this attack. That is really too naive."

"No, maybe he will activate beast phantom. The combined strength of eight beast phantoms is not a small matter. But if he does that, he would be breaking the agreement they made earlier. As long as he attacks, he will be breaking the agreement and it will mean his loss."

The spectators, whether they were of righteous path or demonic path, all wished for Fang Yuan to lose this battle.

Fang Yuan's activities these days brought them an enormous mental pressure.

"No, there is still an influencing factor on the battlefield - Bai Ning Bing!"

Whoosh whoosh whoosh!

Several figures suddenly moved to the entrance of the valley and silently surrounded Bai Ning Bing.

These people tacitly took the same measure.

If Bai Ning Bing moved to save Fang Yuan, they would stop her.

The terrifying thing about the black and white demons was the close cooperation between these two rank four Gu Masters. Now everything bode ill for little beast king after they restrained Bai Ning Bing.

If little beast king fell, then only Bai Ning Bing would be left and it would not be that threatening.

Fang Yuan's gaze was indifferent as he looked up at Xue San Si, in the depths of his pupils was a trace of mockery.

Xue San Si had yet to collide against him, but a formless wind pressure was already pressing towards him. From another side, it showed the tremendous strength of the imminent collision.

The phantom of Biao enveloped Xue San Si, the wings on her back flapped continuously as her speed increased more and more, and closed towards the ground.

Soon, this force would collide against Fang Yuan.

Suddenly!

Fang Yuan's eyes flashed with a bright light, and he activated a Gu.

Horizontal charge Gu!

He suddenly charged towards the left and then turned around.

Vertical crash Gu!

He charged a hundred steps away.

"Little beast king, you!!!" Xue San Si's anger flared up when she saw Fang Yuan suddenly running away, she opened her eyes so wide that the corners were about to rip!

She did her best to control her descent, but her speed was too fast and she could only let Fang Yuan run out of her attack range.

Seeing Fang Yuan suddenly retreat, the spectators had yet to react when the next moment, there was an enormous explosion like a bolt from the blue.

BOOM!

Xue San Si fiercely collided onto the ground, in that instant, the spectators around the valley could sense the ground under them shaking!

Crushed stones shot out everywhere, the collision created a strong wind pressure that immediately shot out towards all direction.

Everywhere the wind pressure reached, stones, trees, and plants were all uprooted and moved with it.

Smoke and dust whirled around, the enormous destructive force instantly formed a thirty meters huge round crater.

Everyone's heart pulsed rapidly in fear, and just as they were feeling moved about this destructive force, Fang Yuan suddenly changed direction and charged into the smoke.

Horizontal charge Gu, vertical crash Gu!

He used the two Gu one after another and rapidly charged towards Sky Tiger Xue San Si, not caring about the pain from the cold wind pressure and the crushed stones.

Xue San Si was in the center of the huge crater, her body covered in dirt from the collision and was cutting out a sorry figure.

Her ears kept on buzzing and a burst of dizziness attacked her mind.

The fierce Biao phantom had already dispersed. Her incomparably powerful bearing from just before was no longer there.

Bitter strength Gu, all-out effort Gu!

Fang Yuan hurried, an ominous glint shot out from his eyes.

Howl howl howl...

Eight beasts roared one after another.

Boar, brown bear, crocodile, green bull, horse, stone turtle, white elephant and black python, eight phantoms made their loud debut in the air above Fang Yuan!

Strength Qi Gu!

Yellow gold primeval essence severely depleted as it poured into strength qi Gu, creating a huge formless strength Qi.

This strength Qi attached itself to the eight beast phantoms; the beast phantoms turned solid and life-like one after another.

With a shift of Fang Yuan's mind, the eight beast phantoms charged towards the crater.

Xue San Si's body was shaking and she was just about to pull out her legs from the ground when she suddenly heard beast roars from above her.

She immediately raised her head and all she saw was darkness, countless attacks rained down on her like a windstorm.

Bam Bam Bam... the tragic sounds of the battle echoed from the huge crater.

Xue San Si did her best to struggle and resist, after all she was a rank four Gu Master and had strong foundations.

However, not even three minutes later, the sounds of battle stopped. Five out of eight phantoms remained and were shortly recalled by Fang Yuan.

And Xue San Si, as the loser, had a mournful end. Pieces of her corpse were littered over the crater, her blood sprayed all over the ground and dyed the white bone pieces, there were also the brain matter, hair and so on.

Smoke and dust dispersed, the whole battlefield became clear.

When they saw such an outcome, the spectators all burst out in an uproar.

"Sky tiger is dead, another rank four Gu Master has been killed by little beast king!"

"Didn't little beast king make an agreement with Xue San Si? He said he would not not move, but he ended up running."

"This battle should be little beast king's loss. Because he went back against the battle agreement he himself set!"

The valley was a scene of commotion as the spectators commented and discussed; they were stunned and furious, showing intense resentment and disdain towards Fang Yuan's shameless behavior.

Bai Ning Bing laughed heartily and her indifferent gaze swept through the battlefield.

She had already expected this outcome. The so-called agreement was only a trap Fang Yuan set.

What kind of person was Fang Yuan? She, Bai Ning Bing, was the person who knew it the best!

The Gu Masters that were surrounding Bai Ning Bing all tacitly retreated at the same time.

Fang Yuan heard the rebukes, disdain and ridicule of the many Gu Masters around the valley, but he stood there with his hands behind his back and his face tranquil. His eyes squinted as if he was enjoying this.

In his eyes, this so-called 'sincerity' was merely people fearing deception, thus hoping and requesting others to follow their standards.

Walking the demonic path, one should have no restraints and taboos.

So what if he went against the agreement?

So what if he did not keep his promise?

As long as one had enough strength, they could do whatever they liked. What could other's disdain and ridicule do? These powerless and hollow words only manifested the helplessness of the weak, could it hurt a single hair of his?

'Hehehe....this Xue San Si is really stupid. She was actually bound by reputation and came running over to accept my challenge.'

Fang Yuan was in contempt of this: "Reputation is meant to be made use of, it is only a tool. But in this world, there are so many people who treats fame more importantly than their lives. Haha... really laughable! Of course, I did use some tricks in this match."

Xue San Si was different from Tyrant Heng Mei and Fei Li; she possessed flying type Gu and she could just fly to a high altitude if the situation turned bad, and Fang Yuan would have no way to deal with her.

Thus, Fang Yuan raised the agreement at the start. His goal was to restrain Xue San Si's movement ability.

When he mentioned the condition of three strikes, he had already not planned to abide by it.

Xue San Si fell step by step into Fang Yuan's trap, and Fang Yuan's injuries enticed her to continually advance forward.

After the second strike, Fang Yuan intentionally healed himself in front of her. Xue San Si was not willing to see her efforts go to waste and under her worry, without thinking much, she flew to the sky choosing to use her strongest attack.

However, in the end, Fang Yuan instead borrowed her strength to weaken her greatly by using little effort, then quickly went in to attack and killed her.

If it was truly an upright and frank battle, Xue San Si could fly with her wings and would absolutely not be so easily killed by Fang Yuan.

"Little beast king, you really are shameless and despicable."

"You went back against the agreement, you are the loser in this match!"

Many spectators started shouting and yelling, saying similar words.

"That's right. I admit defeat, so what?" Fang Yuan scoffed and replied loudly.

His voice reverberated in the valley.

The clamorous din suddenly quietened down...

'That's right, so what if he lost? Look at the winner, she has turned into a puddle of blood and flesh, even her own father won't be able to recognize her. What meaning is there in such an outcome?'

After reacting to this point, the noises in the valley suddenly rose an octave, much more violent than before.

Fang Yuan calmly admitted his defeat and even more showed his shamelessness; causing the spectators to feel indignant and furious.

Fang Yuan threw his head back and laughed heartily: "Since you guys are feeling such anger, do you want to take revenge for Xue San Si? I didn't know she had such good relationships. Come, come, come, all of you who wants to take revenge come at me together!"

The fierce criticism from the spectators suddenly quietened down and the surroundings turned silent in a moment.

Although Fang Yuan pulled a fast one and killed Xue San Si, Xue San Si was a famous rank four middle stage figure in the end and it was impossible for her to lack strength after the three attacks. However, she was also turned into meat paste by Fang Yuan, displaying Fang Yuan's formidable fighting strength once more.

Fang Yuan defeated three rank four middle stage experts in a row with his rank four initial stage cultivation. Such strength, other than a few individuals, who would not feel fear?

Moreover, the heavier the injuries Fang Yuan suffered, the stronger his strength became.

Fang Yuan arrogantly challenged them, but no one stood up.

Demonic Gu Masters were mutually restrained and held suspicions towards each other, almost every one of them was a loner; no one stood out for Xue San Si. On the contrary, some members of righteous path wanted to eradicate this devil Fang Yuan, but they could not easily move at this moment.

Why?

Because once they stood up, it would become taking revenge for Xue San Si. And Xue San Si was a demonic figure!

"Is there no one that wants to take revenge for her? Is there or not?" Fang Yuan again asked loudly.

Countless spectators' expression turned gloomy. Some looked at each other but no one replied.

"If there is no one, I am leaving." Fang Yuan raised his brows and walked a few steps before he stopped, "I am really leaving."

Still, no one spoke.

Fang Yuan's dominance suppressed everyone present. Such a rampant bearing made many rank four experts indignant.

Many people became restless but still restrained themselves in the end.

"Hahaha..." Fang Yuan raised his head towards the sky and laughed loudly as he walked away with large strides, soon leaving the battlefield.

Chapter 344: Talented without Virtue

"Big brother Li, you need to make a move..." Hu Mei Er lied back on Li Xian's chest and spoke coquettishly.

Li Xian was short and fat. He had a round nose, large eyes and wide forehead, his hair also let out a greasy shine. Right now, one of his short and rough hand was on Hu Mei Er's delicate little waist while the other hand was on her leg.

Li Xian was a rank four upper stage Gu Master! However, he rarely fought, making a living by doing business and was a famous unscrupulous merchant of the demonic path, having wide connections.

He embraced Hu Mei Er and said with a lecherous smile: "Mei Er, your body feels like there are no bones with skin as delicate as jade. I haven't seen you for a few days and you have become more beautiful."

Hu Mei Er rolled her eyes and said in a displeased tone: "Big brother Li, I am trying to talk to you. That black and white twin demons offended me, I am already yours, you must seek justice for me!"

"Ok, ok..." Li Xian half-heartedly spoke while his ten fingers wandered over Hu Mei Er's body.

Hu Mei Er's breathing became rough and her face flushed red. Along with her watery eyes, she looked very alluring.

However, her mind was as clear as snow.

She tried to persuade Li Xian but he only muttered 'mmm' and did not agree, instead taking advantage of her.

Hu Mei Er pushed Li Xian and stood up with aggrieved expression: "Big brother Li, give me a definite answer! I have been begging you like this, do you not pity me?"

"Sigh, my darling, my little treasure. It is not that your big brother Li doesn't want to do it, but dealing with the black and white demons will be somewhat tricky. They are two rank four Gu Masters, your big brother Li is a lone force, just one person." Li Xian spread his arms with a helpless expression.

Hu Mei Er snorted: "Alright, I shall lower the bar. You only need to deal against that little beast king. This Fang Zheng is the most hateful! You can leave that Bai Ning Bing alone for now."

"This..." Li Xian hesitated.

"Big brother Li!" Hu Mei Er saw a chance and threw herself into Li Xian's arms, softly blowing at Li Xian's fat ear.

Li Xian immediately felt a fire burning near his crotch.

His eyes became dazed: "Okay, since you are asking like this, big brother Li will help you take revenge. But..."

He slightly changed the topic: "Three kings inheritance will open again in one or two days. There cannot be any problems at this critical juncture. After the three kings inheritance, I will go teach that little beast king a lesson, alright?"

The opening of three kings inheritance was near and everyone was paying attention to it.

Hu Mei Er curled her lips, she did not have much to say about Li Xian's evasion.

After a period of intimacy, Hu Mei Er took her leave.

Although Li Xian tried to make her stay, Hu Mei Er's attitude was firm; in the end, Li Hao could only send her off.

He stood at the cave entrance and impatiently looked at Hu Mei Er's figure gradually getting far and disappearing within the forest.

"Hmph, this little temptress!" Li Xian returned back to his cave, the lust on his face nowhere to be seen, replaced by a cautious and gloomy expression.

"Trying to sow discord and use me as a tool to deal with little beast king? This little temptress really thinks she had reached greater success in her enchantment path. Ridiculous!" The smile on Li Xian's face was cold, "I, of course, have ways to deal with black and white twin demons. But when did I, Li Xian, ever do unprofitable business? Hehe."

"This little beast king Fang Zheng is not simple. He seems boorish but in fact his thoughts are meticulous. Challenging three demonic Gu Masters in a row before the opening of three kings inheritance, this definitely was a premeditated plan!"

Gu Masters came from all over the places and gathered at San Cha mountain, why?

Wasn't it for the three kings inheritance!

Fang Yuan's aggressiveness had not caused him any troubles. These days, only he found trouble for others, why was it?

Because everyone were impatiently watching the three kings inheritance, making every effort and secret preparation for it. Who would want to have a bloodbath with little beast king, this lunatic, and miss this great opportunity?

No one!

"This little beast king used this psychology and acted unrestrainedly, establishing his reputation. Two days later when the three kings inheritance opens, who will want to block his way?" Li Xian shook his head as he predicted the future.

Ever since Fang Yuan killed Xue San Si, even he felt some fear towards this little beast king.

Before, when Fang Yuan killed Tyrant Heng Mei and Fei Li, it did not attract Li Xian's attention. However, when Fang Yuan broke his promise and took the chance to kill Sky Tiger, Li Xian realized what a thorny problem he was!

Why so?

The righteous path categorized talents into four grades.

First grade was having both talent and virtue. Having talent and a moral character was the highest quality talent, able to hold his own.

Second grade was having virtue but no talent. They might have no talent, but they had moral character. Those with filial piety will obey their parents. Those with loyalty will obey their leaders. Those with sincerity would not break their promises. They could be used with ease, at least no huge problems will occur. Moreover, many abilities could be learned through experience.

Third grade was having talent but no virtue. They might have talent but had no moral conduct. With their talents, they could take up a post, but higher ups would not feel at ease using them, afraid they would someday betray them.

Fourth grade was having neither talent nor virtue. No talent and nor moral conduct. They were worthless and no one would feel at ease using them.

What kind of figure would be the most trouble when categorized under the demonic path?

In demonic path, fourth grade was having virtue but no talent. They did not have talent but paid particular attention to virtue, living among their ideals. Often, it was themselves that would cause their own destruction.

Third grade was having neither talent nor virtue. They might not have talent, but they also did not have any moral conduct. They could at least do some lowly works and earn a living.

Second grade was having both talent and virtue. With talent, they could fill their stomachs. However, at the same time, with virtue, filial piety, respect, loyalty and so on became the ropes that bound them. In demonic path, such a mutually deceptive character decided that such a type of people would not play a key role.

And the first grade, having talent but no virtue!

Fang Yuan was such a person.

He had talent, overflowing with talent actually. HIs aptitude was outstanding, A grade aptitude was not something everyone possessed.

Secondly, his battle talent allowed him to overstep realms and fight. Tyrant Heng Mei, Fei Li and Xue San Si had cultivation higher than him, but all died a tragic death in his hands; this was enough to prove this point.

Finally, he possessed the ability to do business. At Shang clan city, he did surprisingly well. And in a short period of a few years, he was able to gather such a formidable set of Gu worms.

If such a talented person had virtue, Li Xian would not be feeling so difficult.

However, Fang Yuan was someone with not even a hint of morality.

He left Hu Mei Er in the lurch, not giving a hoot to beauty. He was boorish, unreasonable, easily killed people and treated life with contempt.

He killed Tyrant Heng Mei and other two, each time he smashed them into minced meat, his savage and ruthless nature was clear from this.

He deceived Xue San Si and broke his promise in front of everyone, but was still proud of himself. This was even more terrifying.

It shows that he did things without any restrain or lower limits, he could betray someone as easily as snapping his fingers with not even a trace of guilt in his heart.

Li Xian was deeply aware: If a person like little beast king were to be placed in righteous path, in a peaceful environment, they would definitely be excluded by the people, suppressed, banished or imprisoned. However, in the chaotic demonic path with its cruel competitive environment, Fang Yuan was like a tiger entering the mountain, a flood dragon entering the sea! As long as his luck was not too bad, he would definitely have great accomplishments!

"Such a person, if I had discovered him early, I would have suppressed and killed him. However, now, it is too late, too late..." Li Xian sighed deeply.

Fang Yuan had already matured and he also had a companion beside him. Although Li Xian had rank four upper stage cultivation, he was best at doing business and not at fighting.

Naturally, there was always someone stronger.

On San Cha mountain, there were also people that could kill Fang Yuan. They were the four rank four peak stage Gu Masters like Kong Ri Tian, Long Qing Tian and others.

However, how could Li Xian command such formidable characters?

Moreover, these four were all in a subtle restraining balance. Not one of them dared to act blindly and all their eyes were set on three kings inheritance, how could they have the mood to consider other things.

"Hmph, this little temptress harbors evil intentions. She actually wants to stir me up and fight with such a demonic figure, how is that possible? Not only will I not offend him, but instead I will build a good cooperative relationship with him. All demonic path figures place benefits at the top."

"However, by killing Xue San Si, little beast king has offended another person. Sky Tiger's godfather who is the rank four upper stage Gu Master Century Boy. These days, Century Boy has been refining Gu in seclusion, he will definitely appear when the inheritance opens this time. At that time, he will most likely find trouble for black and white twin demons."

"Hehehe, I will secretly befriend little beast king while staying at the sidelines on the surface. I will watch the battle between Century Boy and black and white twin demons, then after looking at the outcome, I will wait for an opportunity to make a move!"

No matter what the outcome was, Li Xian would not have much loss.

This was Li Xian.

An unscrupulous merchant of the demonic path who was an expert at benefiting from others' expense.

Swish swish swish...

Under Fang Yuan's will, the bright golden primeval essence tide cleansed the aperture walls.

Even on San Cha mountain, he was always cultivating diligently.

His actual cultivation was only rank four initial stage, it was originally only light gold primeval essence, however under the effect of nine eyes liquor worm, the primeval essence's quality rose by a small realm and changed into bright golden primeval essence.

Bright golden primeval essence was an enormous assistance to his battles. This was also one of the main reasons for him being able to kill three rank four middle stage Gu Masters in a row.

"These days, my reputation has raised greatly. There are certainly many, many people who hate and fear me. However, what does that have to do with anything?"

"Hehe, what I am treading on is the demonic path, it should be like this. Moreover, this is not Earth; here, individual strength can be above a group."

In different environments, the rules of the game were also different.

If it were on Earth, even if one walked demonic path, they would also have to consider moral character.

Because on Earth, the difference between individual strengths was small. Demonic path's people also could only gather into a group to be able to accomplish grand ambitions!

"Two more days and it will be the day the three kings inheritance opens. It is unlikely for someone to come find trouble for me, I will use this time to refine charging crash Gu."

Fang Yuan had a precise plan and arrangement for his future.

Chapter 345: Charging Crash Gu

At that time, when Fang Yuan chose horizontal charge and vertical crash Gu as his movement Gu, he had already considered the situation when he advanced to rank four.

Horizontal charge Gu and vertical crash Gu were the two main materials to refine charging crash Gu.

With these two rank three Gu as the main, together with the Gu Master's primeval essence and some supplementary materials and so on, to refine charging crash Gu.

The process of refining charging crash Gu was not difficult.

Fang Yuan had made sufficient preparations and the success rate of this recipe by itself was rather high.

Two days later, Fang Yuan succeeded in refining and obtained a whole new Gu - charging crash Gu.

Horizontal charge Gu and vertical crash Gu could only charge to the distance of a hundred steps together.

But charging crash Gu fused from these two Gu increased this charging distance to two hundred steps. At the same time, the delay between repeated use was also decreased by half.

However, the consumption of primeval essence was increased a little. But this small flaw was nothing to Fang Yuan who possessed the nine eyes liquor worm and heavenly essence treasure lotus.

"I already have six rank four Gu now; bitter strength Gu, charging crash Gu, yang Gu of yin-yang rotation Gu, nine eyes liquor worm, expend strength Gu and blood skull Gu."

"All-out effort Gu, strength qi Gu, golden shield Gu and others are all rank three. They are slowly failing to keep up with my requirements."

Most of the Gu on Fang Yuan were rank three. He was, however, at rank four initial stage now and possessed middle stage bright golden primeval essence, thus these Gu worms were gradually becoming unsuitable for him.

Naturally, it did not mean that the higher the Gu, the better they were.

For example bone flesh unity Gu. It was only a rank three Gu, but it could allow many Gu Masters to use it even at this rank. This made its value stand out.

On the whole, however, Gu worms and Gu Masters needed to have a mutually cooperative rank, and was best if it were the same for it be more convenient in using them.

Fang Yuan made a small consideration; he had a lot of Gu worms to upgrade.

First of all was the all-out effort Gu.

The all-out effort Gu on him was only at rank three; it could only activate rank three beast phantoms. To advance its rank, he would need to get the undefeated hundred battles Gu from three kings inheritance, so this plan could only be put aside for now.

Strength qi Gu was also at rank three, but Fang Yuan did not have its corresponding recipe, so he was unable to advance it.

Fang Yuan planned to advance rank three golden shield Gu into rank four golden bell shield Gu.

The storage type rank three tusita flower could be upgraded to rank four tusita lantern Gu.

Self-reliance Gu was also a rank three Gu, but it was already at its peak stage and did not have relevant recipe for its advancement. But although it was a rank three Gu, as long as Fang Yuan displayed formidable strength, its healing effects could match with rank four healing Gu.

Similar to self-reliance Gu was bone flesh unity Gu.

Breath concealment Gu that was used to hide cultivation was also at rank three. Although it could be advanced, Fang Yuan decided lay it aside. At the present time, he did not need to hide his aura.

And heaven essence treasure lotus was also at rank three.

Fang Yuan already possessed the fusion recipe for rank four heaven essence treasure monarch lotus. But he needed to obtain a number of spirit springs to refine it. This was a large project and could only be put aside for now.

Calculating like this, Fang Yuan needed to advance all-out effort Gu, golden shield Gu, tusita flower and heavenly essence treasure lotus; these four Gu.

However, it was not just like that.

Fang Yuan had used iron bone Gu, steel tendon Gu and copper skin Gu to transform his body. These Gu were all rank three Gu. The defense they provided during fights between rank four Gu Masters were little.

There were also the eight phantoms in Fang Yuan's body, none of them were from rank four strength Gu. Thus, Fang Yuan also needed replace these phantoms.

"The eight phantoms I have are from ordinary beasts. Only by replacing them with Biao strength phantom, mastiff strength phantom and so on, can I display the strongest fighting strength in rank four realm."

Fang Yuan had been interested in the Biao strength Gu of Xue San Si.

However, he had turned Xue San Si into minced meat and the Gu worms on her body were also destroyed.

Fang Yuan's methods were too brutal. He frequently smashed his enemies into meat paste.

Although this was also a constant characteristic of strength path Gu Masters, this method was too violent and there would seldom be any surviving Gu worms once the battle ended.

Fang Yuan had won against three rank four demonic Gu Masters in a row, but only obtained an expend strength Gu.

And this expend strength Gu was also surrendered and contributed by Fei Li of his own accord.

The way Gu Masters obtained Gu worms was basically from trading, raising, capturing, fusing or reverse refining.

Gu Masters rarely obtained Gu worms as their victory spoils.

On one hand it was because Gu Masters used secretive and dangerous methods. In case a battle started, both sides would use all their strength to attack and would not spare anything for their safety. Like this, the Gu worms would also be wrecked and destroyed.

On another hand, it was extremely easy for the Gu Masters to destroy their own Gu worms. It only required a thought from them and their Gu worms would self-destruct.

"I have a lot to do to advance all of them..." Fang Yuan sighed and walked out of the cave.

Bai Ning Bing was already waiting for him at the cave entrance, and was gazing at the peak.

Fang Yuan followed her gaze and also looked up.

He only saw enormous light pillars rise from the three highest peaks of San Cha mountain, piercing through clouds and soaring towards the sky. Its enormous aura felt like it was supporting heaven and earth.

The three kings inheritance had opened.

"With this inheritance, my set of strength path Gu will be taken to perfection!" Fang Yuan's gaze was burning but he restrained it.

Although he had outstanding battle prowess, it was still not his turn to take the stage.

Whoosh Whoosh Whoosh Whoosh!

Four figures separately charged out from east, south, north and west; they stopped in mid-air and confronted each other.

Rank four peak stage aura were let out without any concealment!

From the eastern direction was poison path Gu Master Long Qing Tian.

He had long black hair, pale-green skin and his green pupils faintly flashed like there were too cold fires burning in it.

From the western direction was righteous path Wu clan's elder Wu Shen Tong.

His fame was powerful and domineering, but his body was thin like a sickly scholar. He had pale complexion and coughed from time to time as if he could not endure this mountain wind.

From the southern direction was the demonic path expert Kong Ri Tian.

He was wearing flower patterned gown. He had a smile on while standing in the air, pink butterflies fluttering around him.

From the northern direction was Yi clan's elder Yi Chong.

His whole body was covered with blue fish scales which formed into a thin armor. HIs nose was long and protruding out, his eyes were larger than twice that of a normal person's and he had a head full of blazing unkempt hair.

The muscles in his whole body tangled forming layers of lumps. His stature was short but his physique was extremely imposing. An enormous triangular fin grew out from his back like the black fin on a shark's back.

These four were currently the strongest Gu Masters at San Cha mountain.

Rank four peak stage cultivation was only a step away from rank five. If they advanced to rank five, they would be the monarchs of the mortal world and wield power over a region, their might and aura would spread everywhere.

These four had already confronted each other for months on San Cha mountain. They had also fought many times with each other over this period of time, but no one could do anything to other, forming a chaotic situation.

Righteous path's Wu Shen Tong and Yi Chong appeared to be allies but inwardly, they were not of one mind. While Kong Ri Tian and Long Qing Tian would also occasionally collaborate if the situation turned bad.

These four occupied the top caves and were closest to the inheritance entrances at San Cha mountain.

The appearance of these four attracted the gazes of all the Gu Masters on the mountain.

The inheritance was right before their eyes. No matter who it was, they were all restraining the desire to make a move.

After the short stalemate, Kong Ri Tian chose King Bao's inheritance; Long Qing Tian chose King Xin's inheritance and Wu Shen Tong chose King Quan's inheritance.

The three inheritances did not correspond with each other, but there were four rank four peak stage Gu Masters.

The Gu Master remaining, Yi Chong, hesitated for a while before finally choosing King Bao's inheritance.

"With this, King Bao's inheritance has Kong Ri Tian and Yi Chong, two experts."

"Long Qing Tian chose King Xin's inheritance this time, we fell in his trap last time, we must avoid him!"

"Wu Shen Tong is an enslavement path Gu Master, reportedly he has already advanced to middle stage of King Quan's inheritance. In this inheritance, he is like a fish in water and can display extraordinary strength. If we choose King Quan's inheritance, we might only get his leftovers."

While the crowd was discussing, a group of Gu Masters ascended to the peak.

They were rank four upper stage Gu Masters. Some had bizarre appearances, some were fiendish, some had dignified appearance and some were gloomy like forest.

Among them, one was a boy wearing black clothes. Before he entered the inheritance, he looked down and gazed deeply at Fang Yuan.

"Hmph, Century Boy..." Fang Yuan narrowed his eyes and let out a dangerous aura.

Century Boy was also a strength path Gu Master and was the godfather of Xue San Si, her patron.

Fang Yuan killed Xue San Si and offended Century Boy.

However, with the three kings inheritance in sight, Century Boy did not have the mind and heart to settle the account with Fang Yuan now. But once the inheritance closed, he was sure to make his moves against Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had not the least bit of fear towards this and was instead secretly looking forward to it.

With his current strength, he was almost unrivalled among rank four initial stage Gu Masters and could also prevail over ordinary middle stage Gu Masters. However, he would be evenly matched against rank four upper stage.

Above that, rank four peak stage would be a difficult opponent. However, if those rank four Gu Masters like Kong Ri Tian and others wanted to kill Fang Yuan, they would also pay a disastrous price.

As the Gu Master's cultivation reached the later stages, the difference in each small realm was big and it would get more difficult to cross these ranks to battle, let alone cross realms to battle.

Fang Yuan possessed plentiful battle experience and also had a set of excellent strength path Gu worms, but he was also only able to cross one realm and kill middle stage Gu Masters.

"Of course, if I replace my Gu worms to rank four then I will have the strength to win against upper stage Gu Masters! And even be evenly matched against rank four peak stage! Three kings inheritance, here I come!"

At once, Fang Yuan activated charging crash Gu and charged towards the peak.

Rank four upper stage Gu Masters had all entered the inheritances.

The light pillars of the three inheritances were already a lot dimmer.

A group of rank four middle stage Gu Masters were just ascending up San Cha mountain, when they suddenly saw Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing charge towards them. All of their complexions changed and by some tacit agreement, got out of the way.

Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing entered King Quan's inheritance together.

Chapter 346: First entry into King Quan Inheritance

The moment his body entered the light pillar, Fang Yuan felt an intense weightlessness.

When his vision cleared up, he found himself standing in the wilderness.

All he could see around him was the greyish white sky.

On the ground, the grey-white rocks formed into short mounds, like gravestones.

The grey colored ground was not fertile, it was hard and dry, with some yellow grass growing in between the cracks.

The sky was white, the earth was grey, and the grass was yellow. The world had three colors.

Other than that, there were no other colors.

All he could hear was silence, or rather, dead silence. There was no wind, no swaying tree leaves, no cries of birds and beasts.

Anyone standing here would feel that in this entire world, he was the only person left, a lone survivor.

Being in the land of nothingness, loneliness, solitariness, loss and even fear would grow in their hearts.

Although he went into the inheritance with Bai Ning Bing, at the moment, Fang Yuan was alone.

But Fang Yuan was extremely calm.

"So this is King Quan Inheritance." He looked around, muttering to himself softly.

Compared to an ordinary rank five Gu Master's inheritance, the three kings inheritance had a huge difference.

An ordinary rank five inheritance, be it central continent, southern border, northern plains, eastern sea, or western desert, they were all in the main world.

But the three kings inheritance was built inside a Gu Immortal blessed land.

Back then, the three kings were stuck and discovered the inheritance of an ancient Gu Immortal by accident, starting their legend.

The three kings were all geniuses in their own field, after failing to advance to rank six, they set up their inheritances in this blessed land before their deaths.

Thus, Fang Yuan was no longer in the main world now.

Gu Immortal Blessed Land — a small world that existed within the main world.

Every world had different rules and laws.

Entering a world means obeying and following its rules.

"Although Bai Ning Bing entered the inheritance with me, she was definitely sent to another place in this small world. But it is not a problem, as long as she continues to advance into the inheritance, we will definitely meet along the way.

Fang Yuan knew that this was the unique law of space inside a small world.

At the same time, there was also a difference in the flow of time.

"The flow of time here is three times that of the outside world." In Fang Yuan's aperture, the slumbering Spring Autumn Cicada had awakened, and was recovering at three times the speed inside this world.

The Spring Autumn Cicada fed on the water in the river of time.

In this small world, the water flow in the river of time was three times faster than the outside world. Thus, it greatly assisted the Spring Autumn Cicada's recovery.

But this was not good news to Fang Yuan.

The pressure that the Spring Autumn Cicada emits in its perfect condition was not something a rank four aperture could contain.

The King Quan Inheritance, although it was a chance for Fang Yuan to grow, it was also a land of death that escalated his demise.

"Staying here for one day means three days outside. I have to hurry, and conserve my time." Fang Yuan felt a strong sense of urgency.

Thankfully, with his memories, this King Quan Inheritance of a rank five Gu Master was not unfamiliar to him.

"If I am not wrong, there should be a dog type wild beast around here somewhere..." Fang Yuan moved around, looking all over the place, searching for what he had in mind.

"Woof, woof, woof!"

Suddenly, he heard a cry from afar, as a weak wild dog ran towards Fang Yuan with its eyes glowing in a weak green light.

This wild dog was thin to the bones, its teeth were yellow and it was only at the height of Fang Yuan's knee.

It appeared extremely ferocious, evidently hungry, after smelling the human flesh that was Fang Yuan, it rushed over without hesitation.

Fang Yuan frowned, this wild dog was very ordinary, meeting it in the first stage was his bad luck.

He stood quietly on the spot, letting the dog run towards him.

In the currently environment, Fang Yuan could not utilize his other Gu worms, he could only use the rank one dog enslavement Gu.

This was the restriction of the laws in this small world.

King Quan modified the Gu Immortal blessed land, allowing a Gu Master to bring in a rank one dog enslavement Gu into his inheritance, and at the same time, other Gu worms cannot be used.

Of course, other than the Spring Autumn Cicada.

Spring Autumn Cicada was a rank six Gu, after a Gu worm reaches rank six, be it the main world or the small world, there only exists one of it.

Spring Autumn Cicada was not a mortal being, it was an Immortal Gu.

Even in the blessed land, it could be used freely.

"Not just King Quan Inheritance, King Xin Inheritance and King Bao Inheritance are the same. When the Gu Master initially enters the inheritance, they can only use the rank one dog enslavement Gu, paper crane Gu, and exploding egg Gu."

Seeing the wild dog rush towards him, Fang Yuan activated the dog enslavement Gu in his aperture.

This dog enslavement Gu, looked like a jade stone, only thumb-size. The exterior of the jade stone looked like a dog head.

Fang Yuan only used one drop of light golden primeval essence, to activate this dog enslavement Gu.

The dog enslavement Gu turned into a jade light, bursting out and turning from solid to hollow, next, it flew into the wild dog in the blink of an eye.

The wild dog cried out, as if it was heavily injured, and fell on the ground.

Because it was running, it slided across the ground until it rolled to Fang Yuan's feet.

After resting for a while, the dog got up.

But this time, it did not bare its fangs at Fang Yuan, but instead, sprawled on the ground, sticking out its tongue and wagging its tail.

"Get up." Fang Yuan willed.

The wild dog obeyed and got up.

Its body had soft fur, the fur was dark but there was no injuries on it. The dog enslavement Gu directly went into its soul, it did not cause any damage to the dog's physical body.

Its four limbs were on the ground, and the head was only near Fang Yuan's knee.

Fang Yuan observed and shook his head.

This was an ordinary wild dog, it had little battle strength. But precisely so, he could use the dog enslavement Gu on it so easily.

"Regardless, I have to rely on it to get through the second round."

Fang Yuan was thinking in his mind, when suddenly a force from heaven and earth engulfed his body.

Immediately, Fang Yuan could not move an inch.

In front of him, a light flashed and a second dog enslavement Gu appeared in front of him.

Fang Yuan knew this was the reward from the inheritance, as well as the key to the second round, thus he quickly refined it.

This dog enslavement Gu was also rank one, it was easy to refine.

When Fang Yuan refined this Gu, and kept it into his aperture, with a swoosh, he vanished on the spot, moved to another location by the heavenly power.

This was still the wilderness, with white sky, grey earth, and yellow grass.

Fang Yuan stood on a low mound, as three wild dogs were surrounding him.

They were all thin as twigs, as two were lowering their heads scavenging for food. The third was slightly older, lying on the ground motionless.

Fang Yuan's sudden appearance caused the three dogs to go crazy.

They started running like they were jolted with lightning, towards Fang Yuan from all three directions.

Fang Yuan controlled the first wild dog and activated its ferocity. Under Fang Yuan's command, it bared its claws on one of the wild dogs.

But it could only stop one wild dog, soon, the second closed in on Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan reenacted the same scene from earlier, using the second dog enslavement Gu and tamed it.

The third wild dog pounced, and Fang Yuan split his concentration into two, commanding both wild dogs to attack.

If it was an ordinary Gu Master, and was not familiar with the dog enslavement Gu, holding two fights at the same time would cause them to lose their bearings. But Fang Yuan was not nervous, in fact he was not even going all-out yet.

With his five hundred years of experience, Fang Yuan had commanded numerous beast groups to battle. Especially the blade-wing blood bats from the blood sea inheritance.

In this life, for San Cha mountain's inheritance, he had trained for several months in Shang clan city, familiarizing himself with controlling dog groups.

The battle proceeded smoothly in Fang Yuan's expected direction.

But Fang Yuan frowned: "The first wild dog's body condition is terrible. Fighting like this, even if I win, I will only be left with one wild dog."

As he considered this, he consciously direct the two dogs to retreat while fighting.

Eventually, Fang Yuan successfully merged the two battles together.

This increased the pressure on Fang Yuan's commands, but it also established great advantage for him.

Fang Yuan's two wild dogs were cooperating perfectly, but their enemies were fighting alone.

Not long after, this intense battle ended.

The corpses of two wild dogs laid on the ground, blood flowing out of them.

The wild dogs Fang Yuan controlled stood on the ground, covered in wounds. The first dog was more injured, while the second dog was relatively healthier.

The battle had just ended, when the heavenly power descended again, wrapping around Fang Yuan and his two ordinary wild dogs.

His vision changed again, as weightlessness assaulted him.

"Third round..." Fang Yuan observed his surroundings immediately.

This time, he was standing on the top of a mound, surrounded by six wild dogs.

"Six!" Fang Yuan's gaze concentrated, feeling pressured.

He had two wild dogs with him, having to fight against three times of his force, at the same time, his dogs were injured.

Without time to rest or think, the six dogs detected him and immediately attacked.

Fang Yuan's eyes brightened, as he saw a pit nearby, he jumped in.

He jumped into the pit, with a hard wall behind him, he placed both his dogs in front of him.

The six wild dogs rushed towards him, at differing speeds. The two healthy wild dogs rushed up first, while the remaining four, with different injuries, were far behind.

Seeing this, Fang Yuan heaved a sigh of relief.

If these six dogs were healthy, he had no chance. But with this terrain advantage, and his skilled manipulation, he was confident of passing this round and moving on to the next!

Chapter 347: What level of proficiency in enslavement path is this!

Woof Woof Woof!

The sound of furious barking of dogs echoed endlessly.

Dozens of dogs were in a fierce fight; one side had many numbers but their formation were scattered. Another side had fewer numbers, but they were in a tight formation, and furthermore they were displaying battle tactics like shielding, retreating, attacking and so on.

Fang Yuan stood on a nearby hill and overlooked the whole battlefield while commanding his dogs.

This was already his tenth battle in King Quan's inheritance.

With his plentiful experience and the understanding of King Quan's inheritance, he had sprinted through the whole process without any incidents.

The battle lasted for five more minutes before it ended.

In the whole battlefield, there were nineteen dogs still standing, all of them the result of Fang Yuan's hard accumulation.

Fang Yuan softly let out a breath of turbid air, his mind felt slightly exhausted.

"In King Quan's inheritance, the difficulty increases sharply every ten rounds of battles. I used twenty eight dogs this time but had to sacrifice nine of them to resist the assault of nearly sixty dogs and cross this barrier."

To be honest, Fang Yuan had some alarming moments during this process.

"The three kings were demonic Gu Masters, demonic inheritance always held the law of the survival of the fittest, an intense and cold competition. This round should be enough to eliminate most of the participants who want to steal benefits."

There were countless righteous and demonic Gu Masters on San Cha mountain. Every time the three kings inheritance opened, large numbers of Gu Master would come pouring in to try their luck.

However, no matter which inheritance of the three kings inheritance it was, they were all extremely strict. To choose the most suitable inheritor, the barriers the three kings set up were high.

Among the three kings, King Quan was an enslavement path Gu Master, King Xin was a refinement path Gu Master, and King Bao was a fire path Gu Master. Their chosen inheritors naturally should also follow these paths.

The difficulty of the first ten rounds ruthlessly eliminated most of the Gu Masters of other paths.

At the thirtieth round, there would not be any Gu Masters of other paths.

At the fiftieth round, those remaining would be elites and geniuses of these paths.

At the seventieth round, only experts with deep foundations would remain.

Very few could reach the ninetieth round and they could be counted with two hands.

Especially from ninetieth to hundredth round, the final ten rounds, the difficulties were extreme and unsurmountable like the heavenly chasm. Even a monster like Fang Yuan could not cross it.

In his previous life, the three kings inheritance lasted for close to ten years. It involved countless people; both demonic and righteous, heroes and villains.

As of now, it had not been even a year since the appearance of the three kings inheritance and it was in its early stage. It was already amazing for many people to be able to charge through a dozen barriers.

By the middle stage, the participants would find it difficult to continue from around fiftieth barrier; they would exchange their experiences and sum up many rules.

At the late stage, most of the participants would hover around seventieth to eightieth barrier. Only an extremely few number of participants would be struggling at ninetieth round. These people were mostly rank five Gu Masters, their every action attracting many gazes.

And at the final period, the mystical figures of many rank six Gu Immortals also appeared.

Fang Yuan remembered most of the parts clearly. Of course, there were also some blurry areas, but they were minor details.

He had a deep understanding of three kings inheritance.

He knew no matter which inheritance he chose, he could only charge to the ninetieth round with his strength.

After the ninetieth round, the barriers were all something only rank five Gu Masters had a chance of clearing.

Fang Yuan knew it would be very difficult for him to cultivate to rank five. Ten years was absolutely not enough.

This was not only because cultivation became more difficult the higher the Gu Master advanced, but also because of Spring Autumn Cicada.

In this Gu Immortal blessed land, time flow was quickened which intensified the recovery speed of Spring Autumn Cicada.

This was an enormous threat to him.

Heavenly power descended once more and Fang Yuan's vision flashed.

In a split second, he found himself transported to another strange place.

His field of view was not clear as the previous ten rounds, the surroundings were filled with dense grey fog, making one unable to distinguish even the directions.

Apart from rank six Spring Autumn Cicada, none of his other Gu worms could be used.

Nineteen dogs walked around him, but there was only a faint connection left from the dog enslavement Gu.

However, Fang Yuan was not flustered, he was clear that starting from the tenth round, the inheritance would give every challenger the power to choose.

He stood calmly and soon was able to distinguish.

Towards the depths of the fog on his left was an orange glow like someone had turned on a lantern. It was accompanied by a sound, the clear sound of a dog's bark.

Towards his front was an indistinct black human shadow, appearing near but also far.

Towards his right, in the depths of the grey fog, a ball of blue lightning crackled.

"The orange light represents chrysanthemum akita dog. This dog is more loyal than the ordinary dogs with me, they are easy to control and can execute exquisite battle tactics. The blue light should be lightning symbol dog; it is very fast, faster than ordinary dogs by two times. And the black human figure should be my opponent, another Gu Master." Fang Yuan pondered.

These were all reminders provided by King Quan's inheritance to him.

The first time a person enters, they would have a blurred vision and could only feel their way through the barrier, not able to make the most beneficial choice.

However, Fang Yuan was well aware; whether it was chrysanthemum akita dog, lightning symbol dog or the Gu Master, they were all challenges but also opportunities.

Fang Yuan considered it for just a short while and directly walked forward, abandoning the left and right directions.

As he walked forward, the grey fog started becoming thinner and his vision became clearer. At the same time, his control over his nineteen dog enslavement Gu also became stronger.

And the grey fog on his left and right became denser.

Han Bu Liu stood still, calmly looked at the person that walked out of the fog.

Han Bu Liu was already forty-eight, he was a righteous path Gu Master with a cultivation of rank four middle stage, and had already entered King Quan's inheritance many times.

This allowed him to have a lot of understanding regarding King Quan's inheritance. Right now, as he saw Fang Yuan's figure in the fog walking slowly towards him, he immediately knew this was his opponent.

However, he was not in the least bit nervous.

He was an enslavement path Gu Master and was like a fish in water in King Quan's inheritance.

In this special environment, all the previous accumulation of Gu Masters were not counted. They could only use the Gu the inheritance gave them to fight. The difference in cultivations had sharply decreased.

"This person is really unfortunate, actually bumping into me. I will do my best to win against this person with the smallest loss. Then I will charge towards the twenty-second barrier."

Han Bu Liu was very confident towards himself. He had charged to twenty-first barrier last time. Such an accomplishment was one of the best in his circles, even surpassing many rank four upper stage and peak stage Gu Masters.

Fang Yuan stepped out of the fog; his eyes as dark as the abyss and his expression as tranquil as water.

Han Bu Liu's pupils shrunk rapidly as he revealed a terrified expression.

"It is little beast king!"

He immediately felt nervous and panicked.

Although Fang Yuan had arrived in San Cha mountain not long ago, he had killed three middle stage Gu Masters with his initial stage cultivation. His might was awe-inspiring and his vicious reputation had spread far.

Han Bu Liu was also at middle stage, but he, himself, knew his battle strength could not compare to Sky Tiger and others.

But soon, Han Bu Liu regained his senses: "This is the Gu Immortal blessed land, not the outside world! In this round, we can only use dog enslavement Gu. Little beast king can't use his Gu set! He walks the strength path and is so young, how could he have any proficiency in the enslavement path?"

Han Bu Liu's eyes shone with ecstasy and greed as he roared in his mind: "Ahahaha, this is a heaven sent opportunity! By killing little beast king, I can greatly spread my reputation. By taking his Gu worms and selling them, I can make a lot of primeval stones! Dogs, charge!"

Righteous path inheritances were gentle and usually did not cause any deaths. Sometimes, even when someone failed, they would have some gains.

However, King Quan's inheritance was a demonic path inheritance.

Here, one could kill and death was a normal thing.

The most crucial thing was in this Gu Immortal blessed land, Gu Masters could not utilize their Gu worms. This meant if the Gu Master died, they cannot will their Gu worms to self-destruct.

The Gu Masters on San Cha mountain had already discovered this point through fights.

This led to a sharp increase in the number of casualties in the inheritance!

At outside world, Gu Masters could cause their Gu worms to self-destruct before their deaths, not letting their enemies have them. The profits from battles were very small. But here, if a Gu Master died, their Gu worms would be left behind. This enticed people to commit crimes!

If Han Bu Liu killed Fang Yuan, almost all the Gu worms on Fang Yuan would be left behind. Such enormous spoils caused Han Bu Liu to let out his killing intent without restrain.

With a shift of his mind, eleven dogs charged towards Fang Yuan.

Woof Woof Woof!

They let out savage barks, and seemed unstoppable.

Fang Yuan was indifferent, he waited till these dogs neared him then waved his hand.

With a light wave, nineteen dogs rushed out from the grey fog behind him.

"Nineteen?" Han Bu Liu was extremely shocked, his eyes almost falling from their sockets.

"How can there be so many?!" He was filled with doubts.

He was an enslavement path Gu Master and had a lot of experience in commanding dogs, but despite his greatest efforts, only eleven dogs remained when he was done with the tenth round.

And little beast king, this strength path Gu Master has nineteen? A whole eight more than his!

What level of proficiency in enslavement path was this!

"No! Impossible! This is absolutely because he was lucky, otherwise how could he have so many dogs remaining? The true contest starts now. I will let you see what the commanding skill of an enslavement path Gu Master looks like!"

Han Bu Liu calmed his mind and was soon filled with fighting spirit.

In his opinion, little beast king was so young, no matter how much of a genius he was, he could not advance in both strength path and enslavement path at the same time.

"Eh? A flaw." Fang Yuan had been observing his opponent from the start.

Seeing Han Bu Liu's expression change irregularly, he immediately grasped this fleeting chance and decisively mobilized the few strongest dogs to form an offensive arrow formation.

The next moment, this 'arrow' suddenly broke the opponent's formation.

"Oh no!" Han Bu Liu's heart jumped rapidly as he immediately controlled his dogs.

However, how could Fang Yuan give him this chance, his remaining dogs formed into two exquisite arcs and outflanked the opponent's formation from left and right, seizing control of the situation in an instant!

Chapter 348: Chrysanthemum Akita Dog

This was an intense slaughter.

Han Bu Liu tried to resist desperately, trying to overturn the situation. But Fang Yuan saw through his actions every time, destroying his battle tactic. All his resistances were suppressed. Every effort he put in yielded no result.

An hour later, there were only eight wild dogs left, they were all Fang Yuan's.

Han Bu Liu's expression was pale, sweating profusely as he stood dazed on the ground.

Plop!

He suddenly kneeled on the ground, begging Fang Yuan: "Lord little beast king, please spare my life! I will do anything for you to repay your kindness. You are a genius, a monsterous genius! I was scared and had no options but to battle you. Your mastery of the enslavement path has left me utterly speechless in admiration. Lord little beast king, from today onwards, you are my master!"

"Oh, is that so, but how do you want me to see your sincerity? Unless you are willing to let me use the slavery Gu." Fang Yuan laughed lightly, manipulating eight wild dogs to surrounding Han Bu Liu.

Han Bu Liu flustered: "Lo... lord, inside this Gu Immortal blessed land, Gu Masters cannot use their Gu worms. Moreover, I do not have a slavery Gu."

"Then I have no choice." Fang Yuan waved his hand coldly, as eight wild dogs pounced.

"Lord Fang Zheng! No!" Han Bu Liu jolted up, screaming in fear, trying to escape.

But it was already too late, the eight wild dogs surrounded him, opening their mouths and chew on his body with their sharp canine teeth.

Han Bu Liu screamed pitifully, shrugging his arms like a lunatic, rolling on the ground.

But it was useless.

Even if he had ice muscles, steel bones, or bronze skin, inside the blessed land, all these were weakened and rendered useless.

"Fang Zheng, I won't let you off even as a ghost... you!"

Under his curses and cries, Han Bu Liu's flesh and skin were torn apart, his eyes were dug out, and blood flowed out of him, showing his pale white bones.

Fang Yuan watched silently, until he was completely dead and motionless.

He waved his hand lightly, and the eight wild dogs stopped their attacks, retreating to the two sides and opening a path for Fang Yuan.

Their bodies were full of blood traces. Some were still chewing on Han Bu Liu's bones, some of their claws still had Han Bu Liu's hair, flesh and so on.

Han Bu Liu's corpse was completely destroyed.

But his stomach area was consciously left intact by Fang Yuan's control.

He placed his palm on Han Bu Liu's stomach, his mind entering the aperture.

This was a standard rank four middle stage aperture.

But Han Bu Liu was already dead, thus his aperture was slowly dying and shrinking.

Due to the law of this blessed land, all his Gu worms were suppressed and unable to move, quietly lying on the surface of the primeval sea.

There were five Gu, all from the enslavement path, with two rank four Gu among them.

Fang Yuan looked around, and retrieved them all out, easily refining them into his own aperture.

Throughout the process, he did not use the Spring Autumn Cicada.

The law of the blessed land did not restrict him at this moment, in fact, it helped him to refine these Gu easily.

King Quan seemed to encourage Gu Masters in killing each other, this showed the cruelty of a demonic inheritance.

Fang Yuan killed Han Bu Liu, having seven wild dogs left.

During Han Bu Liu's dying struggle, he killed the wild dog that was most heavily injured.

At the brink of death, people were often able to unleash great power.

Fang Yuan looked at these seven wild dogs, showing a bit of regret in his peaceful gaze.

"Only seven wild dogs are left, each with injuries, this will make it much harder to get through the future rounds. But compared to the rewards I got, the death of twelve wild dogs is insignificant."

These wild dogs were commonly seen in forests of the outside world.

Using twelve dogs to exchange for two rank four Gu, three rank three Gu, this was too great of a deal.

"The three kings inheritance, not only is the inheritance a treasure, but the Gu Masters that enter the blessed land are all moving treasures! Killing them and taking their Gu worms, it would strengthen oneself!" As the heavenly power descended again, Fang Yuan sneered as his killing intent rose.

The misty fog appeared before him again.

Fang Yuan looked left and right.

Right in front of him, was a black shadow, it means an enemy Gu Master.

To the left, it was also a black shadow, but the side of this shadow was a protruding spiky shape.

To the right, it was an orange shadow, similar to before, it represented the chrysanthemum akita dog.

"I have seven wild dogs now, my battle strength is lacking, I cannot choose a Gu Master opponent. To the left, it is the hedgedog, its body is full of spikes and the attack power is twice of an ordinary dog. The right leads to the chrysanthemum akita dog..."

Fang Yuan's eyeballs darted around, and he walked to the right.

Although the hedgedog had higher attack power, to go through this path, his losses would be severe. Fang Yuan's seven wild dogs were all injured, if their intestines were pierced by spikes, it meant death.

Fang Yuan had experience, the hedgedog was dangerous, without any steel armor dogs or Yin dogs, he should avoid them as much as possible.

All these precious experiences were all intentionally hidden by Gu Masters when they found out during the first few months of the inheritance. Most people only learnt after falling into these pitfalls themselves, and would love for others to experience the same.

Fang Yuan took large steps forward, and the fog thinned.

Near his leg, the seven wild dogs followed closely.

They had battled with Fang Yuan along the way, and were all injured. Especially the intense battle with Han Bu Liu, it expended their life force and battle strength.

Dog enslavement Gu appeared in mid air, landing in Fang Yuan's hands.

When the fog disappeared, Fang Yuan received twenty dog enslavement Gu, all rank one.

Dog enslavement Gu was hard to retrieve, they were planted into the dog's soul. When the dog dies, their soul dissipates, and the dog enslavement Gu dies with it.

Even if the Gu Master brought lots of rank one dog enslavement Gu into the inheritance, it would not help.

With the blessed land's mysterious powers, it would take away all of the dog enslavement Gu in the Gu Master's hands and not return it, only leaving one for them.

After a few tries, Gu Masters learnt their lesson.

A total of nearly sixty chrysanthemum akita dogs appeared in front of Fang Yuan.

These dogs had orange-yellow fur, like the color of an orange. Their long ears drooped down, covering their ear holes. At the same time, there were chrysanthemum patterns on their fur.

Their body size was around the same as an ordinary wild dog, or even slightly smaller.

But Fang Yuan's expression changed.

Chrysanthemum akita dogs were naturally good at cooperation, the larger their numbers, the fiercer they fight. And Fang Yuan's location was terrible, in the middle of a plain, without no terrain advantage, he could easily be engulfed if he relied on just seven wild dogs. Fang Yuan's ending would not be any better than Han Bu Liu.

"I have to get to the top of that mound!" Only in the time of one breath, Fang Yuan scanned the surroundings and ran towards the mound with no hesitation.

He ran for five steps before the chrysanthemum akita dogs found him.

Woof woof woof...

They barked, as numerous chrysanthemum akita dogs responded.

At once, all the surrounding chrysanthemum akita dogs gathered at one spot, forming into a river-like formation as they charged towards Fang Yuan.

This situation, if it was the wild dogs, lightning symbol dog, or hedgedog, it would not happen, unless there was a dog king to command them.

But the chrysanthemum akita dogs had a strong sense of cooperation, even without a dog king, they could still coordinate and unleash a group attack.

This was completely different from fighting individually.

Fang Yuan narrowly rushed to the top of the mound before the chrysanthemum akita dogs surrounded it.

Fang Yuan retreated until there was a cliff behind him.

The chrysanthemum akita dogs stopped for a moment, before charging again.

Because the terrain was narrow, the dog group could only send out fifteen dogs at once.

Fang Yuan quickly commanded his seven wild dogs to defend against them.

The two groups fought intensely, as Fang Yuan used his outstanding manipulation to hold them back.

At the same time, he waved his hand, throwing the five dog enslavement Gu out at the perfect timing.

Immediately, he had new fighting troops! Five healthy chrysanthemum akita dogs, turning around and joining Fang Yuan, causing the situation to reverse.

The original fifteen against seven, became ten against twelve, Fang Yuan held the advantage.

As companions turned into enemies, the dog group went into a panic. Fang Yuan used that opportunity to attack, killing six chrysanthemum akita dogs, as the other four retreated.

He could have taken down all ten chrysanthemum akita dogs originally, but he chose to let the four chrysanthemum akita dogs escape.

Fang Yuan's rich experience was not just in this aspect.

He had twenty dog enslavement Gu, but he did not use them all at once, but in batches.

This terrain restricted the number of dogs that could enter battle. At the same time, the fewer dogs there were, the more Fang Yuan could use his exquisite manipulation skills.

When there are more dogs, Fang Yuan would be more distracted across battles, and his control would weaken.

The chrysanthemum akita dog group attacked again at Fang Yuan's defensive line.

Fang Yuan had calculated to perfection, every time he used the dog enslavement Gu, it was used at the most crucial area. He not only chose the healthiest chrysanthemum akita dog that he could find, but also ruined the formation of the enemy chrysanthemum akita dogs.

Such benefits was not obvious, but in time, he gained much from it.

After nearly ten attacks, the chrysanthemum akita dogs were repelled every time.

Fang Yuan had three dog enslavement Gu left, and the remaining ten or so chrysanthemum akita dogs ran away in fear.

These chrysanthemum akita dogs were all injured, Fang Yuan had let them off earlier, to avoid their dying struggle.

Right now, they were already afraid, and chose to retreat.

"All this is due to the lack of a dog king to command them, otherwise, they would not have escaped so easily." Fang Yuan breathed out some turbid air, choosing not to attack.

After this battle, his seven wild dogs were left with three, but he gained sixteen chrysanthemum akita dogs.

Under Fang Yuan's skillful control, he distributed the injuries evenly on these dogs. Although they all had injuries, they preserved their battle strength, causing Fang Yuan to recover greatly from his losses in the previous round.

Chapter 349: Big Lightning Symbol Dog

Thirteenth round...

Fourteenth round...

Seventeenth round...

Eighteenth round...

Fang Yuan got through all the stages, and the number of dogs he controlled increased. By the end of the nineteenth round, he had over eighty dogs.

Among them, he had over forty chrysanthemum akita dogs, more than twenty lightning symbol dogs, and nineteen hedgedogs.

During this period, he killed another person, it was a rank three peak stage water path Gu Master.

But, he eventually did not meet Bai Ning Bing.

"Twentieth round." Fang Yuan had been counting in his heart.

In the three kings inheritance, every ten rounds, the difficulty would rise sharply.

After the twentieth round, there would be hundred beast kings, and hundreds to nearly a thousand beasts would attack at once.

Three lumps of light shadows appeared again in the fog, left, right, and center.

The one in the middle was orange, the size of a wicker-basket.

The left was a eerie blue lightning static, shining and was the size of a stone mill.

At the right, it was like the moon in water, flower in fog, it was a green-white formless light shadow. Among the three, this was the smallest light shadow.

Fang Yuan was clear, the size of the light shadow represented the size of the beast group, the larger it is, the more beasts there would be.

The orange shadow in front represented the chrysanthemum akita dogs, around two hundred of it. The left was the eerie blue shadow, showing a hundred and fifty lightning symbol dogs. The right was a green-white shadow, showing the Yin dog group, only around a hundred of it.

Fang Yuan eliminated the chrysanthemum akita dogs from his choice.

Once the chrysanthemum akita dog group had a dog king, they would be even more united. The larger the numbers, the larger their battle strength. Over two hundred chrysanthemum akita dogs was a calamity to the current Fang Yuan.

Next, he ruled out the Yin dog group.

Yin dogs were very unique, they did not have physical bodies, and were like a lump of Yin energy in a dog shape, floating in the air. Ordinary attacks cannot kill them, they can even penetrate mountain rocks, phase through the ground, and hide under water, etc.

Fang Yuan's dogs did not have the ability to kill them. lightning symbol dogs only represented speed, they did not have the ability to emit lightning.

After thinking for a while, Fang Yuan chose the left path.

After the fog dispersed, the dog group surrounded him, moving alongside him slowly. A rank two dog enslavement Gu fell from the sky, landing in his palm.

When he got out of the fog, the lightning symbol dog group was loitering around the area.

On the mound, there was a larger dog, lying on the grass and sleeping.

It was larger than an ordinary lightning symbol dog by twice of their size, its body was covered in deep blue fur, sharp and spiky, flowing with static.

This was a hundred beast king — Big Lightning Symbol Dog!

"A godsend opportunity!" Fang Yuan was clear of the battle situation, as his eyes shone in a brilliant light, instantly making his decision.

He waved his hand, and sent out all his troops.

More than eighty dogs surrounded him in the middle, charging towards the big lightning symbol dog.

The big lightning symbol dog's reaction was fast, its ears twitched and it opened its eyes, standing up instantly.

It raised his head and howled, assembling the nearby lightning symbol dog group.

Getting the command from their king, the surrounding lightning symbol dogs responded and quickly gathered at the dog king's side from all directions.

Although the lightning symbol dogs had great speed, Fang Yuan had the initiative.

He gathered the force that he had, using them to collective assault the leader of his enemies!

Some nearby lightning symbol dogs were faster than Fang Yuan and gathered at the dog king's side.

"Charge!" Fang Yuan's eyes shone with resolution, at this time, hesitation was the biggest taboo. Once he had made up his mind, he would charge ahead fearlessly.

The defending lightning symbol dogs were quickly overwhelmed.

Fang Yuan's formation was tight, while the lightning symbol dogs were loosely positioned, as most of them had not reached the dog king yet.

"Woof!"

As the hundred beast king big lightning symbol dog, seeing its subjects slaughtered, its inner ferocity was unleashed, as it charged towards Fang Yuan while brandishing its claws.

Fang Yuan willed, and twenty lightning symbol dogs split into two groups, flanking from the left and right. Nineteen hedgedogs lined into formation, charging fearlessly at the big lightning symbol dog. The remaining dogs — over forty chrysanthemum akita dogs, surrounded Fang Yuan, slowly spreading out and moving ahead with the hedgedogs.

The big lightning symbol dog had fallen into Fan Yuan's encirclement, trapped in the middle.

Fang Yuan did not care about the expenditure of his mental energy, mobilizing his dog group and using the most perfect coordination.

The big lightning symbol dog had greater speed than an ordinary lightning symbol dog, but because of Fang Yuan's encirclement, its greatest advantage was restricted.

It barked loudly, gathering its subjects.

Its subjects were rushing over in a frenzy, trying to defend it.

Fang Yuan had to trap the big lightning symbol dog, while blocking the attacks of the outside dog group, he faced great pressure and his head started hurting, as sweat poured out of his forehead.

The situation was dangerous.

If he fought them head on, even if he won, it would be a tragic victory, and his troops would dwindle. Thus, he thought of the 'capture the king' approach.

But if he could not control this hundred beast king, then Fang Yuan would become the filling inside a dumpling, not only would he fail this round, he might even lose his life.

In this Gu Immortal Blessed Land, other than the inheritance's Gu worms, other Gu cannot be mobilized, thus it was easy for Gu Masters to die.

Fang Yuan's strength qi Gu, all-out effort Gu could not be used.

Of course, he had his final trump card — Spring Autumn Cicada. But with the Spring Autumn Cicada's current condition, although he could activate it, there was a huge risk in doing so. He was likely to self-detonate and die for nothing. Thus, unless he was forced to the extreme, and had no other choices left, Fang Yuan would not use it abruptly.

Sweat gathered into drops on his forehead, falling onto the ground.

Fang Yuan did not care about wiping it, he was clutching onto the rank two dog enslavement Gu, and did not strike yet.

He was finding the best opportunity.

Using a rank one dog enslavement Gu and subduing ordinary dogs, he could do it half-heartedly. But to subdue a hundred beast king using a rank two dog enslavement Gu, there was a possibility of failure.

That is because the hundred beast king has natural Gu worms on its body. These Gu could ruin Fang Yuan's plans.

He only had one chance, if the rank two dog enslavement Gu was destroyed, he would be finished. Thus, he had to be careful!

"Woof!"

The big lightning symbol dog was getting anxious, it suddenly opened its mouth and shot out a lump of blue plasma.

The dark blue plasma was like a sticky substance, falling from above. As it landed on the grass, it did not dissipate, but remained shining, turning the grass and rocks charred black with a crackling sound.

"This is a rank two plasma Gu!" FangYuan immediately recognised the culprit behind this plasma.

Plasma Gu did not have a strong attack power.

Although the attack was very suddenly, and engulfed Fang Yuan's numerous chrysanthemum akita dogs, he quickly ordered the dogs in this field of plasma to retreat at the first second.

The fur on the dogs were all charred, and they were moving sluggishly, after being paralyzed by the current. But they still had some fighting power remaining.

"Woof, woof, woof."

The big lightning symbol dog continued to shoot out plasma, as it covered a large area of grass.

Fang Yuan's brows were tightly knitted, his expression turning grim.

The plasma Gu's attack power was not high, but it would affect the terrain for a period of time. During this period, the area would be a forbidden zone for Fang Yuan's dogs.

Fang Yuan's troops were already in the center, they did not have much room to move.

The plasma added onto this disadvantage, being a huge restriction to Fang Yuan's plans in mobilizing troops, or changing their formation.

Without any choice left, Fang Yuan had to redeploy his troops.

He had originally placed the lightning symbol dogs at the outer line of defense, but now they moved in to deal with the hundred beast king. He sent the chrysanthemum akita dogs out, to defend against the over hundred lightning symbol dogs.

Lightning symbol dogs moved freely in the area affected by the plasma, in fact, because of the electric current stimulation, their movement speed was even raised.

The scene had become extremely disadvantageous to Fang Yuan.

Lightning symbol dogs had some fear and hesitation towards the hundred beast king big lightning symbol dog naturally. This caused Fang Yuan's manipulation to be tougher and more energy intensive, and at the same time his control was weaker.

At the outer ring of defense, the chrysanthemum akita dogs' speed was inferior to the lightning symbol dogs, they could only form into a tight ring of defense and defend against them passively.

If they were the lightning symbol dogs, Fang Yuan could still use speed to restrict them through kiting.

"Endure, we have to endure this! I've already learnt of the hundred beast king's first Gu, next, we have to continue..." Although he was in danger, Fang Yuan's heart was still calm and peaceful.

Everytime the plasma Gu was activated, it needed a cooldown of five breaths. The plasma Gu itself needed rest too.

During this five breaths, Fang Yuan could activate the rank two dog enslavement Gu without fear of the plasma Gu's attack.

But Fang Yuan did not know what other Gu this hundred beast king had.

To be safe, he had to continue testing.

Time continued to pass, and the situation was getting tougher for Fang Yuan.

He had lost fourteen lightning symbol dogs, only having nine left. The hedgedogs were not the same race as the lightning symbol dog, thus there was less casualties, but only eleven remained.

Chrysanthemum akita dogs suffered the greatest loss, from around fifty, they fell to less than twenty.

But Fang Yuan did not manage to find out of the hundred beast king possessed a second Gu.

He decided to strike!

"I can't wait anymore. Most likely, this big lightning symbol dog only has one Gu on it."

He had to take a risk.

If he continued waiting, his line of defense would be completely broken.

Rank two dog enslavement Gu!

While the big lightning symbol dog shot out a plasma bolt, Fang Yuan quickly struck and unleashed his Gu.

Under Fang Yuan's supervision, the dog enslavement Gu successfully flew into the big lightning symbol dog and planted itself into its soul.

A formless impact in terms of mental energy assaulted Fang Yuan through his dog enslavement Gu.

Fang Yuan's head was already hurting, but after suffering this attack, he instantly felt dizzy.

This was the soul of the hundred beast king, the resistance towards the enslavement.

Subduing a hundred beast king was not easy.

Fang Yuan's body wavered, gritting his teeth as he endured.

A mental connection allowed Fang Yuan and the big lightning symbol dog to communicate. The dog was still resisting earlier, wanting to chop Fang Yuan into pieces, but the moment later, it started barking, wagging its tail at Fang Yuan affectionately.

The surrounding lightning symbol dog group heard the dog king's call and stopped their attack.

The intense battle had ended, and peace returned.

Fang Yuan stood on the spot, turning his head and looking at the battlefield.

The risk paid off!

Although he had some losses, but looking around him — there were at least a hundred and twenty lightning symbol dogs.

Not to forget, he had a hundred beast king that possesses a plasma Gu.

Fang Yuan's battle strength surged!

Chapter 350: Dog Guts Gu

The fog ahead was thick.

Fang Yuan was walking in the fog, beside him, there was a large dog group.

Eleven hedgedogs, a hundred and thirty-two lightning symbol dogs, seventeen chrysanthemum akita dogs. Other than that, there was a hundred beast king, big lightning symbol dog.

Restricted by the heavenly power, the dog group followed Fang Yuan silently, quiet and obedient, not making a sound.

In the world of the fog, all was silent.

It was so silent that Fang Yuan hear his own breathing.

Although he had endured twenty rounds, and the dogs in his hand had reached the highest so far, Fang Yuan was not optimistic.

"In this three kings inheritance, every ten rounds, the difficulty would rise by many times. Although I have more than a hundred dogs now, to survive the next ten rounds and get to the thirtieth round on my first attempt, it will not be easy."

Thirty rounds, that was Fang Yuan's goal for his first attempt in King Quan inheritance.

In his previous life, the three kings inheritance was only completely rung dry after many years. Fang Yuan would have to spend quite a bit of time on San Cha mountain, it was not realistic to attempt to get the inheritance in one go.

Three kings inheritance, all three were tough. Even if Fang Yuan had a hundred beast king, and over a hundred dogs, he could only stabilize his current position.

In the future rounds, if he got careless in any of them, he might lose everything, losing the dogs that he had painstakingly subdued, and even his life.

A demonic inheritance was this cruel.

"This King Quan inheritance, the deeper we go, the more advantageous it is for an enslavement path Gu Master. I walked on the enslavement path before in my previous life, but this time, I am a strength path Gu Master."

After experiencing that dangerous battle, Fang Yuan's head was still dizzy.

Using his mental energy so intensely, spending all his energy to control the dog groups to battle, this was the backlash.

But if it was an enslavement path Gu Master who has a strong soul, such symptoms would be very small.

Gu Masters on the enslavement path enslaved beasts or worms. They have to manipulate large numbers of worms or beasts at the same time, it used up a lot of their mental energy. Thus, enslavement path Gu Masters often used a special set of Gu worms to train and increase the quality of their own soul.

In the King Quan's inheritance, the heavenly power did not restrict the soul enhancements of Gu Masters at all.

Thus, enslavement path Gu Masters had a huge advantage in King Quan Inheritance.

"But the enslavement path is very tough. Firstly, food was a huge burden, the large the size of your beast or worm group, the more food you needed. Secondly, to recruit strong worm or beasts, it is not easy. One can easily suffer a backlash, turning into an idiot. Thirdly, enslavement path Gu Masters overly rely on their beasts or worms. Their bodies are weak, and they are easily to deal with when alone." Fang Yuan analyzed in his mind.

The different styles of Gu Masters, all had their strengths and weaknesses, difficulties and advantages.

The world was changing, the world was transforming. In the current Gu world, qi path was non-existent, strength path was declining, only left with a trace of its former glory. Enslavement path was extremely ordinary, and was hard to rise up. Occasionally, some enslavement path experts rise up, but vanish like a shooting star, only brilliant for a moment.

"Enslavement path Gu Masters have a huge requirement for resources. It is tiring on the mind and body, even a middle-sized clan cannot afford to feed an enslavement path Gu Master. At most, large or super clans would choose to nurture a few enslavement path Gu Masters for war purposes. Within the demonic path, it is even harder for enslavement path Gu Masters to survive, barely any even exists. That is why I did not choose this path."

Fang Yuan calmed his spirit, focusing his mind.

After a while, he felt his head clearing up, as the dizziness faded.

He opened his eyes, looking around.

To his left, right, and front, there was a light shadow each.

Earlier, the light shadows were a blur. But after twenty rounds, they became extremely clear.

The left shadow was a group of chrysanthemum akita dogs, around two hundred of them. Some sprawled on the ground and rested, some were playing, while the rest were drinking milk from their mother.

Fang Yuan concentrated his gaze, looking intensely.

The beast kings of the chrysanthemum akita dogs were different from others, the stronger they were, the smaller their bodies.

Especially in a chaotic battlefield, the beast king mixes in with the dog groups, and become hidden. It was a good way to protect itself.

'Where can the hundred beast king be?" Fang Yuan looked around, and suddenly the light shadow changed, showing a Gu.

This Gu was fist-sized, shaped like a pebble, dark brown in color. Its surface was smooth, like it had a layer of oil.

"Dog guts Gu." Fang Yuan recognised this Gu at the first second: "Appearing after the beast group, that means that if I choose this group of chrysanthemum akita dogs, and attain victory, I will get a dog guts Gu..."

A while later, this light shadow vanished.

Fang Yuan did not make his decision, but looked at the middle one.

The light shadow in front of him was showing a black-ish dog group.

These dogs were barking at each other, charging and crashing together. It showed the ferocity and violent nature of this type of dog.

This was the steel armor dog.

There was a leather armor on this type of dog, the leather armor was dark and heavy, like steel, it had strong defenses.

In the process of growing up, the dogs would knock into one another, to reduce the intense itchiness of their bodies growing bigger.

The hundred beast king of the steel armor dog had the same size as the big lightning symbol dog. It was very noticeable among the dog groups, Fang Yuan found it almost immediately.

Immediately after, the light shadow flashed, and a Gu appeared.

This Gu, Fang Yuan was familiar with it; he had used it earlier.

Rank two dog enslavement Gu.

"If I choose the steel armor dog group and win, I get a dog enslavement Gu..."

Fang Yuan muttered, turning his gaze to the right.

In the light shadow on the right, there was no dogs at all. Instead, it showed a mountainous scene, with grey-white mountain rocks and cliffs, green trees swaying with the wind.

After a while, this image vanished, not showing a Gu like before.

"This is a chance to leave the King Quan Inheritance." Fang Yuan knew in his heart.

King Quan Inheritance was created inside the blessed land, Gu Masters who enter were restricted by the heavenly power, unable to enter or leave at will.

But the three kings inheritance was not a place without exits, there was a hope of survival in it.

At every set interval, there would be a chance to retreat from the inheritance.

Just like this time, if Fang Yuan chose the right side, when he leaves the fog, he would be transported out.

He would appear at the mountainous area as shown in the light shadow, and this mountain waist was not far away, it was somewhere on San Cha mountain.

But Fang Yuan did not choose the right side.

"I have the resources on me to continue forward. It is too much of a pity if I leave now. Of course, there might not be a chance for me to leave later."

This was also a formless test.

Many Gu Masters, although they had strength, in order to stay safe, they decided to give up and leave the inheritance, wasting such a good opportunity.

Some Gu Masters had no talent, but went forward recklessly, missing the opportunity to retreat, they die in regret.

Fang Yuan had never lacked courage, he gave up this opportunity resolutely. To him, there was only two options.

"To the left, it is the chrysanthemum akita dogs. This dog is most united, and the location of the dog king is unknown. If I win, I get a dog guts Gu. Dog guts Gu is a rank two supplementary Gu of the enslavement path. It is used on dogs, once activated, it allows the courage and morale of my dogs in a certain range to rise, sweeping away their fear and drawing out their complete battle strength."

Fang Yuan thought about his previous match.

He was forced to use the lightning symbol dogs to attack the big lightning symbol dog. In the end, the lightning symbol dogs were fearful and battled in trepidation, having much less battle strength than normal. Fang Yuan had to waste his mental energy to force them to fight, causing his mind to feel exhausted.

Beast kings suppressed and generated fear in ordinary wild beasts.

But if Fang Yuan had used the dog guts Gu earlier, using it on the lightning symbol dogs.

These lightning symbol dogs would feel extremely courageous, no longer fearful and could execute brave attacks towards the big lightning symbol dog.

Thus, the dog guts Gu, although not an attacking Gu, it was the best supplementary Gu. It targeted dogs, causing their courage to double or triple, raising their morale sky high!

"Dog guts Gu is only rank two, it can allow ordinary dogs to suppress their fear towards hundred beast kings. Above that would be the rank three dog guts above mountain Gu, able to resist the fear towards a thousand beast king. At rank four, it would be dog guts above sea Gu, able to resist the aura of a myriad beast king. If it can rise to rank five, it would be the infamous dog guts above heaven Gu! It can cause dogs to go into a frenzy, going crazy and attacking like a tsunami, even having the courage to overturn the emperor of dogs..."

Fang Yuan knew clearly, and even knew that in King Quan Inheritance, there were rank one to five Gu of the dog guts series.

In his previous life, many people had obtained the rank three and four dog guts Gu, and there was even a lucky person who obtained the one and only rank five dog guts above heaven Gu.

"If I want to conquer the King Quan Inheritance, the dog guts Gu is necessary."

Fang Yuan had to admit, he had always had a desire towards dog guts Gu.

But his steps did not move to the left, but instead, moved forward —

He chose the steel armor dog group.

Although he wanted the dog guts Gu badly, he was not overwhelmed by greed.

The chrysanthemum akita dogs were extremely united, they were extremely strong in group battles, it would be a tough battle. At the same time, they dog king hid itself very well, Fang Yuan could not find it, it would be a huge threat.

But the steel armor dogs were different.

Their dog king was very apparent, and in Fang Yuan's hands, he had a special tool that was extremely effective against steel armor dogs.

Fang Yuan walked out of the fog, and the steel armor dog group was vigilant, immediately having a reaction.

As the hundred beast king, big steel armor dog howled, causing the dogs to run and gather by its side.

During the whole process, Fang Yuan observed silently.

He did not attack like before, because last time, he had a rank two dog enslavement Gu, but now he did not have it anymore.

He needed to exterminate this group of dogs to pass this round, and get a dog enslavement Gu as a reward.

Chapter 351: Multitask Gu

The two dog groups were at a stalemate.

At Fang Yuan's side, the blue color lightning symbol dog were at the main position, with the grey hedgedogs as support along with the orange chrysanthemum akita dogs. As for the steel armor dog groups, it was a sea of black.

Fang Yuan mobilized the big lightning symbol dog to the front, waving his hand and sending the dogs out to attack as the vanguard.

Big steel armor dog barked, upon seeing the big lightning symbol dog appear, it stepped into the battlefield as well.

Beside it, the steel armor dog group followed closely behind, they were like a huge black cloud, flying down from the mound, giving off a terrifying aura.

The dog groups clashed together, Fang Yuan had a limited number of vanguards, quickly engulfed by the huge number of steel armor dogs.

But because of the big lightning symbol dog's existence, the steel armor dog group could not take them down so easily.

The big lightning symbol dog was after all a hundred beast king, under the attack of the dog group, it was able to handle them left and right, putting up a brave fight. Ordinary steel armor dogs were not its match.

Woof!

The big steel armor dog stepped out, finally stopping the assault of the big lightning symbol dog.

Only a hundred beast king could stop a hundred beast king.

As the intense battle continued, big lightning symbol dog started to weaken. It had just undergone a battle earlier, and there was still injuries on it, causing its battle strength to be lower than usual. Furthermore, its specialty was speed, but it was going head to head with the big steel armor dog who specialized in defense, it obviously had the disadvantage.

Fang Yuan saw this, and sent his dog group over.

The new troops flowed in like a river, entering the battle causing chaos.

But the enemy was the steel armor dogs, experts at defense, most adept at such battles.

Although Fang Yuan sent out his army, and only left a few dog guards behind to protect himself, he could not change the situation.

Be it the hundred beast king battle, or the dog group battle, he was at a disadvantage.

But Fang Yuan was not worried.

The truth is, this was what he wanted all along.

He was waiting.

Waiting for the weapon which suppressed the steel armor dogs to appear.

Woof!

Big lightning symbol dog could not block the attack of the big steel armor dog, and suddenly barked, shooting out a mouthful of blue plasma.

Rank two plasma Gu!

"This is it." Fang Yuan's eyes shone brightly, as his lips curled up.

Steel armor dog group gathered at their dog king, attacking the big lightning symbol dog while enduring the attacks of Fang Yuan's dog group, causing them to be closely packed together, like the shape of a black bucket.

Blue plasma landed on the ground, splattering.

Large amounts of plasma landed on the steel armor dogs, causing their bodies to vibrate as they cried. Not only did their battle strength fall, the formation of the entire dog group was broken and heavily obstructed.

The armor on the steel armor dogs were of metallic element. Although the steel gave them superior defenses, it also made them unable to resist the power of electricity.

The attack power of plasma Gu was not high, but once used on the steel armor dogs, it was a formidable move.

The big lightning symbol dog shot out plasma continuously, as plasma covered the entire battlefield, heavily weakening the battle strength of the steel armor dogs.

The firm steel-like formation, had collapsed under the effects of plasma Gu.

Fang Yuan saw an opportunity, and commanded the dogs to charge, the dog group outside worked together with the big lightning symbol dog in the middle, unleashing a high offensive power.

If one watched from the sky, they would see that the large black area was first eroded by blue color, before being devoured by the surrounding blend of colors.

Black continued to reduce, while blue, yellow, and grey overtook them and dominated the field.

The situation changed quickly, soon, Fang Yuan regained his control, killing most of the steel armor dogs and encircling the big steel armor dog in the middle.

Feeling danger, the Gu worm on the big steel armor dog started to work.

Big steel armor dog gained more strength, while black spikes grew out of its body.

Fifteen minutes later, the big steel armor dog's throat was torn by the big lightning symbol dog, and fell indignantly. Its blood flowed on the ground, but it did not get up anymore.

The battle ended.

As for the two Gu worms on the big steel armor dog, one was destroyed during the battle,while the other flew away.

Fang Yuan's expression was grim, in order to kill this hundred beast king, he paid a huge price. He only had half of his dog group left, and it would be a problem for his remaining battles.

After twenty rounds, beast kings would appear.

With the beast king, the dog groups would display greater battle strength, at the same time, the beast king itself was a huge threat.

The more Gu worms on its body, the stronger it is, and the worse the situation would be for the Gu Master fighting it.

Fang Yuan's luck was bad this time, the big steel armor dog he encountered this time had two Gu. Especially when one of the Gu was good at attack and defense, causing Fang Yuan to suffer great losses.

One's own luck matters when challenging the three kings inheritance.

The steel armor dog group was Fang Yuan's best choice this time, but his luck was not as good.

A rank two dog enslavement Gu fell from above, as his prize for winning.

Fang Yuan did not use the Spring Autumn Cicada, he instantly refined the Gu with the help of the heavenly power.

"This Gu is the key to getting past the next round." With such a resolution, Fang Yuan stepped into the fog.

Left, center, right, there were light shadows at all three directions. They were: A large numbers of corpse dogs, a certain number of Yin dogs, and a huge number of hyenas!

Fang Yuan's eyes glowed as he analyzed.

This time, his strength was limited, thus he had to choose wisely, fighting a weak enemy while thinking of the reward of winning.

"If I defeat the corpse dog group, I get a white silver relic Gu. Killing the Yin dogs give me a two tasks at once Gu..."

White silver relic Gu was no use to Fang Yuan. At this stage, only yellow gold relic Gu had an attraction to him.

But unfortunately, yellow gold relic Gu was heavily controlled even in Shang clan city.

Rank four Gu Masters were experts in the mortal Gu Master realm. One yellow gold relic Gu could affect the battle strength among rank four Gu Masters greatly.

In the market, white silver relic Gu was sold normally, while yellow gold relic Gu were extremely rare, often held in the hands of the higher-ups.

Fang Yuan knew, super clans like Shang clan had lots of yellow gold relic Gu in their inventory. But even with the purple thorn token, he could not get them.

Shang Yan Fei held these yellow gold relic Gu in his hand, refusing to let them enter the market.

This was a secret temptation.

If Fang Yuan truly joined Shang clan, the yellow gold relic Gu would be a form of reward.

Shang Yan Fei's brilliance was not something a commoner could understand. Fang Yuan did not want to compete with him in wits and strength just for a yellow gold relic Gu, and cause his own plans to be stalled.

"In the three kings inheritance, there are yellow gold relic Gu. But only after the fortieth round, if I can get one, the situation would improve greatly.

Fang Yuan had desire towards the yellow gold relic Gu.

But he knew, whether he could get one was all attributed to his own luck.

He could not force this.

As for the two tasks at once Gu, it could allow the Gu Master to split his mind into two and was extremely effective in manipulating worm or beast armies.

Fang Yuan himself could do four tasks at once, if he added in this Gu, he would be able to do six tasks at once.

"Two tasks at once Gu is only a rank two Gu. Going higher, there are three tasks at once, four tasks at once, five tasks at once and so on. Multitask Gu is the most important tool for an enslavement path Gu Master. Hmm, wait... this is?"

Fang Yuan looked at the right, after the hyenas disappeared, it showed a token.

An ordinary reward is an enslavement path Gu.

But this reward was slightly special, it was an ordinary looking token.

The token was rough and had an irregular shape, like it was casually molded into shape by someone. On the surface, there was the carving of San Cha mountain, but this map was extremely casual and ugly, giving a strong feeling of half-heartedness. With one glance, one can easily tell that the person who made this token did not put in any effort, only doing it out of necessity.

But once Fang Yuan saw this token, his eyes lit up.

"King Quan travel token!" He immediately forgot about the white silver relic Gu, two tasks at once Gu.

"What luck to have encountered this token, I must get it!" Fang Yuan had a determined mind, he had to get this token at all costs.

Although this token looked worthless, it was one of the best items.

Right now, no one knew its worth yet, but Fang Yuan knew clearly, towards to end of the three kings inheritance in his previous life, the price of such a token was as high as a rank four Gu!

"But this hyena pack is huge, and there are two dog kings. If I choose this path, the risks are huge. The best scenario is that I enslave one of the two big hyenas during battle. But even so, if I win this battle, I would suffer huge losses and would lose the ability to advance further."

Fang Yuan had a clear understanding of his own strength.

The advantage of experience was shown here, it allowed him to clearly know the advantages and disadvantages of every choice.

Fang Yuan thought about it, and decided to take a risk.

Since he walked on the demonic path, he had to take risks, by taking the extreme path, he would gain the biggest profits. Having no regrets after every choice, this was truly being alive!

Four hours later.

An intense battle ended.

On and below the mound, there were dog corpses everywhere. Fresh blood flowed as limbs decorated the ground.

Fang Yuan stood on the mound, slightly injured. In this Gu Immortal blessed land, he could not use his Gu, causing him to be extremely weakened.

"But I won anyway..." Fang Yuan looked at his surroundings, only a dozen or so dogs were left, as he sighed deeply.

Losing almost all the dogs that he had, there was no longer any hope of advancing in this cruel demonic inheritance.

But Fang Yuan had the last bit of hope in his mind.

The heavenly power descended, sending him into the fog once again.

"If I encounter Bai Ning Bing, by borrowing her strength, I would be able to continue." But Fang Yuan was to be disappointed.

All three directions led to dog groups. If he did not have the travel token, Fang Yuan would definitely die.

He took out the travel token.

Grasping it tightly, he bit the tip of his tongue and spit out some blood.

The blood landed on the token, and Fang Yuan opened his mouth, saying to the token softy: "Woof."

The token emitted a strong light, as it tore through space, dragging Fang Yuan with it.

In the silent fog, there was no one left.

Chapter 352: Casually killed

Mountain winds gently blew.

In an ordinary bamboo forest in the middle of San Cha mountain, the space suddenly shattered and light burst out.

The light flickered away instantly; in a bush where there had been no one before, a person appeared.

It was a youth with black hair, black pupils and a calm face. He was holding a token, it was Fang Yuan.

"I have exited King Quan Inheritance..." Fang Yuan had only felt his eyes blur for a moment and the next moment, he was at a strange place.

He looked around, confirming there was no danger around him and that he was somewhere around the middle of San Cha mountain.

According to his initial estimation, he was now at the northern side of San Cha mountain; while the cave he had occupied with Bai Ning Bing was on the southeast side.

He raised his head and looked at the peak.

San Cha mountain possessed three peaks which stood high in the clouds like three equal spear tips.

The light pillars on the peaks were gradually dying down.

The yellow light pillar represented the entrance to King Quan Inheritance; the blue light pillar was King Xin Inheritance; and the red light pillar was King Bao Inheritance.

The size of the light pillars had already decreased by around half compared to when Fang Yuan had just entered.

With the passing of time, the number of Gu Masters that entered the inheritances increased while the light pillars would continue to become small till it completely disappeared; at that time, the entrances to the three inheritances would be closed.

After another round of waiting, the light pillars would activate again and bring in a new round of carnage.

Fang Yuan looked at the token in his hand.

On the surface of this unsightly King Quan token, there were now several deep cracks.

Fang Yuan was not surprised.

King Quan travel token could be used for three times at most. After three uses, the token would completely crack into pieces and could not be used anymore.

However, these three chances for retreating were extremely precious. This was not only a chance to survive, the even more important thing was the Gu Master would have a psychological superiority and could choose their paths more freely.

Fang Yuan stored this travel token carefully and hurried towards his cave.

"Ah, it is Fang Zheng!"

"Little beast king has finally appeared..."

On the whole way, Fang Yuan ran into many Gu Masters; regardless of righteous path or demonic path, they all casted a strange and amazed look at him.

"What happened?" Fang Yuan frowned, he keenly sensed that something rather important had happened.

Halfway to his cave, he casually grabbed someone and questioned.

It turns out Bai Ning Bing killed a Tie clan Gu Master in King Quan Inheritance. After she came out of the inheritance, she was immediately discovered by Tie clan.

Tie clan Gu Masters surrounded the cave and trapped Bai Ning Bing.

Four rank four middle stage Gu Masters moved at the same time and used iron cabinet Gu to lock down the nearby area.

Bai Ning Bing could not force her way through it and was now being attacked continuously by Tie clan Gu Masters.

"Lord little beast king, this matter has been made a big deal and the whole San Cha mountain knows about it. This is no longer a matter of personal hatred but it represents the battle between the righteous path and us demonic path! Actually, everyone is waiting for you. Lord, if you act, those Tie clan Gu Masters won't be able to block you. You are our demonic path's genius, our demonic path's flag! Lord, I have said everything there is to say, can I take my leave now?" That unlucky guy grabbed by Fang Yuan begged in a sobbing voice.

"Such a big thing happened..." Fang Yuan slightly furrowed his brows while holding the unfortunate guy by the collar.

Although this news could startle anyone when they first hear it, it was not beyond Fang Yuan's anticipation.

There were naturally going to be conflicts as they moved through the three kings inheritance.

This was a demonic path inheritance, the competition was extremely cruel. Sometimes, even if one wanted to retreat, they could not.

"Tie clan has rust flower Gu, this Gu is stored in the souls of Tie clansmen. Whoever kills Tie clansmen would be stained with this formless fragrance. It is not surprising Bai Ning Bing was found out." Fang Yuan nodded while mumbling to himself.

"Lord, you are truly knowledgeable, you are extremely right. Lord, you don't know that your disappearance these few days caused everyone on San Cha mountain to comment and say you are an ostrich and are afraid of being involved with a top clan like Tie clan. Do I not know what kind of person lord is? Lord, you are the one I admire the most, since you arrived at San Cha mountain, you have killed the tyrant, Fei Li and Sky Tiger. Is there anyone who do not know of your fame and reputation? You definitely have some reason that the outsiders don't need to know. Right now if you act, those Tie clansmen will definitely wet their pants in fear and implore lord to let them off."

Fang Yuan had great strength and as he grabbed this unlucky guy's collar, the unlucky guy was having trouble breathing and his face was becoming purplish.

However, for survival, this Gu Master talked non-stop, flattering from start to end, showing his immense will to survive.

Fang Yuan fell silent and only after a long while did he slowly speak: "You are right."

He loosened his hand.

This rank two Gu Master immediately flushed with joy: "What kind of person is lord, any discerning person would be clear of it! Lord is absolutely a great hero, great warrior, those slandering lord are bastards, they are all blind! Lord, I have always supported you and argued with others for you..."

"Hehe."

Fang Yuan suddenly laughed coldly.

His hand moved like lightning, like an eagle's claws, as he suddenly pinched this rank two Gu Master's neck.

Crack!

The Gu Master's eyes quickly widened, the spinal bone on his neck was completely crushed by Fang Yuan and he lost his life on the spot.

Gasp... Upon seeing this, the Gu Masters observing from the shadows drew in a cold breath sharply.

Fang Yuan was an influential figure and because of Bai Ning Bing's matter, the moment he appeared, his tracks were revealed and his every movement was watched by many.

Fang Yuan killed this person and immediately searched his body.

Unfortunately, whether it was on him or his aperture, all the Gu worms had self-destructed.

Fang Yuan attacked extremely fast, but how could it be faster than a person's thought?

The speed a person could send a thought was as fast as a jolt of electricity, even a blink of an eye could not match one percent of its speed.

In the outside world, the probability of getting Gu worms as the spoils of battle against Gu Masters was quite low. It was not like at three kings inheritance with the heavenly power's restriction where Gu at rank five and below could not self-destruct.

Seeing Fang Yuan's skilled body searching method, the many Gu Masters observing from the darkness felt the chill intensify further in their spine.

"Such skillfulness, how many people has he killed?"

"Fang Zheng does not let even rank two Gu worms go, he is clearly a rank four, we can see how greedy his nature is!"

"Fang Zheng is extremely addicted to killing! That Gu Master was clearly begging him and was of no threat to him, but he still did not let him go."

"Have you guys seen enough? If you have, then screw off!" Fang Yuan stood arrogantly and shouted while looking around him with a fierce gaze.

Soon after, human figures emerged from the lush bushes, trees, creeks, and from under the soil and stones.

These figures quickly retreated and disappeared within seconds.

The area around Fang Yuan had once again regained peacefulness. It was really difficult to imagine that there were so many people hiding.

Fang Yuan had a great reputation for his violence now, he killed three rank four demonic Gu Masters in a row, he got things done by hook or by crook, he was despicable and cold-blooded, and was fiercely addicted to killing. These people had their courage broken by Fang Yuan's one simple sentence and did not dare to linger around Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan snorted and looked around him once again before proudly leaving this place.

But he knew, he was still being monitored from within the darkness.

The ones scared off by him were all shrimps. The remaining ones were all unique, with the capital to be confident.

Fang Yuan was not concerned about them and strutted out of this place.

In truth, although he had outstanding battle prowess now, he still had a weakness in the investigative aspect. Moreover these Gu Masters who were secretly following and monitoring him were sure to also be experts at speed. Even if Fang Yuan discovered them, he only had charging crash Gu and it would be fairly difficult for him to chase them.

"Where is he going? This direction is not towards the area where Bai Ning Bing is trapped."

"Did he discover me? Just now when he looked around, my heart skipped a beat..."

"Is little beast king afraid? Wait a moment, this cave seems to be Li Xian's residence?'

These Gu Masters followed after Fang Yuan cautiously, they were all inwardly surprised when they saw Fang Yuan stop in front of a cave.

HIs partner, the inseparable white demon Bai Ning Bing was trapped, but little beast king did not seem to be the least bit anxious. Instead, he walked towards Li Xian's residence.

Li Xian was a demonic path Gu Master at rank four upper stage. He was cunning and never suffered losses, a troublesome character. Could it be little beast king was looking to find trouble for Li Xian?

The Gu Masters following Fang Yuan secretly made guesses.

Fang Yuan's arrival immediately attracted Li Xian's attention.

Li Xian was already near his cave setting up detecting methods.

"Lord little beast king, truly a rare guest! You came to my place, what can I do for you?" Li Xian took the initiative to greet Fang Yuan, he approached Fang Yuan and cupped his fists as a greeting at a distance of twenty steps.

He did not dare to be too close to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was a temperamental ruffian; Li Xian, this unscrupulous merchant was also on edge when facing him.

Fang Yuan's visit was beyond his expectation. Who knew what Fang Yuan, this lunatic, cunning and shameless guy would do next?

Thus, Li Xian appeared calm on the surface and was full of smiled, but he was already extremely vigilant.

"I came to you naturally for business. What's wrong, are you not going to invite me in?" Fang Yuan smiled with an indistinct gaze.

"Since you are a customer, I will of course welcome you. Please come in, come in." Li Xian's gaze flashed and he moved aside, letting Fang Yuan enter first.

Fang Yuan strutted past him and glanced at Li Xian.

Li Xian smiled and walked alongside Fang Yuan into his cave.

"They have gone inside!"

"I can't follow them anymore, there are investigative Gu installed around the cave. If I trespass, I will definitely be treated as an enemy by Li Xian."

"Is little beast king really going to make a deal? Why do I feel Li Xian is out of luck this time?"

"I can already predict the scene of the explosive and tremendous battle between the two."

"Li Xian is at rank four upper stage, he definitely has many trump cards. If a fight erupts, it is sure to be a battle of dragon and tiger!"

Outside the cave, the group of Gu Masters could only stop and stretch their necks to look at the dark cave.

Chapter 353: Thunder Boar, Rock Crocodile

Inside the cave.

Li Xian asked Fang Yuan to take a seat and then sat beside him.

"Please have some tea." Li Xian stretched his short and thick fingers, his hand opened up and a fragrant tea appeared on his open palm.

Fang Yuan looked at the tea, but did not accepted it or even budged, instead he sighed: "Eastern Sea's blue sky Gu is really handy. Not only does it have a large capacity, far surpassing others of the same level, it is also easy and convenient to use.

"Eh? I didn't expect Sir little beast king to recognize this Gu." Li Xian's gaze slightly flickered.

He was not from Southern Border, but came drifting to here from Eastern Sea. Blue sky Gu was a Gu unique to Eastern Sea and was very uncommon at that.

When Li Xian had dealings with other people, he frequently used this Gu to show his methods.

Southern Border Gu Masters did not recognize this Gu and when they saw such a method for the first time, they would often look more highly at Li Xian.

Fang Yuan smiled and slowly said: " This rank four blue sky Gu is fused from rank three sky granary Gu. The success rate is quite low so it is rare even in Eastern Sea. If blue sky Gu is to be advanced to rank five, the best method is to fuse it with sky well Gu, to form rank five blue sky well Gu. And this sky well Gu is a natural Gu found only in Eastern Sea's Tian Jing island. Li Xian, if you want to advance it, it will be troublesome. Here in Southern Border, only Yi clan might have sky well Gu."

Yi clan along with Shang clan, Wu clan and Tie clan, was a top clan and had very close relation to Eastern Sea's forces. Yi clan's businesses are very prosperous, second only to Shang clan. Their flying blue whale caravan could move through the sky, which even Shang clan did not have.

"Blue sky Gu, sky well Gu, blue sky well Gu and Tian Jing island....how does little beast king know it so clearly?" Li Xian was startled and suspicious when he heard Fang Yuan's words.

The world of Gu Masters was extremely vast, there were also barriers that acted like heavenly chasm between Southern Border, Northern Plains, Eastern Seas, Western Desert and Central Continent. It was very difficult to communicate with each other and news were also blocked.

Li Xian had already investigated all details on Fang Yuan. Fang Yuan was born in Southern Border and he was so young, how could he have such experiences? Even knowing detailed information about Eastern Sea!

A vague pressure started to form in Li Xian's mind.

'Strange, strange! What is the origin of this little beast king? How could he know so much? Could there be an expert behind him?'

'With his age and experience, how could he know such details? Oh yeah, he stayed for quite a while at Shang clan city and might have received guidance from Shang Yan Fei. Shang Yan Fei is Shang clan leader, a rank five upper stage Gu Master, an expert at the peak of the mortal world. It is not strange for little beast king to know these under his guidance.'

Li Xian's gaze continually flickered, his heart covered with haze of doubts. His whole body was in a stiff position and his palm was still holding the purple clay teapot.

"No!" Suddenly, his thoughts flashed like lightning as he thought of the main thing: "I originally wanted to display my methods and pressure him down. To think I became overly suspicious and my mind became uneasy just from little beast king's several words! Even if he has Shang Yan Fei behind him, so what? Others might be afraid, but I, Li Xian, have my own means! Hmph."

Li Xian softly snorted and placed the teapot on the table. He took this chance to calm his mind.

He was, after all, an elite of the demonic path and adjusted his mind in just few breaths' time. He then faced Fang Yuan calmly.

It was just that there were some cautiousness and graveness in his eyes now.

"Sir little beast king, please taste the tea. What transaction do you want to make with me?" Li Xian asked.

"You don't need to think much, it is only a simple transaction." Fang Yuan said, then took out some Gu worms from his aperture and showed to Li Xian.

These Gu worms were the loot he seized from the Gu Masters he killed in King Quan Inheritance.

There were rank three and rank four Gu, but they were not suitable for Fang Yuan's strength path.

Li Xian could not help narrowing his eyes when he saw these Gu.

He was a very shrewd person and immediately realized many things: 'Who would have expected this little beast king to also have some accomplishments in enslavement path! After entering King Quan Inheritance, he killed two Gu Masters. Such talent is truly demonic!'

Li Xian could not help but think of Mo Wu Tian.

After he came to Southern Border, he had walked on the demonic path for a long time, coming into contact with all sorts of people. He felt that just based on aptitude, talent and temperament, among the younger generation of the demonic path, Mo Wu Tian was at the top.

However, now, he realized the little beast king in front him had a talent that was not inferior to Mo Wu Tian's!

'Little beast king and Mo Wu Tian, I wonder what will happen if these two came across each other? It is just that the current little beast king's cultivation is somewhat weak, Mo Wu Tian is older than him and is already rank four peak stage.'

Li Xian pondered, he spoke excitedly, however: "Sir little beast king, you did the right thing finding me for this transaction. I have a Gu on me which I believe will be important to sir."

"Oh?" Fang Yuan raised his brows.

Li Xian spread out his palm and a ball suddenly appeared.

This ball looked nice, shining with white gold light. Fang Yuan carefully looked at it and saw that the ball was an ant ball; over a hundred flying ants crawling on each other and sticking together to form a ball.

These flying ants did not look any different from normal ants.

Except, they were several times larger and they had a pair of transparent wings on their back.

"This is rank three gold eating flying ant Gu, altogether, there are one hundred and twenty. Those several old fellows from Tie clan trapped lord white demon by using iron cabinet Gu along with qi flow Gu. Now, the thousand feet around that area has been locked down. However, the iron cabinet Gu will collapse easily against this group of flying ants. Sir little beast king, I have just calculated, the price of your Gu is just good enough to buy this group of flying ants." Li Xian smiled warmly.

However, beyond his expectation, Fang Yuan only glanced at this gold consuming flying ant Gu once before shifting his gaze: "Who said I am going to buy this thing? This is the list of items, I want all the things written on it."

Li Xian accepted the list and glanced at it, there were many Gu worms and numerous supplementary materials for refining Gu written on it.

Although there were all kinds of items on the list, with Li Xian's experience and shrewdness, it was not difficult for him to see these things were all necessary for strength path.

'Bai Ning Bing has been trapped by Tie clan, how come this little beast king is not in the least bit worried? Strange! It won't be easy for him to get rid of iron cabinet Gu with just the strength path Gu on him. Does he have some special methods? Or maybe, the items on this list is to refine the nemesis of iron cabinet Gu?'

Li Xian narrowed his eyes, a bright light flashed past the slit of his eyes. He probed: "Sir little beast king, there are all sorts of things on this list, I cannot bring them out in a short while. Moreover, their total price far surpassed the price of these Gu you are selling."

"No problem, no problem." Fang Yuan waved his hand, "I want to buy all the items on this list. Give me whatever you have currently. As for the others, I will have to trouble you to pay attention to them. Money is not a problem."

Fang Yuan had a lot of primeval stones on him, his financial resources were adequate enough.

Li Xian laughed, he could not probe out anything so he only nodded and agreed.

......

Inside a cave, lights flickered.

Fang Yuan was sitting cross-legged on the ground, his whole attention on ball of paste in front of him.

This paste was multicolored and was floating in the air, rolling and churning continually, and gave out a strange fragrance - the Gu fusion process had reached the critical stage.

Fang Yuan constantly threw in primeval stones.

Primeval stones entered the paste and immediately dissolved into essence liquid, diluting the thick paste.

Fang Yuan continued to throw in primeval stones without care, only after the paste thinned to a certain degree did he stop.

Then, he quickly took out a thunderclap Gu.

Thunderclap Gu was a rank three Gu. The paste swallowed it up and immediately flickered lightning.

In a split second, the fragrance in the air was magnified greatly, the multicolored light dispersed and was replaced with abundant blue light. The lightning produced soft crackling sounds like the combustion of tiny firecrackers.

Fang Yuan's breathing accelerated and when he smelled a burnt smell in the air, his eyes shone with bright light!

"It is time... all-out effort Gu."

Boar phantom immediately appeared above him.

Strength qi Gu.

Fang Yuan activated strength qi Gu; the boar phantom adhered to the formless strength qi, immediately become very menacing.

Under Fang Yuan's will, the boar phantom flew towards the paste.

The instance the two collided, lightning burst out and shone upon the whole cave, dispersing all the darkness and revealing all the details in the room clearly.

After the light dispersed, the boar phantom in mid-air had experienced a huge change.

The new boar phantom was twice the original size, its tusks were like that of an elephant's and its whole body was covered with white fur. Especially the fur at its back, they were thick and long, lined up in rows, stiffly pointing towards the sky, and lightning curled up on them.

Lightning boar phantom!

"Success, great. Thunder boar is equal to dragon-elephant, Biao and mastiff. With the thunder boar strength, my battle strength has increased again. Next it is the rock crocodile strength..."

A night of cultivation unknowingly passed.

When the light of dawn shone upon San Cha mountain, Fang Yuan walked out of the cave he stayed at.

Although he was exhausted, he was happy inside. He successfully upgraded boar strength and crocodile strength to thunder boar strength and rock crocodile strength; his battle strength was raised by at least thirty percent!

"Bai Ning Bing..." He looked towards the southeast direction; an area on the middle of the mountain was covered with a dark purple qi barrier.

The qi barrier was like a tall tower, sealing the space within and isolating it from the outside world.

The combination of iron cabinet Gu and qi flow Gu caused Bai Ning Bing to become a trapped beast of Tie clan.

Fang Yuan let out a cold snort.

The situation looked simple but it was a tricky matter.

The four old-timers of Tie clan who trapped Bai Ning Bing were all at rank four middle stage. Although Bai Ning Bing was a genius, she was only at rank four initial stage.

If the Tie clan was truly set on capturing Bai Ning Bing, they would have already captured her but they did not.

On one hand, it was to maintain their strength to fight for three kings inheritance.

On another hand, it was because they were held back by the purple thorn token on Bai Ning Bing.

Finally, it was to bait Fang Yuan!

In case Fang Yuan rashly charged in, Ti clan's four old-timers could combine their strength to activate the rank five search and lock Gu to easily suppress him and Bai Ning Bing.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, Tie clan's four old-timers had used this killer move to capture demonic path's Kong Ri Tian. But soon after, they were killed by a rank three Gu Master.

Rank five search and lock Gu had an extremely huge demand towards primeval essence. Tie clan's four old-timers were really tragic figures, they cultivated the killer move for so many years and finally were in the limelight, but the scene did not last long because they lacked primeval essence and were killed by a rank three Gu Master.

Chapter 354: Ancient Bronze Skin Gu

Dark purple qi barrier was like a high tower firmly locking in thousand meters of area.

The qi barrier, however, did not isolate sight. Who knew how many eyes were secretly watching the scene from outside the barrier.

"Bai Ning Bing, just let yourself be captured obediently. It is impossible for you to escape!" Tie clan's four old-timers occupied east, south, west and north positions separately, locking Bai Ning Bing in the center.

Bai Ning Bing was sitting cross-legged on a boulder, her two hands holding primeval stones as she replenished her primeval essence.

"Bai Ning Bing, don't hold any delusions. You killed our Tie clansman, and still thinking you will be able to escape? Hmph." The four old-timers' gazes were grave and started fixedly at Bai Ning Bing, encircling her with no gaps.

Bai Ning Bing slowly opened her narrowed eyes, her eyes were calm and her tone was indifferent: "Tie clan's four old-timers, what use is it in speaking so much? If you want to capture and kill me, them bring it on! Even if I, Bai Ning Bing, die at your hands, I will definitely take a few of you down."

She paused for a while before continuing: "You have been continuously maintaining this qi barrier, it should have consumed a lot of your primeval essence, right? Hehe, I know you four are experts at team battle tactics while I am only at rank four initial stage. But you can bet on it that if you killed me, even if you guys don't die, you will definitely be heavily injured. And in case my partner appears, what will become of you then?"

"You..." The four old-timers of Tie clan were exasperated.

Bai Ning Bing might have borrowed Fang Yuan's name, but it struck their weak spot.

"Bai Ning Bing, stop being stubborn. Here, let me see what you can do." One of the old-timers stood up.

"Hehehe." Bai Ning Bing softly smiled and slowly stood up to take the challenge. Silver hair and snow white clothes, with a grace that stood out from the crowd, even if she was trapped, she was still calm, a confident bearing that showed she had no worries about this life and death situation.

The two began their fight; sand and pebbles started flying inside the qi barrier, snow light spread everywhere and the clash of steel resounded...

Far away on a short mountain peak stood a group of Shang clan Gu Masters.

"Another round of battle has begun again. This Bai Ning Bing is worthy of her fame in the battle stage. She is able to resist the four rank four middle stage Gu Masters attacking her in turns, she is not simple!" One of them sighed.

"Bai Ning Bing has outstanding battle sense, she is indeed strong. But another reason is because the four old-timers from Tie clan do not dare to use all their strength." Someone analyzed.

"That's right. The old-timers are worried and afraid of the counterattack from Bai Ning Bing when she is near death. They are good at team battle tactics, and their individual strength aren't as fearsome as the Gu Masters at the same level. If they become short of a member, their whole strength will fall sharply and it will be difficult for them to contend for the three kings inheritance."

"What I am worried about now is Bai Ning Bing has purple thorn token. If she takes it out, do we make a move?"

"Don't do anything for now. I have already sent the message, and the clan has already sent a strong reinforcement. Elder Yi Huo is rushing here!"

Hearing this information, Shang clan's Gu Masters rouse their spirits.

Yi Huo was not an ordinary Gu Master, he was one of the five great elders of Shang clan with a cultivation of rank four peak stage! He was one of the experts under Shang Yan Fei, now that he was dispatched, it was sure to change the situation of the entire San Cha mountain.

...

"To think the things turned out this way. If Bai Ning Bing is killed by Tie clan, our deal with Shang clan will fall through." In an underbrush, Meng Tu observed the battle inside the qi barrier with glowing eyes and said with a worried tone.

He was at the prime of his life and was at rank three peak stage, the same as his partner Jiao Huang.

These two were famous assassins in demonic path, some time back even the rank four middle stage righteous path Xiao Fu Lu died at their hands.

They accepted a mission from Shang clan; if they could kill Fang and Bai, they would be allowed to join Shang clan.

They had already made their move on Huo Tan mountain, but the lava crocodile group they attracted did not pose any problems to Fang and Bai.

The two did not give up and continued to follow Fang and Bai to San Cha mountain, waiting for an opportunity ever since.

"Sigh... what can we do? We are good at assassinations and not at frontal attacks. If we move in front of everyone, our success rate will be too low. If Bai Ning Bing dies, we also can't do anything about it; we can only leave it up to fate!" The old man Jiao Huang said with a sigh.

"Yes, who knows how many are watching from the darkness. Who is to say we haven't been discovered while coming here." Meng Tu powerlessly added.

They were assassin Gu Masters and paid particular attention to concealment; it was okay if they did not make a move, but once they made, it must be a fatal strike. Before making their move, they made went through meticulous planning and made large numbers of preparation before bursting out all at once.

If the success rate was too low, they would not make a move and would rather give up the deal.

This was also the reason they were able to survive while roaming in demonic path for such a long time.

Every well-known Gu Master had their own unique ways for survival.

...

"Hehehe... these four old-timers of Tie clan are in such an awkward state." Li Xian stood in front of the qi barrier and looked at the battle inside; his eyes narrowed and were filled with joy towards others' misfortune.

Although this place had already become a focus of many gazes at San Cha mountain, Li Xian did not care.

He was very confident that he would absolutely not be exposed by others.

This confidence came from his rank five Gu - Invisibility Gu!

Gu worms at rank five were rare. Many rank five Gu Masters would only have one or two rank five Gu on them for many years.

Invisibility Gu could only be detected by specific rank five investigative Gu. However, it had not been long since three kings inheritance opened and there has yet to be anyone who had broken through the middle rounds, so it was not likely to attract rank five Gu Masters to make a move.

Li Xian had his own fortuitous encounters to possess the scarce rank five Gu when he was rank four.

"This iron cabinet Gu recipe was created by Tie clan's refinement path master Tie Yi Ban. His original intention was to refine a type of firm and secure storage Gu. After he refined this Gu for the first time, he gave it to Tie Xue Leng to test out. The Divine Investigator used it to capture people and it was very durable. When supplemented with qi flow Gu, its effect was amplified. From then on, iron cabinet Gu had become an efficient mean for Tie clan to capture demonic Gu Masters."

"Hehe... but now, these Tie clan's old-timers have to maintain both Tie cabinet Gu and qi flow Gu, unable to execute their team attacks. If the four attack together, this purple qi barrier will disappear. Without any obstruction, Bai Ning Bing can run free and they will lose a lot of reputation. Hahaha, interesting, interesting. These old-timers have no way out."

Li Xian looked at the show, the corner of his lips could not help but curl up.

But when he thought of someone, the smile on his face slowly disappeared.

"Little beast king, he actually didn't come to rescue! Did he realize the truth behind this tricky situation or is he truly so cold blooded and decided to abandoned Bai Ning Bing? No matter which it is, it all proves how scary this person is... I should hand that Gu over to him."

...

A Gu was handed over to Fang Yuan.

Its appearance was like that of a bedbug, flat and wide, its head was quite small and its body looked oval shaped. Its whole body was yellow-orange, and gave off a metallic luster like a bronze.

People called it 'ancient bronze skin Gu'.

Bronze skin Gu was a series Gu from rank one to rank three. But if it were to advance to rank four, it would be ancient bronze skin Gu whose defensive power was much stronger than rank three bronze skin Gu.

"Li Xian, you are worthy of being a famous merchant of the demonic path. You could get me ancient bronze skin Gu this quick, it was really a correct decision to make the transaction with you. I don't have tea here, please have some wine."

Fang Yuan's tone was polite and his face appeared gentle as he welcomed Li Xian and poured him a cup of wine.

"No, no, it was nothing. It is my honor to be able to do business with lord little beast king." Li Xian appeared very modest, lowering his status.

The two discussed for a while. The atmosphere was very harmonious.

If someone who did not know about them saw this, they would think these two were good-natured and elegant. How would they think these two were two-faced, ruthless demonic path Gu Masters?

"Li Xian, you don't need to be so polite, you can simply call me Fang Zheng. Let me first give you fifty thousand primeval stones, consider it a deposit for our future transactions." Fang Yuan brought out primeval elder Gu and waved his hand, bringing out fifty thousand primeval stones.

Primeval elder Gu appeared like a crystal ball, there were a lot of primeval stones stored in it, the old man in the clouds in the ball appeared to look very kind.

Li Xian looked at the wide smile on the old man's face, he could not help evaluating Fang Yuan much more highly.

"I will have to trouble you to help me with something." Fang Yuan suddenly spoke.

Li Xian's gaze flashed and immediately said: "Please speak."

Fang Yuan brought Li Xian towards the depths of the cave and pointed to a stone vat: "I have a stone vat here but I lack a fire type Gu. I will have to ask you to help me melt these bronze pieces and put them in the stone vat."

Li Xian let out a sigh of relief and smiled: "I just so happen to have a fire type Gu. It will only require a slight effort."

The temperature inside the cave rapidly soared.

After a while, Li Xian melted the bronze pieces into metallic liquid, the stone vat was filled almost to the brink.

Fang Yuan took out coal stones and piled them under stone vat to maintain the temperature.

Then, under Li Xian's astonished gaze, he softly jumped right into the vat.

The boiling bronze liquid sizzled and immediately burned Fang Yuan's clothes. His whole body was soaked in the bronze liquid and only his head was revealed outside.

"Little... Lord little beast king, what are you doing?!" Right now, Li Xian could smell the odor of burning flesh.

Fang Yuan activated the ancient bronze skin Gu in his aperture while smiling with gritted teeth: "Li Xian, don't you know? There is a method to use this ancient bronze skin Gu and accelerate the speed by thirty percent, that is to use it with bronze liquid."

When ancient bronze skin Gu was activated, it could remodel the skin and flesh of the Gu Master into ancient bronze skin. If it was used with the body soaking in bronze liquid, it could shorten the time required. Li Xian had also heard of it, but he had never thought of this.

When Fang Yuan was preparing these things, he had thought these were supplementary materials for refining Gu.

Because this method was extremely painful and cruel.

Gu Master must come in touch with scalding, boiling bronze liquid without using any defensive means. Only a perverted masochist would choose this method.

Is little beast king a masochist?

Li Xian kept on thinking of this question as he returned to his cave with a dazed expression.

At this time, there was another person who was also thinking of Fang Yuan.

"Fang Yuan, why have you not appeared yet?" Bai Ning Bing sat cross-legged on the ground, her eyes half-narrowed as she faintly felt the situation was far from reassuring.

"We have used poison vow Gu, he absolutely cannot leave me in the lurch. But he still hasn't appeared now, could he still be inside the inheritance or maybe met with some trouble?"

Chapter 355: Yi Huo’s invitation

A Gu worm floated above Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's primeval sea slowly fell as he activated this Gu.

This Gu was like a black bone, its two ends were round and smooth, with a thin body. It was emitting black rays of light while floating in the air.

The black light shone upon Fang Yuan's body, passed through his skin and flesh, and brought changes in his skeleton.

Fang Yuan had already used iron bone Gu, his skeleton was pitch black and was firm like iron. But under the effect of this Gu, his skeleton slowly became more firm.

This was essence iron bone Gu, a rank four Gu; one could get iron bone Gu by reverse-refining it.

Three days after handing over the ancient bronze skin Gu, Li Xian personally came to deliver this Gu to Fang Yuan.

Essence iron bone Gu could make Fang Yuan's skeleton even more firm and the effect was many times stronger than iron bone Gu. But at the same time, the process needed much more time.

Fang Yuan had been using essence iron bone continually these days along with ancient bronze skin Gu to temper his body.

In this period, he was also using nine eyes liquor worm to purify his primeval essence, refining his initial stage light gold primeval essence into bright gold primeval essence. Then he used bright gold primeval essence to cleanse his aperture and strengthen its foundation.

He made use of every minute and second, cultivating bitterly, and he could feel his strength increasing little by little every day.

"It has already been over a month since I left King Quan Inheritance. I am almost finished with using ancient bronze skin Gu, but there is still quite a distance before I completely master essence iron bone Gu. Unless I use time path Gu to accelerate the flow of time." Fang Yuan pondered.

The so called time path was related to time.

The Gu Masters of this path used time related Gu worms.

Third watch Gu and Spring Autumn Cicada belonged to this category.

In fact, there were far more time path Gu than just these two. It had a full range of Gu from rank one to rank five.

Normal Gu Masters, if they did not have the patience to do this type of grinding work and wanted to speed their progress, they could ask time path Gu Masters to help or use a time path Gu themselves to accelerate their time.

"But my situation is different from ordinary Gu Masters. I have Spring Autumn Cicada, if I accelerate my time, Spring Autumn Cicada's recovery speed will also increase and will be my death warrant!"

The time flow in Gu Immortal blessed land in San Cha mountain was three times faster than the outside world. The time Fang Yuan spent in King Quan Inheritance had already caused Spring Autumn Cicada to make some recovery, thus Fang Yuan could only patiently choose the method of bitter cultivation.

Just as he was cultivating, there came an unfamiliar voice from outside the cave.

"Little beast king, could you come out to have a chat?"

Fang Yuan walked out of the cave and saw the person clearly, he looked slightly doubtful: "So it was Elder Yi Huo."

Yi Huo was very handsome; sharp eyes, high bridged nose, and long red hair like it was on fire.

He was a fire path Gu Master who was very famous in Southern Border. People called him 'blazing inferno', his cultivation was rank four peak stage!

'Yi Huo is one of the five great elders of Shang clan, an expert under Shang Yan Fei and was ranked above light swordsman Wei Yang. The only one that could command him was Shang Yan Fei, his arrival was surely going to change the power balance of San Cha mountain.' Fang Yuan quickly thought about it and welcomed Yi Huo inside his cave.

"Little beast king, my purpose in coming here is simple, it is to invite you to join our Shang clan." Yi Huo entered the cave, but he did not sit and directly expressed his purpose in coming.

"Join your Shang clan?" Fang Yuan raised his brows, he could fully sense the swift and decisive nature of 'blazing inferno'.

"Right." Yi Huo nodded, his eyes looking straight at Fang Yuan as he smiled, "You and Bai Ning Bing have stayed for some time at Shang clan, you guys surely have deep understanding of our Shang clan's strength, so I won't say much on it. The main thing is your partner Bai Ning Bing has been trapped by the four old-timers of Tie clan for around two months now. As long as you two join Shang clan, I will immediately set out and rescue Bai Ning Bing."

His tone was filled with confidence as if rescuing Bai Ning Bing was an easy matter.

When he spoke, he was slightly smiling; his handsome face was like a perfect statue and when he revealed his teeth, it was dazzling like the sun. Many people would feel ashamed when interacting with him.

Yi Huo and Wei Yang had a similar background, they both ruled Shang clan battle stage and were absolute geniuses.

Among the five great elders of Shang clan, Yi Huo was the most popular and was also publicly recognized as the elder with the highest chance of advancing to rank five!

Fang Yuan's eyes flashed with a contemplative light.

He was not surprised at Shang clan sending Yi Huo here. Shang clan had been in control of San Cha mountain for a period of time before, but was later suppressed by Wu clan. And with the appearance of demonic path experts, Shang clan groups found it even more difficult to hold their heads up.

Under this situation, Shang clan as a top clan, would naturally send an expert to change the situation.

In Fang Yuan's previous life memories, Yi Huo was dispatched here by Shang clan. He suppressed Wu Shen Tong and Yi Chong, and defeated Kong Ri Tian and Long Qing Tian, being the ruler of San Cha mountain for a time.

But later, his dominance drove Long Qing Tian anxious. Long Qing Tian used blue halo Gu and poisoned him. He had no choice but to return to Shang clan city to be treated by Doctor Su Shou.

However, this time, Yi Huo came to San Cha mountain to recruit him. This was beyond Fang Yuan's expectation.

"Lord Yi Huo, I wonder if this invitation came from Shang clan or it is your own thought?" Fang Yuan's gaze flashed, and asked.

"Hahaha, of course it is my own thought. Fang Zheng, you created a lot of commotion at Shang clan battle stage, and almost became the ruler of battle stage. I have been watching you, you are a genius! If you join Shang clan, it will be greatly beneficial to you." Yi Huo laughed loudly and replied.

Fang Yuan smiled as the trace of doubt he had melted away.

"Sir Yi Huo, from what I know, Shang clan's external elders don't have the authority to recommend talents, right?"

External elder, this title made Yi Huo slightly furrow his brows: "You are right. But if you can become the ruler of the battle stage, you can become an external elder of Shang clan. With your talent, I believe the title of the ruler of battle stage is just a matter of time for you."

Fang Yuan could not help but scoff, and did not reply.

Yi Huo's brows furrowed deeper, this scoff sounded ear-piercing to him.

He patiently said: "Fang Zheng, I will tell you the truth. Before I came here, lord clan leader made a promise to me. As long as I accomplish great accomplishments at San Cha mountain and take control of the situation, I will be bestowed a surname when I return to Shang clan city. At that time, I will no longer be Yi Huo, but Shang Huo. I will become a true elder of Shang clan and I will have the authority to recommend talents."

"Eh? So it was like that..." Fang Yuan clearly revealed a surprised expression, his gaze flickered and he sank into contemplation.

Yi Huo waited for a long time but after getting no response from Fang Yuan, his brows furrowed even deeper and he took the initiative to ask: "Have you thought it through?"

Fang Yuan shook his head: "This matter is too significant, I need to consider it properly."

Yi Huo's brows relaxed a little: "Since that is so, then I will give you three days. I will come here again after three days, I hope to get a satisfactory reply then."

"Alright." Fang Yuan nodded in agreement and accompanied Yi Huo out of the cave.

Three days later.

"You still haven't thought it through?" Yi Huo looked at Fang Yuan with some doubts.

"This is a serious matter, I really need to properly consider it." Fang Yuan answered with a heavy voice.

"Alright, I will give you three more days. Fang Zheng, I think highly of you."

Another three days later.

"Lord Yi Huo, I have thought over this matter over and again. I appreciate your good intent but I still prefer the freedom of the demonic path." Fang Yuan sincerely replied.

"What? You thought for three days and this is your answer?" Yi Huo's tone showed his fury.

"Lord Yi Huo, you can lead a horse to water, but you can't make it drink." Fang Yuan's gaze was profound and there was severity within his soft words.

Yi Huo gritted his teeth and said with a deep voice: "Fang Zheng, you need to think it clearly. The four old-timers of Tie clan are not easy opponents. If I don't help out, everything bodes ill for Bai Ning Bing. Besides this, Sky Tiger Xue San Si whom you killed is Century Boy's goddaughter. Century Boy has been watching you all this while, he is a strength path Gu Master at rank four upper stage and is a thorny character of demonic path."

"Eh? So it was like that." Fang Yuan showed hesitation, "Then... let me consider it again. Give me ten days of time to think it through."

"Ten days?" Yi Huo immediately wrinkled his brows.

"Fine." He thought for a while and nodded, "This is enough time for you to think everything through clearly. I believe you will make the most sensible choice. But I have to remind you that time cannot be dragged on further, your woman is in crisis. Anything can happen during this time."

Yi Huo considered Bai Ning Bing as Fang Yuan's woman which Fang Yuan felt was quite laughable.

Whether Bai Ning Bing died or not, it was not an especially important matter to him.

Anyway, the poison vow Gu was already destroyed and he had also matured, reaching rank four initial stage.

Saving Bai Ning Bing or not, it depended on his will.

But if there was no Bai Ning Bing, Fang Yuan would become a lone force and it would definitely create a negative influence on his plans at San Cha mountain.

"There is no need to go save Bai Ning Bing urgently, I should still focus on cultivating and advance forward. I have already no need for the bone flesh unity Gu. As for Bai Ning Bing, she can be outside for a while and attract the attention for me. I should take this chance to surpass her, it will be convenient for me to suppress her in future. And with so many eyes watching the situation, those four old foxes of Tie clan absolutely won't move in for the kill."

Fang Yuan saw the whole situation clearly.

"As for Yi Huo's invitation... hehe."

Ten days later.

"Lord Yi Huo, thank you for your good intention. These days, I have pondered restlessly and from every angle, but I still feel that being free is the best." Fang Yuan wore an earnest expression as he said this.

Yi Huo's expression naturally became unsightly: "Fang Zheng, you have been doing this over and over again, are you playing with me?"

"Lord Yi Huo, your words are not right. I have always been sincere with you. I understand your mood. But right now, the most important thing is three kings inheritance. There is already not much time left before the next opening of the inheritance."

With the mention of the opening of three kings inheritance, Yi Huo could only suppress the anger in his heart. He took a deep look at Fang Yuan and left the cave.

Chapter 356: The hairy men

Five days later.

The three light pillars appeared on San Cha mountain, piercing through the clouds towards the sky.

The red light pillar was burning like fire; it was King Bao's inheritance. Yellow light pillar was bright and dazzling; it was King Quan's inheritance. Blue light pillar had a demonic charm; it was King Xin's inheritance.

After a gap of several months, three kings inheritance opened again.

Yi Huo gazed at these three light pillars at the peak, his fierce eyes under his dashing brows flickered with faint radiance.

"Is this three kings inheritance? Sure enough, it gives off a magnificent feeling!" As long as I accomplish great achievements here, I can truly join Shang clan and change my surname to Shang, becoming a member of Shang clan."

Right now, excitement was surging like waves in his heart.

"Hmph, little beast king doesn't know what's good for him, actually refusing me again and again. But, he apparently knows some secrets related to three kings inheritance. If I can take him in as my subordinate, it will be a great help to me in controlling San Cha mountain."

Yi Huo could not help but think of Fang Yuan.

Yi Huo was one of the five great elders of Shang clan and possessed his own information channel. He already knew Fang Yuan had made a huge sum of money at Shang clan city by relying on his knowledge of some secrets of three kings inheritance.

Besides this, Fang Yuan, himself, possessed outstanding battle prowess, having the fighting strength of a rank four middle stage.

Moreover, Bai Ning Bing never left the little beast king's side. Recruiting one naturally meant gaining the other.

Thus, Yi Huo had accommodated to Fang Yuan and displayed complete sincerity to move him.

But Fang Yuan did not know what was good for him and refused him time and again.

Yi Huo could not help starting to feel angry: "When I come out of three kings inheritance, I will teach this little beast king a lesson and let him know that not everyone can fetch a good price! But, for now... I need to suppress some hindrances."

Yi Huo collected his disorganized thoughts and looked towards the few figures at a distance.

'Pink butterfly gentleman' Kong Ri Tian!

'He who once dyed the sky blue' Long Qing Tian!

Wu clan elder Wu Shen Tong!

Yi clan elder Yi Chong!

These four were all rank four peak stage experts. Every time the inheritance opened, they would be the first to move towards the entrance.

This time was no exception!

"Hahaha, I have reserved King Bao Inheritance. Who dares to contend with me?" Yi Huo threw his head back and laughed loudly, his laughter wild and unrestrained. He crossed his arms and looked at the four with a fierce gaze.

He was fire path Gu Master, King Bao was also of the same path. King Bao's inheritance was naturally the best choice for him.

"Blazing Inferno..." Wu Shen Tong narrowed his eyes and mumbled with some fear towards Yi Huo's reputation.

Yi Huo was one of the five great generals of Shang clan with the nickname of Blazing Inferno, he was at the peak of power! Even Wu Shen Tong had no choice but to admit that Yi Huo was a notch above him.

"Hmph, I will deal with you!" Kong Ri Tian snorted, his whole body suddenly exploded and turned into phoenix winged golden butterflies.

Hundreds and thousands of golden butterflies, with wings as sharp as knives, enveloped Yi Huo.

"Blazing inferno, you have been in the limelight the last few years." Long Qing Tian also laughed gloomily and pushed his palm.

Whoosh!

A greenish-blue palm of light, with poison gas curling around it, broke the void and directly smacked towards Yi Huo's face.

"Let me spar too." Yi Chong sneered and suddenly moved.

Swish!

Blue water waves surged up out of nowhere, engulfing Yi Huo within.

All of a sudden, three rank four peak stage Gu Masters attacked Yi Huo at the same time.

"Good." Yi Huo's lips curled up into an arrogant smile, he stretched his arms then smacked his chest with his palms.

Bam!

Majestic flames suddenly burst forth.

In an instant, the fiery color overwhelmed the light pillars of three kings inheritance and illuminated San Cha mountain.

Flames surged up with incomparable heat and ferocity.

The flames effortlessly covered the water wave, burned the poison palm and sent the phoenix winged golden butterflies retreating in a sorry figure. The golden butterflies flew far away and converged, changing back into Kong Ri Tian.

"This is his rank five Gu prairie fire?" Seeing such a huge fire, Yi Chong and Long Qing Tian's expressions changed.

Kong Ri Tian did not say a word, while Wu Shen Tong's eyes flashed.

"This is the might of Elder Yi Huo!" Shang clan Gu Masters shouted out loudly in excitement.

Yi Huo stood proudly within the flames, giving a feeling of a deity. His fiery red hair seemed to merge with the flames, giving off a wild and intense bearing.

The flames swiftly dispersed and he walked towards the red light pillar, King Bao Inheritance.

The four Gu Masters watched him move towards the light pillar, all of their expressions were more or less stiff and unsightly, but they did not block him. This was them acknowledging Yi Huo's might.

After Yi Huo entered King Bao Inheritance, Kong Ri Tian and other three glanced at each other, but they had no more interest to fight.

Among them, Kong Ri Tian and Long Qing Tian entered King Xin Inheritance; Wu Shen Tong and Yi Chong entered King Quan Inheritance.

"Yi Huo is worthy of being one of the five great experts of Shang clan, he has rank five Gu prairie fire, formidable indeed!"

"These days, Yi Huo has been repeatedly going to little beast king's place, their relation is not shallow."

"Hmph! Black and white twin demons are known as demonic path Gu Masters, but they are actually lackeys of righteous path. They spent some time at Shang clan and everyone knows they have a deep relation with Shang clan's young master Shang Xin Ci."

A group of rank four upper stage Gu Masters started discussing after they saw Yi Huo suppressing other four Gu Masters and enter the light pillar with his head high.

Birds of a feather flock together.

Rank four peak stage experts had all entered the inheritance, now it was these people's turn.

"Century Boy, your goddaughter Xue San Si was killed by little beast king. When are you going to take revenge?" A righteous Gu Master among the group suddenly asked while taking gloating at his misfortune.

Century Boy coldly snorted: "Although Yi Huo has rank five Gu, the battle just before was only a probe, no one used their true methods. If they were to truly fight it out, who lives and who dies is still not certain."

Although he said so, he was actually very afraid.

He had thought of taking the chance that Bai Ning Bing was imprisoned, to find trouble for Fang Yuan. But Yi Huo repeatedly visited Fang Yuan's residence, so he could only restrain his impulse and quietly observe.

Now, when he saw Yi Huo easily suppressing other four, Century Boy's heart became much more heavy.

"Such a great opportunity like three kings inheritance is in front of us, who will foolishly battle each other to death? Let's go, we need to enter too." Soon, this group of rank four upper stage Gu Masters also entered the inheritance.

Fang Yuan climbed up to the peak and was immediately recognized.

"Little beast king!"

"It is Fang Zheng."

"He is entering King Xin Inheritance."

From the peak to the middle of mountain, many Gu Masters stared as they looked at Fang Yuan entering into the light pillar.

"He really forgot about his partner?"

"Bai Ning Bing is still trapped by the four old fellows of Tie clan. This Fang Zheng is actually paying it no heed as if nothing has happened, like he hasn't heard of it." Even demonic Gu Masters felt a chill in their hearts.

"Look, this is the heartlessness of demonic path Gu Masters!" Some righteous path Gu Masters commented disdainfully.

"Fang Yuan... you bastard!" Bai Ning Bing also witnessed this scene from inside the qi barrier.

Her face became pale with anger, she clenched her fists tightly and fiercely gritted her teeth.

The four old-timers of Tie clan looked at each other.

They were in an embarrassing situation right now.

Although they succeeded in trapping Bai Ning Bing, Fang Yuan did not come to rescue her. This made their defensive tactics a cold irony.

"Damn it! We can't deal with so many matters, this time, there will be no share for us at three kings inheritance!"

"How about we retreat?"

"Impossible! We four move together, if we retreat without gaining anything, this will be an insult to our Tie clan and I am afraid we will not be able to raise our heads in front of others."

"Then what should we do?"

Three pairs of eyes looked at the fourth old man, their leader.

The old man pondered for a while and made a decision.

He spoke with a heavy voice: "Request for reinforcements! Shang clan has sent reinforcement, there will naturally be support from our Tie clan too. In the present situation, the competition has turned more intense. Only rank four peak stage powers can fight for a seat. As long as the clan sends a rank four peak stage reinforcement, then with our rank four middle stage strength...."

"Big brother is right."

"Shang clan has sent Yi Huo, if we ask for reinforcement now, we won't lose face."

"Right, we need to ask support from the clan!

.....

There was endless grey fog completely filling Fang Yuan's vision and reminding him that he had already entered King Xin Inheritance.

Fang Yuan surveyed his surroundings, he could not tell east from west. However, in his aperture, Spring Autumn Cicada shook its wings slightly. The flow of time here was still three times faster than the outside world.

"I need to hurry." Fang Yuan felt a sense of urgency.

The constantly recovering Spring Autumn Cicada was becoming more and more like a ticking time bomb.

He grabbed a paper crane Gu and activated it.

A 'key' was required to enter King Xin Inheritance and it was a paper crane Gu. At this very moment, Fang Yuan could only use paper crane Gu, his other Gu besides Spring Autumn Cicada, were all suppressed by the heavenly power.

Paper crane Gu floated in the air in front of him; it flapped its wings and led the way ahead.

Fang Yuan followed the paper crane and slowly moved forward.

He reached a hill and could see a blurry human figure in the fog.

"Human... come out... compete... let's compete." The human figure opened its mouth, the sound was boorish and sporadic.

When Fang Yuan walked closer, the human figure gradually became clearer.

His figure was similar to ordinary humans, two hands and two legs. It was just that he was very buff, and reddish brown hair grew from all over his body; chest, limbs, even on his face and buttocks.

He looked at Fang Yuan with his bronze bell-like large eyes.

"Compete... let's compete. Lose... die!" He roared, his eyes were filled with blood veins and looked very malevolent.

Fang Yuan had already expected this and was not surprised, his expression calm.

This was a variant human.

Beasts had mutated beasts, just like Biao among the tigers, lycan among wolves and mastiff among dogs. Humans also had variations, the variant human Fang Yuan ran into now was a hairy man.

Hairy man's whole body were covered with hair, even their eyelids. This type of variant human has extremely low intelligence but had natural talent in Gu refinement.

There was a group of hairy man in King Xin Inheritance, they were the obstacles Gu Masters had to clear to go forward. Only by winning against them could the Gu Masters continue on. If they lost, the Gu Masters would be torn to shreds by the powerful hairy men and become their food.

"Come." Fang Yuan stood at a distance of ten steps from the hairy man with a tranquil expression.

Several Gu along with some materials appeared out of nowhere in the air and floated lightly to Fang Yuan's hands.

At the same time, the hairy man also received the same things.

The Gu refinement had begun.

Winner lives, loser dies!

Chapter 357: Legend of the Hairy Men

The earliest record of hairy men was in \<\<Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

It was said that Ren Zu dug out his two eyes which turned into a son and a daughter; the son was Verdant Great Sun and the daughter was Desolate Ancient Moon.

Verdant Great Sun liked to drink wine a lot, one time he caused an incident while being drunk and was trapped at the depths of the ordinary abyss. In the end, he profited from the disaster and obtained reputation Gu which looked like chrysanthemum, and was able to escape alive.

Because of reputation Gu, Verdant Great Sun's reputation gradually became bigger. Soon, news that Verdant Great Sun was a huge drunkard spread all over the world.

One day, a group of tiger-striped honey bees brought their beehive and found Verdant Great Sun.

"Verdant Great Sun, we heard you really liked drinking wine and you have been saying the wine made by the four heaven and earth monkeys are the most delicious in the world. But how could the wine they brewed compare to our honey wine? Today, we have specially brought our honey for you to have a taste."

Each of these honey bees was the size of a leopard with patterns on their body resembling tiger stripes; golden with black stripes on top. They were speaking politely but their tone contained a threatening and forceful intent.

Verdant Great Sun complained in his heart, this was truly misfortune befalling on someone who merely stayed home. Tiger-striped honey bees were very powerful, he was not a match against one of them, let alone a whole group.

Verdant Great Sun could only reluctantly taste the honey wine inside the beehive.

He had only taken a sip when his eyes brightened.

Honey wine was sweet but not overly sweet, the wine fragrance was mellow and very delicious, absolutely a treasure of the world!

"Delicious, delicious, really delicious. This honey wine makes one feel like the most fortunate person in the world!" Verdant Great Sun drank a mouthful of wine, praising it to the high heavens.

Tiger-striped honey bees laughed, feeling very happy.

The leader asked Verdant Great Sun: "The tell us which tastes more delicious, our honey wine or the wines of the four heaven and earth monkeys?"

Verdant Great Sun was already drunk and forgot about the terror of the tiger-striped honey bees, speaking frankly: "They all have their own merits, it is very difficult to compare them."

Tiger-striped honey bees were furious: He said our wine is actually at the same level as those mere monkeys? This Verdant Great Sun is too hateful, we need to teach him a lesson!

They were just about to attack when suddenly Verdant Great Sun disappeared.

This intoxication of Verdant Great Sun lasted for seven days and seven nights.

In his haziness, he heard a voice call calling out for him from the darkness: "Verdant Great Sun, wake up quick. If you don't wake up, you will be eaten..."

Verdant Great Sun was startled awake.

He discovered he was bound up and was being carried by a group of savage people.

This group of savage people had hair all over their body and their two eyes were dark blue. There was already a bonfire burning and above the bonfire was a cauldron.

The savage people quietly sat down, speaking pleasant sounding words.

"We are refining eternal Gu and were just lacking a human to be the catalyst. Now heaven has sent us Verdant Great Sun, it is truly worthy of celebration!"

"Human is the spirit of all living beings, Ren Zu is the spirit ancestor. Verdant Great Sun was born from his left eye and has ample spiritual energy. The way I see it, the refinement will succeed this time!"

"Throw him into the cauldron quick, we will obtain eternal Gu and live for eternity..."

Verdant Great Sun turned pale from fright at these words; immediately shouting out and struggling with all his strength.

However, these savage people remained unmoved.

At this very moment, Verdant Great Sun again heard the voice from before in his mind.

"Sigh, it is no use. These savages are the hairy men, loved by the world. They have an innate talent in refining Gu worms."

Verdant Great Sun instantly forgot his predicament and curiously asked in his mind: "Who are you?"

That voice laughed: "I am divine travel Gu, as long as any person drinks four different top-tier wines in the world, they will give birth to me in their hearts. I can let you teleport to any place you wish."

Verdant Great Sun was exulted: "Then, please quickly bring me out of here."

Divine travel Gu sighed: "It is no use. You can only use me when you are drunk. Your mind is sober now and so you can't use me."

Verdant Great Sun suddenly realized: "So that is why I was trapped in the isolated island and almost starved to death that time. Fortunately, I obtained reputation Gu and could leave the ordinary abyss. So it was you who harmed me!"

Divine travel Gu replied: "Sigh, human, I did not have any intent to harm you, it was all because you used my strength after you became drunk. You don't need to blame me, last time you were almost captured by the tiger-striped honey bees, but you were able to escape thanks to me. One harm and one rescue, we can call it even."

Verdant Great Sun also thought of the tiger-striped honey bees and no longer blamed divine travel Gu.

He was thrown into the cauldron by the hairy men.

The huge fire was burning hotter under the cauldron and the liquid temperature inside also soared.

"Add agates and red pepper!" A hairy man threw precious agates and red pepper into the cauldron.

The liquid inside the cauldron immediately changed to red and dyed Verdant Great Sun's body red.

"Add blue smoke fox child !" A hairy man grabbed a small fox and threw it into the cauldron.

The small fox's whole body was hairy and looked extremely cute with its eyes like black diamonds. But the moment it touched the liquid, it turned into blue smoke and blended into the water.

The liquid in the cauldron slowly boiled and Verdant Great Sun also felt more despair, feeling it would be difficult to escape the disaster this time.

Hairy men continued to add in many supplementary materials and Gu worms.

"Add vanity Gu!" A hairy man threw a Gu into the cauldron.

This Gu was strange and looked like a huge blue crab. But different from real crabs, its crab shell was hollow.

The moment it saw Verdant Great Sun, the huge crab like vanity Gu was very excited: "You, you are Verdant Great Sun? I have heard about you, but had never expected I would meet you here, it is really my good fortune. I am too happy, too excited."

Verdant Great Sun gave a bitter smile: "How can it be good fortune when we are about to die."

"I don't care about death. I only wanted to ask, how did you become so famous? I really admire you! I have the utmost admiration for people like you." Vanity Gu asked with urgency.

"I am not in the mood to talk about this now, I need to escape." Verdant Great Sun struggled in the cauldron and tried to climb up, but was quickly pressed down into the cauldron by a watching hairy man.

"Quick, tell me, tell me quick!" Vanity Gu was not tactful and wholeheartedly wanted to ask for guidance.

Verdant Great Sun furiously rebuked: "Can't you see the situation we are in now?"

Vanity Gu opened its eyes wide and started at Verdant Great Sun before it beamed with pleasure: "I understand, I understand now. If I want to be popular, I need to endure the heat. Thank you for the guidance, thank you. Verdant Great Sun, as thanks, I will do a favor for you."

Saying so, the vanity Gu exploded.

This explosion was not intense and was very light, only giving off a soft 'bang' sound. The vanity Gu turned into a formless poisonous wind and attacked the hearts of all the hairy men.

The crystal clear dark blue eyes of the hairy men turned red.

Verdant Great Sun was dazed for a good while, before coming back to his senses. He could not help sighing at vanity Gu's sacrifice, and immediately shouted: "Although you hairy men can refine Gu, but it is nothing. Even if you all live for eternity, so what? You are so ugly with hair all over your body, you are simply an abomination."

The hairy men were stupefied.

If it was before, they would not care about Verdant Great Sun.

But now, the poison of vanity had spread in the depths of their hearts, shrouding their intelligence.

Hearing Verdant Great Sun's shouts, the hairy men started refuting loudly: "Nonsense, nonsense! We hairy men are the most perfect, there can be nothing more beautiful than hair all over the body!"

Verdant Great Sun was suddenly hit by an inspiration: "No matter how beautiful your hair is, could it be as beautiful as my hair?"

Because he had drank vajra monkey's strong wine, his hair had become blazing fire.

The hairy men were baffled at his words.

The beautiful fire was flickering and changing all the time. Even they could not help but admit the movement of Verdant Great Sun's hair was beautiful.

Verdant Great Sun continued to stimulate them: "Even if you obtain eternity, you won't be as beautiful as me! Look at my hair, it is as colorful and charismatic as fire."

The hairy men were spurred on by Verdant Great Sun, and finally someone could not endure it: "You have such amazing hair, I will have it too. Look at mine!"

He then used a fire torch to ignite his whole body.

The hair on his body burned and he became a fiery man.

"Hahaha, you only have beautiful hair, but my whole body is beautiful now." This hairy man shouted.

Soon, the other hairy men also rushed to do the same.

All of them became fiery men, the fire burned them and the intense pain caused them to howl in pain.

But when they realized this, it was too late for them to extinguish the fire, and bombastically displayed their beauty.

Divine travel Gu was overjoyed and praised Verdant Great Sun endlessly: "Human, you are really clever, actually thinking of this method."

Verdant Great Sun escaped out of the cauldron and succeeded in surviving. He replied in his mind with a cold smile: "It is not me who is clever. It is the vanity in people that have turned them stupid. They often silently endure pain for false beauty, giving up the goals they should truly pursue."

......

Grand white moon gold, skull stones, dragon-side tooth, young autumn grass along with fifty primeval stones, a flower boar Gu and a boar cage Gu.

This was handed to Fang Yuan as the materials for Gu refinement.

In front of him, the hairy man was already sitting cross-legged on the ground and refining Gu.

Although Fang Yuan was not a refinement path Gu Master, he had ventured into the refinement path in his previous life and knew many recipes.

Right now, he had three choices, every choice would refine a new Gu.

The inheritance did not mention which Gu he had to refine, this meant the Gu he refined needed to be better than the hairy man.

Fang Yuan looked at the process of the hairy man refining Gu and could already guess what he was going to refine.

He sneered inwardly, but on his face appeared a respectful and flattering smile: "Lord hairy man, you are really amazing. The method of your Gu refinement really makes this one sigh in amazement. You are a Gu refinement grandmaster, there is no Gu in this world which you can't refine."

"Ah? Haha! You... tactful." The hairy man laughed loudly, clearly happy.

This distraction immediately caused the Gu refinement to fail.

The hairy man's expression suddenly changed and shouted in fear: "No!"

But it was already late.

Heavenly power descended as lightning and struck the hairy man into ashes.

"Hehe." Fang Yuan indifferently laughed and collected the materials in his hand. Under the paper crane Gu's lead, he slowly walked towards the next round.

Chapter 358: New Trump Card

Light dispersed and a Gu slowly landed onto Fang Yuan's palm.

This was water cage Gu which was used especially to capture wild Gu worms and was very effective.

The hairy man in front was in the process of refining Gu. When he saw Fang Yuan was already done, he immediately let out a desperate howl.

Thunder crackled in the sky and the hairy man was killed.

Similar to King Quan Inheritance, King Xin Inheritance was also extremely cruel. Gu Masters had to tread through blood and death to move a step forward.

Fang Yuan sighed and stored the water cage Gu before continuing forward.

If he remembered correctly, this was already the thirty-second round in King Xin Inheritance.

King Xin Inheritance was an inheritance related to refinement path. The difficulty increased every ten rounds and the hairy men that appeared also became smarter and stronger.

In the early twenty or so rounds, Fang Yuan was able to rely on his speech to flatter the hairy men and disrupt their concentration, causing their Gu refinement to fail and give him effortless victories.

But starting from thirtieth round, the hairy men that appeared were huge and had remarkable intelligence; Fang Yuan could only compete fairly.

But fortunately, the Gu refinement materials of the first twenty rounds were accumulated by Fang Yuan and gave him ample options in refining Gu.

These Gu refinement materials could be saved by the Gu Masters and used for future rounds.

This was also a trick King Xin had left behind when she set up his inheritance. In Fang Yuan's previous life, this trick was made public only after a year. Right now, it was a secret, even if some people realized this trick, the number was only a small fraction of the participants.

Fang Yuan was able to rush forward like this because of his plentiful accumulation and his previous life's experiences. His achievement here were even better than at King Quan Inheritance.

From fortieth round, the difficulty of King Xin Inheritance increased by several folds.

At this stage, Gu Masters could use one of their Gu. But in King Xin Inheritance, the Gu they use must be of refinement path.

Fang Yuan did not have any refinement path Gu, the materials on him were also almost used up.

He began to feel the difficulty of advancing forward.

It was become very difficult to cross each round.

What was good was that after fortieth round, King Xin Inheritance gave the Gu Masters a corresponding reward.

These rewards could be refinement path Gu worms, recipes, primeval stones and so on, and were very generous.

When Fang Yuan broke through to forty-fourth round, he was given an opportunity to leave. He took this opportunity and left King Xin Inheritance.

The time he spent this time in King Xin Inheritance was even longer than in King Quan Inheritance.

Returning to San Cha mountain, Fang Yuan found Tie clan's purple light barrier was still standing tall. Tie clan's four old-timers were very patient and did not enter three kings inheritance; Bai Ning Bing was still trapped.

The three light pillars on the mountain peaks had already shrunk down to a cup sized thickness.

But as long as the light pillars existed, even if it was only the thickness of a tiny needle, it meant the doors had not closed and people could still enter.

But every time the inheritance opened up, no matter which inheritance of three kings inheritance Gu Masters chose, they could only enter one time.

Fang Yuan looked for Li Xian and made another transaction again.

Li Xian received many things from Fang Yuan and was inwardly startled.

"I have a bad news for you. Tie clan's four old-timers have already requested for support from their clan, Tie clan has already sent a group of reinforcements over and it might be unfavorable for sir."

Fang Yuan was not surprised, this action of Tie clan's four old-timers was also within his expectations: "Eh? Who did they send as reinforcements?"

"The head is Tie clan's Tie Ba Xiu, he is a strength path Gu Master with rank four upper stage cultivation. Besides him, there is also Tie Ruo Nan. She is one of the eight young masters of Tie clan and is a rising star who has been in limelight these two years! Every one of Tie clan's eight young masters are dragons and phoenixes. Especially this Tie Ruo Nan, she is the daughter of Divine Investigator Tie Xue Leng and already has rank four initial stage cultivation at such a young age."

Li Xian placed emphasis on Tie Ruo Nan in this batch of reinforcements, and only gave small snippets of information regarding Tie Ba Xiu and others.

Tie Ba Xiu was already a famous character and everyone knew of him. But Tie Ruo Nan was a rising star and could only be said to have some reputation and had yet to be famous around Southern Border.

Li Xian, however, did not know Fang Yuan was familiar with Tie Ruo Nan.

'Sure enough, she advanced to rank four. Tie Ba Xiu, Tie clan indeed sent this group just like in my previous life...' Fang Yuan pondered in his mind.

Li Xian had been observing Fang Yuan's expression the whole time, but seeing him remain calm, he was increasingly feeling more afraid.

"Lord little beast king, when this batch of Tie clansmen arrives, Tie clan's four old-timers will be free to deal with Bai Ning Bing. There is still time if you make a move now." Li Xian persuaded, with sincerity showing all over his face.

"I will have to ask you to pay more attention to our future deals." Fang Yuan smiled and left the cave.

The moment Fang Yuan left, Li Xian's expression turned grave.

His small eyes flashed with sharp light: "I have been fanning the flames to this extent but this little beast king remains unmoved. Is he really not worried about his partner's safety? Could it be the relation between Bai Ning Bing and him is not as close as the rumors say? He is a man and Bai Ning Bing is so beautiful, he will definitely go rescue her. It seems I need to contact Hu Mei Er..."

Riling up people's emotions had become basic nature to him. He watched others fight and fished in troubled water, obtaining huge benefits.

"Is this true?" Hu Mei Er's eyes brightened with high spirits when she got the news from Li Xian.

"Why would I deceive my darling?" Li Xian smiled while caressing Hu Mei Er's waist.

Hu Mei Er smiled tenderly and threw herself into Li Xian's chest, acting coquettishly: "It is still big brother Li Xian who loves me the most."

.....

A round pearl quietly rested on Fang Yuan's palm.

It was golden all over and was only the size of a thumb. In the dusky cave, the pearl let out faint golden luster.

This was a yellow gold relic Gu, rank four Gu!

This Gu's market supply was strictly controlled by all great clans. Even Li Xian could not get it.

It was all because this Gu could directly raise a rank four Gu Master's cultivation by a small realm. Rank four and rank five were already the higher-ups of a clan; a yellow gold relic Gu could change the power structure of the higher-ups.

"I was quite lucky this time, actually receiving a yellow gold relic Gu as reward in King Xin Inheritance." Fang Yuan sighed before activating this Gu with a thought.

Yellow gold relic Gu immediately turned into golden ray of light and entered Fang Yuan's aperture.

The ninety percent primeval sea in Fang Yuan's aperture surged and ebbed. In the center, Spring Autumn Cicada appeared and disappeared at times.

When yellow gold relic Gu entered the aperture, it was firmly suppressed by the indistinct aura of Spring Autumn Cicada. Fang Yuan could only make Spring Autumn Cicada conceal itself then use yellow gold relic Gu.

A ball of golden light immediately spread and covered the whole aperture. Bright golden primeval essence converged together, cleansing the aperture walls.

A night passed and when the light of clear dawn shone upon San Cha mountain, Fang Yuan slowly opened his eyes.

Rank four middle stage!

If he used nine eyes liquor worm, he would possess rank four upper stage essence gold primeval essence!

This moment, he had officially surpassed Bai Ning Bing in cultivation. At the same time, the stable aperture walls could bear even more of Spring Autumn Cicada's pressure now, somewhat delaying this death warrant.

"Next, it is refining Gu..."

Fang Yuan did not urgently use liquor worm, but instead took out a Gu.

This Gu was a ball of bone the size of a quail egg. On the surface, there were alternating black and white stripes like on a zebra.

Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing had once used this to soar to the skies.

This was the footless bird.

Although it was only at rank three, it could move ten thousand miles and was the number one mount under rank five. But it had a great a weakness - it could only fly once.

The moment it landed, it was the moment of its death.

This footless bird Gu was also obtained from King Xin Inheritance as a reward for Fang Yuan.

Nine palace flowers, aspiring stone, golden crow's essence, chilling grass... Fang Yuan threw all these materials into the footless bird Gu and also constantly threw in primeval stones.

Most of these Gu refinement materials were materials Fang Yuan had remaining from King Xin Inheritance, while a portion was bought from Li Xian.

He used up a total of a hundred and eighty thousand primeval stones before the Gu refinement finished.

Bone wings Gu!

It was a rank four Gu. It looked like a feather, was spotless white, had bony texture and was light as a feather.

Under Fang Yuan's will, this Gu flew towards his back and spread, forming into something resembling two pairs of folded wings that covered almost all of Fang Yuan's back.

He poured primeval essence into the bone wings Gu... suddenly, intense pain attacked him as countless bones grew out from his backbone and ribs. The bony outgrowth pierced through his flesh and grew out before converging together and forming two enormous bone wings.

These bone wings were like the wings on a bird; wide and long. When folded up, the tail of the wings could touch the ground. The current Fang Yuan was truly an eight foot tall man.

Whoosh!

There was a soft sound as the bone wings stretched out. The cave did not look so spacious anymore.

Normal bone wings were spotless white. But the bone wings on Fang Yuan was not only pitch black, but also let out a metallic luster like that of steel and iron.

This was because Fang Yuan's skeleton surpassed ordinary, having been reformed by iron bone Gu and at the same time, he had constantly been using rank four essence iron bone recently.

This led to Fang Yuan's bone wings to far surpass other people's in terms of sturdiness. Rather than to say they were only bone wings, it was better to say they were iron bone wings!

Fang Yuan softly flapped the wings, there was only a blowing sound before a strong whirlwind blew up.

Bone wings could be used as he wished and was like a natural part of his body.

Fang Yuan nodded in satisfaction.

Ordinary Gu Masters were rather cautious in using bone wings Gu. They would often train for two to three years before they were able to fly. If it were to be used in battle, they would have to train even longer, at least five years and above.

After all, humans were creatures who walked on the ground and not flying creatures.

However, Fang Yuan had no such problem.

After five hundred years in his previous life, he had similarly gained plentiful experiences in terms of flying.

One could well imagine, if he suddenly used them, it was sure to catch his enemies off guard.

His newly advanced cultivation and bone wings Gu became the new trump cards of Fang Yuan!

"Now, it is time to deal with Bai Ning Bing's matter." Fang Yuan kept the bone wings, a chilling light flashing past his eyes.

Chapter 359: Obstruction

A group of seven people silently moved through a forest.

'We have been hurrying on our way without resting all these days and are already very close to San Cha mountain.' Tie Ba Xiu thought while rushing through the forest, stepping across stones and tree roots.

He was tall and had a buff physique, on his square face was a steady expression which gave a feeling of reliability.

His cultivation was rank four upper stage and his fame had spread throughout Southern Border. When he was young, he was spurned by the clan, pushed aside and forced to drift outside.

Then he encountered a righteous Gu Master inheritance and changed to strength path, making his name renowned in the world.

Now, he was a famous character of the righteous path. With rank five Gu 'earth overlord', he was called 'present age overlord' and had battle strength that surpassed ordinary rank four peak stage!

'At present, there are five rank four peak stage Gu Masters on San Cha mountain; Long Qing Tian, Yi Chong, Kong Ri Tian, Wu Shen Tong and Yi Huo. Among them, Yi Huo's battle prowess is very high and will be the strongest opponent. In addition to this, there will be more and more formidable characters who will join this struggle. It is just that I do not know what Tie Ruo Nan has planned.'

Thinking of this, Tie Ba Xiu could not help turning his gaze towards Tie Ruo Nan who was running beside him.

Although he had impressive battle prowess, in the group that was sent over this time by the clan, he was not the head. Rather, it was a young junior - Tie Ruo Nan!

After Tie Ruo Nan returned to the clan, she cultivated hard and displayed extremely strong aptitude and talent. Now, she was already one of the Tie clan's eight young masters. She was meticulous, sensitive to the smallest details and was already being called 'little divine investigator'. She was the strongest rising star that emerged in Tie clan these years, she was gradually soaring up and was being watched by many.

This time, when the four old-timers requested for reinforcements, the clan made an exception and appointed Tie Ruo Nan as the leader of this group. Even Tie Ba Xiu, this famous senior had to obey her orders. This showed how much the Tie clan higher ups expected from her.

Tie Ba Xiu only took a glance before retracting his gaze.

He was not in the least bit concerned about the clan's arrangement and was also not jealous.

Tie Ba Xiu was very loyal to the clan; for the clan's future hope, he was willing to be an assistant, willing to become a stepping stone.

In fact, when he was down and out, he had received Divine Investigator Tie Xue Leng's help. Tie Ba Xiu had always felt grateful towards him and with the interaction over these days, he sensed Tie Ruo Nan's brilliance.

"As expected of Divine Investigator's daughter! Big Brother Xue Leng, you have a worthy successor, you can rest assured in the afterlife." Tie Ba Xiu was gratified.

He was very satisfied with Tie Ruo Nan. Not only did he admire her cultivation talents, he admired her leadership capability even more.

Outstanding young Gu Masters had gathered around Tie Ruo Nan. Not mentioning anything else, one just needed to look at the current group of people.

Tie Mu, rank three peak stage Gu Master, looked gentlemanly and was brimming with talent. He had received many invitations but he chose to join Tie Ruo Nan.

Tie Ao Kai, rank three upper stage, he might look dazed and sleepy, but in the field of investigative ability, he had true prowess.

There was also Tie Dao Ku, an offense Gu Master with outstanding battle prowess. He had once served another young master but was now recruited by Tie Ruo Nan.

Tie Xian Hua, one of the beauties in the clan, young and beautiful. Even clan elders praised her defensive abilities.

These talents gathered under Tie Ruo Nan and would become her crew. Tie Ba Xiu seemed to see the radiant scene where this crew endlessly grew and assisted Tie Ruo Nan in ascending to the position of clan leader.

Each one of the eight young masters of Tie clan had a chance to contend for clan leader's position!

As they ran quickly, lights and shadows fluctuated in their vision and green light shone on Tie Ruo Nan's face.

Her slender legs revealed her youthful beauty as she ran through the forest.

Having gained much experiences these years, Tie Ruo Nan had clearly matured. Her brows were sharp as sword and her eyes shone like the stars; when one looked at her from the side, one could feel her power. Her thick eyelashes shaded the resolute light in her eyes.

"San Cha mountain!"

She recited this name in her mind.

She had already received news about San Cha mountain. And she was even aware that San Cha mountain had become a place of unstable changes, a struggling whirlpool that swallowed lives, engulfing countless people of both demonic and righteous paths.

Originally, Tie Ruo Nan had not thought of participating. But an unexpected information made her realize there were hidden details regarding Qing Mao mountain back then.

Her father Tie Xue Leng lost his life at Qing Mao mountain; a hero of a generation had fallen.

Anything that concerned her father, she had to check it out. Thus, she personally accepted the order and hurried to San Cha mountain.

"Bai Ning Bing... Fang Zheng... the truth about Qing Mao mountain, I will get to the bottom of it!"

The group moved forward.

The group of seven moved in an standard battle formation.

The investigative Gu Master Tie Ao Kai was at front, Tie Ruo Nan and Tie Ba Xiu was at middle. Healing Gu Master was at the rear with defensive Gu Master Tie Xian Hua beside him.

No matter what the terrain was, the battle formation showed no signs of disorder. No matter what happened, this group responded to it at the first sight and was not caught unprepared.

"Who is it?!"

Suddenly, Tie Ao Kai who was at the front stopped and shouted, alerting the group.

Something happened!

The whole group swiftly came to a stop, the formation changed slightly to form into the best battle array; it was both closely linked and was also faintly loose to leave a way for retreat.

They could attack if they progressed, and defend if they retreated.

A person who crossed his arms and was standing on a boulder, glanced down at this group of people.

He was tall, with strong back and narrow waist, although he was not exaggeratedly muscular, he still gave a feeling of sturdiness.

He was wearing tight-fitting black clothes, he was standing there alone but it felt like a mountain was standing.

Especially, his black pupils, they were dark as abyss and gave an unfathomable feeling.

"Fang Zheng!" Tie Ruo Nan's pupils shrunk when she saw this person and blurted out.

This person was indeed Fang Yuan.

"Tie Ruo Nan, we meet again." The corner of Fang Yuan's lips curled up into a smile, a grim intent was revealed from his expression.

Little beast king!

Tie Ba Xiu's eyes narrowed and a severe light flashed past them.

The other five people of the group were behaving like they were facing a great enemy. They were very well equipped with intel and knew the person in front of them; a rising star of the demonic path with outstanding battle prowess, his actions were wild and unrestrained - an extremely dangerous character!

"Fang Zheng, I trust you have been since we last met?" Tie Ruo Nan revealed a complicated expression on her face and continued after a sigh, "Fang Zheng, you came to compromise? Actually, there is nothing to it. I know the struggles of three kings inheritance, you either live or die, there are no ways for retreat. Bai Ning Bing ran into my Tie clan's Gu Master and killed him in as a last-ditch move. I have friendly relations with you both, how about this, come to Tie clan as a guest, explain the matter clearly and redeem this sin by doing some assignments for Tie clan. I can plea for leniency for you and Tie clan won't pursue this matter anymore."

When she was speaking, Tie Ao Kai nervously activated his Gu to secretly scan his surroundings.

It was truly strange Fang Yuan appeared alone. Maybe there were others lying in ambush!

Fang Yuan could not help but sneer at Tie Ruo Nan's words: "Sin? She only killed a person, what sin is there? The only slight difference is this person has a somewhat tougher background, that's all. Tie Ruo Nan, I didn't think you were so childish. Thinking of luring me into going to Tie clan, and capture me there? When I enter Tie clan, I will be a dragon swimming in shallow water, a tiger moving in plain sight, wouldn't I be completely at your mercy then?"

Tie Ruo Nan deeply furrowed her brows: "Fang Zheng, you have changed a lot over these years. You feel no guilt over killing a person? Anyway, I am not telling lies. I pledge on my honor that I will guarantee your safety and guarantee you will be given fair trial."

Fang Yuan scoffed: "Is your Tie clan considered safe? At the moment, Divine Thief Lu Zuan Feng has been causing havoc at Tie clan, even infiltrating Demon Suppression Tower. Your Tie clan can't even help yourselves, can you guarantee my safety? Laughable, truly laughable."

"What? The clan has kept the news regarding Divine Thief Lu Zuan Feng confidential. He is an outsider and has also been staying far away here at San Cha mountain, how could he be so clear of the matter?"

The seven people of Tie clan turned pale.

Divine Thief Lu Zuan Feng was a rank five expert, the matter of him infiltrating Demon Suppression Tower had already caused a lot of disturbance in Tie clan's higher ups.

Tie clan had always viewed itself as the holy land of the righteous path, its Demon Suppression Tower was even a renowned prison for the demonic path, but Lu Zuan Feng entered and left it as he pleased. This level of humiliation and disgrace was tightly guarded and kept a secret by Tie clan; even top clans like Wu clan and Shang clan had no knowledge of it.

However, this little beast king unexpectedly knew it!

"Do you really believe such nonsense?" Tie Ba Xiu could not help but refuse it as it concerned the reputation of Tie clan.

"Leader, there are no one in the surroundings, he is alone." At this time, Tie Ao Kai reported in a soft voice.

A bright light immediately flashed through Tie Ruo Nan's mind and she fixed her gaze at Fang Yuan: "Fang Zheng, I understand your intent. You want to use this information to blackmail us and exchange for Bai Ning Bing's life? We can do that! But we need to know how you you came to know about this secret. Otherwise, we will absolutely not let her go."

Fang Yuan threw his head back and laughed loudly: "Tie Ruo Nan, you are truly naive. I just spoke those words casually. You still don't understand the purpose of me coming here? Don't you know there is a battle tactic called besiege an enemy stronghold in order to strike at the reinforcements?"

"What, you want to go against us?" Tie Ruo Nan's pupils slightly widened, revealing an inconceivable expression.

The others also looked at Fang Yuan as if they were looking at an idiot.

We are a group of seven while you are just by yourself. We have rank four upper stage senior Tie Ba Xiu, rank four initial stage Tie Ruo Nan, and five rank three Gu Masters, each of them an expert. Just you alone wants to go against us?

"Has this little beast king lost his mind? Is there a problem with his brain?" For a moment, everyone had this thought.

Fang Yuan knew their thoughts as he looked at the change in their expression and eyes.

He did not feel like refuting them. With a cold smile, he suddenly pounced towards the group from high above like a northern goshawk.

"He really attacked?"

"Looking for death!"

The seven people were both startled and furious.

"No, this aura, how could he be at rank four middle stage?!"

Next instance, the seven all felt their hearts thump as they sensed the aura on Fang Yuan.

Facts speak louder than words.

"Rank four middle stage! Not initial stage?" Tie Ruo Nan's eyes opened wide and was stunned at the revelation.

Chapter 360: One vs Seven (1/4)

Fang Yuan had been using breath concealment Gu and restrained his aura as much as possible. But now that he made a move, his true aura exploded out.

Add in to that, Tie Ruo Nan's group had the preconceived belief that Fang Yuan had rank four initial stage cultivation. Thus, for a moment, this seven person group was very surprised.

"Rank four middle stage, this little beast king is so young but has surpassed young master Ruo Nan!"

"Rank four middle stage, no wonder he could be so arrogant."

"So what if he is at rank four middle stage? He actually dared to approach us alone, he is simply seeking his own doom!"

...

All sorts of thoughts flashed in the Tie clan's group's minds.

Thud!

A dull sound echoed; Tie Ba Xiu came back to his senses the fastest and stiffly struck against Fang Yuan's fists in mid-air.

Tie Ba Xiu stably fell to the ground while Fang Yuan was sent flying.

"Fang Zheng, you want to find trouble with us just by yourself? I know you want to rescue your partner Bai Ning Bing, but think it over. You can't act rashly in a matter of rescuing someone, it is still not too late for you to pull back. If you continue to fight, you will truly be setting yourself against our Tie clan! If that happens, your partner's life will also be on the line." Tie Ba Xiu expressed himself in few words, seemingly earnest, but was in truth attempting to break Fang Yuan's fighting spirit; truly proving old ginger is hotter than new.

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan chuckled and looked at Tie Ba Xiu and the rest, his gaze completely exposed his killing intent, "So what if you are Tie clan? So what if I oppose you? If I really can't save Bai Ning Bing, then I can only blame it on her bad luck. In any case, I already did my best."

Such ruthless and indifference caused the Tie clan's seven people to feel a chill in their hearts.

Fang Yuan turned towards Tie Ao Kai: "You over there, you don't need to scout anymore, it is just me alone. Frankly, this path you guys chose is really good, very hidden and very suitable for me to kill you all."

Hearing these words, Tie Ba Xiu's expression completely turned dark.

"Fang Zheng, you are seeking your own death!"

"Death?" Fang Yuan started laughing loudly without any restraint.

"Is this guy crazy?"

"Has little beast king going mad from cultivation and lost his mind?"

"Demonic path people are all lunatics like this!"

The group all felt the situation was going to be problematic from the unbridled laughter of Fang Yuan.

Fierce people were afraid of unreasonable people and unreasonable people were afraid of those that did not care about death. Despite there being seven people in Tie clan's side and Fang Yuan was alone, the Tie clan's group felt fear.

This type of lunatic that was suicidal and did not care about his own life, what was there that he could not do?

Fang Yuan suddenly stopped laughing and stepped forward producing a loud sound. Like a tiger that left the mountain, he resumed his attacks again.

"Fight!" Tie Ruo Nan shouted with a heavy expression, knowing this fight was inevitable.

Tie Ba Xiu retreated and stood beside Tie Ruo Nan; Tie Dao Ku and Tie Xian Hua moved to the front together; and Tie Ao Kai started running at the side.

The whole formation was instantly loosened up like a sack being opened, displaying their skilled battle tactics coordination.

Charging crash Gu!

Fang Yuan rushed forward like a bull, the stones under him were smashed as he moved with powerful momentum and penetrated into Tie clan's 'sack' without any fear.

"Little beast king, you are simply too arrogant!" Tie Xian Hua shouted in her delicate voice and stretched out the five fingers of her right hand.

There was a soft sound and an enormous black golden lotus flower blossomed instantly from her palm.

The lotus bloomed, its huge petals were bent down, forming arcs like an umbrella. The dark green lotus stalk continued to grow and in a blink of an eye was over an arm's size, becoming the handle of the umbrella.

Tie Xian Hua plucked this lotus with her left hand and then charged towards Fang Yuan while holding the dark green lotus stalk.

Umbrella lotus Gu!

Tie Xian Hua was petite while the umbrella lotus was huge and completely covered her, becoming a shield and firmly protecting her.

Fang Yuan sneered, a white elephant phantom appeared above him.

Beast phantom, the strength of an elephant!

Bam!

With no surprise, Fang Yuan sent Tie Xian Hua, who was blocking his path, flying.

Tie Xian Hua flew a whole ten feet like a dead leaf blown by the wind.

"What great strength!" She gritted her teeth, enduring the intense pain from the collision. She twisted her body in the midair and quickly found a balance, landing on the ground without falling.

But the expected attack did not follow, Fang Yuan ignored her existence and directly charged towards Tie Ruo Nan.

"Damn it, he is going after young master!"

"We must block him, protect young master!"

The battle will and killing intent of the group was ignited when they saw Fang Yuan targeting Tie Ruo Nan.

Tie Ruo Nan half-kneeled, her two hands were pressed on the ground; from the moment the battle started, she was creating a puppet.

Plants grew wildly near her.

The fragile grass beside her feet grew to an adult man's height. Dozens of huge grass intertwined; in the emerald-green light, a grassman puppet was created.

Grass puppet Gu!

Fang Yuan had seen rank one grass puppet Gu at Qing Mao mountain. It was used as a target for practicing moon blades.

Rank one grass puppet Gu was of no threat but once it reached rank two, it could easily kill an ordinary hunter. The one Tie Ruo Nan was using right now was rank three grass puppet Gu.

The grassman puppet she created was short and thin, the leaves tightly weaved together, its one hand was holding a bamboo blade and another hand was raising a rattan shell shield.

This was rattan shell grass soldier! It possessed the strength to kill a rank one Gu Master!

Just one rattan shell grass soldier was no threat to Fang Yuan. But once their numbers increased, they became troublesome.

Rattan shell grass soldier were often used as cannon fodder to consume the opposing Gu Master's primeval essence. Most importantly, using a rank four Gu Master's strength, a dozen rattan shell soldiers could combine into a rank four grass sword elite soldier.

In this short moment, Tie Ruo Nan already had eighteen rattan shell grass soldiers beside her.

"Tie Ruo Nan..." Fang Yuan was filled with killing intent, his icy and sharp gaze firmly locked on to Tie Ruo Nan.

This woman possessed outstanding talents similar to Bai Ning Bing, and she had also investigated the affairs on Qing Mao mountain, she could not be left alive. Fang Yuan had already wanted to kill her back at Shang clan city, but the time had not been good then.

Tie Ruo Nan did not budge. She chose to believe in her partners and was still creating rattan shell grass soldiers.

"Block him!"

Tie Ao Kai flung his sleeves and a large swarm of golden needle mosquitoes flew out.

"Don't even think of taking a step further!"

Tie Dao Ku rushed towards Fang Yuan while activating hand blade Gu and swift shadow Gu.

Fang Yuan laughed and directly clashed head-on without evading it.

Golden needle mosquitoes pierced tiny blood holes all over his body. Tie Dao Ku's arms struck his chest and slashed out long wounds.

Fang Yuan howled with laughter, and stepped forward with his head high, blood flowing out from the wounds all over his body.

"He is wounded!" The Tie clan group was solemn.

If it were other enemies that were wounded, the Tie clan group would feel happy and relaxed, but Fang Yuan possessed bitter strength Gu; the heavier the injuries he suffered, the stronger his fighting strength became.

Green bull, horse, stone turtle!

Sure enough, three more beast phantoms appeared above Fang Yuan.

He opened the way with his huge strength that could not be blocked!

Tie Xian Hua rushed over and was casually sent flying by Fang Yuan. Tie Dao Ku helplessly retreated while Tie Ao Kai could only wander at the sidelines.

"Good, tyrant strength Gu!" Fang Yuan was about to reach Tie Ruo Nan, when Tie Ba Xiu shouted and stepped forward.

Bam!

There was a huge explosive sound from the collision of the two. Both were sent back seven to eight steps.

It was a draw!

Fang Yuan had four beast phantoms, but Tie Ba Xiu was not famous for nothing; his rank four tyrant strength Gu was inherited from the ancient strength path and possessed the strength of a overlord.

"Interesting, again!" Fang Yuan's eyes shone brightly and he charged forward again.

Tie Ba Xiu greeted him head-on, firmly blocking his way.

Tie Dao Ku and others all let out a breath of turbid air, feeling relief as they looked at this scene.

"Little beast king is finally stopped."

"This is senior Tie Ba Xiu!"

"Fang Zheng is trapped within our tight encirclement, he is sure to die!"

The Tie clan group's fighting spirit soared as Fang Yuan lost his momentum. In their eyes, he was like a bull that had fallen into trap, his threat had greatly decreased.

All of them joined in to attack.

All kinds of attacks like swarm of golden needle mosquitoes, flower rain and hand blades were thrown at Fang Yuan from all directions.

Fang Yuan's skin was torn open, the wounds on his body was becoming more serious and he had no choice but to use golden shield Gu to defend. At the same time, he also used self-reliance Gu to heal his body.

The more he fought, the stronger he got, but Tie Ba Xiu was unexpectedly also the same!

He possessed rank five earth overlord Gu which allowed him to absorb an endless amount of strength from the earth, making his tyrant strength Gu stronger and stronger.

Tie Ba Xiu continuously activated earth overlord Gu, acquiring formless strength from the earth that empowered his tyrant strength Gu and continued to increase his strength.

The battle was in a stalemate.

Fang Yuan and Tie Ba Xiu fought intensely, beating each other up with punches and kicks; they were the center of the fight. Like human-shaped beasts, each of their moves carried heavy weight, and wherever the fight went, stones shattered and dust flew.

Howl!

Suddenly, there was a beast howl and a beast phantom appeared above Fang Yuan.

Lightning curled around it, its tusks were exposed outside and it gave off extremely violent aura - thunder boar phantom!

Tie Xian Hua who was blocking Fang Yuan's path was suddenly sent flying.

Umbrella lotus Gu broke and its petals scattered in the air.

"Xian Hua, persevere!" Tie Mu rushed over and held Tie Xian Hua who was throwing up huge amounts of blood, and promptly began healing her.

At the same time, a group of rattan shell grass soldiers came over and blocked any gaps in the surroundings, defending these two.

By now, there were already close to a thousand rattan shell grass soldiers around Tie Ruo Nan and were already providing support in the battle. At the same time, she was continuously creating new grassman puppets.

Tie Ruo Nan walked the enslavement path and one could not let an enslavement path Gu Master like her have enough time to prepare.

Enslavement path Gu Masters were the best at fighting war of attrition, the longer the time passed, the more unfavorable Fang Yuan's situation would be. The best answer was to directly murder the leader.

But this tactic would not work.

Fang Yuan was firmly entangled with Tie Ba Xiu now.

"A ferocious junior!" Tie Ba Xiu could not help but feel admiration towards Fang Yuan in his heart.

Even though he had already predicted it, the strength Fang Yuan displayed still shocked him.

He had thought Fang Yuan's power was due to the set of strength path Gu with him. Inheriting the precious Gu worms of ancient strength path and moreover, their coordination was also exquisite.

However, as the battle progressed till this stage, Tie Ba Xiu could hardly dare to believe the shrewdness, ruthlessness, calmness and steadiness Fang Yuan displayed.

"This lad's battle talent... if I was not personally fighting him, I would never believe that there would be such a monster! He needs to be killed, I must kill him. He is even more dangerous than what the intel said, if we give him time to grow, it will be a calamity for the righteous path!" Tie Ba Xiu was shocked and his killing intent soared even more.

Chapter 361: One vs Seven (2/4)

The battle carried on like wildfire.

"Little beast king is this terrifying! We have so many people on our side but still can't catch him!" Tie Mu looked at the battle while healing Tie Xian Hua, his expressions fluctuating endlessly.

"His strength has improved by leaps and bounds, reaching this formidable stage now!" Tie Dao Ku looked at the battle in front, sensing he was already unable to interfere.

"No wonder he arrogantly blocked us, such battle prowess... but even if he is more ferocious, what can he do? Two fists cannot rival four hands, the battle has reached this stage and we still have seven people! This is the cooperative strength of a group! Fang Zheng, this battle is your loss, no doubt." Tie Ruo Nan observed the battle situation from a tall boulder.

In her sight, Tie Ba Xiu and five others surrounded Fang Yuan as a circle. And surrounding this was a large numbers of green ratten shell grass soldiers that had formed into a tight net.

At the same time, some rattan shell grass soldiers were combining with each other to form rank four grass sword elite soldiers.

"The outcome is a foregone conclusion. Little beast king, look at your surroundings! You are already heavily encircled, do you still want to persist obstinately? Let yourself be captured and maybe you can still have a way out!" Tie Xian Hua stood up and attempted to shake Fang Yuan's fighting spirit.

The injuries on her were already healed by Tie Mu and she now had the strength to fight again.

"Fang Zheng, it is impossible for you to escape even if you grow wings[1]. This is the price for overestimating yourself!" Tie Mu added in from beside Tie Xian Hua.

"Eh? Impossible to escape?" Fang Yuan suddenly exerted strength and forced back Tie Ba Xiu. A mocking smile appeared on his face, "Is it true that I can't escape even if I grow wings? I'll give it a try."

Whoosh!

There was a sharp pain as a pair of pitch black bone wings with metallic luster stretched out fully from Fang Yuan's back!

"This is..."

"He really has...?"

"What!"

In front of Tie clan group's amazed gazes, Fang Yuan flapped the wings and softly lifted off from the ground and continued to rise higher, flying into the air.

Tie Mu could never have expected his words to turn out to be a prophecy, and was baffled.

"The intel did not say little beast king had a flying type Gu... this is clearly a rank four flying type Gu, how did he get it?" Tie Xian Hua stared with her eyes wide open in bewilderment.

Flying type Gu were a type of movement Gu worms, they were rather expensive and also very rare, thus only few Gu Masters possessed them.

"Fang Zheng can fly?! No wonder he arrogantly intercepted us." Tie Dao Ku immediately realized.

Tie Ruo Nan's expression also turned unsightly. Her ratten shell grass soldiers had no use against air targets. The moment Fang Yuan flew, an enormous hole immediately appeared in her painstakingly created layers of encirclement.

"What are you all panicking for!" Right at this moment, Tie Ba Xiu's loud shout echoed in everyone's ears.

This rank four upper stage strength path cultivator was a cornerstone of the Tie clan, and right now his eyes were bursting with bright light. His plentiful experiences allowed him to find out a weakness in Fang Yuan.

"How can flying type Gu be easy to control? By nature, humans walk on the ground, if they want to fly and soar freely, they need a lot of painstaking practice! And to battle while flying? It needs even more bitter training! Even Verdant Great Sun, son of the great Ren Zu, died while flying. How much time could it have been since this little beast king obtained his flying type Gu?"

Tie Ba Xiu words forced the Tie clan group to wake up and their spirits rose up again.

"That's right, the intel did not mention Fang Zheng having any flying type Gu. He definitely obtained the bone wings very recently!"

"Flying needs a huge amount of practice, it is not something that can be picked up and used immediately. Little beast king is too naive."

"The main thing is we are really fortunate to have senior Tie Ba Xiu by our side."

Tie clan's group regained their fighting spirit.

"My long distance methods are lacking, you guys attack and take him down. Fang Zheng, you made an extremely stupid move! If you had continued to battle steadily, you could have still lasted for some time, but now you have trapped yourself." Tie Ba Xiu shouted loudly.

"Eh? You think so...?" Fang Yuan smiled indifferently, a look of pity in his eyes.

"Little beast king, you won't be proud for long. Golden needle mosquito... huh." Tie Ao Kai wanted to attack when suddenly his expression turned stiff.

In the battle just before, his golden needle mosquito Gu were already exhausted.

It was all because he saw Fang Yuan not defending against the golden needle mosquitoes' attack, thus using it readily. The battle was also very intense which made him forget the intense expenditure of the golden needle mosquitoes.

"Not good, my star arrow Gu has already been destroyed by little beast king!"

"Damn it, I only have two flower rain Gu remaining...."

A similar situation played out on, more or less, everybody.

Tie Ba Xiu's heart sank, it turned out little beast king had already been ready and had all along been hiding his schemes deep within his heart.

"It's okay, I have blade qi Gu and can do long distance fight!" Tie Dao Ku stood up.

"I have snowball Gu with me and can make little beast king suffer some consequences." Another Tie clan Gu Master also stood up.

Many hands provide great strength; there were seven people in this Tie clan group and thus they had plentiful methods. Even if Fang Yuan had aimed at this, he was not able to wipe out all their methods.

"Little beast king, get down here!" Tie Dao Ku sent out a ray of blade qi.

The blade qi whistled towards Fang Yuan, but Fang Yuan evaded it with a light flap of his wings.

Three snowballs moved in to block Fang Yuan's retreating path.

Fang Yuan folded up his left wing and made an agile whirling movement, safely passing through the gaps between the snowballs.

Tie Ba Xiu's heart thumped at this scene and a bad feeling rose up: He evaded them so effortlessly, was that luck?

Soon, the Tie clan group felt stunned and helpless as Fang Yuan agilely and confidently evaded countless attacks.

"He has such a good control over flying type Gu!"

"Damn it, our attacks simply can't hit him."

"My primeval essence is already running dry, blade qi Gu's consumption is huge. It seems we can only let Fang Zheng escape this time."

The Tie clan group's attacks gradually became sparse.

"Little beast king, I can't help but admire you, you are indeed a great talent. Today, we made it easy for you to retreat, that is also because of your talent. But watch out for the next time we meet." Tie Ruo Nan warned in a heavy voice.

Fang Yuan seemed to have heard the most ridiculous joke in the world and started laughing loudly.

"What are you laughing at?" The ominous feeling in Tie Ba Xiu's heart became even more intense...

"Hahaha, of course I am laughing at your naivety. Why would I run? The real battle has only begun!" After saying this, Fang Yuan activated all-out effort Gu and strength qi Gu at the same time.

Green bull, horse, stone turtle, white elephant and black python; five beast phantoms turned solid and slammed down.

Bam! Bam! Bam!

In an instant, the battlefield shook, stones crumbled and dust flew everywhere. Ratten shell grass soldiers were sent flying or destroyed and the Tie clan group retreated madly.

"Attack! We can't be taking hits passive, we must give him no time to take control of the battlefield!" Tie Ba Xiu roared furiously and punched at Fang Yuan from afar with his bowl-sized fists.

A formless majestic fist energy exploded out violently and actually broke the sound of sound, creating a sonic boom!

However, Fang Yuan flapped his wings and rose higher, easily dodging the attack.

Tie Ba Xiu helplessly sighed. His fist energy might be a long range attack but the distance it could reach was short.

He was a strength path Gu Master, this path had always lacked in long range attack methods. Fang Yuan could be said to be an oddity because his strength qi Gu originated from the ancient qi path.

Upon Tie Ba Xiu's reminder, other Tie clan Gu Masters warded off the beast phantoms and started making aerial attacks.

However, Fang Yuan displayed unmatchable flying ability!

Occasionally, he was like a butterfly, dancing between the attacks and agilely evading them. Occasionally, he was like a goshawk flying towards the sky, forcing people to watch helplessly. Occasionally, he would make arcs with his bone wings like a swift. And occasionally, he would hover and wait for an opportunity before moving, like a dragonfly.

Most of the attacks were dodged by him. And a few attacks that managed to strike his body were resisted by the defensive light of golden shield Gu.

"This is impossible! How could his flying capability be so superb!"

"This level of control isn't inferior to Lan Mei He, Hong Fei Yu or Fei You Wang!!"

Lan Mei He, Hong Fei Yu and Fei You Wang were experts in flying and were already famed throughout Southern Border.

The Tie clan group were stunned and horrified.

Fang Yuan constantly activated Gu worms to attack to his heart's content. The earlier battle was only setting up this current situation.

Tie Ruo Nan's expression was ashen.

She had painstakingly created so many ratten shell grass soldiers but they could only passively take hits now! Moreover, it had wasted a lot of her primeval essence!

"Die!" Fang Yuan hovered for a long while before he suddenly saw an opportunity and pounced down.

"Tie Mu, careful!"

"Dodge quickly!"

Tie Mu heard the others' fearful shouts and looked up in a flurry.

The dazzling sunlight pierced his eyes first of all. Then he saw a black figure pouncing down like a goshawk.

The intense whistling sounds immediately filled his ears.

An enormous feeling of crisis filled his heart.

"Not good, run!" This thought had just emerged in his mind when Fang Yuan's hands grabbed his shoulders.

Beast phantom retract!

Fang Yuan's strength gushed up and he pulled apart his arms, ruthlessly ripping apart the arms.

Blood spurted out like a waterfall and Tie Mu's two limbs were torn apart from the shoulders.

A violent pain drowned Tie Mu's mind and he roared furiously, his handsome face twisted into something terrifying.

Bam!

Fang Yuan again exerted strength and smacked his hands; Tie Mu's head was forcibly burst open like a watermelon!

In an instant, blood and brain matter sprayed on Fang Yuan's body, face and hair. It was either the grey brain matter or red blood, even the eyeballs stuck on Fang Yuan's clothes.

The dense bloody stench assaulted the nose. If it were any other person, they might have vomited on the spot, but Fang Yuan smelled it like it was the world's most fragrant smell. He was enjoying this and there was even a very intense excitement in the depths of his heart!

"Death, such a sweet fragrance!"

"Kill, kill!"

"Let the flower of life bloom brightly in the blood."

He threw his head back and roared, actually improvising a poem.

"Tie Mu!" Seeing Tie Mu's death, the Tie clan group looked with furious eyes, the fire of their fury seemingly able to burn the sky and ocean!

[1] It's a chinese idiom that means you have no way of escaping. But in literal terms, it states you can't escape even if you grow wings. Back

Chapter 362: One vs Seven (3/4)

"You killed Tie Mu, I want you dead!" Tie Xian Hua raised the umbrella lotus Gu, shouting as she pounced.

Fang Yuan smiled lightly, after waiting for Tie Xian Hua to get close, he turned his body quickly, and opened his wings, as he moved elegantly and brushed past Tie Xian Hua.

Tie Xian Hua charged for five to six steps before stopping.

Her beautiful face was in a daze. The umbrella lotus Gu fell on the ground, as a trace of blood slowly showed on her neck, before blood poured out of her like a fountain, sending her head flying as she was beheaded.

"Xian Hua!!" Tie clan's group shouted pitifully, but it could not bring her back to life.

Tie Ba Xiu quickly came over.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily, spreading his wings and flying into the sky.

Tie Ba Xiu was obstructed by the ratten shell grass soldiers, although he created a path for himself to charge out, how could he match Fang Yuan's speed?

Fang Yuan flew in the sky, after some indiscriminate dive bombs, he flew towards Tie Ruo Nan.

"Oh no, his target is young master!" Tie Dao Ku quickly reinforced her.

Fang Yuan suddenly changed directions, landing quickly in front of Tie Dao Ku.

"Die!" Fang Yuan had a cold expression, exchanging blows with Tie Dao Ku, not dodging or evading at all, showing his fierce nature.

Tie Dao Ku was also a man with great courage, facing Fang Yuan head on.

Swift shadow Gu! Hand blade Gu! Iron hand Gu! Consecutive slash Gu! Quick battle gale! Blade qi Gu!

He was an attack type Gu Master in the first place, as he attacked with all his strength, his arms moved like wind as blade shadows flashed quickly.

Fang Yuan activated the golden shield Gu, but it broke quickly under his barrage.

Even with bronze skin's defense, Fang Yuan's skin was torn open as blood and flesh flew out.

"Just like this, hold on!" The others quickly changed their directions, going to assist him.

"Oh no, my primeval essence is used up!" Suddenly, Tie Dao Ku's attacks stopped.

He was a rank three Gu Master, and had been battling intensely. Now, after a flurry of attacks, his primeval essence dried up.

Without primeval essence, Tie Dao Ku turned from a tiger to a sick cat.

Fang Yuan smiled, grabbing his neck and twisted.

Crack, Tie Dao Ku's neck was easily broken by Fang Yuan. A blade expert, Tie Ruo Nan's capable general, brave and courageous, lost his life here.

"No!!!" Tie Ruo Nan saw this and her eyes turned red with sadness and anger, as the flames of anger was ignited in her, attempting to burn her into ashes.

Ratten shell grass soldiers, under her command, gathered into a green tidal wave, moving and attempting to engulf Fang Yuan.

Thousands of grass soldier puppets, having strength in numbers, they were already a threat to Fang Yuan.

Tie Ruo Nan's eyes, nose, and mouth was bleeding, such intensive manipulation of her Gu caused great strain on her mind, and it started affecting her body.

"Ruo Nan, don't be rash! Do not get engulfed by your own anger!" Tie Ba Xiu saw this and reminded.

But Tie Ruo Nan had lost her reasoning, she had watched her friends die in front of her, this was a huge stimulation to her, it even brought back the pain from back when her father died.

"She is still too young." Fang Yuan sneered, flapping his wings and flying up.

The imposing ratten shell grass soldiers missed their target, as they collapsed together, squeezing into a lump. Not only was their formation a mess, it even caused Tie Ba Xiu and others to have no space to move.

"This is the weakness of a team! Once the cooperation breaks down, you yourself will be the biggest burden to them. Hehehe... such specific allocation of duty also caused the members to be overly reliant on others. Relying on yourself instead of others, that is the truth of the world!" Fang Yuan flew high in the sky, looking at the battlefield emotionlessly, as he moved his gaze towards Tie Ao Kai.

Tie Ao Kai was an investigative Gu master, since the start of the battle, he had been moving around the outskirts.

His speed was fast, he could easily run away and seek reinforcements, he was very crucial to Fang Yuan's plans to eliminate them all. He had to die at all costs!

Seeing Fang Yuan fly towards him, Tie Ao Kai's face was aghast.

Fang Yuan was bathed in blood, his black hair, eyes, and wings, made him look like a demonic god incarnate. Ruthless and courageous, but also cruel and devious.

Tie Mu, Tie Xian Hua, and Tie Dao Ku had all died in his hands, even Tie Ba Xiu could do nothing to him.

Facing such a strong foe, how could he be Fang Yuan's match?

The swarm of ratten shell grass soldier army was once Tie Ao Kai's reassurance, but now it was a cold mockery towards him.

"Escape, I have to escape to San Cha mountain and report to the four elders of Tie clan!" Tie Ao Kai was scared, giving himself a reason to retreat as he immediately left the battlefield, running rapidly.

"Don't run, come back now!" Tie Ba Xiu's gaze was on Tie Ao Kai as he ran into the forest, shouting loudly.

If Tie Ao Kai stayed behind and was united with them, he might have a chance of survival. But he ran away alone, having little primeval essence and low cultivation, how could he be faster than Fang Yuan by running with his two legs, restricted by the terrain?

As expected, in a moment, Fang Yuan carried his head and flew back.

"AHHHH! Gu Yue Fang Zheng! Gu Yue Fang Zheng! You are dead, you are dead meat! You killed my Tie clansmen, you heinous being, there is no salvation for you. Don't run if you have guts, what kind of man are you to run away from me. You have no balls you coward, come fight with me, I will tear you to shreds, and grind your bones into ashes!" Tie Ba Xiu was extremely furious, giving off a thunderous scream.

Fang Yuan chuckled, not falling for the taunt: "Heinous? Heh, I've killed so many people in the past, why didn't you call me heinous back then? Because I killed a Tie clansmen, that makes me a heinous villain? Hehe, if that is so, then I love such a sin, let me kill a few more and add a few more sins to my name."

Saying so, Fang Yuan spread his wings and continued to divebomb, killing the rest of the Tie clan Gu Masters.

Tie Ba Xiu watched with bloodshed eyes, almost vomiting blood out of anger. But he was trapped by the ratten shell grass soldiers, and his speed was no match for Fang Yuan, watching all these outstanding Tie clan youngsters slaughtered in front of him, losing their lives.

Very quickly, in the battlefield, only Tie Ruo Nan and Tie Ba Xiu were left.

"Die, I want you dead!" Tie Ruo Nan's eyes were bloodshot as she gritted her teeth, chanting.

She had activated the ratten shell grass soldiers to her limit, her body oozing with blood, combined with her crazed expression, it gave people chills.

"Ruo Nan, calm down, calm down now." Tie Ba Xiu rushed to her side, shaking her shoulders. But Tie Ruo Nan had no reaction towards it, staring at Fang Yuan with deep hatred.

Below Fang Yuan, the ratten shell grass soldiers had gathered together, tightly like a lump. But they could not hit Fang Yuan, thus acting like lost flies.

Tie Ba Xiu sighed helplessly, he had great experience, he knew that this battle was extremely impactful to Tie Ruo Nan, causing her mental state to breakdown, filled by hatred and fury, she was almost taken over by her anger, and could provide no assistance in the short run.

Fang Yuan flapped his wings from time to time, causing his body to remain in the air.

Tie clan only had two people left, but Fang Yuan stopped his attacks.

That is because, among these two, Tie Ruo Nan was like a crazy b*tch, while Tie Ba Xiu had great battle strength, he was a tough opponent. If Fang Yuan got distracted, he would receive great injuries from him.

Looking at Tie Ruo Nan, Fang Yuan's gaze shone with consideration.

"Tie Ruo Nan has already lost her reasoning in this state. Why don't I keep these ratten shell grass soldiers here to erode her remaining mental energy. After her mind breaks down, I will take her life. Mm... no, there is a better way. She is the Tie clan young master, Tie Ba Xiu has to protect her. I should use this Tie Ruo Nan to indirectly attack Tie Ba Xiu! If I can kill him, that would be the best."

Tie Ba Xiu was an established expert, rank four upper stage cultivation, and due to the earth overlord Gu, his battle strength surpassed normal rank four peak stage Gu Masters. He could be said to be Fang Yuan's most powerful foe after leaving Qing Mao mountain.

Facing such attacks, even if Fang Yuan used all his strength, he could not win.

His only weakness was a lack of long range attacks, but that was not a fatal flaw.

But, battles change due to circumstances, even if Tie Ba Xiu had no flaws, right now, he had someone he had to protect right beside him.

Unknowingly, Tie Ruo Nan had become the hostage that Fang Yuan was using to threaten him!

"If I can kill Tie Ba Xiu, even Yi Huo would have to feel threatened by me. But, I have to observe the situation, we cannot drag this. Although these seven Tie clansmen chose a hidden route here, the four Tie clan old-timers might come to reinforce them." Fang Yuan thought in his heart, reminding himself.

He had a careful, vigilant, calm, and rational nature. He did not panic in dangerous situations, while not arrogant when he had advantages.

The four old-timers of Tie clan had a combination killer move, called limitless search and lock. If they plant the lock Gu on the Gu Master, no matter where he goes, they can find him. It is the number one capturing method. In his previous life, even Kong Ri Tian was a victim to this killer move, causing the downfall of a demonic expert.

Although Fang Yuan had the bone wings Gu, and could fly anywhere he wanted, free and unrestrained while having the capabilities to attack or escape, all according to his will. But once he was planted with the lock Gu, no matter where he flew to, above the heavens or above the sea, he would be captured.

There is always someone who can bring you down, balance exists in everything, although the bone wings Gu was good, it was restricted by other methods.

The only reason why this battle was so successful was because Fang Yuan had his previous life's memories, and knew everything about these seven from Tie clan. Secondly, he had destroyed and expended their long range methods from the battle before.

His thoughts only lasted a second in real time.

After deciding, Fang Yuan took out his primeval stone to recover his primeval essence.

The aperture's primeval sea level started rising again.

At the same time, he inspected his own body, using the self-reliance Gu to heal some critical injuries.

"Damn it!" Seeing this, Tie Ba Xiu's heart was heavy, like a mountain rock was weighing on it.

If little beast king continued to attack, he would be happy instead, but right now Fang Yuan took his time to rest, not indulging in the pleasure of having the upper hand, instead stopping his attacks to recover his primeval essence and heal his injuries!

"This little beast king, he is so young, how can he be so scheming and calm?!"

Chapter 363: One vs Seven (4/4)

Fang Yuan's composure made Tie Ba Xiu shocked and cold.

When the battle started, Tie Ba Xiu had absolutely not expected he would be in such a situation and at a disadvantage.

But now, this established expert, a cornerstone of Tie clan, had no choice but to admit he was in a dangerous situation.

The culprit that led to this situation was this young man in front of him!

He fought against seven people by himself and forced them to reach this stage.

How in the world did he accomplish this?

"From the moment little beast king appeared, his actions and words were all unfathomable and unpredictable traps, luring the seven of us right into it. Even more unexpectedly, he holds a flying type Gu and possesses such skilled flying techniques. With his flying ability, he has taken the initiative, able to retreat and advance as he pleases, eventually leading to this situation, a one-sided slaughter."

Tie Ba Xiu felt his heart turn cold as he recalled the situation.

How did Fang Yuan possess such incredible flying techniques, that question was no longer the most terrifying thing.

"The truly terrifying thing about this lad is his head. How could he have such a meticulous scheming ability at his age? He is simply a monster! If he used it for the righteous path, he would become the most brilliant rising star of the righteous path. Unfortunately, he chose to use his intelligence for the evil demonic path. This is a disaster to the people of the world!!"

Tie Ba Xiu had a premonition, one day this young man in front of him would become a calamity to the whole southern border. At that time, blood would flow into a river and dye the land red, and an uncountable number of living beings would fall victim to his vicious attacks!

"No, my current situation is very dangerous. Tie Ruo Nan can't fight and my long range attacks are inadequate. Little beast king however, can fly, thus attacking or retreating as he desires. Retreat, we must hurry to San Cha mountain and join with the four old-timers!"

Although Tie Ba Xiu had been famous for a long time, his heart was steady and was not misled by fame and profits.

He could not display all his strength, but under the continuous empowerment of earth overlord Gu, tyrant strength Gu was becoming stronger and stronger, surpassing the limits of Fang Yuan.

But Tie Ba Xiu was not drunken in his powers, with his experience, he could see the situation he was in. Continuing to fight only ends in disaster, the most sensible choice was to retreat!

He did not care that he was forced to retreat by a junior. Even if he lost all his reputation, it was better than dying.

"What's more, big brother Xue Leng, I can't let your child die in front of me!" As he thought of this, Tie Ba Xiu became decisive and dragged Tie Ruo Nan to retreat.

"Hmm? Running away!" Fang Yuan's suddenly shone with severity.

He felt the situation was problematic.

Retreating was truly the most sensible choice for Tie Ba Xiu. This place was near to San Cha mountain and if they managed to attract the four old-timers of Tie clan, it would be Fang Yuan's turn to retreat.

"Kill!" Fang Yuan naturally did not want to see such a situation happening.

He pointed his hand and activated his all-out effort Gu along with strength qi Gu; beast phantoms turned into solid forms and landed on the ground, blocking Tie Ba Xiu.

However, Tie Ba Xiu was strong, his punches and kicks seem to whistle like the wind and cackle like lightning, scattering these beast phantoms.

Fang Yuan suddenly changed the attack target, the beast phantoms all moved towards Tie Ruo Nan.

"Despicable!" Tie Ba Xiu cursed and moved to protect Tie Ruo Nan.

Fang Yuan laughed loudly at this, if Tie Ba Xiu gave up on Tie Ruo Nan and escaped by himself, Fang Yuan would not be able to stop him. However, Tie Ba Xiu was protecting Tie Ruo Nan, this was seeking his own doom.

Because he was a Gu Master that specialized in offense, not defense.

By protecting Tie Ruo Nan, he was sacrificing himself, tying his own hands and feet, fighting his enemy's specialty with his weakness.

One side escaped and other pursued, the situation was in a stalemate.

No matter how Tie Ba Xiu cursed and provoked, Fang Yuan only flew in the air and used beast phantoms to attack.

Tie Ba Xiu could not hit Fang Yuan and thus was passively taking a beating. Moreover, there were light injuries on his body while protecting Tie Ruo Nan.

"He is only at rank four middle stage, why does he have so much primeval essence?" Tie Ba Xiu was starting to feel desperate, he did not know Fang Yuan not only had liquor worm, but also heavenly essence treasure lotus; in terms of primeval essence, he could completely match rank four upper stage.

Fang Yuan attacked furiously, sending attacks without an end. If a beast phantom was destroyed, he would immediately send another.

Beast phantoms attacked one after another, if one fell, another arrived. Especially, the occasional thunder boar and rock crocodile phantom which could threaten Tie Ruo Nan.

Tie Ba Xiu was getting exhausted and was slowly unable to endure the attacks, his strength decreasing rapidly.

"Why hasn't the four old-timers arrived yet!" Tie Ba Xiu kept on running and was already near San Cha mountain, but he still did not see any signs of the four old-timers.

The path they chose was too hidden. And to prevent news from leaking out, they had intentionally departed two days earlier.

These setup instead became an obstruction now for Tie Ba Xiu.

Tie Ba Xiu was very passive now, the injuries on his body continuously accumulated and turned from light to heavy injuries.

Beast phantoms were starting to pose more of a threat to him and it was becoming hard for him move forward!

Tie Ruo Nan had become the greatest burden to him; she kept on struggling and Tie Ba Xiu had no choice but to knock her unconscious and run while carrying her in his arm.

"We are already close to the foot of the mountain, I just need to hold on for a while." Tie Ba Xiu's body was shaking and his vision was already a scene of blurriness.

"Is he really going to escape? Damn it!" Fang Yuan's face was gloomy as he saw this from the air. He started making more ferocious and continuous attacks, his offense surging like a tidal wave.

As they were near San Cha mountain, Gu Masters started appearing the surroundings.

"There is a battle going on, it is little beast king!"

"Heavens, did I see wrong? The one being pursued seems to be 'present age overlord', a cornerstone of Tie clan, Tie Ba Xiu!"

"Little beast king is defying heaven, he is actually chasing the rank four upper stage Tie Ba Xiu!"

...

The Gu Masters that saw the battle were all flabbergasted and incomparably shocked.

Some righteous Gu Masters felt their hearts go cold when they saw Tie Ba Xiu being chased, running away like a pathetic dog who fell into the water.

"Big brother Li Xian, why has little beast king still not appeared? We have been waiting here for such a long time, is your information reliable?" From a dark corner, Hu Mei Er looked at the purple light barrier in front of her and yawned in boredom.

In the light barrier formed by iron cabinet Gu, Bai Ning Bing was still trapped by the four old-timers of Tie clan.

"There is no problem with my information, let's wait a bit more." Li Xian said that but he muttered in his heart, 'This should not be happening, I have already told the news of Tie clan's reinforcements to him. How could he still restrain himself? Could it be, he is really going to leave Bai Ning Bing in the lurch?"

If little beast king really did not appear, such heartlessness made even Li Xian terrified when he thought of it. But if he came to rescue her, both sides would suffer, and the benefits in such a chaotic battlefield would be huge.

Just as the two were talking in whispers, they heard some clamor.

"What is going on?" Hu Mei Er puzzledly turned her head to look, but the moment she saw the sight, her puzzled expression quickly became sluggish and after a while, it turned into shock!

The person whom she had been painfully waiting for appeared and even appeared while ostentatiously flying in the air.

Wait a second...

The person that little beast king is chasing looks a bit familiar?

"Wha... what the f*ck, it is Tie Ba Xiu. The 'present age overlord' from Tie clan is being chased! So little beast king went to intercept the reinforcement!" Li Xian stared tongue-tied at this pursuit and could not help but curse.

At the same time as his realization, he felt extreme shock and bewilderment.

"Little beast king actually went to intercept the Tie clan reinforcement, how can he have such guts? Is he crazy! No, he is not crazy, he won the fight and is now chasing Tie Ba Xiu!"

Tie Ba Xiu was rank four upper stage but his battle prowess surpassed that level, even common rank four peak stage Gu Masters were not his match. Even on San Cha mountain, among the five rank four peak stage Gu Masters, only Yi Huo would be able to contend with this 'present age overlord'.

However, right now, Tie Ba Xiu was actually being chased by little beast king and in such a sorry state.

"Oh god, am I hallucinating?" Someone grabbed his head and looked with an incredulous expression.

"This world is too crazy, it is changing so quickly..." Someone muttered with a dull expression in his eyes.

"Fortunately, I haven't gone against little beast king!" Li Xian felt fortunate, but immediately felt fear, "No, I still need to be cautious when dealing with Fang Zheng, this guy cannot be assessed using common sense."

"In such a short time, he advanced to rank four middle stage and is also able to fly?!" Hu Mei Er kept her hand over her heart, extremely shocked at this abnormal growth speed of Fang Yuan.

"Demonic path's scoundrel!"

"Quick, we need to rescue them, that is Tie Ba Xiu!!"

Tie clan's four old-timers also sensed the situation and immediately revoked iron cabinet Gu and hurried to rescue. As for the trapped Bai Ning Bing or whatever, they stopped caring.

But unfortunately, they were still late by a step.

"I was still a step too slow..." Tie Ba Xiu felt extremely bitter, his eyes were blurry, the pain from the wounds all over his body had already made him numb, and the heavy injuries had already increased so much that he was in a near death state now.

He protected Tie Ruo Nan all the way and did not let even one attack reach her.

"Such a pity that this little beast king did not come down to fight in close combat. Otherwise, I would have killed him!" Tie Ba Xiu felt very regretful, he had a trump card that he had not revealed. However, Fang Yuan acted cautiously the whole time, never flying down and only attacking from the air.

"Ba Xiu, hold on!"

"We are coming to reinforce you."

The four old-timers of Tie clan shouted together and rushed over rapidly.

"Hahaha, you were just a step away, Tie Ba Xiu, you have failed!" Fang Yuan threw his head back and laughed loudly, a rock crocodile phantom fell down with an explosive sound, sending Tie Ba Xiu rolling on the ground.

Tie clan's four old-timers were rushing over and were extremely near, but this small gap was like the distance between clouds and mud.

"It is over." Fang Yuan's expression was cold as he pointed and made the fatal attack.

"No, not yet. Iron cabinet Gu!" Tie Ba Xiu used his final remaining energy and placed his palm on Tie Ruo Nan's back.

A square shaped iron cabinet quickly formed and tightly sealed Tie Ruo Nan.

Beast phantom attacked, ripping Tie Ba Xiu into pieces, but the iron cabinet was firm as ever and Tie Ruo Nan who was inside was unscathed.

At the crucial moment, Tie Ba Xiu gave his final chance of survival to Tie Ruo Nan.

"Ba Xiu!" Tie clan's four old-timers howled in anger and grief, they reached the scene but were late by a step.

"Little beast king, our Tie clan will not rest till you die!" The four old-timers stared at Fang Yuan, wishing they could bite him to death.

"Eh? Is that so... I fought against seven Tie clansmen this time, six including Tie Ba Xiu lost their lives by my hands. You four old-timers also want to deal with me? Then fly over and fight me." Fang Yuan laughed coldly, a dangerous look appeared in his eyes that made people avoid his gaze.

Chapter 364: Soaring Reputation!

"Heavens, little beast king fought against seven, but actually won!"

"Even 'present age overlord' lost his life."

"The number one rising star, he is this generation's number one star of the demonic path!"

There was an uproar in the crowd, many discussed and whispered to each other.

Tie clan's four old-timers released their aura and started attacking one after another. However, Fang Yuan flapped his wings and lightly evaded them, his nimbleness causings gasps of amazement in the crowd.

"You old-timers, I have still not settled the score with you for trapping me." Bai Ning Bing slowly walked over with a grim expression. She casted a glance at Fang Yuan; her gaze hiding complex feelings.

In these days when she was trapped, Fang Yuan had grown so much!

Not only had his cultivation advanced to middle stage, he also held such skilled flying techniques. Looking at this control, Southern Border now had one more flying expert, how did he manage to accomplish all this?

Bai Ning Bing had once thought of training her flying skills. However, the matter regarding flying was too troublesome; the amount of practice needed was huge and at the same time, it was very time-consuming and needed a long period of grinding. The amount of energy spent was huge but would provide little results in a short period. Bai Ning Bing thus did not do it.

She had never expected Fang Yuan to be able to train his flying ability to such a level without any signs or words!

This was surpassing all common sense!

"Could it be that he had some mystical encounter in three kings inheritance?" Bai Ning Bing naturally considered this point.

In truth, there was no need for Fang Yuan to explain it, many people would connect his performance to three kings inheritance.

With Tie clan's four old-timers revoking iron cabinet Gu, Bai Ning Bing was free.

Now, with the coordination of Fang and Bai, the situation had become extremely dangerous.

The four old-timers were on their guard, tightly protecting Tie Ruo Nan's iron cabinet Gu in the center and guarding against Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing.

Fang Yuan felt somewhat unresigned as he looked at the iron cabinet Gu.

Tie Ba Xiu had failed at the last moment while retreating. And Fang Yuan had also failed at last step while chasing them because he was not able to claim Tie Ruo Nan's life. No doubt, she was a threat.

"But without Tie Ruo Nan, I could not have killed Tie Ba Xiu so easily. At this point, I can only let it go." Fang Yuan revealed increasing killing intent on outside, but his battle intent was already dispersing.

He had been engaged in intense battle and the primeval essence in his aperture was already inadequate, while Tie clan's four old-timers were in perfect condition.

At the same time, there were too many spectators, many wolves were preying in the dark and gain some benefits. Even Li Xian had such plans let alone others.

'It is time to stop.' Fang Yuan heaved a sigh inwardly before shouting in a clear voice, "Tie clan's four old-timers, my partner killed one of your clansmen and you trapped her till now. I have killed six of your clansmen, how long will you trap me?"

Tie clan's four old-timers' eyes twitched when they heard this clear provocation.

"Little beast king, don't go too far! You killed our Tie clansmen, killed Elder Ba Xiu and chased Tie clan's young master; you are already our Tie clan's sworn enemy. I hereby swear, I shall use the rest of my life and pay any price to capture you and throw you inside Demon Suppression Tower, and make sure you suffer endless torment and punishment!" The head of the four old-timers roared in anger.

Although he said so, he did not dare to act rashly.

The battle prowess little beast king revealed greatly shocked him. And if you add Bai Ning Bing on top of that...

"Hahaha, alright. Since it is so, then I shall also view Tie clan as my sworn enemy! From now on, as long as it is a Tie clansman, I will kill one if I see one and will kill two if I see two!" Fang Yuan laughed wildly before flapping his wings and leaving.

Under the disappointed gazes of many Gu Masters that had ulterior motives, he left of his own accord.

Bai Ning Bing also left.

The outcome of this battle spread over the whole San Cha mountain at lightning speed.

What kind of place was San Cha mountain at present?

It was a place where three kings inheritance appeared; a place which was paid attention to by countless clans, righteous path members and demonic path members.

Soon after that, the battle report of Fang Yuan taking on seven Tie clansmen by himself and killing Tie Ba Xiu was spread throughout the whole Southern Border.

Fang Yuan's reputation soared!

...

"This kid actually killed Tie Ba Xiu? Is this news reliable?"

In Yan clan, when young master Yan Jun heard this report from his subordinate, he almost did not dare to believe his ears.

Who was Tie Ba Xiu?

He had been famous for a long time and was known as the 'present age overlord'. He possessed earth overlord Gu and had a fighting strength that surpassed normal rank four peak stage!

He was a cornerstone of Tie clan, one of the top clans, and was an expert who could take charge of a region by himself.

But he was actually chased and killed by little beast king Fang Zheng, a junior that only had rank four middle stage cultivation?

"This little beast king can surpass realms to battle and killed Tie Ba Xiu. Who in the world is he? I have never heard of him before." Yan Jun asked with a frown.

His subordinate quickly reported: "Young master, you entered an Immemorial Era's phantom path inheritance and was in closed cultivation for five years, not knowing about Fang Zheng is also normal. This person is only around twenty years old and is a genius rising star of the demonic path that only came to fame in the recent years..."

...

"Little beast king Fang Zheng? The youngsters these days are really terrifying! The new waves are constantly replacing the old waves, while the old waves die by the shore. Tsk tsk..."

In a forest, Feng Tian Yu slowly walked forward while thinking of the news he had just received, mixed within his sighs was a trace of fiery passion.

"I heard the reason little beast king could grasp flying methods and grow up so quick was because he received some benefits from three kings inheritance! Three kings inheritance..."

Feng Tian Yu thought of this and felt a desire to immediately rush towards San Cha mountain.

He was a famous refinement path Gu Master in Southern Border. King Xin Inheritance perfectly matched him.

...

"Fang Zheng actually fought against seven and killed six Tie clansmen including Tie Ba Xiu?!" As one of the five great experts of Shang clan, the moment Elder Yi Huo came out from inheritance, he received this incredulous news.

Tie Ba Xiu's fighting strength was equal to his. Fang Yuan was able to kill Tie Ba Xiu, does that mean Fang Yuan could similarly kill him?

How could this be?

But the cold hard truth overruled all doubts and claims!

After Yi Huo found out even more details, he slowly came to an understanding: "So he has learnt flying and can use it in battle. No wonder he was able to fight against seven and kill Tie Ba Xiu..."

To Gu Masters, grasping flying methods and being able to use them in battle meant their fighting strength would soar qualitatively.

Humans were creatures that walked on ground and did not have wings. Even Ren Zu did not have ability to fly. Being able to fly by itself was a miracle in defiance of heaven.

If one could fly, then the encirclement tactics on the ground would possess almost no threat.

The wide sky would become the stage that allowed the flying Gu Masters to travel freely. They could attack and defend, advance and retreat; firmly grasping control of the battle.

There were famous flying Gu Masters in Southern Border; Fei You Wang, Lan Mei He and Hong Fei Yu. They were feared by people, battling with them was extremely troublesome and no one wished to make an enemy out of them.

Yi Huo had deep impression of flying Gu Masters.

Because there was a perfect example near him, that was Wei Yang.

Wei Yang was called light swordsman, he could evade as fast as light and quick as lightning. He was also a flying Gu Master!

His aptitude was inadequate and only had rank three peak stage cultivation, but he was able to become a major figure of Shang clan, one of the five experts and was equally famous as Yi Huo, a rank four peak stage Gu Master!

Once, Yi Huo had felt it was a disgrace to be listed together with Wei Yang in the five experts, thus he challenged him to a fight. The result was depressing for him, Wei Yang moved around the battlefield unobstructed, and he could simply do nothing to him!

"If we only look at flying speed, Wei Yang can be said to be the number one in Southern Border, little beast king cannot compare to him. Recently with clan leader's help, Wei Yang has advanced to rank four..."

Yi Huo felt the pressure in his mind increasing by a layer as he thought of this.

The five great experts of Shang clan were not a united group, they each had their respective factions and were always contending against each other.

Yi Huo accepted the command to come to San Cha mountain in order to establish great merits and become a clansman of Shang clan, obtaining the resources within Shang clan's living treasure door and advance one step to become a rank five Gu Master!

"Fang Yuan's battle strength increased greatly with the ability to fly while that Tie Ba Xiu is weak at long range battle and was also concerned about Tie Ruo Nan, thus being killed by little beast king. If we talk of true battle prowess, Tie Ba Xiu surpasses little beast king. It is a pity I cannot recruit little beast king anymore!" Yi Huo felt extremely regretful when he understood this.

The battle prowess Fang Yuan displayed might not equal his, but with flying methods, Yi Huo also could not do anything to him.

Forcing little beast king simply would not work. Instead, it would ruin his reputation since Fang Yuan was Shang clan's purple thorn esteemed guest.

Besides this, there was also another reason: Tie clan.

Little beast king had now serious offended Tie clan!

The losses to Tie clan were huge and they would certainly deal with little beast king, there was no room for compromising. Moreover, Fang Yuan proclaimed in an extremely arrogant tone in front of everyone that he would kill Tie clansmen if he saw them.

If Yi Huo really recruited little beast king, it would be equal to offending Tie clan.

Tie clan was also a top clan like Shang clan, a major party of the righteous path. At that time, Yi Huo would have to endure pressure from both Tie clan and Shang clan's higher-ups.

...

"Little beast king definitely grasped some secrets of the three kings inheritance! Otherwise, how could he suddenly gain such profound flying techniques?!" Li Xian was sitting on his seat, his eyes narrowed to a slit, sharp light flickering endlessly inside them.

He had all the details regarding Fang Yuan. However, Fang Yuan suddenly grasping flying methods was simply inconceivable and broke all common sense.

"Even if he bitterly trained in Shang clan city, it is not possible that there were not even a single trace of information about it. Also, he was only there for a few years, how could he have such such a powerful flying tool? Could it be..." Hu Mei Er also pondered from the side.

"Three kings inheritance!" A ray of divine light seemed to pass through his mind and caused Li Xian to blurt out.

In a split second —

The matter about little beast king earning huge profits at Shang clan city by relying on information about three kings inheritance...

The matter of him intentionally delaying the rescue of Bai Ning Bing and entering three kings inheritance...

And also all of the battle gains he brought out from the inheritance each time...

All these events converged in Li Xian's mind and formed a clear clue — little beast king definitely held some secrets about the three kings inheritance. The time flow inside three kings inheritance was different from the outside world, it was a Gu Immortal blessed land! The reason he could grasp flying methods was definitely due to three kings inheritance!

"That must be it, Fang Zheng holds the secrets of three kings inheritance!" Hu Mei Er also came to a realization. Her thought of charming Fang Yuan and making him become her sexual slave suddenly became even more appealing.

Fang Yuan had his previous life memories and naturally grasped the secrets of three kings inheritance. In this secret discussion, Li Xian and Hu Mei Er had accidentally speculated the truth.

"The problem is since we know this, how do we obtain even more benefits? Little beast king has already grown and even Tie Ba Xiu fell by his hands, he is not someone we can go against." Li Xian clicked his tongue as his thoughts moved rapidly.

"We cannot, but it doesn't mean others cannot. Humans can be instigated, hehehe." Hu Mei Er laughed coquettishly.

"Are you saying we should leak this information?" Li Xian slightly pondered over it before suddenly slapping his thigh, "Excellent plan, it is an excellent plan!"